
<xml>
<title>The Magical Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Mr. Reus">Mwahahahaha! Behold my might!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ahhh! Shame on you, Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Reus">No!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Using magic for evil!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Reus">Rrrrgh?! Nnnrrooogh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And that's how the evil magician, Mr. Reus, was defeated!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Reus">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See you for Act Two, everybody!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Brava! Brava, Trucy! Wow, Apollo! Wasn't that a great trick?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You bet! I've never seen such a great magic act!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you know they even featured Trucy's show on TV this morning?! "Penrose Theater. A well-known gateway to success for entertainers! It's here at this famous theater that we'll finally get to see... ...Trucy Wright's... 'Trucy in Gramarye-Land'! The long-awaited revival of the magic of Troupe Gramarye!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow! That explains why there's a TV crew here to cover the show!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is the perfect opportunity to promote the Wright Anything Agency, too! After all, people look up things they see on TV, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But wouldn't they be looking up the talent part, and not the law part of our agency?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mamma mia! You're right! We'd get nothing but requests from Trucy's fans, wouldn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, well. Guess we'll just have to make it the old-fashioned way. My name is Apollo Justice. I'm a rookie lawyer with only about two years of experience under my belt. We're here to see Trucy's magic show. She's a fellow member of our agency. We came on behalf of our boss, Mr. Wright, who's away on a trip.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, and did you hear, Apollo? Even though it's only her debut, her shows are completely sold out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Really!? <thought>That's amazing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Voilà! A star is born! Who knows HOW far she'll go? At this rate, nothing in the world can stop us! Wahhh ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, you do realize this has nothing to do with you, right? This is Athena Cykes. She's another member of our agency. She may not look it, but at just nineteen years old, she's a lawyer as well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean, "She may not look it"...? Of course I look the part!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Care to explain how, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww c'mon, have a heart...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Stop treating me like a child!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That gadget around Athena's neck that spoke just now? That's Widget. Widget helps Athena out with her special field of expertise: analytical psychology. He also has a habit of blurting out whatever Athena's really thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, this little guy can be a little unruly at times.</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Hey, upgrade me already!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, why don't we go say hi to Trucy in her dressing room during the break?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, yes! Let's go see the big star! I'm so nervous! What should I say to her?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, whatever you usually say to her at the office every day...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is Trucy's dressing room... Looks like she's busy over there with someone.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Could you sign this, please, ma'am?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure thing! Just the one sheet in this clipboard, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A fan asking for Trucy's autograph, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think so. It looks like some kind of contract.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Thank you very much. I'll get this to the producer right away.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Great. Thanks! ...Oh! Polly! Athena! You came!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! Congratulations on your big debut!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who was that just now, by the way?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Somebody from Take-2 TV. They want to turn my magic show into a TV special! They're planning to broadcast it nationwide! Hee hee! Can you imagine?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. You really ARE a big star!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, can I get your autograph later, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure! My signature's in high demand today! Would you like one, too, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>............Yeah, actually, I would...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oops! Looks like I ran out of flyers, so I'll have to sign your forehead instead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Hey! Knock it off! Look, just forget about the autograph! This is Trucy Wright. She's a magician, and Mr. Wright's adopted daughter. She's becoming quite renowned in the magic world these days for her impressive skills.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A lot of people get this wrong, but... ...Apollo's actual job is being my magic assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, YOU'RE the one who gets it wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, think you can do that trick you always do at the office for me, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Okay! Behold! The wondrous magic that can make anything disappear! Three, two, one... Ta-dah! My magic panties are an extra-dimensional galaxy!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Brava, Trucy! Brava!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Okay, but why do you always have to make MY attorney's badge disappear?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, that's because, out of everyone at the Wright Anything Agency... ...you're the one I get the best reaction out of!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That doesn't make my poor badge feel any better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess I shouldn't touch anything while Trucy's around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You shouldn't touch anything while I'm NOT around either!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She read my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks again for inviting us, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee. Thank YOU for coming!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your show sure packs a wallop! I nearly fell out of my seat when that dragon showed up! And when it attacked you --whew... ...I was terrified, even though I knew it was all just a part of the show!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's good! Because that trick is the crowning glory of Act One! I'm really glad you're enjoying the show!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I heard your shows are completely sold out, Trucy! They say your fans were all over the tickets the instant they became available! Like hungry wolves going after their prey!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like you've made a loyal pack of followers for yourself already, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But you two are the only ones who got a special VIP invitation from me! Today's just a dress rehearsal for the performers, staff, family, and friends.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A "Generalprobe," huh? That's what they call it in Germany!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The real show isn't until the day after tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By the way, are you going to finally do your magic panties trick onstage after the break?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sorry to disappoint anyone who came just to see my magic panties... ...but my next trick is completely new! I'm debuting it today!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! A new trick, huh? Are you gonna chop Apollo up into little lawyer bits?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Funny, I don't recall EVER agreeing to anything like that...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... While that DOES sound like a good idea... ...today's trick is a totally new Troupe Gramarye Original. The entire future of the troupe is riding on the success of this special new trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This show is really important to me -- it isn't like any of the other shows I've done. As the rightful heir to the Troupe Gramarye repertoire of magic... ...this show is my first chance to unveil the tricks I've inherited.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Troupe Gramarye, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, I have a poster of them hanging right over there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh. It feels like it's been ages since I've seen a picture of them. <thought>Troupe Gramarye was a group of magicians who dominated the magic world in their day. Trucy is the sole heir to the troupe's entire repertoire of stage magic.</thought> Huh? Who's this guy in green and purple on the left here...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that's The Great Mr. Reus, the other magician in today's show. He used to belong to Troupe Gramarye, too, a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, so tell us more about this special magic you're going to reveal today!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a secret Troupe Gramarye trick... ...left behind by my late granddaddy, Magnifi Gramarye. It's never been performed before, so this is the first time it'll be seen by the public!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The grand unveiling, huh? <thought>No wonder she's been working so hard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, your attorney's badge! Does this mean you want me to...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I knew I shouldn't have done that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! Why'd you put it away? Fine. If that's the way you're going to be... Three, two, one... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, don't make it...! Wait my badge is still here...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was MY badge, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Where to?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">To practice my act, of course! The show's only a few days away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're really pushing yourself. Didn't you practice until late last night, too?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yup! Because everything's gotta be just right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy inherited all of Troupe Gramarye's magic tricks from her father when he died. And the troupe's entire legacy is now resting on her shoulders. No wonder she's feeling the pressure.</thought> It looks like everything's going well today, though. I mean, that last trick was perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Grace under pressure -- that's me! After all, "a true entertainer always keeps a smile on their face!" That's the Troupe Gramarye creed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's hard to believe you've accomplished so much, even though you're still in high school.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee. But, to tell you the truth, I'm actually pretty nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who wouldn't be? <thought>Oh, I bet this would do the trick...</thought> You'll be FINE, Trucy! If anybody can do it, you can!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">P-Polly... That was just the boost I needed! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo's "fine" sure has a way of really hitting you right in the heart -- and in the ears.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Enough ragging on my voice already...</line>
<line speaker="???">Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, hi, Bonny!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">It's almost time for the second act.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, okay. Thanks! Well, Apollo, Athena -- enjoy the rest of the show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Break a leg, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks. I will!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope her new trick goes well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, this is Trucy we're talking about. She'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, I wouldn't be so sure...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Performing magic is like walking a tightrope -- there's always an element of danger. One little mistake can even cost you your life, you know. I wonder if she'll make it across today...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... and what do you mean by that, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hee hee. Oh, nothing! Now, if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's gone... <thought>What was that all about? Judging by what she said, I'm going to guess she's probably a magician, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, Apollo! We've gotta get back to our seats now or we'll be late!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ow! Hey, stop pulling! Okay, let's see... <thought>Guess it's time to Move back to the stage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hurry up, Apollo! It's about to start! I want to see what Trucy's next trick is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're really wound up today, aren't you... Why don't you take your seat and try to relax?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa! Look! There's a TV reporter over there! With a TV camera and everything!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Oh, yeah, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, sit down! You're blocking people's view! Yeesh, I feel like I'm babysitting here...</line>
<line speaker="Reporter">Hello, everyone! I'm reporting from the beautiful Penrose Theater... ...where the public performance of "Trucy in Gramarye-Land" begins in just two short days! But today, they've very kindly agreed to give us a sneak preview! Isn't this exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Do you think I was on TV just now?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How should I know? But if you were, you were disgracing our entire agency, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Hey! What the heck's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ooh! Here it comes!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, give up your dastardly ways! Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Over here!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Come now, Mr. Hat! Offer the girl's life up to Mr. Reus and bring him back to life! Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">- Whaaahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">- Wow! Just when and how did she make the switch?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You won't be reviving anyone today!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, that was amazing! I have no idea how she escaped that coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm glad Trucy's escape trick went off without a hitch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And when I open the coffin, like this... inside you seeeee... ...M-Mr. Reus? But how...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what's going on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's... not getting up...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy?! Wh-What just happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Wait. That's not part of the act?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Attention, please! For your own safety, we ask that everyone please evacuate the building.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's going on? Is Trucy okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Outside, everyone! Evacuate immediately, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Hey! Stop grabbing at me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They kicked us out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Poor Trucy! I hope she's okay... ...Hey, here comes that staff member from before.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Your attention, please! We regret to inform you that today's show has been canceled!</line>
<line speaker="Staff">W-We are very sorry, but the theater is on lock-down pending a police investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Excuse me! Is it because of that accident? That man in the coffin -- is he...?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">U-Um, well... We're still trying to figure things out, sir... But I can tell you that Ms. Wright is fine. She wasn't injured, so please don't worry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank goodness she's okay...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you there! What the heck's going on?! They wouldn't even let ME in. ME, for crying out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Oh, Mr. Retinz! There was an accident during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">An accident? Great, just great. That's all I need right now. Do you have any idea how much money we're sinking into this program?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... and you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">The man behind the scenes, that's who. This is a fine kettle of fish, let me tell ya! Spinning all this is gonna be a real pain in my posterior, believe you me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Spinning? As in covering it up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Look, I gotta get inside. Seriously, can't a guy catch a break around here?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there he goes...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't we go back to the office for now? I'm sure Trucy will call us once things have settled down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What an odd building.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The name "Penrose Theater" comes from the "Penrose triangle" -- an impossible object. It's called an impossible object because it only exists as an optical illusion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An optical illusion?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh-huh. Just like how that "cube" on the front of the building isn't really a cube at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ It isn't? It sure looks like a cube to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just the way it's shaded. The dark and light parts make it look like it's jutting outward towards us, but it really isn't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh-whuh? It isn't?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on. Let's take a look at it from over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Okay? Whaaat?! You're right! That's so weird!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now do you get it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think so? It's kinda hard to tell...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are all these weird objects, anyway? Are they supposed to be "modern art"? Like that clock... Is it just me, or are the hands moving awfully fast?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">¡Ay, caramba! What kind of clock doesn't show the proper time? Is that part of what makes it "art"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who knows? ...Hey, take a look at that man in front of the clock. He's trying real hard to set his watch to it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">! H-Hey! Mister!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look! There's Trucy -- front and center! So the show actually starts the day after tomorrow, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know if you've noticed, but... ...you see that man in front of the poster? He's been standing there a long time looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I noticed! And sometimes, he kind of stretches his hand towards it a little bit...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... I bet he's one of Trucy's fans. You think he's gonna try to make of with it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who knows... Oh, look! I guess we don't have to worry! Ha ha ha! Every time the man reaches for it, the dog growls and pulls at his pant leg.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, it kinda begs the question: Who's the master and who's the pet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Athena, any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry... I've got nothing. I mean, it was just one amazing trick after another! Who could figure it all out?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I was asking if you have any ideas about the accident, not the show, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't believe they had to cancel the rest of the show. I wonder if Trucy's okay...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, poor thing... After all her hard work, too! I sure with Mr. Wright was here right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess we'd better head back to the office. There's nothing we can do here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh! Myyy badge is shinier than yooours!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. Yours is newer than mine. A great weathered finish like this only comes with age and experience.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What?! I can get a finish just as good as that on my badge, too, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Getting it dirty on purpose doesn't count, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">¿Perdón? Ha ha ha! Wh-What makes you think I'd ever do anything like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's no use. I can't get a hold of Mr. Wright. I wonder if something happened to him in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe he got caught up in some kind of trouble again, as always.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, trouble's drawn to him like iron filings to a magnet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Apollo! Speaking of Khura'in, they're showing something about it on TV right now!</line>
<line speaker="TV">There has been some surprising news coming out of the Kingdom of Khura'in. The country recently saw defense attorney Phoenix Wright win a "not guilty" verdict... ...the first verdict of its kind in twenty-three years!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Mr. Wright won a trial in Khura'in?!</line>
<line speaker="TV">Lawyers are said to be highly disrespected in the Kingdom of Khura'in... ...so Mr. Wright's win was an upset victory amidst entrenched hostility.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! Did you hear that?! The first time in twenty-three years!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... But what was he doing in court there in the first place? I thought he just went for a visit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So he WAS in some kind of trouble, just like we thought!</line>
<line speaker="TV">Next, an update on the unfortunate accident that occurred at the Penrose Theater...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, now they're talking about the accident at Trucy's show!</line>
<line speaker="TV">Famed magician "The Great Mr. Reus" was skewered with a sword and died on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, no! So... he really is dead...</line>
<line speaker="TV">And now, here is the footage of that deadly moment.</line>
<line speaker="TV">Mr. Reus's body isn't visible in this footage... ...but these are still very shocking images. The magician, Trucy Wright, is reportedly still only a high school student. Could it be that this unfortunate accident happened due to a lack of proper training? Did the young magician have enough experience, preparation, and knowledge? Some might say that Troupe Gramarye should be held accountable for this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! What kind of biased reporting is this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! They're making it sound like it's all Trucy's fault!</line>
<line speaker="TV">Oh! We've just received more breaking news. ......Oh, my! The young magician in question, Trucy Wright... ...is now under arrest on the charge of involuntary manslaughter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="TV">We will keep you updated as this unfortunate tale unfolds. Stay tuned!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy's under arrest?! She can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo! We've gotta do something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. Let's get down to the detention center right away! <thought>But before I forget, I think I'll jot a few things down about the case. I'll just open up the Court Record... ...and make a few Notes. I can use it like a kind of "To Do" list. If I ever get stuck, I can just refer to these notes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright sure has a lot of law books and old case files.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sure looks that way, doesn't it. But take a closer look. Most of those books and files have to do with magic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, wow. You're right... They're just hidden behind law book covers...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Little by little, Trucy is taking over the whole office with her magic equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hate to admit it, but recently... ...I sometimes feel like I'm going to forget I'm even a lawyer when I'm here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sounds like Trucy's magic is starting to take over your brain, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just watered Charley, so he's looking pretty perky.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For a guy whose desk is always a big jumbled mess... ...Mr. Wright never forgets to water Charley.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sometimes, I catch him staring at that plant and smiling. It must hold some special meaning for him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could be. He did say Charley's been in this office since his first days as a lawyer... He doesn't seem to want to talk about it much, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">One thing's for sure: Charley is no ordinary plant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's yet another magic prop.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! A hoop! I'm really good at that! How about you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nope. I just don't seem to have the knack for it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I figured as much. After all, you're not really in-tune with your body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You DO realize this hoop is used for the "levitating woman" trick, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! It's not for hula dancing?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And since you're "really good at that"...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! What I meant was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think I'll recommend you to Trucy for the assistant role, then! You can take over for me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What did I hula myself into...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what kinds of tricks Trucy uses these things for. Like this little guillotine, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, a human head definitely wouldn't fit. So maybe something small and fuzzy?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eww! That's disgusting! Not to mention cruel! Trucy would never do anything like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmph. You didn't get mad that time Trucy put MY head in a guillotine!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's because you performed your role with such gusto! I mean, your screams were so realistic, I couldn't stop laughing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's because they were 100% real...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've always thought these shelves were a little awkward and hard to use.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. The shape doesn't really lend itself well to the concept of "shelves." I mean, there's a hole in the top part and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you ever notice that every now and then, things disappear when you put them inside? It's like the shelves remember that they used to be a magic prop or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not the most useful piece of furniture in the world, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With everyone's personal items littering the office, this place is as messy as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... Take this loud jacket of yours, for example. It's been sitting here forever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Loud"?! What do you mean by, "loud"? I love that jacket!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, yeah? Why don't you ever wear it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, uh... <thought>The last time I wore that jacket...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Polly! I'm so happy for you! You finally decided to take the plunge! Now you're ready for your stand-up comedy debut! You, Daddy, and Athena should form a group! I can see it now: "Primary Color Punch-Lines"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's just say that jacket brings back painful memories...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How dare they cover it like that?! They're putting everything on Trucy! I'm going to stage a huge protest! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes. Athena's scary when she's mad!</thought> Okay... So what's the plan?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm gonna stop watching TV completely, starting today!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's your "huge protest"?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah...! But there's this show I want to watch this week... Nrrrrgh! I can already tell this is going to be a hard, uphill battle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Good luck with that, Sisyphus.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll race you to the detention center! Loser buys the winner juice. Deal?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A race?! You mean, I have to RUN?! ...Let's just skip the running and go straight to me buying you juice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">YES!!! That's the fourth free juice this month!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Athena is getting really good at sponging off of me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Poor Trucy... What can we even say to her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Oh! Polly! Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucy... Are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I'm fine. Don't worry about me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We saw the news about the accident on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh heh heh. Guess I can't Houdini my way out of this one. I got arrested and everything! They say I'm the one who caused the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's not true... right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">To be honest... I don't really know. I mean, I have no idea how an accident like that could've happened. The trick went off without a hitch. I'm sure of that much! Still, the police just won't listen to me! They've already decided that it was all my fault! *sigh* I'm exhausted after all their questions...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like she's been able to hang in there at least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... <thought>She really is one tough cookie.</thought> I know you're tired, but... ...can you tell us a little bit about the accident?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes, of course! Go ahead and ask me anything! I'll be... I'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The security camera stares at us with its cold, unblinking eye. I don't know why, but it gives me the heebies, with a side order of jeebies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The guard is just standing there completely motionless... ...and Athena keeps making faces at him, trying to make him crack at least a smile.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! I think I made him smirk a little!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C'mon. Leave the poor guy alone, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's the microphone for speaking with people on the other side of the glass. Athena is trying to stump the guard with trivia questions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, this guy is good! He answers in the blink of an eye without batting an eyelash... or moving a muscle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is he that bored?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For starters, can you help us understand what happened? In today's show, there was a dead body in the coffin. How did that happen? Was there some kind of... accident?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I-I don't really know. The coffin was supposed to be empty when I opened it. But instead, Mr. Reus's body was in there...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must've been a huge shock for you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And when the dragon set piece fell down at the end -- was that an accident, too?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must have been. I have no idea how or why that happened, either. Nothing went the way it was supposed to! I still can't believe Mr. Reus is actually dead...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>As tough as she is, this is obviously taking a toll on her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But how did Mr. Reus's body get into the coffin in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, we need you to tell us the secret of the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... You know what they say, "a magician never reveals her secrets." ...But I guess I should make an exception this time. But if you ever tell anybody... ...I'll make you my guinea pig for every single new magic trick from now on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">D-Don't worry! I'm a lawyer, remember? Client confidentiality is part of the job!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So let's call this trick "Trucy's Great Escape." How did you get out of the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...All right. Here goes. I'll reveal the trick just for you two. Prepare yourselves for an exclusive explanation by Magical Girl Trucy Wright! There's a secret trapdoor in the stage that leads down to the understage passage. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A trapdoor...? So when did you slip down into the understage passage?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Remember when Mr. Hat was onstage, holding a sword next to the coffin? Well, by then, I had already escaped from the coffin and was waiting understage. And, while I was down there, I did several things to get ready for the next part. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What technique! Okay, so what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Hat was quickly raised up to the catwalk by wire. There's a cushion up there that acts as a shock absorber when Mr. Hat hits it. Meanwhile, I popped back up onto the stage through a different trapdoor! And voila! The switch is complete!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I had no idea all of that was happening! I was convinced you were still in the coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's what professional magicians do. They make their audience see something that isn't really there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words, you make us see illusion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get it – it's kind of like a magical bluff.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... but there's no escaping the fact that the victim's body was actually inside the coffin. It wasn't empty like it was supposed to be.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, that's the part I don't understand. The last thing in the world I expected to see in there was Mr. Reus!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could he have climbed in there by mistake? <thought>I should get back to asking Trucy about the accident.</thought> Can you tell us more about the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who exactly is this Mr. Reus? You said he used to belong to Troupe Gramarye, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, you don't know who The Great Mr. Reus is, Apollo?! He's super famous! He's all people talk about on TV!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? I just assumed he was one of Trucy's assistants.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to diss the dead, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So how did the two of you come to perform together, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, like I said, he used to be a member of Troupe Gramarye. He was a protégé of my granddaddy, Magnifi Gramarye. So the TV station arranged for us to perform together this time because of that connection.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did he continue performing as a magician after he left Troupe Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No. He got injured while practicing for a show about thirteen years ago. That's why he left the troupe. After that, he took a break from magic for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm pretty sure it's a recent thing, him getting famous again. I only started seeing him on TV again maybe last year.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I had nothing but respect for Mr. Reus as a magician. I can't tell you how sad I am this happened...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't imagine how traumatic it must be to have someone die during your big show...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry, I'm fine! I have to stay strong for my fans!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>My bracelet is reacting... People tend to unconsciously tense up when they're trying to hide something. And when I pick up on their distress, the bracelet around my wrist starts to feel tight. So I guess this means that Trucy's trying to hide something from me. Well, I guess I should give my bracelet a touch (X</thought>...)</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can see things others can't -- the slightest twitch, gesture, or change in expression... Yes... I can see it all when I'm concentrating intensely like this. And when people are feeling tense, they sometimes reveal a certain habit or little tic. I'll just shift my viewpoint around until I find Trucy's nervous tic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay. I think I found her telltale tic. Now, to listen carefully to every word and see what she gets shifty-eyed over. Then I'll "Perceive" (X</thought> whatever she seems nervous about to get to the bottom of things!)</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry, I'm fine! I have to stay strong for my fans!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Flustered? I don't think so? What about you? You have little beads of sweat on your forehead! And you only display that tic when you don't know what you're doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch. Trucy's tongue is as sharp as her eyes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I should touch "Perceive" <thought>X</thought> while she's displaying her nervous tic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come on, Trucy. You should know by now that you can't hide anything from me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! Don't tell me that your bracelet reacted...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And here I thought my smile was going to do the trick... Heh. Looks like I broke the first rule of being a magician. "A true entertainer always keeps a smile on their face," right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I remember hearing you say that before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right. It's a Gramarye motto that my daddy used to say before he passed away. I'll never forget it. It's one of the few precious memories I have of him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you can't keep everything inside, Trucy. You'll burst! Why don't you tell me what's bothering you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't! If I did... ...you wouldn't believe in me anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not true. As an entertainer, you believe in always keeping a smile on your face. And as a lawyer, I have a belief that's important to me as well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well... Something about the shape maybe...? Or the color...?  Heh. Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's okay... If you can't believe in me, then you just can't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I just made a mistake. Let me try that again, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! Your attorney's badge...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I swore on this badge that I would always believe in my client to the bitter end. That's the cornerstone of being a good lawyer. Mr. Wright taught me as much. So no matter what you tell me, I'm going to keep on believing in you, Trucy! All I ask is for you to have a little faith in me,</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............ All right. Thanks, Polly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Polly... What if I made a mistake...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What if it really was me who stabbed Mr. Reus...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What makes you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, in my escape trick, I use both a real sword and a rubber sword. I switch the real sword for the rubber sword just before I stab it into the coffin. So even if somebody HAD been in there, the rubber sword shouldn't have hurt them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But Mr. Reus was found dead in the coffin...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know! It just doesn't make any sense! I know I swapped the swords!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Positive! I practiced that trick hundreds of times with no mistakes! I remember very clearly swapping the swords this time, too! But could I have...? Could I have made a mistake this time...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Could she really have...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I'd better get going!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Where to?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">To practice my act, of course! The show's only a few days away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're really pushing yourself. Didn't you practice until late last night, too?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yup! Because everything's gotta be just right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......... M-Maybe I really did kill Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The worst possible mistake I could make... Such a horrific accident, right in the middle of my show... And yet, all I can think about is... ...now that this has happened... ...Troupe Gramarye will get its performance rights pulled! There'll never be another show! Everything my family worked so hard for will be gone forever! And poor Mr. Reus had his whole life and a great career ahead of him! I...  ruined everything...! I destroyed it all!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Polly... I... I'm ready to pay for what I did...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Trucy, I don't think you did anything wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You don't?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I've had one question going through my mind this whole time... Was this accident... really your fault?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't have any proof or anything -- it's just... ...I don't think you'd ever make a mistake like that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I saw how hard you worked on your tricks, staying up late every night to practice. And I know you. You always get everything picture-perfect.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Nobody's perfect all of the time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Still, I think something else caused Mr. Reus's death, not any mistake of yours. After all, you're sure you swapped the swords, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes... I remember doing it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then I just know it wasn't your fault, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But... how can you say that?! We don't have any proof it wasn't me! I-I mean I know you're a great lawyer, Polly, but...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe in you, Trucy. And I believe in your skill as a professional magician. So I'm going to prove your innocence. Don't worry -- you're going to be FINE!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............ ............ ............ *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thank you, Apollo. Thank you for believing in me. I-I'm going to... believe in you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Good!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I-I'm sorry... I need a tissue... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've never seen Trucy cry like this before... She always seems so strong... ...but maybe sometimes, she's just putting on a brave face. She's still just a kid, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, your attorney's badge! Does this mean you want me to...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not even you can make it disappear through this glass.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Three, two, one... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! It's gone! Wow, how did you do that?! And how are you going to make it reappear?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, guaaard! I'm ready to go now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what about the rest of the trick?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are you saying you want me to conjure up a copy or two of this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Forged evidence isn't going to help us in court.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It'll be fine! With my magic, I'll make sure the audience can't see the strings attached!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's not the audience, but the discerning eyes of the law I'm worried about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes! I'm counting on you! I don't want to have to cancel the show on its opening day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! <thought>She seems fine now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">*sniffle* Truuucyyyy! Let's wiiiin this triaaaal togetherrrr! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Unlike some people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we'd better get right to investigating. Come on, Athena. Wipe that nose and let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Excuse you! Do you see any snot on my face, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeesh... Talk about an emotional roller coaster...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll need to investigate the stage at the Penrose Theater where the body was found.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... I hope no one will try to stop us.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you're going to the Penrose Theater, can I ask you a favor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I left a very special notebook behind in my dressing room...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure. We can pick it up for you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That notebook is really, REALLY important to me! I-I don't know WHAT I'd do if anybody read&amp; it...! Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>W-Wow. I wonder what's in it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The notebook is in my blue handbag on the table. lt's big and black -- you can't miss it. Thanks in advance! And with that, I've gotta go. It seems they've got more questions for me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. See you later, Trucy. <thought>So, should we investigate the stage first, or go get the notebook...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It must be so hard for Trucy, yet you saw how bravely she held back her tears!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you should practice a little of that "bravely holding back your tears" thing, too. And by "maybe," I mean your nose is running again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Enough with the snot-shaming! Haven't you ever heard the song, "Into Each Life Some Boogers Must Fall"?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'll take your word for it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We have to investigate the Penrose Theater from top to bottom! And talk to every single person involved as well!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you're really fired up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! Trucy's entire future depends on this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The agency's entire financial future, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, some evidence from the case? Well, too bad. I don't have a single thing to say about it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you're proud of that... why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's get down to business...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Hey! What do you think you're doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're the attorneys for the defendant in this case. Is it all right if we examine the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Of course it's not all right! I don't care if you're the defense or the president! No unauthorized investigations!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aw, come on. It wouldn't kill you to let us take a little look around...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">I said no! Now get out of here! Scram!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess we'll just have to try and get permission from the lead detective.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we're real quiet and sneaky, maybe we can--</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Hey, you kids! Don't touch the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we're the defendant's lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Big deal! You think that buys you some kind of special privilege or something?! If you try and touch anything again, I'm gonna arrest you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if we give you a super discount coupon for when you need legal representation?</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">.........I said no!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He actually thought about it for a second there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess we'll have to find the lead detective and get permission after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh. I've tried calling Mr. Wright a hundred times, but he never picks up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We've left him some voicemails, so he'll probably call once he gets them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's going to flip out when he hears what happened to Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, this is the place -- the theater where that "magical murder" happened!</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, yeah. Wonder if they brought the dead body out yet.</line>
<line speaker="???">I hear they already arrested the murderer. They say it's a young girl!</line>
<line speaker="???">Yeah, a high school student. Can you believe it? Kids these days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with all the curious bystanders? They sure are kicking up a fuss.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How dare they call Trucy a murderer?!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">They've got some nerve!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We can't let people think that about her. We have to defend her!</line>
<line speaker="???">Apollo? Is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...E-Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's sure been a while. How've you been?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, can't complain. I haven't seen you in ages. ............ <thought>Ema is not usually in the best of moods... ...so I never quite know what to do or say around her...</thought> ...Well, we have some business to take care of, so I guess we'd better get going!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, wait a minute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Was it something I said?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're darn right it's something you said! What's with you brushing me off like that? We've got heaps to catch up on! After all we've been through... You're not still mad at me about something, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry. I didn't mean to upset you...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who's this, Apollo? A distant cousin or something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, Ema's a detective I've had the, uh... pleasure of working with before.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hello. I'm Ema Skye, forensic investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? So you're finally a full-fledged forensic investigator?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah! I finally achieved my life-long dream! Look! I even have an official forensic investigator armband and everything!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's great, Ema! I bet the exam was really hard, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, it was a cinch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? 'Cause I thought you said something about failing it over and over...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, never mind that! The important thing is, I'm not a plain ol' detective anymore! So no more boring ol' investigations for me! I'm so happy, I could hug the whole world!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Coming from you, that's really something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Criminals beware! Fingerprinting, luminol testing, DNA analysis -- Ema Skye is raring to go, o bring it on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow. I guess it's "goodbye, grumpy clouds -- hello, fanatical sun."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">She's very cheerful, isn't she? Is it because of the weather or something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She sure wasn't like this before. She was pretty frustrated back when she was assigned to the Criminal Affairs Department. And she was always munching on chocolate Snackoos to relieve her stress.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Snackoos and stress are a thing of the past. I've said goodbye to both of them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And may you never have to see either again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">By the way, are you two here because of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Murder"? Don't you mean the "accident"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh. Then I guess you haven't heard. The case is being treated as a straight-up homicide now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just so you know, I heard that the prosecution is going to argue tomorrow that... ...Trucy outright murdered Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you kidding?! They're treating it as a murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema! Please tell us everything you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course! Anything to help Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why is the case being treated as a homicide now, and not involuntary manslaughter?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, apparently... ...there's something that proves it was a straight-up homicide.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's vague. Do you know any of the details?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">N-No... I'm afraid that's all I was told...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? How come?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, because the lead prosecutor is kind of a hard guy to read. Though maybe it's just a culture gap thing? Anyway, he's not one to really share his thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what do you mean by "culture gap"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I mean that he's a foreigner, so his way of going about things is different.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So who exactly am I up against tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Congrats on finally becoming the forensic investigator you always wanted to be.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Thanks! I failed that exam so many times, but I finally did it! I can finally use my forensics kit openly, whenever I want!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, yeah. You used to have to stealth use a kit you sent away for.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I still use that one, too. But now, it's more of a hobby kit. It's important to have hobbies too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, basically, nothing's changed.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you kidding? I don't have to worry about getting in trouble for taking fingerprints for fun now! It's positively life-changing! I can take all the prints I want!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Are you sure you're allowed to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure, I'm sure! I've been collecting all the prints I've taken into a personal database! Now, hold out your hands! I need to get your prints, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just promise me you won't use them for evil...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I can't believe she took my prints, too, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth has been reorganizing the prosecutor's office lately. As a part of that effort, he's gotten rid of a lot of corrupt prosecutors. So the prosecutor's office is looking pretty empty these days...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that's how a foreign prosecutor got assigned to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's part of it, yes. We were short on prosecutors, and this guy just happened to be visiting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what's the purpose of his visit?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, some insurgents from the Kingdom of Khura'in are thought to be hiding out here. As an international prosecutor, he apparently came to investigate the matter personally.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he's from the Kingdom of Khura'in?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. He's also a Khura'inist monk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A monk? So how did he get assigned to this particular case anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It seems he's very devoted to furthering his studies as a prosecutor. He wanted to learn how crime scenes are investigated here, so he just showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he was just curious, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He looked the entire crime scene over quite earnestly... ...and just as everyone else was ready to call it a case of involuntary manslaughter...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's what he said. Just like that. Then he volunteered himself as the prosecutor for this case. With the shortage of prosecutors right now, the prosecutor's office was glad to have him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Trucy was arrested for murder all because of this guy, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I have to say, he's definitely not your typical prosecutor. He says court is where a victim receives their last rites. Where the truth is revealed, the criminal is judged, and the victim's soul sees salvation... Receiving last rites in court allows the victim to finally rest in peace, or so he claims.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, to him, a trial is like performing funeral rites for the victim, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's certainly a unique way of looking at it...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">His name is... Nahyuta Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Nahyuta... Sahdmadhi?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. What, do you know him or something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh... I guess you could say I've heard of him...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, well, he IS pretty famous.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. They say he travels the world, solving difficult case after difficult case. Where there is a hard case to crack, he's called in to prosecute it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. Sounds like he's going to be tough to beat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I... I can't believe this... I have to stand in court against... him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He seems like a very kind and gentle person, though. He's very polite and understanding to everyone he talks to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh. So he's a pretty agreeable guy, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah. He's bound to see what kind of person Trucy really is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But don't they hate defense attorneys in Khura'in? Would he even listen to what we have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't see why not. He certainly seems like the type of person who would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even so... do you think you could do us a favor, Ema? Could you tell Prosecutor Sahdmadhi about Trucy -- about what a good person she is?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course. Leave it to me! I'll make him understand there's no way Trucy could've committed murder!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope he listens to reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Me, too...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's been two years since we first met... ...but you're still just a newbie to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, that's not fair! I'm not even the newest lawyer in our office anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! That's Apollo and me -- just two newbies working our way up!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aww. Look at you two, the newbie duo. Must be nice, right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Ema">O-ho! Are you asking me to test that? .........Hey! Why are you putting it away?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't... I just can't let her cover this in chemical reagents...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Look on the bright side, that's what.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Bright side? What bright side?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the good thing about there being proof is that it has to point to the real killer. If we can find out who that is... ...we can prove Trucy's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! H-Hey, you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which means our objectives are clear. We have to find two things: proof of Trucy's innocence... ...and evidence of the true culprit's identity.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know what, Apollo? You're starting to give me a glimmer of hope!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And that means there's only one thing to do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, would it be all right if we investigate the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If I said no, you'd just do it behind my back anyway, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha... Would I do something like that? <thought>Guess the jig is up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, all right. But I'd better come along. Who knows what sorts of mischief you'd get up to if I'm not there to keep an eye on you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Mischief"? Sounds like Ema trusts you about as far as she can throw you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He HAS been known to move things around at the scene of a crime, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what about you? You used to do all kinds of forensic tests on things without permission.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's nothing wrong with that! After all, forensics is ALWAYS on the side of justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How is that even remotely fair?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The dressing room looks just the way it did before the incident. All these items look kind of lonely without their owners...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We have to find Trucy's notebook for her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see. She said it would be in her blue handbag on the table, right? <thought>We should see what else we can check out while we're here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, here's that handbag Trucy was talking about. <thought>I feel a little funny about digging around in a girl's purse...</thought> .........I guess it's okay to open it. After all, she DID ask us to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But not you, Apollo! Let me do it! Let's see... Huh? No, not this... What's this? Oh, wow! She has--?! Oh, Trucy! You are BAD!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is it? I want to see, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's funny...She said it was a black notebook, right? But there's nothing like that in here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Trucy was wrong about where she left it? Let's keep looking around for it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe you! You were just going to open a lady's bag without any consideration!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I did so give it consideration! Bagloads of it! It's just, well... Okay, I'll admit I was a bit curious...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It only took seconds for your ethics and morals to crumble... ...giving way to a desire to satisfy your insatiable curiosity...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> You don't have to make it sound so obscene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all of this stuff. They must belong to Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, look at the colors on that briefcase. Do you think he carries that around with him on his time off?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, during his shows, he wears a mask to hide his identity. If he carried that briefcase around when he wasn't working, wouldn't it give him away?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ahh, but you've got to change gears and look at things in a different way at a time like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, yeah? Meaning...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, what if Mr. Reus wore his full costume all the time -- even when he wasn't working? Then that briefcase wouldn't have given him away one bit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okaaaaay...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh. I'm getting pretty good at this "turn your thinking around" stuff, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's like a little kid who's learned a new trick and couldn't wait to try it out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I say we take a look through Mr. Reus's things, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey... Is that a notebook sticking out from behind his briefcase?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right. It's practically screaming, "Over here! Look at me!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think it could be...? Oh, wow! Athena! Our hunch was right... It's Trucy's notebook!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's it doing mixed in with Mr. Reus's stuff?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good question.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm, it's locked. I guess that means we can't read it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder what kinds of secrets are in there to make her want to lock it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A girl her age needs her privacy! Besides, everybody has a secret or two they don't want others to know about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If there's anything in there about kisses or crushes, I think Mr. Wright would cry.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What was Trucy's notebook doing in the middle of Mr. Reus's things?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The obvious assumption is that he was trying to steal it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But if he was, then why would he leave it sticking halfway out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he was just a sloppy guy? I can think of a few people like that. <thought>Like Mr. Wright, for example.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... If you say so... Takes one to know one, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Say what now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy put some posters up, I see. Oh, here's one of Troupe Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Troupe Gramarye: Magical Menagerie," huh? Looks like a bunch of folks dressed in outfits a bit too gaudy for their age, if you ask me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But isn't that pretty much how all the best magicians dress?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Was Troupe Gramarye really such a big deal back in the day?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess so. Everybody in the country knew them back then. They had great tricks... ...like making a building disappear, or escaping a safe dropped from a helicopter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. I was in Europe at the time, so I had no idea. But if even YOU know about them, then they must've been really, really famous!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I used to see them a lot on TV. I think it was back when I was in junior high. The one in black was the original leader of Troupe Gramarye, Trucy's grandfather. His name was Magnifi Gramarye. The one in pink with the moustache -- that's Zak Gramarye, Trucy's late biological father.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! And look. There's Mr. Reus. So this poster's from back when he was a member of Troupe Gramarye, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy said he left the troupe after he was injured during a show or something, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a dove. Trucy must use it in one of her tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah. Hm? There's another birdcage next to it. I wonder what's in that one.</line>
<line speaker="???">Cooooooo cooooooo ka-choooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Wh-What in the world was that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, look at the adorable little bunnies!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Rabbits, huh? I used to have a pet rabbit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? You? Ha ha ha ha ha! You sure don't look the type!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?! What's wrong with me having a pet rabbit?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aren't people who have rabbits as pets usually the quiet, sensitive type?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, pardon me for being so loud and insensitive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Aren't these nine-tails flowers? You know, those flowers that only grow in Nine-Tails Vale?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, my goodness! You're right. There's a card here, and a letter to go with it. The card says, "Good luck, Trucy! From Damian and Jinxie Tenma."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mayor Tenma and Jinxie, huh? What does the letter say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see... Oh! There's a message for you in here, too! "Please tell Mr. Demon Lawyer I said thank you for everything. Thanks to him, I overcame my fears and now I'm not afraid of yokai anymore! And guess what? I've even become friends with yokai like Ittan Momen and Konaki Jiji!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. No matter what happens, I guess she'll never grow out of her demon obsession.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, these are from Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Roses, huh? How like him: pretentious.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They might be pretentious, but you know what? He makes it work!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I've noticed this for a while now, but... ...you get awfully prickly when it comes to Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You think so?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I mean, don't hate him just because he's beautiful.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's not it at all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, these flowers! They're from Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Lamiroir...? Where have I heard that name before?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's a famous singer. They call her the "Siren of the Ballad," and she's pretty popular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would a famous singer be sending Trucy flowers?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we met her through a case I headed up once.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. Your circle of acquaintances is bigger than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir... I don't know why, but her songs really touch me for some reason... I hope she's doing well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at all this stuff. I bet it belongs to that bunny assistant we saw in the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. That's a LOT of stuff. Does she really need all of that? I mean, I don't think I've ever seen so much makeup.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When it comes to sheer number of items, your desk back at the office isn't any better.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those things are the natural accumulation of two years of work, and they're all necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Instant noodles and crackers?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course! I need those for when I have to stay at the office all night prepping a case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And the comic books, too?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... O-Of course I need those, too. Manga these days are super realistic and informative. I need them for research...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh-huh. I see. So you need to research street fighting and the funnies, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? A script of the show? It says "Bonny,"so it must belong to that bunny assistant we saw in the show. You and I got to see the first two parts, up to the end of the 10:20 AM segment. But this "Mr. Reus's fire trick"... We didn't get to see that part.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, because they canceled the show after the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, there's a note about the fire trick. "This will be dangerous. Make sure the fire bucket is ready!" Come to think of it, hen Mr. Reus turned into a dragon, it breathed fire, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Coin tricks and fire tricks were Mr. Reus's specialties. Maybe they had some big finale planned... ...where Mr. Reus and Trucy would face off in a grand magical showdown after his revival.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all these costumes. I bet they're all Trucy's.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, could you tell by the scent? Are you like, some kind of bloodhound or something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm her "assistant," not her pet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a shame Troupe Gramarye won't ever be as they were back in their heyday...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... But I have every faith Trucy will restore the troupe to its former glory.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And then you'll be REALLY busy as Trucy's assistant...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, did you just agree with me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! Why DID I agree?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess it means you're finally settling into the role!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N- No, it doesn't!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A mysterious, locked notebook... I wonder if there's anything about me in there! Like that one time I ate her pudding... I wonder if she was mad at me for doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry. If there's one thing I know about Trucy, it's that... ...she's more mature than some people I know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know what you mean. Just don't go poking around in my things at the office!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why? What do you have to hide?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think I like how her eyes lit up all of a sudden...</thought> Anyway, we'd better get this notebook to Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's weird, but I keep running into the name "Troupe Gramarye" over the years.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's fate. Have you ever considered joining them? You could use your expertise in forensics to do scientific magic!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're not thinking of stuff like picking the right card using fingerprint powder, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha! You can hardly call that "magic," Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-ha ha... Yeah, I guess not...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looks like we hit the nail right on the head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. Let's get down to investigating, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just make sure you don't move anything or I'll get in big trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine. I promise... <thought>...to only move the things I have to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I have my own investigation to conduct, but let me know if you need anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's been a while since we've done any investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well? What are we waiting for? Let's dive right in! You DO remember how to do this, right? If you don't, I can give you a quick rundown.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Should I have Athena give me a rundown?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I guess I could use a refresher course.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then take a seat, Mr. Justice! Professor Cykes here's gonna learn you a thing or two!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, brother. What did I get myself into?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you remember how to go about examining a crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see. I just touch whatever I want to examine, right? Either that, or I can place the cursor over it and press [A]. How'd I do?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hrmph, hrmph. I suppose that's acceptable. What else do you know about examining?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If I recall correctly, we can also take a closer look at certain notable areas or objects.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ten points to House Justice! Now, do you know how to change perspectives?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Touch the arrows on the Touch Screen, press left or right on [D-Pad], right? By changing our perspective, we might even find some new evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Marvelous, Apollo! Top of the class! I'm proud to have such a model student! And thanks to you,&amp; Professor Cykes here just remembered how to investigate, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could've just asked!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry about me! I've got it all locked away in the vault up here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'm sure it'll all come back to me, too, as we go along.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wait, wasn't it YOU who just offered to give ME a rundown?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, hey. This is a curtain. I wonder what's behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The backstage area. There's magic equipment and stuff like that back there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>I'll open it a crack and check it out later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...You weren't thinking of opening that curtain, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Who me? Ha... ha ha! Would I ever do a thing like that? <thought>Rats. Guess I'll have to ask her to open it for me later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That video camera is pointed right at the stage. I wonder what it recorded? I want to take a peek, but Ema would...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wow... This residue data is so fascinating! Hee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's so fixated on that bloodstain data, her eyes are getting bloodshot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Quick, Apollo -- while Ema's off in forensics fantasyland... ...let's see what's recorded on the camera!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the same video we saw on TV where you can't see the body at all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, did you notice a strange shadow in that footage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, why?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think it was my imagination, but I'm pretty sure I saw something...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A strange shadow, huh? I wonder what it was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I want to take another look at that footage, but Ema's right there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You just leave this one to me -- Athena Cykes: Human Whisperer! Oh, Eeemaaaaa! Could you teach me how to find fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Could I ever! I like your moxy, girl! Here, now watch carefully. What you do is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nice work, Athena! Now's my chance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I really want to check out that shadow. I sure wish I could take this video with me, but I guess I'd better not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a sword here... It's covered in blood. Must be the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucy said she was sure she switched it out with the rubber sword.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Unfortunately, this one certainly doesn't look like it's made of rubber... Hey, Ema? Were there any fingerprints on the sword?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's see... According to my data... ...no prints were found. But that could be because the culprit wiped them off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it, Trucy was wearing gloves during the show. So she certainly wouldn't have left any prints either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A white outline, huh? So this is where the body was.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What exactly did it look like just after the incident occurred, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I have a photo of the crime scene. Here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, wow... It looks like he was stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, that's definitely what killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this thing around his waist?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's a stunt harness. A stunt wire can be attached to it so the person can float and fly through the air.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come to think of it he did fly in Act One, didn't he.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is what they call a "set piece." It's a piece of the onstage scenery. It suddenly fell down after the body was revealed, if I remember correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just as the brave heroine screams, the spell on the dragon breaks... Losing its wings, the dragon falls to the ground... That moment marked the collapse of Trucy's magical kingdom...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Magic, huh... Yeah, sure. The timing was so perfect, I'd be genuinely surprised if it was magic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, this dragon is a lot more handmade than I expected.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well... I can't tell you how many hours I put into that freaking thing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? You made it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy had me help put it together. You know, as her "assistant"...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...She has you wrapped around her little finger, doesn't she.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy's smile has some kind of magical power that makes it impossible to say no...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! I've seen something like this before! It's like that game where you stick swords into a barrel until a little man inside pops up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, that doesn't sound like any game I've ever heard of.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? It's pretty famous in Europe... Did you have ANYTHING to play with as a kid?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, you know us simple Americans -- we're happy with just a hoop and a stick.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We have one of these in the office, too, don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, that poor magic prop we use as a shelving unit. I'd kinda like to see Trucy perform this trick sometime...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, we both know you'd be the one in the box if she ever did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I feel bad for the prop, but... ...it can stay a shelving unit, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Ema, can I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Shh! This is the best part!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She won't even look this way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh, what great prints! Another set for my collection! Hee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She, uh... certainly seems to enjoy her work, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is the coffin the dead body appeared from.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I actually haven't examined that yet. Would you two mind giving me a hand?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No sweat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy said the coffin was supposed to be empty when she stabbed it. So how did the victim even get in there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet there's a secret door or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It sure is an oddly shaped thing, isn't it? Who knew it could unfold into something like this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I heard that since it's used for magic tricks... ...the left and right panels are made to be interchangeable. How that helps with magic tricks, though, I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure they make use of it in some way we can't even imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's check it out up close.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, look! There's a secret door in the back panel of the coffin. Do you think Mr. Reus could have entered the coffin through there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If he could've done it without Trucy noticing, then maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's like two magicians trying to out-magic one another right under each other's noses.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a secret door in the back panel of the coffin, too. I wonder if Mr. Reus entered the coffin through there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a minute. It looks like the bottom of the coffin opens, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, a secret door! Let's try opening it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, look at that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It seems to lead to someplace under the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. It goes to the understage passage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's pitch-black down there... Hold on. I think I see something glowing faintly. It's hard to make ANYTHING out from up here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If you try to go down there, the magicians will get mad at you. Apparently, there are things down there that will give away the secrets behind their tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that sucks. It's all right there and we can't even check it out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're definitely gonna have to examine that understage passage at some point, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is how Trucy pulled her Great Escape trick off, huh. She went through this hole and down into the understage passage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looking at it like this, the trick seems so simple.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I remember Trucy saying once that... ...making a simple trick seem mysterious and magical is the hallmark of a great magician.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Kind of like how pulling off the most amazing bluffs is the hallmark of a great lawyer, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The victim was a popular magician, "The Great Mr. Reus"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was this Mr. Reus really all that famous?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah -- he was especially well-known for his "time reversal" tricks. He could turn even a fully-grown chicken back into a baby chick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. I wish I could've seen that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something isn't right... It just doesn't make any sense...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the matter, Apollo? You're making that weird thinking face again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How did what should have been a rubber sword get switched with a metal one? Plus, the timing of that dragon set piece falling down... Wasn't that just a little too convenient? Something just isn't sitting right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ground control to Major Apollo! Can you hear me, Major Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Athena! I think I've got it! I think somebody switched Trucy's rubber sword for the metal one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">To pin the murder on her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Someone switched the swords? But when could they have done that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When everyone was too busy to notice. Somebody could have switched Trucy's rubber sword with a metal one...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They could've switched the swords right before Trucy's trick.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? But wouldn't that mean... ...Trucy herself stabbed the victim with the metal sword?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly. And that's why it COULDN'T have been right before Trucy's trick. Very good, Athena. You managed to avoid my little trap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo, do you really think you can pull the wool over my eyes so easily?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Heh, heh... There's no fooling you, is there...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Could the swords have been switched at some other point in time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">During Trucy's trick, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... And how would they have done that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, they would just... Er... Hmm... ...If I knew how they did it, I could be a magician, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, you have absolutely no idea. I think it would've been pretty hard to switch them during the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After the set piece fell, everybody in the audience was kicked out of the theater. In the ensuing chaos, somebody could have carried out a cover-up operation. Any one of the stagehands or show personnel could've done it before the police arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So what you're saying is... ...somebody's actively trying to frame Trucy for the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, some disgusting individual is trying to get away with murder.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So it's someone related to the show...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's definitely a very high chance of that. <thought>Now, if we could just figure out who it is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see. What else do we need to do on this stage? Ema, did you find any fingerprints on the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually, I haven't checked yet. I was going to do that at the end. I like to save the best for last!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, we aren't exactly talking about dessert here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, but we are! Would you like to partake in my delicious dessert? I don't mind sharing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, yes, please! There's always room for dessert, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right... I guess I'll join you two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, could you show us how you check for prints, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure. Let's start with the basics. As you know, fingerprints are an excellent way of identifying someone. That's because no two people have the same set of fingerprints -- not even twins.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So if we find any prints on the coffin, they might lead us to the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If the culprit was dumb enough to leave prints behind -- sure. Let's go ahead and dust for prints now. Let's see... This looks like a promising spot. Try dusting the area with fingerprint powder. Keep tapping the Touch Screen until the powder covers the surface thoroughly. When you're done, blow into the mic to get rid of the excess powder. The powder in this bottle is all we have to work with. If you run out, try blowing into the mic. Any excess powder will be returned to the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. I think I'm ready to give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You found some prints. Looks like the fingers of somebody's left hand. Now, let's try comparing these with the ones we have on file. First, touch "Analyze" <thought>L</thought> to select a print. Next, select the print you want to analyze and touch "Confirm" <thought>X</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've got a pretty clear print here. I wonder whose it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I have the prints of everyone involved in the case right here. Just choose the person whose prints you'd like to compare the sample against.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the last person who was in the coffin was...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...You seriously thought THAT was the last person in the coffin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I just wanted to see what would happen if I picked the wrong person, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, right. Anyway... If you're done with your little experiment, would you care to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, please... Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bingo. Looks like the prints belong to the deceased, Mr. Reus.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if we found prints here... ...maybe we can find them elsewhere on the coffin, too. <thought>Guess I'll try dusting for more prints.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't look like there are any prints here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's too much powder stuck to this print, making it impossible to analyze. Let's use a different, clearer print.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There. I found some!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">These prints are apparently Mr. Reus's, too. Shall we try looking for prints on the outside of the coffin now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, let's.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This time, you'll be able to rotate the coffin and look at it from different angles. That'll give you a chance to examine it thoroughly. If you ever get stuck or confused... ...you can always touch "Reset."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. And if I find any prints, I'll choose one to run against your data -- just like before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I found another print! Judging from its position and location... ...it might've been made when someone put this lid on the coffin. Let's see, now... There was one part during the show where someone put this lid on... ...after Trucy had gotten into the coffin. Therefore, this print should belong to...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like the print belongs to that bunny girl.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it... ...she DID put the lid on the coffin during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's probably when she left her print on the lid.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No good, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because Trucy was wearing gloves, remember? She couldn't have left any prints.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Let's see... The person who closed the coffin with this lid during the show was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guess it wasn't that person.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Since the print is on the lid of the coffin... ...it's got to be someone who had a chance to touch it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Let's see... The person who closed the coffin with this lid during the show was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This print must also be from when the lid was placed on the coffin.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Which means it must belong to that bunny assistant, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There. I got a print!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All right. I'll just check it against my data... Huh? That's funny. It doesn't match the prints of anyone involved in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? None of them? <thought>How can that be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now, then. wonder if I can find any more prints...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I already checked this print.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How's this, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That print is from the base of the palm. You want to get prints from the fingers or the thumb, so why don't you give it another try?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's still too much powder left on this print. Try blowing some more of it off.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This print is too faint for analysis. Try applying some more powder to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It looks like that's about all the prints we're going to find. To sum everything up, the prints we found belong to... ...the victim Mr. Reus, the bunny assistant Bonny... ...and some third, unidentified person.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But that's strange. We didn't see anybody else up there on that stage during the show... Does this mean some outsider was up there -- somebody unrelated to the show?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I guess we can't really say at this point...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, thank goodness we didn't find any of Trucy's fingerprints, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But that's only because Trucy was wearing gloves.</thought> Hey, Ema, there's something else that's been bothering me about the prints... Don't you think there's something odd about Mr. Reus's prints?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Odd? What's odd about them?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if Mr. Reus was standing in the coffin facing forward... ...he would've left prints like this, right? But when we look at the actual prints... ...they're facing backwards. It doesn't make a whole lot of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, what do you know! You're right! I wonder how they wound up like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe he was accidentally facing the wrong way at first, but then turned around later?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, the coffin is much too small for a guy his size to turn around in. About all he would've been able to manage is maybe a little bit of twisting.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then it really doesn't make any sense, does it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I might've hit on something major here...</thought> ......Oh, I have just one more question, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, yeah? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Reus was stabbed in the back, right? But if he was standing in the coffin like this... ...how would that have worked?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, right. That. The lead prosecutor has an explanation, actually. He thought that the victim might've tried to dodge the sword as it came into the coffin... ...so maybe he twisted his body and the sword ended up stabbing him in the back. That's his theory, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see... <thought>I guess that sounds plausible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, guess that about wraps up our investigation of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually... there's still the area behind that curtain... Don't you want to know what's back there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure do. But Ema told us not to move or touch anything, remember? ............</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............Would you quit staring at me?! Fine. I'll go open it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, look at you, flaunting your lady-killer eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-ha ha. I have my ways!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm only doing this so I won't get charged with animal abuse for not throwing you a bone.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess puppy eyes can be just as effective.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All right, I'll be back. Well, go on and investigate to your hearts' content. But before you go moving anything...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know -- we'll be sure to ask first.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, by the way... Just "Examine" the backstage to move to the area beyond the curtain.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay! Time to get investigating!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Seeing the stage this way kind of breaks the illusion, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It just goes to show that some things are better left unseen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, listen to you -- sounding all grown-up and stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry. I'm sure you'll have some cynical one-liners of your own someday, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, boy... I can't wait.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway, on to more pressing matters. Let's go examine the backstage area.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Back to the backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a winch. I'm guessing they used it to pull Mr. Hat up. Oh, look. There are two winches -- one back there, and one up here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently, each winch was rigged up to something different. One of them was used to hold up the dragon set piece... ...while the other was connected to that weird puppet up in the catwalk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A "weird puppet," huh? <thought>We'd better go check out the catwalk later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of the two winches, one is connected to the dragon set piece......while the other seems to be connected to the weird puppet on the catwalk. Guess we'll have to go up there to check it out eventually.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a winch. I'm guessing they used it to pull Mr. Hat up. Oh, look. There are two winches -- one back there, and one up here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently, each winch was rigged up to something different. One of them was used to hold up the dragon set piece... ...while the other was connected to that weird puppet up in the catwalk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you mean Mr. Hat, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The wires from the winches have been pulled up through the catwalk. One of them is connected to the dragon... ...while the other is connected to Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A dustpan, a broom, and a bucket. Guess they use these to keep the stage tidy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I doubt that's what this bucket is for, though. See how it says "FIRE" on it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh. I guess it's a fire bucket, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, I heard the theater owner went out and bought that just for this show. When he heard there was going to be a fire trick, he flew to the store to get it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But can a little bucket like this really put out a raging fire?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm guessing the owner thought it could.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But it doesn't look like it's been used. In fact, the inside is caked with dust. What was the point of even buying the bucket, then?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait a minute. That means nobody actually prepared for the fire trick after all... Hmm... I have a feeling this might be an important bit of information...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, there's a coffin back here, too. It looks like there's a stuffed dragon inside.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No wait, look. It's just an illusion. See? The dragon looks like it's inside... ...but it's really just painted on the front lid.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, wow! You're right! That's really something else.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the show hadn't been canceled, we might've gotten to see this trick, too, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a guillotine. But it's not real -- it's just another one of Trucy's props.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if it was supposed to appear in the show.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? You mean she didn't mention it to you? She said you were going to make a guest appearance onstage for her guillotine trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I'd DEFINITELY remember not agreeing to something like losing my head on national TV!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a sign here that says "Understage." I bet these stairs go to the understage area.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucy told me she and her fellow magicians call it "the Abyss." I wonder why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who knows. Maybe because it's really dark down there or something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I bet they've got all kinds of magical goodies stashed away down there. C'mon! Let's go check it out! Huh? The door's locked. The entrance to the abyss is barred to mere mortals like us, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, well. That's what you call "a swing and abyss."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks like this ladder leads to the catwalk overhead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Do I really have to go up there...?</thought> Why don't you go on up and check it out, Athena? I'm sure you'll like the air up there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Where in the world did you get that idea fro... Waaait a minute... Are you saying I'm an airhead?! How rude can you get?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-ha ha... That's not what I'm saying at all. Now, up you go! I'll just wait down here...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Okay, NOW I'm starting to get the picture. You're afraid of heights, aren't you, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, now! This is for Trucy. She NEEDS us, so up to the catwalk we go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>W-Well, guess it's time to put on my big-boy pants...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you all right, Apollo? You're white as a sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha, ha ha! I'm F-F-FINE! <thought>Don't look down, Justice. Don't look down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Those green things over there look like cushions. I guess one of them was used to absorb the force of impact when Mr. Hat zipped into it. Let's go check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>W- Way over there...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. That's a big pulley! Looks like it's connected to one of the winches down below.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The dragon set piece must've been hanging from this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like Mr. Hat is rigged to this smaller pulley. Let's see... How did it go? After being blown a kiss, Mr. Hat goes wild and... ...just as he's about to stab the coffin, he gets pulled up to the catwalk... ...and the smokescreen was to hide his ascent from the audience's view.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">These set pieces look like a rabbit and a moon. Although... they kinda look like they could be a duck and a croissant, too... What do they look like to you, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........The Grim Reaper, and a guy falling to his death.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">C'mon, let's wrap up this investigation before your imagination catches up with you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look! There are cushions attached to the underside. Well, what are you standing way over there for? Come on over and look!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're not gonna try and push me off, are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Seriously, Apollo? C'mon, you'll be fine. Here, do you want me to hold your hand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, actually... if you wouldn't mind... Looks like you're right... And Trucy mentioned something about this, didn't she? That a cushion was supposed to absorb the force of impact when Mr. Hat was pulled up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? What's that? Look, Apollo! It's Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's attached to a wire. Actually, didn't Trucy say something like: They quickly raise Mr. Hat up by wire... ...into a cushion on the catwalk.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the stagehands pulled Mr. Hat up and left him here afterwards?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That wire attached to his back... It looks like it's connected to one of the winches down below. Huh? Mr. Hat's cape is ripped. Did that happen during the show? That's odd... It almost looks like... it was slashed with a blade... How in the world did that happen?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I see that you're trying to take this all in stride, and I respect that... ...but seriously, you're trembling like a newborn fawn up here!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Get it together, man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I can't help it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I think that about does it for the catwalk. Do you think we missed anyth--?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nope! Uh-uh! Didn't miss a single thing! We're all done here, yes siree!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I take it you're ready to go down?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I think we'd better. I feel a fainting spell coming on...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, brother. You don't need me to hold your hand again, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All done?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pretty much. There's just one thing: The door to the understage passage was locked. Any way we can get down there?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That place? They locked it up as soon as we police finished our investigation down there. If you want to check it out, you'll have to ask a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Trucy's at the detention center, so she can't help us. I guess we'll have to look for somebody else from the show.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay. And I'd better get back to my own investigation. See you around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's too bad about the understage area, but at least we learned a few things.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, like one of your greatest fears, heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I wasn't talking about that... I meant how all the behind-the-scenes stuff is set up. Let's see...&amp; We found out there are two winches backstage. Mr. Hat was rigged to the first winch... ...and the dragon set piece was attached to the other one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And both of them were used during the show. Right after the body was discovered, the dragon set piece fell to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And in the chaos that ensued... ...the culprit could have switched the rubber sword with the real one. <thought>So it looks like the best way to prove Trucy's innocence... ...is to identify the real killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? <thought>There's somebody on the stage. I wonder who it is and what they're doing. Maybe we should go talk to them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me. Are you connected to the show?</line>
<line speaker="???">What, you two got a couple more headaches for me to handle? I got my hands full as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, I remember this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you there! What the heck's going on?! They wouldn't even let ME in. ME, for crying out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Oh, Mr. Retinz! There was an accident during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">An accident? Great, just great. That's all I need right now. Do you have any idea how much money we're sinking into this program?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's that man who was going off at the staff in front of the theater.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I ain't never seen you guys before. If I had to&amp; guess,&amp; I'd say you're not production staff. Hm What's that I spy with my little eye? An attorney's badge...? Well how dooo you dooo! I didn't know you fine folks were laaawyers! My business card, if you would. Chaaarmed to make your acquaintance, I'm suuure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, thank you. So you're from the TV station I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Sharp as a tack, you are! I'm the producer of this TV special -- all myyyy idea, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm Apollo Justice, Trucy Wright's defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...Trucy Wright's....? Well ain't that a kick in the head. How about you open with that tidbit next time, champ?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, okay? <thought>What happened to the schmoozy magoo bit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I'm Roger Retinz. Hold the applause! And no autographs, kids -- I'm on the clock.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this guy looks reeeeally familiar, but I can't quite...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Really, kid? Then try this on for size... Hang loose, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Hang loose, baby"? ......*gasp!* Apollo! It's the Ratings Rajah! From Take-2 TV! He's huge! CRAZY HUGE! Like a real famous producer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? I've never heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Seriously, man? What kind of cave did you crawl out of? "Roger Retinz, the Ratings Rajah -- Titan of the TV screen!" Still not ringing a bell?! You ain't seen my hit Saturday night talk show at 8 PM eastern, 7 PM central?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, no. I can't say that I have.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You're blowing my mind, kid. You even know what a TV is? Say it with me: "Teh-leh-vi-sion."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, do you mind if I ask you a few questions about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">No, no, no! What kind of comeback is that?! Grow some backbone, kid! I basically lobbed that one at you. Now hit me with your best barb! Viewers'll love that! C'mon -- you gotta sell it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sell what...?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Say something funny for the nice people at home! Go on, hit me with your best shot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-My "best shot"?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">We're rolling here! Hurry up before they change the channel! Chop, chop!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, okay... Here goes... "T-Talk to the hand! KA-POW!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............"Ka-pow"? Really? And why are you pointing all dramatically like we're in court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I dunno... It just seemed like the thing to do... Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ha ha... Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oof! That's going in the cringe reel for sure. I think we can all agree that was a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. If I choked any harder I'd need the Heimlich maneuver.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I blame myself, really. Should've known better than to waste good film on a nobody. ...So, you wanted an exclusive or what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Today's magic show was being broadcast live on TV, wasn't it? And you were the producer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know... It sounds kind of tacky, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I'm telling you, man -- modern viewers eat this stuff up with a spoon! Trust me! All we gotta do is serve it up nice and hot. A feast for the eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>More like junk food for the brain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">But that little brat had to go and ruin everything with that accident of hers! You have any idea how many times they dragged me over here to prepare for today?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... He must know this theater pretty well if he came by that often...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ooh! That gives me an idea! How 'bout this?! "Mad Mindscape of a Magical Murderess! Closest Comrades Come Clean!" Tell me, has Trucy always shown signs of being unhinged? When could you tell she was about ready to snap?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz [on cue card]">GIVE ME THE LOWDOWN!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This guy's cruisin' for a bruisin', Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As long as you don't get caught on camera...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What were you doing at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Shooting a show in the station's studio. We had a whole bunch of girls in bikinis wrestle each other for the camera.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you didn't see the accident as it actually happened?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">That's right. That's why I was shocked when I first got here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he didn't hear about the accident until he arrived, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">...I'm guessing what you really want to know is whether or not I have an alibi, am I right? My staff at the TV studio can vouch for me. Why not go there and ask them yourself? You can give 'em my card, and they'll let you in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you have an alibi, huh? Good to know.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Magicians are all a bunch of good-for-nothings, if you ask me! Con artists and thieves is what they are! They trick people and take their money!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Coming from you, that's rich, pal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Magic tricks aren't the same as con jobs, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! The people watching never feel like they've been cheated!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">"Lawyers spout hypocritical nonsense. Big surprise there, lol" ...Aaaand "Post"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did he just post about us in real time?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Those Gramaryes are all criminals! It's in their blood. Trucy Wright ain't no different! That girl is no good! She may look all sweet and innocent, but she's a stone-cold killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't you dare talk about Trucy like that! You don't know the first thing about her! You won't find a sweeter, harder-working girl anywhere, period!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ha ha ha! She's got the wool pulled over your eyes, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What in the world are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You'll see! I'll dig up the dirt and expose the dark heart behind that sweet smile. I'll prove those Gramarye magicians are all a bunch of low-lifes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does he have a grudge against Trucy? Or maybe against all of Troupe Gramarye?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">TV is a window to the truth! It's not like that magic stuff, or the streetwise charlatans that perform it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here. Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">What are you showing me that for? What, you want me to do a special on you guys? "It's a Lawyer-ful Life: Justice in the Courtroom!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That doesn't sound half-bad, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Plus, it'd get some publicity for the agency! Count us in, Mr. Retinz!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">All right, then let's jump right into it. Eh-hem. "What made you decide to become lawyers?"</line>
<line speaker="Retinz [on cue card]">SAY SOMETHING DUMB!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? S-"Say something dumb"...? I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Now it's your turn! Jump in with a snappy comeback!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz [on cue card]">LAY DOWN A SICK BURN!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? "Lay down a sick burn"? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You two... I'm practically falling asleep over here! Where's the drama? The gravitas? How're you gonna draw in viewers with that yawn-fest? Work on your delivery and get back to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Y-Yeah, okay, sure...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think he's confusing actors and attorneys...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Is that a scoop? No? Then get it out of my face! Who's gonna tune in to see something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does this guy judge everything by potential TV ratings?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's a shame -- a crying shame, I tell you! What was supposed to be a fun, light-hearted program turned into this sorry affair... I'll have to sell it to news outlets all over the world if I'm gonna make my money back. Trucy Wright will make her debut, all right -- not as a magician, but as a criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WH-WHAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">It's my duty to report it! Can't let a tragedy like this happen again, now can I?! Even if she gets off somehow, I'll make sure she never walks the streets again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We won't let that happen -- we won't let you do that to her. We're going to prove her innocence in court.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hmph! Listen to you, acting all high-and-mighty! You're just another money-grubber! I know how you lawyers do things! You'll stop at nothing to win!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">If you win your trials, you get fat stacks, right? Is money really all you care about?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's with him, Apollo? Why won't he listen?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">But enough about you -- I'm all about going after Trucy now. I won't stop until she's behind bars. That's how we in the media dish out justice! Before you even get to court, my exposé is gonna take you down!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not if I have anything to say about it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Welp, gotta get back to the station. Hang loose, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like the prosecution won't be our only opponent this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But no way are we gonna let that guy have his way, either!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! Okay, we're done with this stage, so let's go someplace else. <thought>I still wish we could check out that understage passage... But what else can we investigate right now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>About all that's left to check out is that understage passage. We'll have to try to get one of the staff members to unlock the door.</thought> Hm? Someone just came into the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, it's you people again! You came back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">I... I saw you, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, it's you! The bunny assistant from the show, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What? Oh, um, yes, that's right. .........My name is Bonny de Famme.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I remember her talking to us earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Performing magic is like walking a tightrope -- there's always an element of danger. One little mistake can even cost you your life, I wonder if she'll make it across today...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... and what do you mean by that, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Hee hee. Oh, nothing! Now, if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She said some pretty strange things then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I... I saw you take it. Y-You took something from our dressing room... The, um...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Bonny! That teleportation trick you did was AMAZING! Fantastisch!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What? Oh, um, thank you! But what you did... S-Stealing is...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What other kinds of magic tricks can you do?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Me? Oh, well... H-How about this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Splendido!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, I think Bonny's trying to say something to us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She is?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Thank you, Mr. Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thief?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I saw you. I saw you take that notebook. Please don't take things from our dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">So it's true what they say... Thieves really do return to the scene of the crime, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Thieves? I thought it was just arsonists in real life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess that means she really saw us, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I bet this looks pretty bad...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">If you return what you stole right now, I won't call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, boy...</thought> You've got it all wrong -- we're Trucy's lawyers. She asked us to bring the notebook to her.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">T-Trucy's lawyers? Oh! I'm so sorry I called you thieves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you really thought we were thieves, why were you still doing magic tricks for us?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I can't help it. Whenever anybody asks, I just can't bring myself to refuse...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does that mean she's a real people-person or that she aims to please a little too hard?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">In that case, can you tell us the secret to your teleportation trick?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">W-Well... I don't know if I should... Oooh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I keep up the pressure, she just might tell us! I've been dying to know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leave the poor girl alone.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Are you... investigating the case...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I'm Trucy's biggest fan! I just love her to bits! I'd do anything to help her!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We appreciate that. In that case, would you mind if we asked you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're a magician, right, Bonny?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's right! My specialties are teleportation and this little trick right here... ........L-Looks like Mr. Bunny's in a bad mood right now...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Or that she messed up...</thought> You said you are a big fan of Trucy's, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, yes! I look up to her more than anyone else in the whole world!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about her makes you respect her so much?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">She's just incredible! Not only is she extremely talented... ...but she's so cool under pressure and always manages to keep a smile on her face! In spite of all that talent, she still works harder than anybody I know! You couldn't ask for more out of a magician!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm sensing a shift into hyper-fangirl drive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I love the unique way she does her tricks, and how she charms the audience! I especially love her magic panties trick, which is both cute and comical! The first time I saw her do that trick, I was so impressed... and so moved... I've gone to her shows to see her perform so&amp; many times, I've lost count, and...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...And that's why I think Trucy is top class -- a real first-rate magician!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I-I see. I think we have a pretty good idea of how much you adore her now.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh! W-Was I talking too much? I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better be careful about when and how I ask her about Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Anyway, that's why I'll do anything -- anything at all -- to help Trucy! Oh, Mr. Lawyer, you just have to prove her innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, I plan to do just that. <thought>I wish Trucy could see that she has people like Bonny in her corner, rooting for her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were in the magic show, right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's right. I take it you saw my teleportation trick?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, it was just wonderful! You moved from one place to another in the blink of an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I admit it WAS pretty amazing. I have no idea how you transported yourself over such a distance in just a split-second.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It must be so fun to be able to do a trick like that! Teleportation looks so cool! It's like a superpower or something!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yeah, my trick is turning some heads in the magic world right now. They're calling it "new, miraculous magic." Some even say it's the real deal! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Real magic, huh? I know there must be an explanation, but it sure does look real.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just have to figure that trick out... I want to do it myself!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, you'll never figure it out. I always perform it perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! <thought>This feeling... Looks to me like Bonny is hiding something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, you'll never figure it out. I always perform it perfectly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bonny:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, uh, I just thought you looked a bit flustered, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Well, anyone would get flustered with you shouting at them like that! Any more of that... ...and I'll bend those horns of yours like a spoon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hands off! Do you have any idea how early I have to wake up to get these just right?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bonny, when you said, "perform it perfectly"... ...your right hand would tremble and move your hat a tiny bit. I even caught a glimpse of the little rabbit hiding underneath.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ulp!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you really perform the teleportation trick perfectly this time?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">O-Of course! I definitely got THAT part right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean, "THAT part"?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a minute. Are you saying that you...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does that mean you regret ever choosing to become a magician? Is that why you perform your job with such a forced smile on your face? Is it to hide your true feelings of regret?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you feel like you made a mistake in your choice of career?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">...How can you even say that to me? I became a magician because I looked up to Trucy, and wanted to be like her. I'd never regret that decision!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Maybe YOU'RE the one in the wrong line of work, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ouch! So I made ONE mistake! Look, if what you messed up wasn't the teleportation trick, then...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you maybe make a mistake in the switching the swords?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I wasn't involved with that part, so how could I make a mistake? Not even I could mess up if I was simply watching!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you were simply watching...?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Ulp! I-I-I never make any mistakes under any circumstances! That's what I meant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She seemed pretty flustered just now... I bet she DID make a mistake somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You might have performed the teleportation trick flawlessly... ...but what about Trucy's escape trick after that? Did you make some kind of mistake during that?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, er... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I, uh... You see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you or didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Eep! I-I did... You're absolutely right, Mr. Lawyer. I made a mistake during Trucy's escape trick. I'm sorry I lied...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew... I feel like I pulled off a magic trick of my own just trying to get that out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you made a mistake during Trucy's escape trick?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yes... I was in charge of operating Mr. Hat, you see... ...but I made a huge goof. So, um, did Trucy explain to you how the escape trick works...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, she knew we'd need to know for our investigation, so she shared the secret. Let's see... After Trucy escaped from the coffin down into the understage passage... ...Mr. Hat was to be pulled up to the catwalk by a winch. Trucy would then pop up on stage through a trapdoor.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I was operating Mr. Hat at the time... ...but I flubbed up where I was supposed to have him stand. I was supposed to make Mr. Hat stand to the left of the coffin. But I messed up, and had him stand to the right by accident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... That matches up with what we saw during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? But, then, doesn't that mean... ...Trucy would've ended up popping up on the side opposite to Mr. Hat?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Yes, she would have, if she hadn't done some quick thinking on her feet. She managed to pop up on the right-hand side of the coffin for me. So the audience never even knew a mistake had been made.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to go, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">But my mistake caused her so much trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I'd better ask Trucy about this later, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I'm sorry I accused you of stealing earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you think we were some random fans who had snuck into your dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">No... Your flashy red and yellow getups had me thinking you're some new comedy duo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C-Comedy duo?!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I thought you were polishing your old married couple routine while you were poking around.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Old married couple routine?! Is that really how other people see us...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I-I guess I'd better keep my badge handy at all times...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I-I've been a fan of Troupe Gramarye for a really long time!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Was Troupe Gramarye really as amazing at magic as people say?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">O-Oh, yes! Yes, of course! Magnifi Gramarye's unique and wonderful tricks kept his audience mesmerized! And he crafted so many rare and special tricks -- things I could never come up with! He just created them one after another! He really was like a god when it came to magic! And Magnifi's protégés, Zak and Valant... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Oh, yes! Wow! V-Very, very interesting! I see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't believe she dozed off halfway through Bonny's history lesson... No, wait -- I can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">That's Mr. Reus...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were Mr. Reus's assistant, right? Did he teach you any tricks?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">A few, yes. But he once said to me... "Your magic isn't strong enough yet." "You would have a difficult time transforming into a dragon at this time."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What was all that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Mr. Reus always stayed in character, even when he wasn't on stage. It made it kind of difficult to talk with him sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like he was a rather quirky guy...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh! What is that? Some kind of new magic prop? I can help when it comes to all things magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... It's actually case evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh. Sorry. I'm afraid I can't be of much help then...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, by the way, we'd like to investigate the understage passage. Would that be all right?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, yes, by all means -- anything to help prove Trucy's innocence! I'll unlock it for you.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, there you are! You got a minute?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, Mr. Retinz! Y-Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Not you, bunny. The lawyers! They're the ones I want to see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have business with us?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I hear you two are from the same agency as Trucy. Is that true?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A contract? ...between Take-2 TV <thought>the 'first party'</thought> and Trucy Wright <thought>the 'second party'</thought>." "If, through the fault of the second party, the show must be canceled in part or in full..." "...the second party will pay three million dollars as compensation to the first party." TH-TH-THREE MILLION DOLLARS?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Yeah! That's more like it! That shocked reaction, that dopey expression! You'd make a great comedian!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I know -- I'll put you on my show. We'll get one of those cartoon anvils to fall on your head.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait a minute... Is this for one of those hidden camera prank shows?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You wish! That's an official contract! See for yourselves. You're the lawyers, after all. You should know one when you see one, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's right... It's all signed and everything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Are you kidding me?! The Wright Anything Agency doesn't have that kind of money!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">F-Fishing on the high seas?! No, thanks! <thought>I can't even swim!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> What kind of ridiculous, lowdown, unfair, one-sided contract is this?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hey, now! There's nothing ridiculous here! It's all perfectly legit! It's got her signature on it, see?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Urrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaarghh...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">My boys have gotta see the stupid look on your faces! It's priceless! Aaaand "Post"! Ha ha ha! I'm getting responses already. It's gonna go viral!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooooo... How could he...?</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Bye-bye, reputation...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You ain't seen nothing yet, baby! Heh heh! I'm gonna drive Troupe Gramarye and everybody associated with it into the ground! Serves ya right for getting involved with the Gramaryes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this grudge you have against the Gramaryes, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Huh? What are you talking about? Stress is making you paranoid, champ! Come on, Bonny. We have more filming to do!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Oh, um... Y-Yes, sir! Excuse me, Mr. Lawyer! Oh! And I'll unlock the door to the understage passage for you later!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would Trucy sign a contract like this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And why did all of this have to happen when Mr. Wright isn't here?!</thought> We'll have to come back for the understage later. Let's go hear Trucy's side of the story.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good thinking! We can't let you hit the high seas just yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There must be something we can do! We can't let the "Ratings Rajah" get his way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So if we can't pay back the money, I'm off on a tuna expedition for a TV show?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Cheer up, Apollo! You have to have a positive attitude about these things! Mmm, tuna... I wanna eat tuna tartare! Although...&amp; herb-crusted seared tuna sounds pretty delish, too... Hmm... Which one do you think sounds better, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Having a positive attitude is one thing, but I have zero intention of going tuna </line>
<line speaker="Athena">......Aw, phooey.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She really thought I was going to go...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Any bright ideas on how to get us through this crisis?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Our biggest problem right now is how to pay the money... Y'know, in times like this... ...we should consult a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Gee, now why didn't I think of that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Three, two, one... Ta-dah!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Wow! Now you made my handcuffs disappear! How did you do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's doing magic tricks for the guard?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, should I try making YOU disappear next, Mr. Guard?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">C-Can you do that?! Ooh, yes, please! This is so exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should probably stop her before there's another "incident"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T-Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! Hi, Polly! Hi, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We, um, have some more questions for you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Judging by the look on your faces, it must be about something big.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I guess you could say that... Things have gotten a little... sticky. <thought>Oh, and I have to remember to give her that thing she asked for, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, do you remember this contract?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes. I signed it before I went on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about this liability for compensation article here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Liability for compensation...? What are you talking about? Let me see that! ...What?! Th-Three million dollars?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just as I suspected, she didn't know about that part.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've never seen this article! And I read the whole contract from top to bottom!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I didn't think you'd miss such a big thing. But there's your signature, so what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">.........Maybe... ...there was some kind of trick involved? You know, like, when I signed it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, you think there might be some foul play afoot?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'm willing to bet that the Ratings Rajah is the one behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bonny told us about the mistake she made on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you mean with where Mr. Hat had been placed? Even I was at a loss about what to do for a second there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So how did you fix the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I was down in the understage passage when I found out. I had to work my butt off to fix it, let me tell you! After I escaped from the coffin and went down into the understage passage... ...I got a signal from Bonny saying she'd made a mistake with Mr. Hat's positioning. I was freaking out... I had to be back up on stage in a few short minutes! Magical Girl Trucy Wright was faced with an unprecedented crisis beneath the stage! Would this spell the end for "Trucy in Gramarye-Land"?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And? And then what happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Athena's totally hooked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was supposed to get back up to the stage through trapdoor #1 on the left... ...using a platform that can be raised and lowered called a stage lift. There was a stage lift, ready and waiting in the lowered position, under trapdoor #1. But Mr. Hat had been placed on the right, above trapdoor #2, by mistake. There was already another stage lift under trapdoor #2, but... ...it was in the raised position, since we hadn't planned on using it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. So how did you get back up onto the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why... through brute strength! I couldn't lower stage lift #2 by myself. So I pushed it back and out of the way. Then, I moved the lowered stage lift #1 into place under trapdoor #2.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hngrh! Ggggh! This thing is heavy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............I wish I could've moved it with magic! Unfortunately, my magic is useless under the stage. The understage is a dark abyss that drains magicians of all their powers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can see why it's called "the Abyss" -- I never knew it could take so much out of you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's just how it goes in the real world. Illusions are created by the blood, sweat, and tears of those behind the scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, I learned so much just now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, have you told anybody else about all this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Nope. Nobody.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This sounds like some critical information. better make a note of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We found this notebook... mixed in with Mr. Reus's belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think... he might have been trying to steal it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No way! I can't believe it! The Great Mr. Reus would never do any such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But would it be so far-fetched if he was after Troupe Gramarye's secret tricks...? It makes for a pretty compelling motive to take the notebook...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here you go, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're just letting me have it? What's come over you all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If it'll take her mind off things for a bit, why not let her have a little fun with it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I see how it is! Throwing down the gauntlet, are you, Polly? Fine then. In that case, why don't I make the money vanish from your wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. My money will disappear on its own when I take you out for a treat after this trial. Ramen at Eldoon's Noodles, cake -- anything you want!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...That's it? No sarcastic barb at the end? Are you sure you're feeling all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? Did I say something wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No matter where I perform, always put this poster up in my dressing room. As long as it's up on the wall, I feel like I won't make any mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like a superstition, I know the feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Still, it didn't stop such an awful thing from happening today... I hope my granddaddy doesn't show up at my bedside to scold me tonight...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Me, too, Trucy... Me, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still can't believe Mr. Reus is gone...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Had you been acquainted with him long</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, I just met him for the first time for this show.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But didn't he used to belong to Troupe Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes, but he left when I was still little. Even if I had met him back then, I don't remember it. That's why I was so excited about working with him...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah. Who could've predicted anything like this would happen...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here you go, Trucy. Here's your notebook back.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, great! Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what's written in there, anyway? It looks like it's full of secrets or something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's because it is. It was originally my granddaddy Magnifi Gramarye's notebook. He used it like a diary, nd as a place to jot down ideas for new magic tricks. Some of which, only members of Troupe Gramarye have ever laid eyes on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow... This notebook is a really big deal, then.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes. That's why it's always kept under lock and key.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet a magician would do just about anything to get their hands on that notebook!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And we found it mixed in with Mr. Reus's belongings... Could he really have been trying to steal it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Troupe Gramarye creed is also written inside. "A true entertainer always keeps a smile on their face." That creed was passed down to me from my daddy, as his daddy passed it down to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's true that Trucy always keeps a smile on her face... I guess it's due, in part, to her family creed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, I want to talk to you about where we found this notebook...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This notebook is super important to me... Thanks for getting it back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it like a diary or something?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, sure. Sometimes I write about my love troubles -- you know, stuff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just kidding! Did I get you?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No. So you were just joking, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Maaaaaybe. Wouldn't you like to know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Am I ever going to get a straight answer out of a Wright...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In any case, we'd better focus on doing something about this contract for now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucy signed it in her dressing room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we'd better do a little more investigating there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm so sorry to put the two of you through all of this...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, we'll get to the bottom of this. There's gotta be some kind of mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you need me to, I'm willing to take drastic measures! With my magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Y-You're not planning on pulling some "magical money" out of there, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No. My magic panties are much better at making things disappear than appear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...D-Do I WANT to know what she's planning to make disappear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We have to do something -- anything -- to fix this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I agree. Let's check out the dressing room again, for starters.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay. And we should finally check out that understage passage, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Abyss? Then you'll have to go through the backstage area. Be careful down there!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This notebook pretty much embodies the Troupe Gramarye creed, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about you, Athena? Do you have any principles of your own?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! First of all... I believe in doing at least one good deed every day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kindness to your fellow man, huh? That's a good thing to believe in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Next, I believe in always working to improve yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Keep challenging yourself, huh? That's some resolve you've got there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And last but not least, I believe you gotta have steak the night before a trial!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess it's true that no one can fight on an empty stomach, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. This is where Trucy signed that contract.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. And there must've been some kind of trick that was used when she signed it. The question is what kind of trick and how was it done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If some kind of object or tool was used, there still may be a trace of it somewhere. Like with the pen, or the paper...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well! It's time to find the secret to that trick! Auf geht's! Let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Hey, take a look at this clipboard.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Could you sign this, please, ma'am?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure thing! Just the one sheet in this clipboard, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't this the clipboard Trucy used when she signed the contract?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think you're right! Let's give it the once-over!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's try opening the folder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This part here holds papers in place.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Could this clip have something to do with how they conned her? ...OW! It bit me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only you could get hurt by a clipboard, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like a screw.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess that means this clipboard can be taken apart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I can't loosen this one without a screwdriver.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This screw won't budge. I don't think even your crazy strength could budge it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Crazy strength"? What kind of thing is that to say to a delicate young lady?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't see you denying it, either...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's just a screw.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmph. That observation won't get you any laughs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What? Do I have to make with the funny all the time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, this screw... It's different from the others. Not only that, but... ...I think it's loose. Look. I can move it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you sure you should be fooling with it like that, Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! It came right out...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See? I tried to tell you, but would you listen? Noooooo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hm? Hey, take a look through the hole, Athena. I think there's something back there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, wow, you're right. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, look. The back panel is loose. I think I can take it off. Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're just breaking things left and right today, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">L-Look! There's something inside!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is this black sheet of... I want to say, paper?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh I know! It's carbon paper! You put it between two pieces of paper and it copies what you write onto the bottom one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So when Trucy signed the contract... ...there was actually another contract underneath.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And her signature on the top contract got copied onto the hidden contract!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So THAT'S how Trucy was conned! This is that Ratings Rajah's doing! I just know it!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">How dare he?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You gotta hand it to him, though. It couldn't have been easy fooling Trucy. That girl's no slouch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. But I bet we can use this clipboard as evidence if we ever take this to trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What a rotten trick he played on Trucy with this clipboard!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And three million dollars? That guy is a real crook. It's quite the feat he pulled off, though. It's not everybody who can fool our Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can say that again! I still can't quite believe it, though. She may be the youngest member of our agency, but she's also the most level-headed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It kind of feels like someone sunk our battleship...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see... We should be able to get to the understage passage from backstage. Hopefully, Bonny unlocked the door for us like she said she would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The door's unlocked! Thank you, Bonny! Well, Athena, here we go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The stairs to the Abyss... This is how we get to the understage passage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It sure is dark and dusty down here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"The Abyss" -- the magical underworld. And look! There's a denizen of the Abyss now! A fearsome beast with long, sharp fangs, ready to prey on unsuspecting souls...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What're you...? Oh, you mean that tiny little rat over there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No. I mean that "fearsome beast" over there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I take it you don't like rodents.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at all these props! Hey! There's something in this hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A dove? Cards?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... A juice box and some snacks...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like somebody planned to have a little treat in the middle of the show...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This sword is the exact same design as the murder weapon. Wait... What's this...? HYAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OWWW! What are you doing?! That hurts! I-- I think I'm bleeding out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, stop being such a drama queen. It's only rubber.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? ...Hey, you're right. So this must be the sword Trucy used during the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">After the incident, someone must've switched this rubber sword with the real one onstage. And maybe that's when they brought the rubber sword here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"I'm gonna make it big someday, too! Just you wait and see!" Wh-What's that all about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My guess is... ...it's the soulful cry of some poor assistant made to toil here in the darkness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And who would know about the soulful cry of a bitter assistant better than you, right? You really understand the writer's feelings of despair and frustration!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sadly, yes. Yes, I do.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...You really shouldn't scribble on the walls, you know, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this glowy stuff? Oh, it's glow-in-the-dark tape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This must be what I saw through that secret door in the bottom of the coffin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But who put it here, and why?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's probably a marker of some sort since it's so dark down here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it's meant to mark which ladder to climb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This ladder goes up to the ceiling. So I guess it leads to one of the trapdoors on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trucy must've used this ladder when she escaped from the coffin. ...Why don't you climb up there and see if I'm correct? It's not so high. You'll be fine, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Why me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'd make a young lady wearing a skirt climb a ladder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine... I'm going, I'm going... Aaagh! T-The lights! It BUUUUUURNS! Ooooow...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I can now confirm that the ladder does indeed lead up to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that tasty bit of info was definitely worth risking life and limb for. Well done!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This ladder goes up to the ceiling. I wonder what's just above?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo. ............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-All right. Fine! I'll climb the ladder! Why does it always have to be ladders...? H-Huh? Where am I? It's pitch-black! And cramped, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know what I think? I think you're in that coffin we saw backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... So that's where this ladder leads. But I still don't get what that coffin was for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a stage lift for getting up to the stage. Trucy moved this one here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess it used to be where that yellow tape is. How in the world did she manage to move this huge thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It couldn't have been easy for her. She's pretty petite. But I bet it'd be easy for you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just what are you implying?! That's it, chump. You're looking up "microaggressions" later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a stage lift for getting up to the stage. It looks like this crank lowers the platform. But Trucy said it's impossible for one person to do it alone.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That sounds like a challenge! Now I wanna try it! HRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRGH! GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! ............ *huff, huff* *huff, huff* Ha ha... It's probably just broken...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Or you could just take people at their word.</thought> If I'm reading this room right... ...this must be the stage lift Trucy moved during the show. Originally, it was there, where stage lift #1 is now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hold on, Apollo. I hear... voices... Quick, hide!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? OW! Quit shoving!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hurry up and get down there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">YEOW! My arm doesn't bend that way! What the heck, Athena?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Shh! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">*sigh* It's so much WORK pretending to be cute and sweet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Isn't that Bonny?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Hey, bunny! Wait for me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And the Ratings Rajah?</thought> What did we have to hide for, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because I heard something funny. There was something off in their voices...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right. Athena's super-sensitive hearing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">Those lawyers are poking around, trying to stir up trouble. Should I be worried?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Relax! I didn't say anything to the police, and I won't say anything to them, either.</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">You better not! Or you're gonna get it! POW! Right in the kisser!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the...? Is it just me or does Bonny seem kinda different from before?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, shhh!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I'm sick and tired of this whole investigation! All I want is Trucy's head on a platter!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. Leave everything to me, babe. Don't forget the power of mass media! TV can accomplish anything! I'll make sure Trucy gets much worse than a guilty verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I can't wait to see that girl crying and begging for mercy.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">You really hate Trucy, don't you, bunny?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">I hate her. I LOATHE her! I can't stand that Trucy Wright! Just because she's a little good at magic, she thinks she's all that! So this is exactly what that sniveling brat deserves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! What the heck...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bonny">If you mess this up, you're gonna really be sorry. You hear me? I'll crush you flat. Like a cockroach under my foot!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Oh, you KYOOT widdle thing! You're so adooorwable when you're thwowing a fit! OW! OW! My foot! C-Can't you take a joke?</line>
<line speaker="Bonny">C'mon! Grab my things! We're leaving!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">D'awwwwwww. Lead the hippity-hopping way, my little bun-bun!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What was that absolutely revolting scene all about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess the entertainment industry attracts all kind of eccentrics... But that conversation... ;It set off every red flag in the book.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You said it! I smell "plot" with a capital "P.U."!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Retinz claims he was at the TV station at the time of the incident... ...and we saw Bonny onstage ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Apollo, I have an idea. Why don't we pay Take-2 TV a visit? We can check up on the Rating Rajah's alibi while we're there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like a plan.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is one of the stage lifts I moved in the understage passage during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't believe you were able to move something this heavy all by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I couldn't disappoint the audience, now could I!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's some real determination! You're a true pro, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, it was nothing, really. My granddaddy once finished an entire show after throwing out his back on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Now THAT'S magic!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! Look at this place!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's so much going on at once, it's making my head spin.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Take a look at that screen! And listen to those hosts! "Magical Murder! Live audience witnesses shocking skewering!" " 17-Year-Old Magician, Trucy Wright!" "See exclusive, unedited footage of the heinous crime -- complete and uncut!" We can't let them broadcast that! Trucy will get tried in the court of public opinion!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I doubt we can stop them from airing it... ...but we can prove her innocence in a realcourt of law! No matter what garbage they report on TV, we can set the record straight at the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A slot machine and roulette wheel, huh. They really went all in with the gambling theme.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks like that slot machine really works! I've always wanted to give gambling a try!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not worth it. Besides, you're not even old enough to gamble in most states yet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's all right. I get to experience it enough in court... ...guessing whether you'll win or lose the case on any given day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for the vote of confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Apollo. I only bet on winners and I haven't lost yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at that logo above the screen. "Scandal Gamble Gambit!" Is that the title of this show?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup. Haven't you ever seen it? They present scandalous rumors about celebrities... ...and then people bet on whether the rumors are true or not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh... o it's just another tasteless TV show. Today's scandal is... "Tragedy on stage! Did Trucy Wright cause an accident, or did she commit murder?!" It looks like "murder" is in the lead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I say neither.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then we'll just have to create a third option tomorrow -- in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This must be a video production workstation of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... That coffee cup looks awfully familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Yeah, that's where Mr. Retinz always sits. He's very hands-on, you know. You'll always find him on the set of his projects.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But he was here at the station during the magic show, right?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Yeah, well, he had two shows going at once this morning. He had his regular program to oversee here, so he couldn't be at the Penrose.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you can vouch for him -- that he was here at the station during the magic show?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">What, like an alibi? Sure can. He was definitely here. Still, after a while he couldn't stand being away from the Penrose, it seems. As soon as his part was over here, he took a taxi to the theater... ...but he apparently didn't get there until after that thing had already occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like he has a rock solid alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what that guy sitting down there is doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... It looks like he's reading that script he's holding.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........I think he's reading a comic book he's hiding in his script.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you're gonna goof off on set, that's a pretty bold way to do it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're looking into the incident that happened at the magic show this morning...</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Oh, that? Yeah, I was the cameraman for that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell us anything about what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">...Bonny was supes adorbs! Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... that's not exactly what I...</line>
<line speaker="Staff">I couldn't get enough of her! I filmed her the whole time! Got some primo footage, if I do say so myself! Heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better quit before he decides to share what he intends to do with said footage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pardon me. I know you're busy right now...</line>
<line speaker="Staff">What are you guys? Street?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Street"? Does that mean "people off the street" or something?</thought> We're Trucy Wright's lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Oh, okay. Lawyers. Got it. Well, whaddaya want?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He must be REALLY busy. He hasn't even looked this way.</thought> We're investigating the incident that occurred at the magic show this morning... ...and we heard that Roger Retinz was in charge of that program.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Yeah, that's right. The guy hates magic, but the show was all his idea. Just between you and me, I think it was Bonny that egged him on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Egged him on? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">I saw the two of them together -- you know, walking along arm in arm. I bet she sweet-talked him into doing the program because she wanted the work. She hasn't been selling very well on her own, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Oh, hey, if you're looking into the incident, I guess you'd want the show footage, right? It's on the disc in my back pocket. If you want it, go ahead and fish it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. Thank you very much. <thought>He turned out to be surprisingly helpful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Staff">Huh? You want something else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, uh, we're good. Thanks for your help earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's a pretty big back pocket you have to be able to fit a whole disc in there.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Yeah, I can fit all kinds of things in there! It's pretty handy for when I have to be out on location.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what other kinds of things do you put in there?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">...........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Um, maybe I'd better not tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>Now I really want to know...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess we got just about everything we can out of this place. It looks like Retinz's alibi is pretty airtight. <thought>But if that's true... then who could've killed Mr. Reus?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like we're pretty much done here. Should we go back to the office? We can get a snack and talk over our plan of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds good to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What in the world...? What's going on here?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All these stickers say "REPOSSESSED"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who did this? Who's responsible for this?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Whoa, now! This is a restricted area, champ! No trespassing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Trespassing"?! But this is our office! You're the one who's trespassing!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Enough with the lip, boy. Don't tell me you forgot about your debt?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">I'm just abiding by the contract. If the agency can't pay me, I have every right to seize its property, am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just like that?! We haven't even had a chance to take this to trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. If you're gonna be mad, shouldn't Trucy be the one you're mad at? I told you. It serves you right for getting involved with those Gramaryes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why, you dirty, rotten—!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These stupid stickers are all over the place!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Well, would you look at that? There's something I forgot to put a sticker on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! Don't put one on me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you going to do with all of our stuff?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Sell it, of course. Every last bit of it. That's why I'm seizing everything. And I'll take this little office of yours, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think you can just waltz in here and do whatever you want?!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Indeed I do! Unless you Wright Whatever Warehouse jokers got three million ready?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nnrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">That a no, then? Because I gotta recoup my money somehow. After all, the entire program went south because of Trucy. It's called "liability for compensation." And this infantile agency is the liable party!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why, you black-hearted...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Apollo. What about the crooked clipboard?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's no good. We don't have any proof that Retinz was behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Darn...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. You're gonna have to do better than that, folks! Looks like the famed Mr. Wright left behind nothing but incompetent newbs to run things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No way... He was counting on Mr. Wright to be away for this plan of his...? What a two-bit thug! We'll show him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Ha ha! There's the sugar! That expression! It's priceless! So, how does it feel to lose the precious office your boss left you in charge of?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Now, not to rub it in or anything... ...but I think you should know where you stand right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, man. What now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Here. Have a gander.</line>
<line speaker="TV">The trial of young, up-and-coming magician Trucy Wright is scheduled for tomorrow. We're here, just outside the office of the suspect, hoping for an exclusive peak inside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Is this LIVE?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ahh! Apollo, look! There's a sea of reporters outside!</line>
<line speaker="TV">Oh! A questionable-looking pair are peeking out the window at this very moment! Our viewers at home can see for themselves their vicious, brutal expressions...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yellow journalism at its finest...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">And that's the way it is. The majority of the public already thinks Trucy is guilty. They saw the whole thing happen with their own eyes during the show's live broadcast. Everybody in the country is against you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No way...</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">No office... No allies... Are you sure you still want to represent that girl?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course we do! We believe in her innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Heh heh. Go ahead, think what you want -- it's a free country!</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Just know that you'll be the biggest losers in the end. In the meantime, feel free to keep on flopping&amp; around like the dying fish you are.</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Huh? What's this? You want me to look at something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't show him that now, Apollo. He'll just try to take it from you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, good point. <thought>Better play our cards closer to our chests.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">What do you want, a handout? Fine, fine. Here. Now go away, kids -- ya bother me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, Apollo! The humiliation! He's treating us like beggars!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it bothers you so much, why do you have your palm stretched out?</line>
<line speaker="Retinz">What, you want me to repo that, too? I'll take anything you wanna give me as collateral.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, no. It's not for you. <thought>I'd better be careful not to show him any important evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Retinz">Now then, you gotta be outta here by tomorrow. Take in this cozy little office tonight while you still can! Heh heh. Hang loose, baby!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I can't believe we let Mr. Wright's office get placed under seizure! Of all the--!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is just ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Look out!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Clear out! We don't want murderers here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">HEY! If it's a fight you want, I'll take you on! C'MON!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">YIKES! Let's get outta here before we get killed, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*huff, huff, huff, huff* I can't believe this is happening...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We have to do something to protect ourselves... and fast...</thought>&#160;! ............It's Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">......*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-A-Apollo!!! I got your messages! How is she?! Is Trucy okay?! S-She's not crying, is she?! Does she have a lawyer?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-M-Mr. Wright!!! It's all a giant mess! Poor Trucy...! And the office...! Our office...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Apollo...? Okay, okay. We'd better both take a deep breath...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... I see... And he's saying you have to be out by tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm so sorry, Mr. Wright... I wish there was something I could've done...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... is quite the mess, isn't it? Even if I left right now, I wouldn't be there in time for the trial tomorrow. I'm sorry, Apollo, but I need you to handle this for me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course! We can handle the defense, but the office...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too soon to give up on that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The contract only addresses Trucy's liability if she causes the show to be canceled. So you just have to prove in court tomorrow that it wasn't Trucy's fault.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So everything depends on your winning that trial tomorrow. Trucy's fate... and the fate of our office. It's all riding on your shoulders, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I-I know... <thought>I-I'll be... fine... right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've been watching you grow over these past two years. That's why I can say, with absolute confidence... that you'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've seen you earn victory after victory in some pretty dicey situations... ...and guide Athena -- helping her along her way, too. That's why I know you're ready, why I know I can leave Trucy and the office to you. ...I believe in you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-Thank you, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good luck tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thank you! I'm... I'm fine! Everything will be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can call me anytime if you feel you need to, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But I'll be fine on my own, right? Yes, I think so, too. I can do this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the spirit. Give it your best out there, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">......*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it, Apollo? What are you smiling about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who, me? I-It's nothing... <thought>Mr. Wright believes in me. I-I can't let him down!</thought> We have to win this trial, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I couldn't agree more! And I'll do everything in my power to help!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Our opponent tomorrow... "Prosecutor Sahdmadhi," huh? Why now of all times...? Still, I don't care who it is! I can't afford to let my guard down for anyone!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">O restless wandering soul of the dead...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. Sorry to disturb you, but... I figured I should tell you...the lead attorney's been decided. It's...Apollo Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Apollo... Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
</xml>