
<xml>
<title>The Rite of Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What do I do now...? I can't believe Maya and I were actually found guilty...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial need not be drawn out any longer. The defense has failed to counter the charge filed by the prosecution. In accordance with the law, I invoke the Defense Culpability Act against the defense. Now, then. This court finds the accused, Maya Fey...  ...and the defense, Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">M-M-M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I saw the whole trial! What's going to happen to Miss Maya now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm worried about that, too. But right now...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">I have one more thing to report, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">This dagger... It bears the fingerprints of Maya Fey on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right now, I need to focus on the next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The murder of Acolyte Zeh'lot, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least the jury is still out on that one, so to speak. <thought>The two murders are most likely connected. If I can get to the bottom of Acolyte Zeh'lot's murder... ...it might give me the ammunition I need to overturn Maya's guilty verdict.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Let me help you investigate! I want to assist you any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I appreciate it, Ahlbi, but we're talking about a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yeah, but it's going to be hard for a foreigner to investigate this on his own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have a point there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I wish I knew what to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hm? Isn't that...?</thought> ...Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Princess Rayfa?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? ...Oh, it is you again. ...The dead lawyer walking, guilty of abetting a murderer under the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I see she hasn't lost any of her charm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why the long face? I thought you'd be glad I was found guilty under the DC Act.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Hmph. I am in no mood to take joy in your suffering. For I was unable to defeat you, and had to leave the job to others. I failed in my sacred duty as the royal priestess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that answers my question.)</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Have I misunderstood... the voice of the mitamah... yet again? ...Th-This--! This cannot be!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I did was defend my client... Nngh... I can't bear to see her looking so sad like this, though...</thought> ...Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? Oh, Barbed Head. I thought you had already begun your journey to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not dead yet! I still have an investigation to do... for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?! D-Do you mean to say... ...you have not given up yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. I'm going to prove Maya innocent tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............ But why? Why do you refuse to give up? I cannot fathom such obstinacy. Investigate all you want -- I care not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You really don't mind? But aren't you worried that a lawyer backed into a corner by the DC Act... ...might do something desperate, like forge evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If left unsupervised, I'd be free to do whatever I wanted, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, now to see if she takes the bait.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes... I see your point. Barbed Head...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I know what happened yesterday. You perpetrated some sort of fraud or other misdeed while I was not watching!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That explains why I misunderstood the voice of the high priest's soul! Yes, of course! That is the only explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I was just trying to cheer her up. Now she thinks even less of me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I must not allow you to sully our sacred Hall of Justice with your misdeeds ever again. Therefore, today, I will be monitoring your every move once more! I will not fail to spot your misdeeds this time! The moment I see anything out of the ordinary, I will send you straight to prison. And you, boy. Do not throw your lot in with this foreign devil.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...B-But... Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's okay, Ahlbi. You don't need to worry about me. I'll be back before you know it. <thought>But first, I should probably lighten my load a bit.</thought> Ahlbi, would you mind holding on to some evidence for me?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course not! I'm always glad to help!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">May the Holy Mother's blessings be upon you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now then... The scene of the crime is the logical place to start. If I recall correctly, the body was found at the Plaza of Devotion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That boy has grown far too close to you. He will require re-education if he persists in befriending lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Re-education? What exactly does that entail?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">First, he must meditate upon Lady Kee'ra for forty-eight hours in the prayer pose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How is that re-education? It sounds more like torture to me.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! You have an investigation to conduct, do you not?! Get on with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, but... <thought>Why does she always have to be like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What? Would you have preferred that tour guide boy tag along instead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! Oh, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, it would appear I have read your mind most accurately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That smile of hers is downright scary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaah! What the heck was that?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Honestly, what sort of grown man jumps at the call of a warbaa'd?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? That roar came from this bird? ...I-It is a bird, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">W-Well... give me a moment! ...Nayna! The warbaa'd has many natural enemies. Therefore, it mimics a lion's roar in order to scare them away. But you did not know that, did you? And you call yourself a lawyer! Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't know, either, until you asked Nayna.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Enough! You... You... lamebrain!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Have you never seen a yak before, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only in zoos.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well in Khura'in, they play an important part in our daily lives. Therefore, they must be treated with kindness and with respect.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H-Hey! What are doing?! I command you to cease that at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... That yak is really licking and nuzzling the daylights out of Rayfa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Foul beast! You have made a mess of my royal raiment! For that, I shall make a leather coat out of you later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was that about treating them with "kindness and respect" again...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why, this giah'pam looks positively delicious. I think I shall take this one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your Benevolence! You can't just take things without paying!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Shopkeeper! You will receive your payment from this barb-headed foreigner.</line>
<line speaker="Lady">Thank you, barb-headed foreigner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Peasants paying for princesses? This place is absolutely feudal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a poster... That's the Plumed Punisher, Khura'in's famous action hero. I guess we're not the only country with superheroes like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Was that your stomach?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">N-No! Th-That was not me!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Th-That... was the cry of the warbaa'd!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you like a magatah'man?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Enough! I am not hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why can't some people just admit when they're hungry?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the police already finished their investigation. <thought>To think someone would be killed here --  a place devoted to prayer. A body outline and... flowers? Did someone leave them here in memory of the deceased? Hm? And there's something different about the prayer flags today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I keep trying to tell you, Maya has nothing to do with any of this!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And you can prove this... how?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think I'm doing here?! Gathering dirt and dust for the trial?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You and your smart mouth! This is precisely why you and your lawyerly ilk are so reviled.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It's that detective from your country again...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Eep, it's the princess!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You seem displeased that I am here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, n-no, no! Don't be silly! Mr. Wright? I'm, uhh... I'm so sorry about what happened to Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not your fault, Ema. You were just doing your job. And if I had just done mine...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But it's no use crying over spilled milk! Would you mind telling me what you know about the murder? It's do or die in court tomorrow. And I mean that literally.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Gladly. I'll help in any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Remember, I have my eyes on the both of you, so see to it that you commit no misdeeds.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course not! Hmph, you're talking to a professional here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot died bent over in prayer. There's no trace of blood on the ground, though... The fact that there's so little bleeding could mean it was a single stab to a vital point. ...Not that that would've been very difficult, considering the position he was in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acolyte Zeh'lot was killed in a prayer pose. With his head bent over like that, the last thing he saw must've been this rug.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is a prayer rug woven by devout monks. May the Holy Mother's blessing be upon his departed soul.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's strange that there are no bloodstains, though...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... Perhaps it was so cold, his blood froze. Or perhaps it was absorbed by his vestment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It IS pretty cold. Maybe the blood really did just freeze inside his body.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So these flowers were left here in memory of Acolyte Zeh'lot? What are they called?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">They are known as nahmanda, and they are given to express sorrow when a life is lost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems offering flowers in memory of the dead is a universal practice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This prayer flag looks much newer than the rest. Umm, Your Benevolence? What does it say here?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The dearest wishes of our subjects are written upon these prayer flags. Reading the prayers of others is considered rude, but if you must know... ...it says, "At the usual spot. Bring grub. The key, too." Hmm,  that is one of the more direct and practical prayers I have ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I wonder if it's even a prayer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... How about starting with an overview of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure. The victim is Puhray Zeh'lot. He was the high priest's disciple. His body was discovered around noon today... ...right after the rite wrapped up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, during the high priest's murder trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. Apparently, he had been here praying since the day before the rite even started. Talk about serious devotion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I barely lasted a few minutes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is a picture of Mr. Zeh'lot's body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That dagger in his upper back looks like it would've been particularly painful. Hm? Is that a tattoo on the back of his neck? It's... peach shaped...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Everyone started leaving when the praying was finally done... ...but the victim remained bent over in prayer. And when they went over to check on him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They discovered he was dead, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. The estimated time of death is May 9, sometime between... ...the start of the rite and the discovery of the high priest's body. In other words, we believe the crime took place during the Purification Rite. And the murder weapon was the same ceremonial dagger that killed the high priest. The prosecution believes Maya came down the stairs after killing the high priest... ...and then stabbed Mr. Zeh'lot with the same dagger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Circumstantial evidence does point to Maya, but...</thought> What about the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He apparently died instantly from the dagger that was left thrust into his upper back. Here's the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Estimated time of death, you say? How can you know such a thing? I want to know! ...Well, Barbed Head! Out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, so the princess of the spirit medium kingdom is interested in forensic science?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph! I have no interest is science, forensic or otherwise! Nevertheless, I will someday be queen. As such, it would be wise to know what silly things the common folk believe in.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Tsk! There's nothing silly about it! I'll have you know, even Prosecutor Sahdmadhi holds forensics in high regard.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Does he?! Hmm... Perhaps I should not underestimate the power of science. Still, I suppose it is nothing much compared to the Divination Séance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She really doesn't have an adorable bone in her body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, I think she's actually interested. Would you mind explaining it to her?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I guess I have to now. ...Okay, there are many ways to estimate the time of death... ...but the most well-known method uses the change in body temperature.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Body temperature drops at a steady rate from the moment a person dies. That means we can tell how long someone's been dead by measuring their temperature.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... I see, I see! That was quite enlightening. Barbed Head! Present your forehead now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... You feel just a little over ninety-five degrees. It seems you are not dead yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I'm not!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Heh heh. It was but a jest. After all, you're still the dead lawyer walking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I fail to see the humor in any of this.</thought> Were there any witnesses? With so many people here at the plaza, you'd think somebody would've seen something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'd think so, wouldn't you? But we haven't found a single witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How's that even possible?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Because everyone was bent over, utterly devoted to prayer, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right, the back-shattering pose that nearly killed me. Still, you'd think someone would've noticed something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I thought so too, but... ...with the monk's scarf he had on, no one could see the dagger in his upper back. Plus, everyone was so absorbed in prayer, they didn't see or hear anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe this.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What you choose to believe is your choice, but the fact remains there were no witnesses. However, there is one piece of irrefutable evidence. ...The dagger.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sadly, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The killer used the Warbaa'd Dagger, the legendary weapon of Lady Kee'ra. It was discovered impaled in the victim's upper back.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The accused's fingerprints were found on the dagger, were they not?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes, they were.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">With such irrefutable evidence, there is no questioning the accused's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not so fast. What about a motive? Maya had no reason to kill Acolyte Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What do the police think about this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya had no reason to kill Acolyte Zeh'lot!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So you say, but let us now hear what the police think about the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The police believe Maya is the Lady Kee'ra figure who has been battling the rebels. And since Mr. Zeh'lot was the disciple of the high priest, who turned out to be a rebel...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">He, too, was likely a rebel, and therefore met the same untimely demise as his teacher.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Yes, that is how the police currently view this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way Maya is that Lady Kee'ra vigilante!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I agree on a personal level, but the police are just going with what today's trial concluded.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngrk! <thought>I really blew it in court today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Based on the estimated time of death, we believe he was killed during the rite itself. It appears he was stabbed in the upper back with a dagger and died instantly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there were so many people here. How could no one have noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I know. I can't believe it, either. I guess they were just that focused on their prayers or something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maya's fingerprints were found on the dagger that was used in the murder. The police are, therefore, investigating her as their prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The evidence is irrefutable, with no room for argument.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I really don't want to treat Maya as a suspect, but... ...based on the evidence and police reports I've received so far, it's not looking good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not good? More like, how could it get any worse?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That message on the prayer flag seems a little weird, but... ...I think I've seen everything there is to see around here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have not found or heard anything of particular worth. Are you ready to give up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm not calling it quits yet!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...D-Does it look like you have any hope of winning, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema... I can't really say at this point. All I know is I have to keep investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What are you two sneaks up to? I would advise you to get back to work if you are done here, Detective. Otherwise, I will report you to Prosecutor Sahdmadhi for dereliction of duty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I-I, I'm going, I'm going! Well, see you later, Mr. Wright. And good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should really pay a visit to everyone and every place connected with this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">We have paid a visit to all of the people and places connected with this case. I think it is about time you prepared yourself for the inevitable. Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...D-Does it look like you have any hope of winning, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema... I can't really say at this point. All I know is I have to keep investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What are you two sneaks up to? I would advise you to get back to work if you are done here, Detective. Otherwise, I will report you to Prosecutor Sahdmadhi for dereliction of duty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-I-I, I'm going, I'm going! Well, see you later, Mr. Wright. And good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, Barbed Head? Is it not time to give up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, there is still someone I need to talk to first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello. I'm sorry to bother you again, but...</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Oh, it's you.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! You are not contemplating casting suspicion upon Lady Beh'leeb, are you? She lost her beloved husband, and now Acolyte Zeh'lot, who was like a son to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, I'm not. But since she was close to both victims, I wanted to hear what she has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And then there's the fact that Lady Kee'ra didn't attack Mrs. Inmee. That probably means she isn't a rebel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Is this about poor Puhray? Well, I'm sorry, but I don't think I can talk about that right now. ...B-But what about Maya? She's innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Maya? I heard she was found guilty. First, my dear husband, and now Puhray?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mrs. Inmee, you don't really believe that Maya is the killer, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">I-I... I don't know. But that was the verdict, so what else can I believe? What am I to do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The verdict was already reached in your husband's case... ...but the truth of the matter is yet to be found!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Because I believe that Maya is innocent. That is all I have right now -- my faith in her. So please. Help me understand what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">So you're... you're defending her based solely on faith? Even though you'll be punished for abetting the accused?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">...A-All right, then. Your faith has moved me. I will tell you what I can.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A-Are you sure about this, Lady Beh'leeb?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">"My lovely wife is also a devout follower of Khura'inism. As such, she is not one to make light of another's faith. But if I find that you have lied about your faith in Maya Fey's innocence... ...I shall curse your entire family and all your disciples for the next eight generations."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! Leave Athena and Apollo alone, buddy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A photo of the high priest, his wife, Acolyte Zeh'lot, and Maya... Since Maya's in it... ...it must've been taken the day before the rite. I should ask Mrs. Inmee about it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">To think that this would be their final family photo... That no-good Maya Fey has some nerve. I mean, here she is posing with the two men whom she would soon kill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ. I see this photo as proof that she didn't kill them.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph.That smile of hers does not fool me. I sense a deep and abiding malice behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll prove Maya's smile is the real deal!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's that family photo they took. Mrs. Inmee said it was taken the day before the rite. I don't suppose any of them could've possibly imagined what was to come...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did Acolyte Zeh'lot end up living here as your husband's disciple?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">About two years ago, while my husband was at a spiritual retreat in the mountains... ...he came across Puhray collapsed on the ground. That's when he brought him here. You were always one to help those in need, weren't you, dear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And he'd been living here ever since? <thought>About two years ago... That's around the same time Maya arrived in Khura'in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes, he was born in a poor village and had nowhere to call home. My husband felt pity for the boy, so he took him in as his disciple. ...But not only as his disciple. He was like a member of our family, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. <thought>If this is where Acolyte Zeh'lot lived... ...there might be something I could learn about him lying around here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">This photo was taken during the Feast of Blessings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Feast of Blessings?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes. It is forbidden to eat during the days of the rite, so the day before it's performed... ...we enjoyed dishes full of gingihl, an herb known to strengthen the body and mind. You loved the gingihl-based dishes I make, didn't you, dear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gingihl... I heard you can go three days without sleeping after eating some.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes, but many foreigners don't care for it because of its strong smell.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Our customs say that these dishes can only be eaten the day before the Purification Rite... ...and only between noon and 3 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's pretty specific. Is it because the smell is too strong?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">A very good guess, indeed. It is to ensure the smell is gone by the time Lady Kee'ra is welcomed the next day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, is it really that strong? <thought>Come to think of it, the evening before the murder... ...an overwhelming odor was all over town. It was like a cross between garlic and mint.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">After the Feast of Blessings, Puhray went over to the plaza to begin his supplication. I never thought that would be the last time I would see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was Maya doing at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Shortly after Puhray left, she went to the temple to prepare for the rite. ...I don't know what she did after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Acolyte Zeh'lot went out to pray the afternoon before the rite? <thought>According to the newspaper... ...on the day before the rite, the plaza was so cold, the whole place had iced over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Puhray always prayed a lot -- far more than anyone I have ever known. He was a devout young man whose faith was twice as strong as others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know why, but that's... kinda intimidating to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Oh, poor Puhray. He has joined my husband in the Twilight Realm. He was so full of life before he went out to the plaza.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This must be most difficult for you. It is like losing a family member.</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">What's that, dear? ...Yes, you're right. I don't know what would've become of me if my husband were not here by my side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Is there anything you can tell me about Acolyte Zeh'lot that might help?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">He was a kindly young man. Let us leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you about this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">It was taken during the Feast of Blessings, the day before the rite was held.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Feast of Blessings? Would you mind telling me a little more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I'd have made some progress by now. But I haven't come across any particularly insightful information, even here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You seem disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mrs. Inmee, is there anything else you could tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Forgive me. But if I keep thinking about those two any longer...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I understand. Thank you for your help. I'm sorry to have troubled you.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have not found or heard anything of particular worth. Are you ready to give up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm not calling it quits yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought I'd have made some progress by now. But I haven't come across any particularly insightful information, even here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You seem disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mrs. Inmee, is there anything else you could tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Forgive me. But if I keep thinking about those two any longer...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I understand. Thank you for your help. I'm sorry to have troubled you.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">We have paid a visit to all of the people and places connected with this case. I think it is about time you prepared yourself for the inevitable. Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah, the second murder victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know Acolyte Zeh'lot, too, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I knew of him. I know he had been living under the care of Abbot Inmee at his home, but little else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean like how they're letting me stay at the temple?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you seriously trying to insult the poor victim with your comparison, you filthy dog?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! What was THAT comparison for?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is the sacred dagger used in the Purification Rite. In using it for murder, the vile criminal known as Maya Fey shall be cursed for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing's been proven yet, so stop treating her like a criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How do explain the accused's fingerprints all over the dagger, then? And the fact that Abbot Inmee was slain with this very weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-I hate it when I have no comeback...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya sure looks tired.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm so sorry, Maya. I failed to defend you during that trial earlier today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry, too, Nick. I never meant to get caught up in this whole mess. Even worse, I got you caught up in it, too, and you were convicted under that stupid law. Nick... You should really withdraw from this </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I could never abandon you like that! You might not believe me, but I'm going to pull off a win somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not like I don't believe in you, it's just...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. Maybe this extra day in court is a blessing from the Holy Mother. Let's use it to our advantage. We'll turn this trial inside-out and upside-down! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're awfully quiet, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is only a matter of time until your executions are carried out. I simply thought I would allow you two a good talk before you depart from this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but we're not giving up yet. And we won't till the bitter end.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is no need to put on a brave face. Your fates were sealed with today's verdict. Worry not of Maya Fey. The Twilight Realm will cleanse the taint from that neophyte practitioner's soul. Then, perhaps, the Holy Mother may finally forgive her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... Was that her attempt at comforting me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, further resistance shall come to naught. Stop your desperate struggle. Accept the judgment that has been passed upon you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She obviously doesn't know me very well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then, perhaps, your sentence will be commuted, and--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hold it right there, Your Benevolence. Why do you always have to be like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya,what are you...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-What is the matter? I was simply showing some mercy upon your souls.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick here is risking his life to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And that is why I told you it will come to nau--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, it won't! Nick is just doing what lawyers are supposed to! He's defending his client, no matter what!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Enough! There is no place for lawyers in the Hall of Justice! For we have the Divination Séance!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But your Insights were wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nnngrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ooh boy, that's gotta hurt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you get it? Errors are bound to happen if your Insights are accepted without question. So I ask you, royal priestess: What is your true duty? Do the victims' souls or the Holy Mother herself wish you to judge people in error?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oooooh... You dare bring Her Holiness's name into this?! You know nothing, you... you... phony baloney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please, you two! Enough already!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Sorry, Nick. I got a little carried away. That's not really like me, huh? Aha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No,I should be thanking you, Maya. It's good to have you in my corner.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hrrnh... How dare you mock me so! You will not get away with this! I was a fool to show you compassion. And to think I could convince you to accept your fate. So struggle all you want in the Hall of Justice tomorrow. You will receive your just desserts, as the scorn of our kingdom is heaped upon you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(...I can see straight through that contorted smile on your face, you know. *sigh* She may say these terrible things... ...but it's just the way she was raised, I </line>
<line speaker="Maya">A guard will come running if you ring that bell there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Let's put that to the test, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, but they got really mad last time when I rang it for no reason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could've told me that before I rang it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you try to remember what happened one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've been trying as hard as I can... But I can't remember anything from the middle of the rite onward.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. You suddenly felt sleepy, and everything after that's a blank.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even so, I didn't kill anyone! And I'm not the one going around dressed like Lady Kee'ra! ...Although it's kind of cool to think there's a mysterious female vigilante out there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you close to Acolyte Zeh'lot?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... We met several times during the meetings about the rite. But I didn't know him very well. He seemed pretty quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you eat together the day before the rite?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! We ate this one super-stinky dish, but it was actually really good!I wasn't sure I'd like it, but it was love at first bite! Like... You know the salty noodles at Eldoon's Noodles? It's like if you added garlic and herbs to that,and then let it simmer for a really long time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds more like a hot pot than ramen to me at that point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sigh* Now I miss ramen, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... so what was Acolyte Zeh'lot like while you were eating?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He seemed to be enjoying the food. But as soon as we were done, he left to go pray.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what did you do? Oh, umm... I returned to the temple to prepare for the rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That coincides with Mrs. Inmee's description of events.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any idea who might be pretending to be Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... When the rite started, it was just me and Abbot Inmee.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the Séance vision showed a third figure who looked like Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know... *sigh* Lady Kee'ra... I wish I could've seen her in the flesh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, yeah... <thought>Let's stay focused on the case, shall we?</thought> It was supposed to have been impossible for a third party to enter the Inner Sanctum.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! But what if she came from the sky? You know, like that bushy-bearded paratrooper! That mountain would've been no match for Lady Kee'ra's wings!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's from the Plumed Punisher TV show, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-How'd you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because the real Lady Kee'ra doesn't have wings.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! I've got it this time! There must be a secret room with a secret door at the Inner Sanctum! Did you know there are eighty-eight secret Plumed Punisher bases here in Khura'in?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we please stop talking about the Plumed Punisher show for a sec, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess so. *sigh* Keeping it real is much harder than it looks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's my Plumed Punisher strap! There's only one of them in the entire world! I'll treasure it for the rest of my life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Your Benevolence? I can't help but notice how hard you're staring at this strap.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">M-Me?! Want that?! Sorry, but you are sorely mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Your Benevolence? Would you let me out of here in exchange for the strap?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">....................................... ...What a preposterous idea!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It didn't stop you from entertaining it, though, did it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I'm not the one going around impersonating Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, Maya. I believe you.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh, please. Dispense with this bungling act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to prove that Maya isn't Lady Kee'ra.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why bother? She is already as good as guilty. And floundering about will not change that fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care. I'll keep fighting until the very last crack of His Magistry's gavel!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. You truly are...a nincompoop.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">First Abbot Inmee,and now Acolyte Zeh'lot...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Spare me your crocodile tears. We both know it was YOU who slew those pious men!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No, it wasn't me! Nick... How can we make her understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably only by getting to the bottom of things in court tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe the sacred dagger was used in a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Only a truly irreverent individual would dare do such a thing. And it was your fingerprints that were found upon the weapon. How do you explain that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I used the dagger during our rehearsals! That's why it has my fingerprints on it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">And how do I know you are not lying?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ugh... Why won't you believe me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just let it go, Maya. There's no changing her mind right now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We took this picture during the Feast of Blessings... ...before all of these unthinkably tragic things happened...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Unthinkable? I doubt that. You were surely plotting your murderous rampage at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was thinking of nothing of the sort -- especially not during that meal! The smell of gingihl was so strong, I couldn't think of anything else.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, well, it IS a rather intense aroma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... Do I even want to know how strong of a smell gingihl gives off up close...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Sorry I wasn't any help.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. I've got this. We'll beat the charges tomorrow and be on the first plane back home before you know it. Then we'll go grab dinner at Eldoon's, or your favorite burger joint! You pick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Sounds good! I think I'll get the extra-large Hamburg steak topping on my salty bowl! Best of both worlds!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can have whatever you like! <thought>But first, I have to beat the charges.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! I almost forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I have a favor to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... But why are we whispering?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I forgot I left something at the high priest's house. It's super important! Would you mind getting and holding on to it for me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure. So what's this super important thing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In my bag, you'll find a folding book. It's only given to the priestess who performs the rite. It's called the Tome of Secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That does sound important. How could you leave something like that just lying around? <thought>That explains all the whispering. If Rayfa found out, all heck would break loose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, it's got Lady Kee'ra's real name written in it, so... Oops! Don't tell anyone I told you that! In fact, just forget I said anything at all! It's supposed to be a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Tome of Secrets contains... secrets? Imagine that.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? What are you two whispering about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, n-nothing. It's just she forgot something, so I told her I'd go get it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...You are up to something, I just know it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks, Nick! I'm counting on you!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So, are you ready to give up, Barbed Head? Any more of this and you will cause Lady Inmee to suffer more than she already is.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Stubborn fool. ...But you have already been found guilty. If you wish to continue floundering about, I suppose now is your last chance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll take every chance I can get.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What? Have you given up already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not even close! Still, it does feel like I'm barely treading water over here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Water? Do all the people of your country go for a swim when they are troubled? If so, seek the rivers on the edge of town. There you will find all the water you need. Go ahead, paddle to your heart's content!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>English idioms go right over her head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello? Anybody home? No answer... Mrs. Inmee's probably out right now. Well, I'll just get what I came for.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am watching you like a warbaa'd, Barbed Head! You had better not steal anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would never do something like that! I'm just here to get what Maya asked for!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then get on with it. I would if you'd stop interrupting me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, here's Maya's bag.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? What is that strange patch on her bag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the Steel Samurai. He's the hero of an action-hero show back in my country. It's actually Maya's favorite show. She's got all sorts of merchandise related to it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I see... He looks strikingly similar to the Plumed Punisher.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They are similar, but... <thought>...the Steel Samurai definitely came first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I see... How interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa seems genuinely intrigued. There must a common thread between Plumed Punisher and Steel Samurai fans. Come to think of it... ...didn't Maya mention something about trading with a Plumed Punisher fan? But I digress... I'd better find what she asked me to look for and get going.</thought> Let's see here... This must be that Tome of Secrets that Maya was talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, Barbed Head? Are you finished now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on a second. The string around it is coming undone... Whoops! Oh...!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">AHHHHH! YOU FOOL! Do not lay eyes upon it! Put it away! Quickly! Before we go blind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Relax. My hand just slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is the Tome of Secrets! Are you trying to get us cursed?! Lady Kee'ra is liable to swoop down and gouge our eyes out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. This book is related to Lady Kee'ra, isn't it? Your Benevolence, would you mind if I asked you some questions?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is that strange patch on her bag again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's for the Steel Samurai, this action hero back in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It looks so similar to the Plumed Punisher -- strikingly so. Hmm, I see... "The Steel Samurai"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're actually interested in it, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-Whatever gave you that idea?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is not something I would normally speak about to an outsider such as you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, can't you make an exception?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you insist... Nayna! What of this folding book? ...Yes, I see... This very important tome is bestowed upon the priestess in the Purification Rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp* Very important? Wh-What's written inside?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, yes... Yes, I see... ...Really? Is it all right to reveal that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, uhhh... Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Patience, patience! The book contains Lady Kee'ra's true name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her true name? Is a name really that important of a secret?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">To a Khura'inist priestess, a person's name is one of the most important things to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's so important about a name?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Without a name, a priestess's voice will fail to reach a person's mitamah. It is much like trying to send a letter without the recipient's address. A spirit can only be identified once you know the deceased's face and name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I get it. It's like when you see someone in a crowd you recognize, but you don't know their name. It makes it impossible to get their attention.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed. You must know a spirit's face and true name before you can commune with it. It is the same for Khura'inism's most secret art, one that my mother alone may use.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The queen has a secret art?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, it is something a foreigner such as you could never hope to guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In Khura'inism, spirit channeling is a secret art that can only be performed by the queen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should pretend this is all new to me. Besides, I get the feeling she secretly really wants to tell me all about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about this secret art of the queen you spoke of?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, sorry. Maybe we shouldn't talk about this. It IS a secret after all, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is the secret art of spirit channeling. But I suppose those words are meaningless to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just surprised how willing you are to tell me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A third-rate lawyer could not channel spirits simply by learning of the technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Third-rate is a bit harsh. I'd even settle for second.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is it? You have the look of a tentacled hag frog upon your face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the heck is a tentacled hag frog?!</thought> ...Spirit channeling... That's where a medium lets a spirit possess her body to return to our world, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well now. I see you have done your homework.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I guess I studied a bit. Eh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">With the power of spirit channeling, one can bring back even the most ancient of spirits! It is quite a magnificent power, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen her eyes light up like this before.</thought> I imagine they're pretty shocked when they come back from ancient times.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed. A spirit's memory is cut off at the moment of death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So even a spirit that is brought back after centuries doesn't sense any gap in time... ...between the moment of its death, and the moment it is channeled?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, and yet, it clearly recalls all of the memories it had in life. Thus, even heroes and scholars of antiquity can be channeled and directly learned from. Our queens have also used this power to help the rulers of neighboring lands seek counsel. That is why we have never been invaded, and how we have maintained our unique culture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, spirit channeling is a really effective tool for international politics.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is, indeed. And that is why only those with the power to channel spirits may rule our kingdom. But of late, there has been an endless influx of illegal immigrants from neighboring lands. The fools come seeking the same great power as my mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Illegal immigrants?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes. It is becoming quite a problem. Some have lost their way in life, and look to Khura'inism for their salvation. Among them are also those of dubious nature, who have been driven from their own lands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dubious nature... Driven from their own land...Gaspen Payne definitely fit that bill. But they sure weren't treating him like an illegal alien.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you channel spirits, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I am but the royal priestess. There is still much that I must learn. As of now, the Divination Séance takes me to the very limit of my ability.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, her spiritual power doesn't measure up to Maya's.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...You were just mocking me in your mind, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is written all over your face! You... impudent nincompoop! The Divination Séance was once one of the important roles fulfilled by the queen. That is what my mother taught me when I was little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the queen can perform the Dance of Devotion? That'd be a sight to see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Someday, I will be a powerful priestess and queen, just like my mother. And the Divination Séance is a vital part of my training to prepare me for that day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Forgive my ignorance, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, you shall see. It will not be long before I, too, master the secret art of spirit channeling! I will be a magnificent queen who unites her people for the greater good of Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I see... Spirit channeling is something she really aspires to.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm going to ace that test and become the next master! After all, I can't let my clan and the other villagers down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like she actually has something in common with Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You fool! Why have you put the Tome of Secrets before me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the big deal?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">S-Stay back! Come no closer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, this thing's actually pretty useful!</thought> Lookie here, Your Benevolence. It's the Tome of Seeecrets.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you do not desist this instant, I shall have you put to death for the crime of blasphemy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! S-Sorry! <thought>...If looks could kill, I'd already be dead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Where do you think you are going, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Were you not the one who said you wished to speak with me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I better stay here and talk to Rayfa for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you quite through now? There are more important things to do than to stand here and talk about spirit channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true. It doesn't have anything to do with this case, as far as I can tell. Or does it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... If the queen is a spirit medium...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you about to suggest that my mother was channeling Lady Kee'ra?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, lawyers are indeed a witless breed! On the day of the rite, my mother was engaged in other duties at the palace.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My mother is a very busy woman. And the idea itself is preposterous. Do you truly believe the queen of Khura'in would personally battle the insurgents? This is precisely what makes you third-rate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>Another dead end! This is bad!</thought> A-Anyway, I need to continue looking for leads, so...</line>
<line speaker="???">Over there! After him! Don't let him escape!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is all that racket? What? That escaped prisoner has surfaced here in town?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Escaped prisoner? You mean... that guy with the bushy beard?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There is no reason to panic. The police are on his trail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's no longer a suspect... But he might know something, considering he was at the scene of the crime.</thought> Let's go take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*huff* *puff* Oww, my aching back. I forgot how badly I'd injured it. Ow, ow, ow... I need to do some stretching and exercise more when I get back home.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*huff* *puff* ...H-Hey, Ahlbi. Datz... Are'bal... Have you seen hi--</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">A-Are you all right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One second... *huff* *puff* *wheeeeeze* Have you seen... that escaped prisoner around here?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, so that's why all those police came rushing over here. I heard them saying something about an escaped prisoner disappearing in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He disappeared in this area? He couldn't have taken to the air again, could he?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! *huff* *huff* I told you to wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too dangerous for you around here, Your Benevolence. Mr. Are'bal could be lurking nearby!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What sort of a princess would I be if all it took was an escaped prisoner to frighten me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's fearless, I'll give her that.</thought> I can't be responsible if something happens to you. <thought>As long as I'm here, though, I might as well search the area myself. Hmm... If I were an escaped prisoner, where would I hide?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That patch on the accused's bag... It is the Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. It's a huge hit back in my country.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I see... It has a rather fine design, I must say. However, it pales beside the Plumed Punisher, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course... </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How dare you leave me behind like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... <thought>It sure was a lot easier without her, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do that again and I will levy a penalty on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A penalty? Like what...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Like... Oh, I know! You must clean my room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, that's not so bad.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...All thirty of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forgive me for leaving you behind, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That manhole cover... It's open!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Whoa! What is it, Shah'do?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did he sniff out someone or something in the manhole? <thought>Hmm, I wonder...</thought> Could Shah'do track Mr. Are'bal if he had something with the rebel's scent on it?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel like I've got something with Mr. Are'bal's scent on it... Something he might've touched...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you noticed anything around here?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I haven't seen the escaped prisoner. But I did notice how slow you run, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's just the high elevation. I'm out of breath before I know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The police said the escaped prisoner vanished right around here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, there aren't any really good hiding places, so where could he have gone?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Maybe he melted into the crowd.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You should be careful, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You need not tell me that! I am not a child, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, okay...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That is THE Plumed Punisher strap. There's only one in the entire world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, do you know a lot about the Plumed Punisher?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course! She's a real hero to the people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ratings for the show must be through the roof.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">They are! It reached 100 percent viewership at one point!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One hundred percent?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Well, when there's only one TV channel in the entire kingdom...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that explains it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's the dagger that was used in the rite. It's said that Lady Kee'ra once wielded it. In addition to that dagger, there are many other items that are said to have been hers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">There's the obvious stuff, like swords, spears, and other weapons. But there are other, more interesting items, like her favorite hat and her favorite pillow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her pillow...?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yes. They say if you use it, Lady Kee'ra will ensure you have a restful slumber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As long as it's not eternal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, Shah'do. How about this? I hope it works...</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Grrr... Ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think he's picked up a scent! You mind if I borrow Shah'do for a bit?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">By all means! I had no idea you could do this! Yeah! Go get 'im, boy!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, I'm heading down the manhole now. It could be dangerous, so please wait here!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I won't commit any of those misdeeds you're so worried about.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is not what I fear! There may be a vicious insurgent lurking down there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, are you worried about me?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No. I was simply wondering why you would go to such lengths in your investigation. After all, if you would simply withdraw from this case, they might commute your sentence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm doing this to prove Maya innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But how can you be so sure of the accused's innocence?! She has already been found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. Maybe this extra day in court is a blessing from the Holy Mother. Let's use it to our advantage. We'll turn this trial inside-out and upside-down! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe in her. If she says she's innocent, then that means she's innocent. Lawyers must trust in their clients to the bitter end. That's just what we do.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">......... You...lamebrain. Do what you will!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm going in!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Be careful!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do!">Ruff, ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! Come back here! It's pitch black down here. I can't see a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ooogh... Owww owww owwww... What happened? I went down into the manhole, and then...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, ya finally came to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! <thought>I'd remember that face anywhere! And that dragon symbol on his armband... That's the mark of the rebels! There can be no mistake! It's him -- Datz Are'bal!</thought> YIKES!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sorry I got a little rough with ya back there. Thought ya were the cops. Why ya making that face? ...Hey, want an apple?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew...I thought he was going to kill me.</thought> I-I'll pass on the apple, but thanks. <thought>I don't mind a good apple, but not right now.</thought> What is this place?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">This is the office of my brother in arms, Dhurke! But right now, we're using it as a rebel safe house!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, back up a sec. What kind of office is this exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">A law office, what else?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! Dhurke used to be a lawyer?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep! Just like you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Khura'in's public enemy number one is an ex-lawyer? Didn't see that coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">But I don't suppose I'll be coming 'round here anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You won't? Are you planning to flee or something?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">It's just... I wanna get outta the rebel business. Tired o' being hounded by the cops and all that. So I came by today to pick up the last o' my stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I'm gonna sell Dhurke's info to the minister o' justice, then slip outta Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...W-Wait a second! You're a key person of interest in this case! You can't go running off like that! </line>
<line speaker="Datz">Relax, will ya? I'll tell ya whatever ya need to know. Oh, and sorry about punching your lights out back there. My bad! So, Mr. Lawyer Man, whaddaya wanna know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about the murders of the high priest Tahrust Inmee, and his acolyte Puhray Zeh'lot.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sure, I'll tell ya whatever I can. Don't know if it'll be much help, though. I mean, I'm not a rebel anymore, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder how true that really is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a knife driven deep into a photo of the queen. I guess the rebels really hate her. I better remember to stay on their good side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Incense and white flowers... <thought>The flowers are still fresh. They must've been put here maybe today or yesterday.</thought> Did you put these here, Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Something wrong with flowers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">It's just a traditional thing here in Khura'in. Pay it no mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a ladder leading underground. He must've brought me in through there. But there's no reason for me to leave yet. I should see what else Mr. Are'bal has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This looks like a photo of Dhurke and his compatriots... And here's one that looks really old... Wow, this was taken about twenty years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those are Dhurke's sons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? So this is the rebel Dhurke in the center? He doesn't look so evil. And both of his sons... look kind of familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The one on the left is Yuty. Oh, but you know him as Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Prosecutor Sahdmadhi is Dhurke's son?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That he is! Yuty was once a rebel, too! He used to really respect his old man... ...both as a father and as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why'd he become a prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Being a lawyer in this kingdom is the same as signing your own death warrant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On account of the Defense Culpability Act, right?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah. That's why Yuty decided to be a prosecutor instead. He wanted to spark a revolution from the inside, so he dove right into the enemy's den!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would've never guessed it, looking at him now.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You can say that again. Dhurke is battling to change Khura'in's legal system. The will of the dragon spurs him on. We all thought Yuty was taking up the mantle to carry on that will, too... We were sure he'd help overthrow Ga'ran one day, but... As you've seen, he now uses the law to do her Dhurke's been beside himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he no longer carries the will of the dragon in him, huh... I wonder what happened between father and son for it to come to this?</thought> What about the other child in the photo?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's Dhurke's adopted son, but he's gone back overseas. His name's Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo? Wait a second... That bracelet... It really IS Apollo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">He was a rascal, that one! And his voice could shake the entire room! I imagine he's out there raising high hell somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha, aha ha... Yes, I'm sure he's doing just fine. <thought>Considering how far he's come, Mr. Are'bal's description really doesn't do Apollo justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Apollo! I've been watching you grow over these past two years. That's why I know you're ready, why I know I can leave Trucy and the office to you. ...I believe in you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thank you! I'll... I'll be fine! Everything will be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's a responsible young man now. He never lost that loud voice, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This looks like a photo of Dhurke and his compatriots... And here's one that's really old...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those are Dhurke's sons. The one on the left is Prosecutor Sahdmadhi when he was younger. I used to call him Yuty. Thought he'd carry on the will of the dragon and become a fine lawyer, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the other child is...?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's Dhurke's adopted son, but he's gone back overseas. His name's Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That name, and that bracelet... Yep, that has to be our Apollo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">He was a rascal, that one! And his voice could shake the entire room! I imagine he's out there raising high hell somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha, aha ha... Yes, I'm sure he's doing just fine. <thought>Considering how far he's come, Mr. Are'bal's description really doesn't do Apollo justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are these hanging here? Lizards? ...If so, they're pretty big.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those're sewer lizards! We call 'em that 'cause they live in the sewer! They grow bigger than your average lizard, which makes 'em fine eating!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, you eat these?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">What else would ya do with 'em?! Here, try one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pass! I'll definitely pass!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...You're missing out on a fine treat, my man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Somehow, I think I'll live without it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are bowls and platters of food here. ...They're still warm, as if this was all recently prepared.</thought> You must have a pretty big appetite, Mr. Are'bal.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har! Guys as big and strong as me... Got even bigger appetites, y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you just fled from the police. I don't know how you could eat this much after all that excitement. Ack! S-Sorry if I offended you!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">But first, let's start with an apple-tizer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where's he getting all those apples from?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Wanna join me, Mr. Lawyer Man? Got plenty of sewer lizards, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Thanks, but I already ate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that coat yours, Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Nah, it belongs to the rebel leader Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's pretty impressive. I like the color, too.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Wanna try it on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? You sure it's okay?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Of course. Bet it would look great on ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well then, don't mind if I do... ......... Ack! It smells all moldy!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Haaaar har har har har! I can't believe ya fell for it! Haaar haaar! That thing's been hanging there forever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Note to self: Don't trust this guy ever again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this thing with the dragon on it? Some kind of a sign?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. That was his business sign back when this was Dhurke's office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He used to be a lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That he was, but it was a really long time ago. This place has seen better days, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I hope he can put his sign back up someday.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">.........I wouldn't hold my breath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You guys get electricity?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, but the power goes out occasionally.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's pretty inconvenient.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You're telling me! Sometimes, it goes out for an entire day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the stuff in the refrigerator?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Why don't you see for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget I asked! <thought>I'm afraid of what I might find...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this... a law book? <thought>A dragon mark's been branded into the cover.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's Dhurke's law book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! The leader of the rebels? That Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's right. And that "Mark of the Dragon" is the emblem of the rebellion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, the pages in this one section are really dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Must be the section on the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must've done a ton of research on the Defense Culpability Act. He practically wore out the entire section.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me everything you know about the high priest's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Uhh... Well, as ya know, I don't remember much about that. I banged my head on a rock as soon as I parachuted into the Inner Sanctum. So when I told you I had nothing to do with his murder, I meant it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay then, where were you when you came to after banging your head?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Uhh... By the time I came to, it was already dawn. I musta been out cold the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you didn't see the crime happen at all...?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Ya got that right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why did you say you did when you testified?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, uhh... About that... Since I didn't remember a thing... ...I was afraid I'd seem suspicious, o I came up with that whole story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does he even realize how much trouble his big fat lie has caused me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sorry for the trouble! It was definitely my bad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He doesn't seem very sorry to me!</thought> So, the bottom line is you were at the scene of the crime, but weren't involved in it. Got it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Dhurke used to be a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've got to be kidding me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">But most important of all, he would never surrender. He'd fight for the accused, no matter how the odds were stacked against him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that what you mean by the will of the dragon?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep, that would be it! Actually... Your work in court yesterday was mighty impressive, too! You didn't give up, no matter how hard of a beating you took! ...Not unlike Dhurke, I might add!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... thanks. <thought>Even if a big part of that beating I took was because of you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Is this a parting gift for me leaving the rebels?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, you can't keep it! <thought>I'll just ask him what I can for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Well, I gotta start packing. Who knows when they might catch up with me if I don't scram soon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, wait! I still need to ask you something.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Go ahead, shoot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you rebels trying to do?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why were you at the Inner Sanctum in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why were you at the Inner Sanctum on the day of the murder? Or more precisely, what were you trying to do there?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I was trying to escape from prison, that's all. But that high priest was a fool for getting taken in by Dhurke. He shoulda tried hightailing it outta Khura'in like I'm doing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... Psyche-Locks! <thought>Mr. Are'bal is hiding something! But I won't know exactly what until I can undo the locks!</thought> What exactly are you trying to hide, Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Huh? I'm not hiding anything! No way, no how!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'll just have to use my magatama on him, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">-- Datz's Plan --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to ask you again: Why were you at the Inner Sanctum on the day of the murder? Or more precisely, what were you trying to do there?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Ya can keep asking, but the answer's still the same. I was trying to escape from prison, that's all. ...But that high priest was a fool. He fell for Dhurke's line and sold his own country out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you say such things about him?! He helped you escape, didn't he? Don't you even care about what happened to him?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Nope. I was getting out of the rebellion, anyway. He should've opened his eyes. We never stood a chance against the Ga'ran regime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hang on. Do you really believe what you're saying? Didn't the high priest's death really hurt you on the inside?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Like I just said, I couldn't care less about the whole thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I beg to differ. This wouldn't be here in this room if you didn't feel a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Datz:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't know? Try looking deep into your heart.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Umm... I still don't get it. But I'm starting to think you don't, either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Arngh... Why does it feel so much worse when it's him who's pointing out my failures?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">I told ya, I couldn't care less about the high priest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really...? Because I'm pretty sure I have something that points to his grief.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard these flowers are offered in memory of the dead here in Khura'in. The high priest's death hit you hard, so you've been grieving here alone, haven't you? Well?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hee-HO!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those flowers don't mean anything. It's just a Khura'inese way o' saying goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why hide the fact that you're mourning his death?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You're reading into this too much. I told ya, I'm done with the rebellion! I haven't even heard from Dhurke or the rest of 'em for a few days. And tomorrow, I'm planning to kiss this kingdom goodbye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I know you've been in contact with the other rebels lately!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">And how exactly do you plan on proving that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence ties you to the other rebels! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Datz:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cat got your tongue?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">No, it's just, I was shocked at how off-target ya are. Wait, you're not stalling for time or something, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, I'd never do that. <thought>I hope he doesn't think I'm in cahoots with the police or something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">I keep trying to tell ya -- I got nothing to do with the rebels anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This food was brought here for Mr. Are'bal after he escaped from prison. So he must've gotten in contact with the other rebels somehow.</thought> No, I know you're still involved with them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this prayer flag at the Plaza of Devotion. You wrote a message on it, and left it behind for your fellow rebels, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Gulp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They brought this food for you at your request.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hoo-HA HA!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're lying about leaving the rebels. You're still involved with Dhurke and the rest of them, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Naaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you ready to tell me the truth now?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, you're good, Mr. Lawyer Man! I admit it! I requested the grub. But I was just taking advantage of 'em, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">With my face plastered all over the place, I couldn't stay out in the open anymore. So, I just took advantage of my former comrades for some grub and a place to hide. I was gonna kiss this kingdom goodbye tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not buying it. You're obviously lying. I can tell just by looking at you. The white-hot flames of revolution definitely still burn on inside of you!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">What?! That's ridiculous. Those flames burned out a long time ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This proves that the flames of revolution still burn on inside of you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Datz:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm right, aren't I?! That's why you're so shocked!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeesh, I almost forgot about dessert!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Would you give up already? The flames of revolution burned out inside of me a long time ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, I know they still burn on. Because he's wearing something that proves it!</thought> You can't fool me, Mr. Are'bal.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Dhurke's law book? I'm no lawyer, so what's that got to do with me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the mark branded onto the cover. This mark that stands for an unwavering commitment to the revolution. It is Dhurke's way of representing the will of the dragon!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah? So what of it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have that same mark on the scarf tied around your left arm. But you wouldn't be wearing that if you were no longer a rebel!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I-I... I forgot to take it off, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, as a wanted man, that should've been the first thing you took off! The fact that you haven't hidden that mark yet... proves you're still a rebel!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hoo-HA!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Think whatcha want! But you don't know nothing about me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you're wrong. You wear your heart and your beliefs right on your sleeve -- just like me. And this is what I believe in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Datz:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure! And I never waver from it!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's the lamest belief I ever heard of! Haaaaaar har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't think it was THAT funny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">I was right, you don't know a thing about me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I know you wear your beliefs right on your sleeve -- just like me.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When a person's back is against a wall, they always fall back on what they believe in. Just as I always have my badge, you always have the will of the dragon with you.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">And would you risk your life for your beliefs?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No, I wouldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">No?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, because I wouldn't be much use to my clients dead. Now, admit it! You've never once thought about leaving the Defiant Dragons, have you!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">.........That look in your eyes. It's just like Dhurke's. ...Looks like you've got the will of the dragon inside o' ya, too.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I had planned to take ya out if ya turned out to be on the side of the royals... But I think I can trust ya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe I was that close to getting shanked here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">It's like ya said. I've no intention of leaving Dhurke's group.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, you were testing me. You're a foreigner, and a lawyer who's been charged with abetting a criminal to boot. And I've seen a fair share of lawyers get pardoned... ...after weeping at the feet of the queen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm going to keep fighting till the end.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, I can see that now. Sorry I ever doubted ya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what are you doing here, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I came to get the secret hideout key from a helper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A secret hideout?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. I was supposed to get my next order from Dhurke there. But the town's swarming with cops thanks to that murder. Nothing I can do about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the order Dhurke was supposed to give you?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Gonna have to abort that mission. Now I'm just lying low, waiting for a chance to make contact with Dhurke again. ......... Hey, why the long face?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you'd be able to tell me something about the high priest's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sorry to disappoint ya... Oh, I know. Lemme make it up to ya with this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">This orb is actually a key. It opens the door to one of our secret hideouts. I can't say any more than that. Anyway, I hope it helps.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This orb... is a key?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep! Plus the hideout's in a totally unexpected location! And being that it's super secret, we couldn't have just any ordinary key!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe this will help me unravel the truth behind this case.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Don't mention it! Besides, you're a fellow brother in arms, fighting the powers that be! If it'll help ya, feel free to pick my brain a bit more.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Everyone's been talking about the return of Lady Kee'ra lately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, my friend Maya's suspected of being the rebel hunter disguised as Lady Kee'ra. You wouldn't happen to know who she really is though, would you?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Beats me. But whoever she is, she bushwhacked me and hauled me off to jail! Even worse, on top o' attacking us and delivering us to the cops... ...she's been watching us like a hawk and framing us for different crimes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Watching you like a hawk? Framing you for crimes? Why would anyone go to all that trouble?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Our kingdom likes to pretend that its people are free to think what they want. Because of that, the authorities can't arrest ya just for sympathizing with the rebellion. So they resort to framing people for things they didn't do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then that Lady Kee'ra figure is...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep, she's just some lickspittle working for the Ga'ran regime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow...</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh, even without the DC Act, Dhurke and his insurgent scum buddies' days are numbered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Let's just say... I got a little trick up my sleeve. So I'd watch it if I were you. 'Cause you got a defiant attitude -- like one o' them dragon dupes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he was talking about Lady Kee'ra, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Advanced combat skills, detailed surveillance, and clever set ups... She's no amateur if ya ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're saying the monarchy is using Lady Kee'ra to secretly take out the rebels?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Exactly! The Ga'ran regime is using her to control the people, even down to what we think!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't the people protest if the monarchy is doing things like that?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Unfortunately, we don't have any conclusive evidence. And without that, we can't prove anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh! I know the feeling... If I bring this up in court, they'd probably dismiss it out of hand. <thought>I'll have to unmask Lady Kee'ra if I want to get anywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Our goal? To get rid o' that evil, no-good Defense Culpability Act!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can tell just by looking at Dhurke's law book.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The DC Act has turned this kingdom into a corrupt cesspool... ...where false charges are overlooked, and prosecutors are the only ones heard in court. It's been twenty-three years since it was first enacted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened twenty-three years ago to make them pass such a terrible law?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The assassination of Queen Amara...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">It happened before I was even born, but... ...Queen Amara -- the previous queen -- was assassinated. And it was the rebel leader Dhurke who did it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dhurke assassinated the former queen, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's the official line, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The official line?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those charges were completely trumped up! Dhurke was framed, I'm telling ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-He was?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Plus, Dhurke was a lawyer. Once the people thought a lawyer had killed the queen, they turned against all lawyers. And that's how the DC Act was first passed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, that's why there aren't any lawyers left in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Even worse, it changed the significance of the Divination Séance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The significance of the Divination Séance?</thought> They were holding Séances in court, even before the DC Act?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You bet they were! Lawyers and prosecutors used to hotly contest the Insights that came outta Séances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean like what I've been doing?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Right! It's like Dhurke used to say: The royal priestess's Insights are just another piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... I see what you mean about the significance of the Divination Séance changing.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep! The Insights became the only truth, and arguing against them was banned!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">As royal priestess, it is my duty to reveal the truth through the Divination Séance. This time, I will prove that the insights I glean thereof are the very truth itself. Prepare yourself, for this shall be your last trial... and your last rites. Tomorrow shall end with you under the headsman's axe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>From what I've seen, Rayfa would agree with that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">This kingdom's a shadow of its former self. It's become a dictatorship where the royals use the fear of trumped-up charges to rule!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's what Dhurke's been rebelling against?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. All we want is to live in a kingdom with a fair and impartial legal system. And there's only one way to make that come true: Overthrow the current regime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, that's the truth behind the rebels.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">I've seen the will of the dragon within ya! You're gonna make a fine rebel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">What's wrong, my friend! You've gotta rise up with me! Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I don't recall joining the rebellion, though...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The high priest left Lady Inmee all alone when he died. Even worse, they say she's expecting a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's always hardest for the family members left behind.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I know exactly what you mean. Blast it! If only I could remember what happened after I escaped from prison.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems Mr. Are'bal feels responsible for the high priest's death.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">The dragon emblem branded into that book is a sign of defiance against the Ga'ran regime. That evil law's led to the deaths of many of our brothers in arms.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the Defense Culpability Act?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. But we're not gonna stand for it much longer! That's the main reason we have to see this revolution through!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen him so serious before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">That orb's the key to the secret hideout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, where exactly is this hideout, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Umm............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me you forgot when you bumped your head?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">.........Har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I'll have to find it myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hmm... This is that whatchamacallit, ain't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You know, that whatchamacallit. Um... What were we talking about again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's all right. You don't have to force yourself if you've got nothing to say...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Well, PW, my friend, it's about time for me to get going. After all, I AM the fangs of the Defiant Dragons. Datz Are'bal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not going to do that "alley-oop" thing again, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I was just getting to that! See ya when I see ya! Alley-oop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does he have to jump like that before running off?</thought> ...Well, I guess we're friends now. But enough about that. I've already spent way too much time here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew... I finally got out of there!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Mr. Wright! I'm so glad you're okay! I was so worried about you!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">*whine*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shah'do... What happened to him, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">He came out of the manhole about five minutes after you went in. Sorry he wasn't much help!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">*whine*</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Well? Did you find anything of worth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... I tripped and fell down there. I must've been out cold for a while. <thought>I better keep things to myself for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I figured as much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to find that secret hideout Mr. Are'bal was talking about. I should probably start with places that have something to do with the high priest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is it, Barbed Head? Is the sewer calling to you once more?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not exactly... <thought>I probably shouldn't tell her about Mr. Are'bal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head... I detect a foul odor emanating from you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I did walk through the sewers, so...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Stay back! Keep your stink to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd be glad to leave you alone if you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Who said you could walk away from me, you muttonhead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fine, I'll stick to you like glue.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No, that is too close!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just can't win with her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Even after investigating the sewers, you have nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm not ready to give up yet! <thought>Besides, I wouldn't say I have nothing.</thought> There's nowhere I wouldn't go if it would help Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">So, what will it be next? Will you dive into a septic tank?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uuh... I-If it would help Maya, I wouldn't rule it out!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">S-Stay back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought it was just a hypothetical!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That orb has a mesmerizing core. I must take a closer look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Are'bal entrusted me with this, so maybe I shouldn't let even Princess Rayfa handle it.</thought> Y-Your Benevolence? Wouldn't you be defiled by touching an object that has been in the hands of a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You do know that there are no such things as lawyer cooties, right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head. You already searched here, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... I just thought I'd look around again. You know, in case I missed something? <thought>I probably shouldn't tell her I'm looking for the secret rebel hideout.</thought> We have a saying back home: "Leave no stone unturned."</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm? ...Oh, yes. You cannot stump me. I know that one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, "I don't have a clue" is written all over your face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe Mr. Are'bal used this as a parachute.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That reckless fool... Then again, he must have a screw loose if he counts himself among those vile rebels.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't exactly call him crazy... but he's certainly one-of-a-kind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a statue of a bird... I should take a closer look later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, this eye is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What are you doing? You must not touch that for no reason!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! But that shape... Hmm, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Pohlkunka! Wh-What are you doing?! You... chowderhead! Remove your hand from there this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! I just thought this might fit in there.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Are you blind?! They have entirely different shapes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that was a long shot. Still, I can't help feeling I have something that would fit in there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do not let me catch you needlessly touching the statue again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Alright already, I get it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-Wh-Wha...?! ........................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must be at a loss for words. And that doesn't happen too often.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...What is this place?! E-Explain yourself at once, Barbed Head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think she's ready for the full story...</thought> I don't really know much myself, but... It seems to be a secret rebel hideout. <thought>If I'm shocked there's a secret door here, I imagine that goes double for Rayfa.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A rebel hideout in the Inner Sanctum?! Somebody will pay for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well for now, I think I'll have a look around.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wait! You must not enter before the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, I won't disturb anything. <thought>Or at least I'll try not to...</thought> Besides, with you watching over me, it should be fine, right? And, uh, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Fine. Just please stop pleading your case. I can only stand so much lawyerly drivel. But I will be presenting all information gleaned from your efforts here to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. Now, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I will go no further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. You're not supposed to come in contact with the taint of Lady Kee'ra's battles.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Very good, Barbed Head. I commend you for remembering!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, well thank you! <thought>Wait, why am I thanking her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I may not be able to enter, but I will allow no misdeeds on your part. I will be watching you like a warbaa'd from the entrance here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I told you I'm not going to do anything! <thought>I better hurry before she changes her mind!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who'd have guessed a rebel hideout would be at the back of the Inner Sanctum? Then again, the sanctum's not open to the public. What better place to hide away from prying eyes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I believe this to be a sacred space that enshrines the source of the spring water.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That makes sense. The rebels must've converted it into a secret hideout. But what about that warbaa'd revolving door? I wonder if that, too, was originally intended to hide and protect this sacred space.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">To think those filthy rebels were scheming their schemes in this most sacred space...! It is a desecration upon Khura'inism itself! The Defiant Dragons shall pay for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose it's only natural that she'd be upset. But the investigation must go on!</thought> I think I'll start by taking a picture of the place. <thought>Good thing I brought a camera to snap some souvenir shots.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Stop that! You must not take photos here without permission!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa's really fired up. She's sticking her head in as far as it will go. I guess she won't be "tainted" as long as she doesn't touch anything...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, to search every nook and cranny...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! Just because it is hard for me to see your every move... ...do not use that as an excuse to touch and break things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard you the first time! <thought>Sheesh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How dare those filthy insurgents raise their banner amid such a sacred space! Barbed Head! You must burn it at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, didn't you tell me not to touch or damage anything?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, this is an exception! Very well, if you will not do it, then I will!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Your Benevolence, I thought you're not supposed to come in here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nngrrrrrrr...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For once, the strange customs of this kingdom are working in my favor.</thought> Hm? <thought>There's something under the banner. A microphone? What's this doing here? Was someone trying to record something with it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A large stone slab... <thought>It's shaped like a magatama. It looks rather unstable. I bet it'd tip over in an earthquake.</thought> Hm? What's that earthy, grass-like smell?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is the smell of the moss that covers the stone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, so this shaggy green stuff is moss... ...Hm? It looks like some of the moss about halfway up has been disturbed. ...I wonder why that is? <thought>One quick touch can't hurt, right…?</thought> Whoa! <thought>The slab's starting to wobble!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is happening?! What have you done to the sacred space?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-N-Nothing! <thought>All I did was nudge it a little... I knew it looked unstable. Probably best not to touch it again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, this is the water source that supplies the Inner Sanctum's spring. It flows through the channel built into the floor before heading outside.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Lady Kee'ra uses this sacred water to wash the taint of battle from her body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's also not red like the water in the spring.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like an order from Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What's this?! Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you're not supposed to touch anything in here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This is an exception! Now hand it over! Let's see here... Hmm... ...O Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What does it say?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is an order intended for that rebel named Datz. It reads... "After the rite, infiltrate the palace under the guise of returning Lady Kee'ra's costume... ...and search for clues about that incident from twenty-three years ago. --Dhurke"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Twenty-three years ago? He must mean the assassination of Queen Amara. I wonder what the rebels are up to... <thought>It's intriguing and all, but it doesn't seem related to the case at hand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This will not do! I must warn my mother at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No need to do that. This order will never be carried out. Lady Kee'ra's costume is still here, and Abbot Inmee is no longer able to aid the rebels.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, I-I knew that!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Is there anything else you would like me to read, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, let's see... Uhh... How about this note?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Let me see that. Konuuro, zabaas, bahr'bahr, yak, and roux... Wait, this looks familiar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it? Some kind of Khura'inist spell?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No, it's a recipe for Khura'inese curry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the rebels enjoy a home-cooked meal, just like everyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a Plumed Punisher calendar here.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah, now I understand. The villains in The Plumed Punisher are based on the insurgents. Watching the show must have roused their ire against Lady Kee'ra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... I doubt that's it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What is it, Barbed Head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a Plumed Punisher clock!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why, I believe it's... It is a limited-edition promotional item given to fifty lucky viewers! This rare item plays the Plumed Punisher theme song ever hour! H-Hand it over now, Barbed Head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! <thought>She snatched it away from me! No matter what she says, Rayfa is definitely a huge fan.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... What a fine item. And this switch... If I'm right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's the Plumed Punisher theme song…</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, now I see! The insurgents who use this room... ...must be Plumed Punisher fans!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That may be so, but I don't see how it's relevant to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The statue door rotates when you pull this chain.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I see...Then you must shut the door and destroy its mechanism! That will deprive the insurgents of access to this place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But wouldn't that trap me in here?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Not to worry! I would come to visit you once a year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's actually serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Weapons! And lots of them, too.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">We are lucky we found them before they could be used. Excellent work, Barbed Head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, thanks... <thought>If the rebellion ever happens, I hope it's bloodless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A bloodstain...? I should probably try to figure out what happened in here. Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do not tamper with any evidence before the police arrive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The police? Hey, that reminds me. Ema gave me something just for times like these.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I thought it might help your investigation. Here, it's all yours! I wanted to bring you a bunch of other forensic tools... ...but they were confiscated at the airport.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Luminol testing fluid... This actually might come in handy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Luminol testing fluid glows in reaction to even the tiniest traces of blood. So it can even detect areas where blood has been wiped up. It might help us figure out what happened in here. Okay, time for science to do its thing! First, let me put these red-tinted glasses on to see the luminol's glow... ...then I just touch wherever I want to spray some of the luminol. Areas where there was blood will react by turning blue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-This is a huge bloodstain! Something big must've happened here!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Perhaps the high priest's blood flowed in there from under the warbaa'd statue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...There was definitely a lot of blood here. But it's impossible to say much else at this point. I'll just take a picture for now. Oh, right. Luminol reactions don't show up in photos. I'll just have to take some notes. That should do it!  <thought>...I didn't notice before, but the bloodstain looks like it was smeared away in one place. Is it because the warbaa'd revolving door passed over it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That bloodstain on the floor... The luminol showed that it was even bigger than I expected. Something definitely happened here, and it wasn't good.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">How can you be so sure? Perhaps the high priest's blood flowed in there from under the warbaa'd statue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True... But there's not much else we can say at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, I think that covers about everything here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright! You shouldn't have come in here before the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I was in a hurry. I didn't do anything I wasn't supposed to. Her Benevolence can attest to that.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It is your fault for being so slow. I expect the police to work faster and more efficiently!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, Barbed Head? Have you not already seen enough?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it's about time I got back to the temple and go over everything I've learned.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Welcome back, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, I didn't find anything conclusive.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">N-No way!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...I do not understand, Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What don't you understand?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Why you did not commit any misdeeds during your investigation. After all, lawyers ply their trade primarily through illicit means and methods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Who told you that?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My mother. Are you saying she was wrong? ...No, that cannot be! You must have committed some sort of misdeed right under my nose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that were so, she wasted her whole day following me around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hm? What is it? ........................ Prosecutor Sahdmadhi has need of me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I must go perform a Divination Séance for Puhray Zeh'lot. It is our custom for the prosecution to review its contents before a trial begins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........The third time will be the charm. My insights will finally bring you to your knees tomorrow! And I will teach that neophyte practitioner a lesson!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the royal priestess is back with a vengeance. She's made a full recovery from when we started the investigation earlier today.</thought> I look forward to seeing you in court, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. Your overconfidence will be your downfall. You will not look so confident when I am finished with you tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I'm not really looking forward to seeing her tomorrow. Especially without any solid evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Why don't we go over everything you know so far?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Hmm, let's see here... Acolyte Zeh'lot was killed during the rite with Lady Kee'ra's dagger. And Maya's fingerprints were found on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That doesn't sound very good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know... It's the very definition of being up a creek without a paddle. The day before his murder, Zeh'lot enjoyed a meal with the high priest, his wife, and Maya. I also learned about spirit channeling here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">None of that sounds very helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, but I did hear something interesting. That the rebel-hunting Lady Kee'ra might be working for the justice minister.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What?! Really?! Our kingdom is supposed to be ruled through faith and laws. We can't allow the people to be controlled by fear and violence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, that sounds like something a rebel might say.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I-It does? But if that Lady Kee'ra really is one of Minister Inga's subordinates... ...that would exonerate Miss Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, I have no way of proving it in court.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Oh, that's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I almost forgot about the secret rebel hideout we found at the Inner Sanctum. There was a bloodstain inside. But I don't know if or how it's connected to this case, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Wow! A secret room at the Inner Sanctum?! That would be a huge hit with tourists!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This kid really is an entrepreneur at heart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Er, what I mean is that hideout could be important to your case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe, but it's still too early to tell. Argh... Looks like I'm heading into court without any useful evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">We'll just have to pray something appears during tomorrow's trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Princess Rayfa's Divination Séance might be my only hope. There could be some new information in it that might help.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Th-The Divination Séance?! But I thought it always works against the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Not always.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Right! It's like Dhurke used to say: The royal priestess's Insights are just another piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Really?! I never heard anyone say that before. It's hard to figure you out sometimes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Divination Séances worked both ways before the Defense Culpability Act. It's only now that the people of Khura'in find it strange.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Um, Mr. Wright? I just wanted to say... good luck tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. I can't afford to lose this next one. <thought>I've collected all sorts of information, but I haven't even started connecting the dots. If I could do that, I might have a shot at pulling off a win. Rayfa's Insights will be the deciding factor. It's a huge gamble, but it's all I've got!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure I know what I need to, but... ...maybe I should go over it all again.</thought></line>
</xml>