
<xml>
<title>The Cosmic Turnabout</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">The courtroom bombing incident -- a terrible attack launched by the will of a madman. That incident perfectly symbolized the state of the legal world in this dark age of the law. Mr. Wright brought it to a resolution... of sorts. Ted Tonate was discovered to be the one responsible for the bombing. ............If only it were that simple. Somehow, I can't help but think... ...that there's a darker influence at work -- one that's lurking in the shadows, waiting... That's why I want to review the trial that was taking place when the bombing occurred. After all, I've got more than a few personal stakes in it...</line>
<line speaker="Operator">One hour remaining until launch. Please begin your final equipment check.</line>
<line speaker="Astronaut">Check complete! Everything's all okay! We're ready here whenever you are!</line>
<line speaker="Operator">Come in HAT-2! Come in! Do you copy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time for another trial to begin... But this one is different.</thought> ............</line>
<line speaker="???">Umm.. Sorry to bother you, but... Are you all right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! Was I making a scary face just now?!</thought> Oh, hi, Juniper! Yes, I'm fine! I was just doing my Chords of Steel exercises. Now I'm all ready to go!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, knowing you, I'm sure you will be just fine! Oh! I brought you a present from my garden.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this... a lotus root?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's right. My grandma says lotus root is good for your eyes. She says that if you look through the holes, it can help you see into the future! It's for good luck! Maybe later, you can cook it and--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for this! I'm gonna have some right now!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Mmm. *crunch* Kinda tough, though...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hee hee! You can't eat it raw! But... thank you for the enthusiastic try.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops! If she didn't think me weird before, she will now! I've gotta calm down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! I'm sorry I'm late!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hi, Thena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie! I didn't know you were coming today. Did you come to cheer Apollo on? Oh, I get it. You sly little thing, you! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-Thena, stop!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Quit kidding around, Athena. The trial's about to start any second. Is everything all set?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Apollo, Apollo... When will you ever figure it out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Figure out what?</line>
<line speaker="???">............Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow. That was the longest sigh I've ever heard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Haaaaangh... This is it. It's all over for me... They're gonna find me guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is our client, one Mr. Solomon "Sol" Starbuck. He's a very famous astronaut, who happens to be an acquaintance of mine. You wouldn't know it right now, but he's usually a very upbeat and driven person. The scene of the crime this time happened to be the Cosmos Space Center. Back in high school, my best friend and I went there almost a little too much... ...but that's where we met Mr. Starbuck. We'd ask about space travel and he'd launch into story after story with so much passion... Back in those days, the man was one hundred percent my hero.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Are... you sure you're okay with being my lawyer, Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course I'm sure. I know you, Mr. Starbuck. I know you're not the type to commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Thanks, but......... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I was supposed to be in space right about now... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's so depressed, it almost seems like an act. The launch getting called off must've been a huge shock.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I'll probably never get the chance to go into space again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't say that! Don't stop believing! Besides, you just have to go into space again!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah... I don't think I could face Clay in the afterlife if I just rotted away in a cell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Clay Terran... I can't believe he was murdered. I mean, he was such a promising astronaut under your command...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah... He was a good guy -- always there to pick me up when I was down. No one loved life as much as him, that's for sure. He was always so full of energy, telling me, "You're fine, Mr. Starbuck!"... ...Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... How could something like this happen to a guy like him, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've never seen Mr. Starbuck so down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">...Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Clay's gone, and I'm going to prison... I wish I could burn up like a shooting star right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Mr. Starbuck! You'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ah! Wh-What is it?! What's with the yelling?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll get to the bottom of this today! You'll see! And in exchange, I want you to go back into space for you and Clay! Promise?!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">...Does that mean you have lots of evidence to prove my innocence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh! Umm... Well... About that... We... didn't get to investigate the area as much as I'd have liked, thanks to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............I'm done for. I'm a goner. Everybody thinks I did it. Thought I was gonna soar like a comet, but I'm just gonna crash like a meteorite.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, don't say that, Mr. Starbuck!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't count yourself out yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know it's hard to lose a teammate, but you've got to keep going.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............And what about you, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was just thinking, wasn't Clay your best friend?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........We need to focus on the trial right now. Are you all ready to go?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to begin. If the defense would please proceed into the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Okay! Here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it. This is one trial I can't afford to lose! For Clay's sake and our client's, I WILL find Clay's killer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Solomon Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Excuse me, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What happened to your eye?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm fine! The defense is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Are you sure? I don't--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine, Your Honor! The defense is ready!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sorry, Your Honor. He's been like this since yesterday. He keeps insisting it's just a sty.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose it's something he doesn't want to discuss. Maybe he's entering a touchy age...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. And the prosecution...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution appears to be ready as well.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ ............... ...Not yet. I'm... not quite ready yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh... Graaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The prosecution... is now ready.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it didn't take him long this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>What's up with Blackquill?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-N-Now, then. I-I-I shall give the opening statement...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'll do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will? Wh-What an unexpected surprise!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This time, I can't leave it to anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see... Hmm... Something is off with the two of you today. You both seem different somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Prosecutor Blackquill. Your opening statement, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It was just yesterday. The crimes in question occurred at the Cosmos Space Center.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, that famous federal research facility of all things related to astrology, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Astronomy. It's astronomy. Anyway, a rocket was set to launch from there... ...but at 9:28 AM, before they could even move the rocket to the launch site... ...two explosive devices were detonated, and the launch was canceled.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word! Two bombs? How dreadful...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defendant in today's trial is charged with both the bombing and with murder... One Mr. Solomon Starbuck. For whatever inane reason, he detonated a bomb on the rocket he himself would be in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Solomon Starbuck? I recognize that name. Isn't he that famous astronaut?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Correct, Your Baldness. Mr. Starbuck was the pilot of the HAT-1 rocket seven years ago. As you may recall, despite some interstellar trouble, his mission was a success. Some say it was a miracle he returned alive. I suppose you could say he's a living legend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I remember now. He's become something of an international celebrity, right? They even turned that incident into a movie and everything! We've got a real space pioneer in court today!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. But even heroes tumble from their lofty heights. Returning to the subject at hand...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. The victim was one Mr. Clay Terran, a subordinate of the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. A loyal disciple brutally stabbed to death by his mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Stabbed to death, you say? You mean his death wasn't a result of the bombing?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Correct. Despite his lofty dreams, the victim was seen as an interloper by the defendant. And so, he was sent not into space, but to the universe which we mortals cannot see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Clay...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think I've heard enough. The case seems pretty clear-cut at this point. However, there is one thing I'm curious about. That metal box next to the witness stand... What purpose does it serve, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Since you asked so nicely... It's your coffin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Have mercy on meeeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............I jest. It's evidence. Due to its immense size, we've little choice but to lay it where it rests now. We shall get to the contents of the box in due time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Phew... I feel like I just lost fifty years off of my life.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Does he even HAVE fifty years left?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Inner monologue, Athena! Inner monologue!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough jabbering.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Bobby Fulbright's the name! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, Detective Fulbright! Very well, them. Please explain the details of this incident to the court, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">On it! First, take a look at this pamphlet from the Cosmos Space Center! In it, you'll find a diagram outlining the overall layout of the Space Center. Ah, here we are. For a more detailed look at what's on the left side of this building... ...take a look at this cross-section that we the police have created. See the launch pad and the main building?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The launch pad is the square building, and the rounded structure is the main building, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You got it. The incidents took place in Launch Pad 1 and in the main building's Lounge. I'll be using this diagram during my testimony -- it'll make it easier to understand!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Just before the rocket was set to launch, two bombs went off. BOOM! BOOM!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A murder on top of a bombing...? Detective, the victim was already dead by the time you arrived at the lounge, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. Thinking he'd sabotage the bombing, the defendant attacked and killed the victim. Just look at this tragic photo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! I-Is that a knife in the victim's chest?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, Your Honor, it's the knife that cruelly ended this young man's dreams! We couldn't get any prints off of it, though, because the defendant was in his space suit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way, Detective Fulbright... Why are the victim's helmet and right glove absent in this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">We had to remove them to identify him, Your Honor. I personally removed his glove during the investigation. We had to get his fingerprints to confirm his identity, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, it would be very difficult to identify him without a face or fingerprints. Now, there's just one more thing I'd like to inquire about... What is this round thing next to the victim in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Something so important to the victim he took it with him as he escaped the launch pad. A capsule that apparently contains asteroid samples. While obviously valuable for research purposes, it has no relation to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... we know that the bomb in the main building was on the second floor... ...but where was the bomb that was in Launch Pad 1 located?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Heh. That one was on the rocket itself. It was situated around the central part of the rocket. Apparently, the area around the launch pad's elevator was a sea of flames. I would like to submit this diagram and report into the record!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The trial's just started and we're already in a bind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You get used to it. Besides, that's what cross-examination is for, right? <thought>What the two astronauts were doing during the bombing... That'll be the key!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Just before the rocket was set to launch, two bombs went off. BOOM! BOOM!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, the one in the main building wasn't strong enough to bring the place down... ...but the room it went off in was burned black! Thankfully, nobody was hurt. Due in large part, of course, to me stepping up to lead the evacuation!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait. What were you doing there in the first place, Detective Fulbright?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! I'm Bobby Fulbright, hero of justice! I'll be there, wherever and whenever people need my help! I'd go to the other side of the world, or even the edge of the universe!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not sure he knows how far that actually is... But I guess I'll leave that one alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Admirable decision, Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh? What'd he decide...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway, could you describe what it was like at the Space Center at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The bomb cut the power to the central bank of elevators and the third floor lounge. It was pitch black in there, I tell you. However, the security cameras and whatnot were running on emergency backup.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And how did the evacuation go?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I immediately and heroically whisked people down to the Space Center's basement shelter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The basement shelter?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, there's an emergency shelter beneath the Space Center!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">An emergency shelter, huh? Oh, here it is! It's at the bottom of the diagram. The Space Center's pretty impressive to have its own shelter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... The power outage and evacuation seem unrelated to the murder at this point. I guess I'll leave that aside for now.</thought> So there were two explosions in total, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">One on the second floor of the Space Center's main building and one in Launch Pad 1.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the defendant really did plant the bomb on his own rocket... ...he'd get caught in the explosion as well!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I hadn't thought of that!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Fine. A simpleton for a simpleton. Fool Bright. The motive.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Understood! The defendant actually had astrophobia.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... Astrophobia? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">A fear of space, naturally. Just the thought of space can cause the afflicted to freeze up. And so, in his terror, the defendant found a way to stop the launch at the last minute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Unfortunately for you, we have evidence! Take a look at these!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What are they?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">These anti-anxiety tablets were found among the defendant's possessions! Apparently, he was taking them in secret to quell his fears.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There were a multitude of problems with the rocket Mr. Starbuck rode seven years ago. Rumor has it, it threatened to crash a number of times as well. That was, of course, very traumatic for Mr. Starbuck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defendant couldn't bear to mar his good name, now could he? No, not after the media had branded him "Sol Starbuck: space pioneer extraordinaire." Given these conditions, the defendant could hardly run away like some base mutt.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, so THAT'S why you think he resorted to the bombing?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Naturally. He constructed this act of sabotage in an attempt to blow up the Space Center... ...which would effectively abort the launch, but spare his reputation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Now I'm sure you understand why we have to bring justice down on this atrocious criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Thankfully, only the two astronauts were in Launch Pad 1 at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It was before the spaceship was set to launch, so of course it was only those two!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ungh... Well, there could've been somebody else inside that rocket!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The notion of a third party in Launch Pad 1 is utterly absurd. Just to enter the area from the lounge... ...one must pass through a door guarded by a fingerprint recognition device. And allow me to state up front that there are precious few with the clearance to do so.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A fingerprint recognition device? It sounds as futuristic and complex as a space center!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Actually, it's not as amazing as you think, Your Honor. Take a look at this photo! This is the door in the lounge with the fingerprint lock. Only personnel whose fingerprints are registered can pass through.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see... That is very different from what I had in mind. And is there a record of the number of people that passed through that door yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, there were only three: the defendant, the victim, and... ...the director of the Space Center, Yuri Cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then doesn't that mean it's possible that the director is the one who did it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Not a chance. He was in the main building when the bombs exploded at 9:28... ...doing his job directing the launch. Besides having an alibi, he has no motive for committing these senseless acts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He has a point... I guess the director can't be considered a suspect then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The two of them managed to make it back as far as the boarding lounge...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You got it! In fact, that's what I've been trying to say this whole time! If the victim had been alive, he would've for sure tried to stop the bombing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is there any chance Mr. Terran could have been killed before he boarded the rocket?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">They were both alive and well at boarding time, and embarked under their own power! Their hearts full of hopes and dreams of space!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And then both of their hopes and dreams were dashed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">If I may continue my explanation! After the evacuation order was given... ...the defendant made his escape, carrying the victim to make it look like a rescue.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">...but after the escape, one of the two was found stabbed to death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Actually, there were two of them!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The Space Center director... ...Yuri Cosmos... ...and Detective Candice Arme.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One of them was a detective?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup. Detective Arme specializes in bombings, you see. She and the director were ordering the evacuation following the explosions. They were also worried about the astronauts, so they hurried over to the boarding lounge. That's when they discovered the victim along with the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Two witnesses, huh? And one of them is a detective! I doubt either one would have anything to say that would help me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... It's like he's trying to give us as little information as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Prosecutor Blackquill's got his tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, don't let that hold you back. Keep pressing until we get what we need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What little I could get out of him only hurt my case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Justice-dono, foolish is the warrior who rushes headlong into battle. Preparation is an essential element of battle, so I advise you to take a gander at this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Footage from a security camera. As the two astronauts emerged from the bowels of the Launch Pad 1 Corridor... ... the boarding lounge security camera captured their desperate escape. Now, I would direct your attention to what the defendant is shouldering... ...which you can see, is none other than... the lifeless body of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh.....Whaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order I say! This... This lines up exactly with what the prosecution has been asserting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I should've known Blackquill would have something like this ready.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Apollo...? How exactly did they determine that Clay was... already gone in that footage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Ah, I see what you mean! Whether Clay was still alive at that point IS pretty crucial. Your Honor! Please take another look at the footage. Isn't it possible that Mr. Terran was still alive here and that Mr. Starbuck was helping him?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe you're right. One man carrying the other to safety... What a beautiful expression of friendship...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Perhaps that's what it looks like to a one-eyed hothead and a dotard... But it only makes sense if it's the victim's dead body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Fool Bright, explain it to Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You got it! Ready, kid? If the murder had occurred in the lounge, someone could've spotted it. Anyone can enter the lounge, after all. But doing it while they were alone in the spaceship? That's a horse of a different color!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your assertion... is based on emotion. It's based in your belief that Mr. Starbuck would surely help his own disciple. But you have no logical explanation as to why the victim could still be alive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, Mr. Justice, the prosecution is right. Your argument is lacking in sound logic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But it sounded perfectly logical to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? If you have no further objections... ...I believe it's time to bring this cross-examination to a close.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Objections...? Well, I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Given the facts, I'm not sure I see the need...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is it, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just... There's something that's been bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. If it isn't the defense stalling for time, as always. ............Very well, I'm feeling generous. You may have a small measure of time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You have......... five seconds.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">F-FIVE SECONDS?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">After that, I declare this cross-examination to be closed, and a verdict to be rendered. Your Baldness! Raise your gavel high. It's time for a countdown!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... OH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ready?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We don't have time! Spit it out, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only three more seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ack! L-Look! I don't think the prosecution's explanation is very complete.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Meaning?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Meaning there's something missing -- like they conveniently left it unexplained...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something they didn't explain... Something they didn't explain... .........Ah! You're right! I think I know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your five seconds are up, Mr. Justice. Is there anything about the prosecution's argument that you'd like to rebut?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor! Actually, there is! There is something the prosecution has yet to make clear to this court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, if you put it that way... What is it that the prosecution has failed to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecution hasn't explained the defendant's motive yet, have they?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? But didn't they just explain... ...that Mr. Terran was a threat to the success of the bombing, so he had to be disposed of?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! No, wait! Time out, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Time out," Mr. Justice? This is hardly a sporting event.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack. <thought>That didn't score me any points... Time to put my game face on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They have failed to explain why Mr. Starbuck would bother bringing the body back at all. If the defendant wanted to kill the victim, why didn't he just leave the body in the rocket? Why go  through the trouble of bringing him all the way back to the boarding lounge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's true! I don't think we've heard the prosecution's thoughts on that yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's because they have none, Your Honor. After all, how does one explain something so illogical?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecution is claiming that the defendant moved the victim's dead body. But what if the entire premise of that argument is wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's hear your theory, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense proposes that the defendant didn't kill the victim! He was helping him! Aaaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool Bright. Explain it for our sad friend here before I nod off to his monotone monologue. Inform him exactly why Space Boy moved the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>They've gotta be joking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It's simple! Mr. Starbuck did what he did to direct suspicion away from himself! He wanted to create the impression he heroically risked his life to save his partner! That's why he made sure to make it to the security camera so there'd be a record!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">At the very least, he appears to have achieved success with you and the old man.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One man carrying the other to safety... What a beautiful expression of friendship...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The average person wearing a space suit weighs easily over 200 pounds. Saving the life of a partner who weighs as much, while trying to escape deadly flames... What a dramatic sob story fit for the silver screen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. I was completely taken in by the humanity of the story.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You see? Yet the true ending is that all traces of his hammy act were meant to be blown up. Yes, and now we arrive at the thrilling conclusion: the third explosion!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed, you are correct. But that is thanks to Detective Arme. It was she who identified and secured the bomb. However, it doesn't change the fact that the third bomb was discovered in the lounge. The steel coffin beside the witness stand. That would be... a bomb transport case. We used that to transport the deactivated bomb here. It was found in the lounge... A bomb in the form of a most distasteful toy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">One on the second floor of the main building, one on the launch pad, and one in the lounge. The defendant planned to set off three firework displays. Fortunately, the third one was discovered before it could be detonated, for had it not... ...the victim's body and other vital evidence would surely have been immolated.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Before you utter a word, know that the evidence supports me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... It's like he's reading my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">As it is still undergoing forensic investigation, I do not have the evidence on hand. However, know that a peculiar item was found in one of Mr. Starbuck's pockets. Specifically, a bomb detonation switch...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You found whaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I suspect the defendant had no time to destroy such damning evidence... ...when the Space Center director and Detective Arme stumbled across the murder. So he thought to hide it in his pocket... feeble-brained that he is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaaagh... No! Mr. Starbuck would never do anything like that! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Justice-dono, open your eyes and see the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, this appears to be irrefutable evidence that the accused set off the explosions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No! There has to be some kind of mistake! This can't be the "truth"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Still can't accept it? You'll believe in your client, come what may? ............Then why don't you cross-examine the defendant himself?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>......This has got to be a trap.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's like Blackquill's controlling the entire game.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It seemed like he was waiting for me to bring up the body moving issue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because he had just the right argument when I pointed it out... ...and to really rub it in, he had a decisive piece of evidence up his sleeve, too. He was trying to shake my faith in Mr. Starbuck and break me down!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then, making you cross-examine Mr. Starbuck at this point was part of his plan, too...? Totally underhanded, but I wouldn't expect anything less from him.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, let us hear from the arch villain, the fiendish murderer himself. Famed astronaut, Solomon Starbuck!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, your name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Solomon Starbuck. Astronaut... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... How did this happen?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Starbuck, you aren't looking very well. Will you be able to give testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh............ No.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Well, unfortunately, "no" is not an option. You are being accused of the Space Center bombing and the murder of Clay Terran. Please testify to these allegations.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Umm... Mind if I take this suit off? It's getting really heavy...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It's not the weight of the suit that you feel, but of your sins. Prepare to carry that weight for the rest of your life...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............Banish me to the moon... I don't care anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow... That was super-negative... Is he going to be all right up there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-He'll be fine! I think... <thought>As long as he doesn't totally give up and say he did it, that is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">All I did was support Clay over my shoulder and get us out of the rocket!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you assert you didn't set off the bombs or murder the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ha ha. Ha ha ha... But I bet you think I'm lying, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I reserve all judgment until after I've heard your full testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I'm sure you don't believe me. I bet you don't even believe I'm an astronaut.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think the judge doubts THAT!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who'd wear a suit like that EXCEPT an astronaut...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I will say that when I saw you in that movie... ...you appeared quite courageous, though I suppose reality never quite lives up to fantasy.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I guess I'm just a big disappointment... Ha ha. Ha ha ha. Ha ha... I really don't care what happens anymore. Ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, no! He's completely give up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. What a depressing fellow. If you were to join me in the clink... ...I imagine that annoying sighing of yours would rub off on the other inmates.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like how it rubbed off on Prosecutor Blackquill a second ago?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? That was Blackquill sighing? Mr. Starbuck's testimony contains a glaring contradiction. The question is, what does it mean? Even if Mr. Starbuck is my client, I can't be gun-shy now! It's time to find out the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">All I did was support Clay over my shoulder and get us out of the rocket!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Of course! He was alive and well!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If so, then you took a man who was alive and well... ...and silenced him permanently with this?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">What?! No! Aaaaagh! Black hole confirmed, dead ahead. Aaaaaaaaaaaaah! It's no good, captain! I'm getting sucked iiiiiiiiiiiiiiinnnnnnnnnn!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I-It was just nerves, but maybe I shouldn't have said he was "alive and well." It was more like he was slumped over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Those are complete opposite ends of the spectrum!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Like always, I took the elevator down to the middle level and headed for the corridor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">That's right. We always use it to get to and from the cockpit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That makes sense. So he was just using the route he always used.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In spite of the fact that there had just been an explosion...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think Mr. Starbuck is hiding something. Something pretty big...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Clay had passed out by the time we got the order to evacuate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Probably because of the explosion. The noise and vibration were incredible. It's little wonder a person would pass out, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I guess...? <thought>Not that I'd know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaagh! I've been hit by space debris! The main engine's on fire! It's gonna blow! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, I see... I guess it does make sense that someone would pass out... <thought>Especially if the person in question is Mr. Starbuck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">A-Anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I didn't kill Clay! I was trying to save him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............But everyone's glaring at me like I did it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you have to reassure him better than that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And how am I supposed to do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Try to imagine how he's feeling, and use that to figure out how to boost his confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck, think back to what Clay used to always say. It's times like these when he would repeat, "I'm fine!" to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">"I'm fine"...? Yeah, I guess he did say that a lot... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... But even if I shout it, Clay will still be dead. Haaangh... What's the use...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... <thought>Could somebody please reassure me now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, there's something strange about Mr. Starbuck's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I was thinking the same thing. There's a glaring contradiction. I just wonder why it's there and what it means for our case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it doesn't look like he's lying, at least...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Guess I'll have to show some evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck, I need your testimony to be as accurate as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">W-Was I not being accurate?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, because it's impossible for you to have taken the elevator down to the middle level.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What makes you say that, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please recall where the bomb went off in Launch Pad 1. Also recall that after the explosion, the middle level elevator was engulfed in flames.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! You're right. Which means...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. The launch pad's elevator would've been unusable. In other words... ...Mr. Starbuck, your statement is decidedly inconsistent with the facts! Wh-What's with the helmet?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaaagh! Mission command! Mission command! Do you read me?! Come in, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaagh! M-My helmet! Ah! My oxygen taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaank! Oxygen concentration and body temperature declining! Requesting medical assistance! Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Starbuck! We are not in space right now! Please stop pretending you have lost consciousness and stand back up!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I-I apologize, Your Honor. I forgot I was still on Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I feel like we all just got a real glimpse of Solomon Starbuck the astronaut.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he seemed more like an astronaut now than when he was doing all that sighing. Mr. Starbuck, could you please explain the inconsistency in your statement? About how you used the middle level elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I, uh... was nervous, and I said the wrong thing! I'm sorry! I actually, uh, took a different route, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A different route?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............I hope you're able to deliver a straight story this time.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ack! I-I-I'll get it right this time! Maybe. No, I mean, probably!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Probably...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's understandable to be nervous, but let me remind you that accuracy is paramount in court.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Let's see... Uh, my escape route... What I said before was a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're saying you escaped without using the elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Th-That's right! There's a ladder that spans the upper and middle levels. I used that ladder to get to the middle level. Luckily, the fire hadn't reached the ladder, so we could make our escape that way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the capsule you mentioned... I suppose you mean the thing next to Mr. Terran here? Was the capsule that important that you'd risk your life to take it with you?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">It almost goes without saying, but yeah! That capsule contains asteroid samples. Therefore it's invaluable as research material. With his space suit on, Clay weighed a ton, but securing the capsule was also important.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I need you to answer to the best of your ability! Mr. Starbuck! Please remember that your verdict is riding on your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ha ha... ha ha ha... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Maybe I am guilty after all. I wonder if you can see the stars in prison? Bet it's more comfortable than a spaceship.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Let's see... Uh, my escape route... What I said before was a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Hey, everybody makes mistakes, but try thinking about the vastness of space instead. From Earth, it takes four light-years to travel to our nearest neighboring star. So you see? Compared to the vast expanse of space, human error is insignificant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wish he'd consider it just a little more significant than zero...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough jabbering. Get on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ungh...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I, uh, I remember now! I took a different route... Maybe... Probably...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I-I didn't say either of those things! Aaaaagh! Mission control! Come in, please! An error has occurred in the sound system! Activate the emergency tin can telephone! Oh, nooooooo! Tin can telephones are ineffective in the vacuum of space!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Stop this nonsense or I will sever you AND your tin can telephone.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">All right! I'm begging you! I'll tell the truth! Just don't sever anything!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, is he going to be all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm... starting to think he's not...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Um, let's see... So about when we were running away...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">With the capsule and Clay in my arms, I made my way down from the upper level.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Th-That's right! That's what I said, isn't it?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Granted, that route does exist...</thought> So, to recap, you had Clay over your right shoulder and the capsule in your left hand?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah! It's really important, so I couldn't let it get burned up. So, even though Clay was really heavy, I couldn't afford to carry him with both hands. I did the best I could with him over one shoulder and the capsule in my other hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>............I don't think the meaning of what he just said has hit him yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. You know what you have to do with that statement, Justice-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, I know! <thought>Well, I've come this far. No turning back now. It's time to present some evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Mr. Starbuck escaped with Clay and the capsule, which means... ...it's just like in the footage. I can see why he couldn't run, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He must've weighed over 200 pounds just by himself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and he had to support Clay, who was another 200 pounds. Plus, he had to ensure the safety of that capsule. I don't think I could've even walked under those circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Walking straight forward is probably about all I would've been able to manage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck, why don't you just tell the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Th-The truth? Um, let's see... The Earth is blue...? No, no. That's not right. So, uh... I guess the Earth isn't blue? Yeah, that's it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The truth, Mr. Starbuck!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Gawrh! The oxygen concentration is super low in this area! Prepare the emergency oxygen tanks!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, the witness appears confused. Please help draw out the truth from him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck, under the circumstances at the time... ...you couldn't possibly have reached the boarding lounge via the upper level route.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not as long as this was along the escape route!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Starbuck:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's the matter, Mr. Starbuck?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Well, you say, "not as long as this," but I don't know what the "this" is. Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must admit I have no idea, either.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</thought> Your Honor! Please let me try that again! Under the circumstances at the time... ...Mr. Starbuck couldn't have made it to the boarding lounge via the upper level route.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">To get down from the upper to the middle level where the Launch Pad 1 corridor is... ...you would have to go down the ladder, isn't that right, Mr. Starbuck?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">O-Of course! That was the only way we could escape!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ah! Ooooooh! W-W-Well, it's easy on the moon! Gravity is only one-sixth of what it is on Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Oh...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Mr. Starbuck! How exactly DID you climb down that ladder with your arms full?!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck! Come clean and tell us the truth! NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Engineer! Where's that engineer?! Oxygen leak detected due to faulty maintenance! Evacuate immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--!? <thought>He's flying the coop!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaagh! Help! I'm caught on the ceiling! .........Um, help? Anyone...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Prepare the cherry picker! We must launch our rescue mission at once!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's one way to take off while being questioned...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd rather prove his innocence so he can go to space again someday for real...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Starbuck, do you think you can keep your feet planted on the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yes. I apologize for losing control.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you ready to tell us... the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ungh... Not that... Anything but that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is going on? This isn't the Mr. Starbuck I know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...It appears Space Boy is prone to deception. Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Y-Yikes! Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I thought your story odd, but perhaps the inconsistencies can be explained as... ...the result of a medical side effect?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Prosecutor Blackquill! Please... Please don't talk about that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-What are you talking about, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Didn't I already state that Space Boy is, ironically, terrified of going into space? That's why he took some "precautions" just before the launch. For you see, traces of this anti-anxiety drug were found in his system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...? <thought>I sense things are about to nosedive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Starbuck:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was found in his system, but he doesn't remember taking it...?</thought> How could that be?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Somebody must've slipped them to me! B-But I guess maybe that's why I don't remember... because of the side effects... Yeah, that's why I don't remember much about what really happened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We can't get any useful testimony out of him if he doesn't remember anything...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, this certainly explains why his testimony kept changing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ungh... Why didn't he just tell me he couldn't remember?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess he didn't want anybody to find out he was terrified of going into space.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... Maybe I really DID do it...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Which brings us to the answer of our original question... ...of how the witness climbed down the ladder with a dead body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It does? ............Um, so what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A dead man feels no pain and makes no complaints, Justice-dono. So the body was simply dropped down from the top of the ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! I see... And then the defendant could climb down with his free hand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So you are capable of quick thinking. ...Yes, you are correct.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Oh, um, thanks...? Heh heh. Aaaaaaagh! ...Huh? What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It's the oxygen tank from the victim's spacesuit. It's ruptured, and I'm sure you can figure out why.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Y-You can't be implying it ruptured when the defendant dropped the victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I am, for they fracture easily when struck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A spacesuit isn't heavy for the sake of being heavy, Justice-dono. It includes the latest technological devices and is made of the fabric of tomorrow. The fabric is made to protect astronauts from the dangers of space... ...so falling a few Earth yards would hardly leave a mark on the wearer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It should, and yet, through sheer coincidence... ...the knife slipped through a weak spot in the suit's structure and found its way to its target.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What are the chances...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You forget that our killer is an astronaut himself with knowledge of how the suits work.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nngh... <thought>He's got me there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And now my argument has been proven. Space Boy killed the victim in the rocket and then dropped his body from the upper level. After climbing down, he shouldered the body and made sure the camera recorded them. There's no room for debate about these facts. It is clear that Solomon Starbuck is the only one who could have killed Clay Terran!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Here. The report regarding the astronauts' oxygen tanks. Consider it my send-off gift. Feel free to use it as payment to cross the river Styx.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, this report is pretty detailed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see... "The display on the astronaut's left shoulder shows how much oxygen remains." I guess that means these glowing cyan digits represent the amount of oxygen remaining...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... I'm done foooooooooor! I'm going to prison instead of spaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaace!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Space Boy.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Y-Y-Y-Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Take heart. The bejeweled night sky is still beautiful even when viewed through bars.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Y-You mean... the stars as seen from... prison...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That's right. Your cell will be your spaceship. Picture the view through the iron bars. It's like being an astronaut in your own craft for all time.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Ha ha ha. That's not a half bad thought...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Mr. Starbuck..? <thought>Prosecutor Blackquill got to him good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Spaceship "Prison Cell," fly me, my guilt, and my despair into the deepest, darkest space. And then, let's get sucked into a black hole together!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Oh...! Yes, Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, Clay really looked up to you. He said you are an incredible man. He said you'd never give up your dreams and passion for space, no matter the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">He said that...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So don't give up now and help me prove your innocence! For the sake of the man who respected you and believe in you -- Clay Terran!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">For Clay...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. You're wasting your breath.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Unnnh... Nngh... Raaaaaaaaaaaaagh! RAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">............Apollo, thank you! I can see things clearly now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Starbuck!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I'm... I'm fine now -- thanks for reminding me of my life's mission.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. We'll both be fine! I'll prove you're innocent. You'll see! And after that, we'll get you back into space!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Raaaaaaaaahhhh! You've ignited the booster rockets of my soooouuuul! I'm on fiiiiiiiiiiire!!! I am Solomon Starbuck, astronaut! A cosmic hero chosen by the universe itself! This is no time to be whimpering and crying! I can't let you and Clay down!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Balderdash.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">The sun... the moon... all of space is calling me! Solomon "Sol" Starbuck! Ready for launch! Begin the countdown! Five!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Four!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Three!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Two!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">LIFT OFF!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! I feel like I've witnessed an actual rocket launch!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! You did it! You broke Prosecutor Blackquill's grip over Mr. Starbuck!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't take the credit. It was all Mr. Starbuck. He pulled himself through.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. If you simpletons are done massaging one another's egos... No matter how positive your mood, my advantage remains unshakable. I have but to wait for the final guilty verdict. Isn't that right, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gah... <thought>I can't let up now! I have to stop Blackquill! I have to see this through... Mr. Starbuck just has to make it back into space! I won't allow Clay's dream to remain unfulfilled! I've got to destroy Blackquill's argument somehow! Think, Justice! Think! If the only people at Launch Pad 1 were Clay and Mr. Starbuck... ...and if Clay was already dead by the time this footage was taken... ...then the only person who could've killed him is Mr. Starbuck. So the only way to counter Blackquill's argument is... ... if I can prove that Clay was still alive when they arrived at the boarding lounge. In which case, I should be able to find some contradiction in the evidence itself! Now, let's see... About this data that we just received... This supposedly proves that Mr. Starbuck dropped Clay's body in Launch Pad 1. But if I'm going to prove that false, then there must be something I can use here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough of this farce, Your Baldness! Let's have your verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Then I guess it simply means that it's faulty, as evidence goes.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You will explain what you mean, Justice-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's simple. This evidence contradicts the facts of this case. Take a look here at the detailed description and you'll see what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hope you have some evidence, Mr. Justice, because I don't see what's so contradictory!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor! Right away! This is the evidence that the oxygen tank report stands in contradiction to!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...If you think about it on a cosmic level, this world is full of inconsistencies! Wouldn't you agree that this evidence is just one of those mysteries of the universe?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, I wouldn't. But I am going to give you a cosmic penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Too bad he didn't take a more cosmic view of things and forgive me on that one...</thought> Your Honor! Please let me try that again! <thought>I think the problem must lie in the remaining oxygen in the two tanks... Mr. Starbuck's tank was 80 percent full, while Clay's was at 0 percent. Can I find something that contradicts this information?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And how does this evidence present a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The problem is this part here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Oh, um... I just thought it looked... problematic, you know? Don't tell me I'm the only one who thinks so!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're the only one. And you'll be the only one to receive this penalty, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ungh... <thought>One is the loneliest number... But now that I'm looking at it, I definitely see something strange in this footage.</thought> Your Honor! Please allow me to give that another try!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Note the remaining oxygen in Mr. Starbuck's tank as he carries Mr. Terran.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears to say 50.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, but according to the data, our client's tank had 80 percent remaining.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The oxygen in the tank increased?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see Your Honor finds it as strange as I do. It's bad enough that there is a contradiction, but the increase in oxygen is beyond illogical!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! You're absolutely right! What is going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I, too, find it odd that the oxygen remaining has increased. It would be as odd as if my rations were to increase. But what does that prove? It doesn't change the fact that it is the defendant carrying the victim's corpse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In that case, do you have an answer to this riddle of the mysteriously increasing oxygen? You'd better not disappoint, or I'll declare the inconsistency as mere equipment malfunction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Prosecutor Blackquill has a point. I suppose it could be a simple malfunction. Mr. Justice. If you cannot provide an adequate counterargument to this point... ...I'm afraid I must bring this trial to an end. So, do you think you can explain why the remaining oxygen level increased?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course I can! <thought>The thing to do at a time like this is turn my thinking around! Mr. Starbuck has no memory of it, but he claims to have carried Clay. So this man with the 50 on his tank ought to be Mr. Starbuck. But, if anything, the display on his oxygen tank should have shown an 80. This is a clear contradiction between the report and the security footage. So what I should be asking is not, "Why did the oxygen level increase?"... ...but, "What had to have happened to make it LOOK like it increased?" Am I making some kind of mistake in my base assumptions here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? We're waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor! I'm ready to answer! This is why the remaining oxygen appears to have increased!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe they were escaping in the opposite direction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The opposite direction? Like how rewinding a video makes things look like they're repairing themselves? ...In which case, I think the one who's going to need rewinding is you, Mr. Justice. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I'd rather fast-forward through this myself... "What had to have happened to make it LOOK like it increased?" Wait a minute! I think I've got it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The answer is simple. The tanks were damaged! Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't think the problem is with the tanks, but with your eyes, Justice-dono. It's written in the report that the tanks were functioning properly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! It's amazing how diligent reporting can come back to bite you in the rear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And it's amazing how your diligent negligence can come back to bite you in the rear, too! Let this penalty remind you of the consequences of your actions!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ow, my aching rear... Let's try that again. "What had to have happened to make it LOOK like it increased?" Wait a minute! I think I've got it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if it was the other way around?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The other way around? Would you care to explain, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As you can see, Your Honor, both men had their helmets on in this footage. But it turns out, this is where our base assumptions went astray. We assumed that it was Mr. Starbuck helping Mr. Terran, but it was actually the other way around. It wasn't Mr. Starbuck helping Mr. Terran at all. It was Mr. Terran who was helping Mr. Starbuck to the boarding lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I-It was whaaaaaaaaaaaat?! Order! Order! Mr. Justice! You mean to tell me that the person on the right in this image is the victim, Clay Terran?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the only way the riddle of the increasing oxygen level can be solved, Your Honor. At this point in time, the remaining oxygen in the victim's tank was at 50 percent. And when the victim was found in the boarding lounge, his tank was at 0 percent.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! There's nothing contradictory about the oxygen level decreasing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This means Mr. Terran was alive as they made their escape to the lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How short your memory is. Have you forgotten what you yourself proposed? Even if the victim was alive at this point in time... ...how did he descend the ladder with his arms full?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's true that we don't know how they got down the ladder. I suppose that matter needs further investigating. But we have proven that Mr. Terran was alive when he reached the boarding lounge. This fact alone shatters your claims... ...and opens up the possibility that the victim could've been killed by a third party!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAWR!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There were two people who claimed to be the first on the scene. But can we truly trust their statements?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see. The two people were Detective Candice Arme and Yuri Cosmos, right? You think that one of them might have given a false statement to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, it's certainly possible. We might have to do a little more digging.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we'll have to hear the testimony of these first two people on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Score!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Come to think of it, Detective Arme should be here in court right now. Bailiff, could you please show Detective Arme to the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Tonate:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's the meaning of this? We're in the middle of a trial here!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">P-Please remain calm and listen carefully. Someone has reactivated the bomb! The bomb was diffused, but, but, but...... I-It's about to explode!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">EX-</line>
<line speaker="Athena">PL-</line>
<line speaker="Judge">OOOOOOOOODE!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A bomb? Now?!</line>
<line speaker="Man">-- Aaaagh! Everybody run!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">-- Eeeeek! I don't want to die!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no! Everybody's panicking!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Headless chickens with a death wish, the lot of you! Calm yourselves afore all else!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">C'mon, Apollo! Let's get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what about Mr. Starbuck's dream? And who will carry out Clay's final wish? I don't care what happens to me! I'm not letting some bomb blow the truth up forever! I... I... I refuse to let things end here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, this is no time to be dramatic! If we don't get out of here now, we're gonna die! C'MON! THIS WAY!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! Ouch! Let me go!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">J-Juniper? <thought>She hasn't evacuated yet?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Eeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">J-Juniper! Are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! No! Not that way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your gall knows no bounds. It's shocking, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You stand there, brazenly objecting to perfectly factual statements... One does not see such shameless behavior that often.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for our shameless attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, no. Looks like Blackquill is turning the judge against me</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I object to you on personal grounds. The sole contradiction lies in what your faulty logic dreamt up just now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. The defense will think twice before making such erroneous statements!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It seems that statement didn't particularly conflict with the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...........................Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What do you make of this objection of his?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I don't know if I should, um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I've no patience for vagaries. Now, answer my question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir! The defense's objection was clearly misguided!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bravo. Nicely done.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. It seems our misguided attorne has earned himself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Erk... I better look before I leap next time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I can't flag any inconsistencies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there haven't been any contradictions in the testimony so far... That can mean only one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Time to press the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. We'll have to work to get the testimony we need. Let's press the heck out of any statements that stick out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... There has to be a contradiction here somewhere. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Too bad I'm drawing a blank.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There was a statement that I thought was a little strange, but... ...I wouldn't bet my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........And which statement would that be? Since I'm the one betting my life on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee hee. Okay, if you must know, I'll show you the one I'm thinking of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to swallow my pride and let her lend a hand.</thought> <thought>There must be an inconsistency in the testimony Athena's pointing out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Solomon Starbuck...</line>
</xml>