<xml>
<title>The Return of the Great Departed Soul</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This set of scales is supposed to be the symbol of a defence lawyer, I think. And it's set on a background of a sunflower design. ...Or was it a dandelion? ...Or a chrysanthemum, perhaps... .........Well anyway, no one should be judged on their knowledge of flowers...or lack of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The name of the armband's owner is very finely embroidered here. 'Kazuma Asogi'... One day, when I'm back in Japan and I've earned my official law qualification there... ...I'll wear one band on each arm. ...That should make me a very well-balanced lawyer, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't believe it's been six months since I was last allowed to work in court. And now here I am, back at the Old Bailey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah! M-Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good morning, Professor Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I don't understand! It doesn't make any sense! The atmospheric pressure in here is off the charts! I've never felt anything like it! It's, it's crushing me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I feel it every time I'm here. That...gravity.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well, this is Britain's highest court... But are you telling me it's filled with some kind of device that can actually control air pressure?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think it's probably all in the mind.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah. Yes, well...you won't let me down, will you, Mr Naruhodo? I'm counting on you in today's trial...to save my life! To save the secret of my super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis machine from being made public!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I understand. <thought>I know what I have to do. I have to establish that the explosion two days ago was nothing more than an unfortunate accident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Well, I'm sure there's nothing to worry about, really. Justice will prevail!</line>
<line speaker="???">My commiserations, Mr Naruhodo. You appear to have been lumbered with a most tiresome case here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes! I didn't expect to see you here.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That was very mean, Runo, leaving me alone at home with Hurley. It took me at least an hour to wake him!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah... Oh... Ah... Is it...? Are you...? HEEEEEERLOCK SHOOOOOOLMES?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, sir. I am he. Heeeeeerlock Shoooooolmes.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, I've heard all about your exploits, even whilst living in Germany.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah yes. Randst Magazine is on sale in Germany, too.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">This month's instalment was sublime! Your deduction in 'The Adventure of Silver Blaze' was wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, a memorable case indeed. It concerned a snake, I seem to recall.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No, that was 'The Speckled Band.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, thank you for coming. I do appreciate your support.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sorry to disappoint you, my dear fellow, but I'm afraid I can't stay.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have urgent business at Madame Tusspells.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...your waxwork job?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No no, the waxwork abduction, of course. Madame has engaged my services.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, so you're trying to get to the bottom of that ransom note, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The week's wages depend on it! ...As does the safe return of the waxwork, naturally. As such, I intend to give it my undivided attention.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, never mind then. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, with my skills of observation and reasoning, resolving the matter will be as easy as proverbial pie. I shall return forthwith. For until I solve the case, I shall have no money to afford a pie of any description.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, then you must absolutely give it your full attention, Hurley!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Quite, Iris, quite. But life is riddled with irony, you know. Whenever I give something my full attention, I have a quite insatiable desire for a pie. One of the universe's intractable mysteries, you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh yes! Quite! Definitely! Absolutely! I totally understand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Is someone a little starstruck?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I wish you the very best of luck, Professor Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh! Ah! Ooh! Why, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Before I depart, Mr Naruhodo...a word in your ear, if you please?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...? What's this about?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As you have remarkably little grounding in science, I feel I ought to inform you... As compelling as this 'super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis' hypothesis may be... ...a practical implementation, such as was attempted by the professor at the Great Exhibition, is quite impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but the professor said the demonstration was a success!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, it would appear that he fervently believes it was.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've read Professor Bunnybrain's paper about it, too, Runo. And I have to say... ...I'm sure it can't be done. It could barely be done theoretically, let alone practically.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he's completely barking up the wrong tree?</thought> But how could an experiment that had no possibility of succeeding in fact succeed? That's contradictory.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And it's that contradiction that will be at the heart of the trial, I've no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now, I must hurry along. I wish you the best of luck, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">See you later, Hurley! Well, it looks like you're on your own today, Runo. But chin up! You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! What about you, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah, no, I'm afraid I can't help. I have something I need to do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hehe! It's going to be a big surprise for you when you find out what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... <thought>That sounds ominous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel for the Defence! And the defendant! Court is about to be in session. Make your way into the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're on our way! <thought>An experiment that the laws of science say can't possibly succeed... ...and a scientist who's convinced that it did. That's the riddle you have to unlock here, Ryunosuke! That's the key to this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session. We are sitting today for the public trial of Professor Albert Harebrayne. I now call upon the counsels for the prosecution and defence to declare their willingness to proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence is... The defence is ready, My Lord! ......... <thought>I'm six months out of practice. And what's more... ...I'm without Susato-san today.</thought> ......... <thought>Ugh... Is it just my imagination, or does the air in here feel even more oppressive than usual?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... ...I must say I recollect the victim of this case all too well. Mr Odie Asman.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Mr Asman was well known as a financier...though that was merely a front for his diverse criminal activities.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was only a month ago that the man appeared in court prosecuted by you, Lord van Zieks. But the jury unanimously found him not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because every member of the jury had been bribed, by the sound of it. These powerful London criminals are prepared to go to extreme lengths to keep their freedom.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But two days ago, on 21st October, Mr Asman met his end. The work of the Reaper, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... If that is how Your Lordship would describe divine retribution... But the fact remains that Mr Asman's death... ...was a direct result of the actions of the accused, Professor Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Now, ladies and gentlemen of the jury... You have been selected at random to represent the will of the people. Are the six of you ready to fulfil your societal duty?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I'm most gratified to have been selected to carry out this important civic duty, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">To have a man's fate in the palm of one's hand... Oh gosh! Oh golly! It sends shivers down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Science experiments, magic, conjuring tricks, courtroom trials... All are nothing more than performances.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Any spurious scholar that defiles the reputation of science deserves to hang!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Um, we 'ave to listen to what's said on both sides 'the fence, and um...then settle on one... That's it, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">......... Wasn't like this in my day! Wasn't like this at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>That's...that's... ...the police killer Ottermole look-alike...again. And he's as exhausted as ever, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, as I'm sure you are all aware... ...the incident we are here to judge today tragically took place at the Great Exhibition, shortly after its opening.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Though the death toll could have been far worse. With the exception of the victim, no one was killed. Nevertheless, the dream of the science being exhibited rapidly turned into a nightmare for the spectators.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A tragic turn of events. And as such, the eyes of all London- No, of the whole world will be on this trial. It is our duty to reach a swift and just conclusion, I feel. So...your opening statement please, Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At the heart of this incident... ...is technology never before demonstrated anywhere in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One of science's latest developments, I take it? The government is keen to capitalise on the Great Exhibition to improve Britain's technological advantage.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The technology being demonstrated by the accused was described as 'super-high-voltage instantaneous kinesis'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's designed to 'disassemble' human subjects using extremely high-voltage electricity... ...and 'beam' them instantly to another location where they are subsequently reassembled.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is...is such a thing even within the realms of possibility?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Well I don't believe it, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Disassembling people with electricity? My goodness! How shocking!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Hah! The whole idea is absurd! The hypothesis would never stand up to scrutiny!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sir, I believe you are a fellow of the Royal Society, are you not? An expert in your field?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I am, and my word on the matter can be considered final. Instantaneous kinesis is poppycock!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So this expert and Mr Sholmes are in agreement. It's impossible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the prosecution's view on the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... The prosecution would assert... ...that the accused's instantaneous kinesis demonstration was a success.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">What rot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The professor's hypothesis is currently under investigation by the British government. If it is deemed to have merit, a substantial research grant would be made available. The accused made use of the invention built on his new hypothesis to take Mr Asman's life... ...in order to be the sole benefactor of the grant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This disastrous demonstration was no accident. It was carefully designed from the outset to end the life of the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Lord van Zieks. The prosecution's stance is clear. But you will now bring forth witnesses to substantiate your claims.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Gladly, My Lord. Bailiff! Show the first witnesses to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Witnesses, state your names and occupations for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, sir! Tobias Gregson, Detective Inspector at Scotland Yard's homicide division. I was on duty at the demonstration on the day in question and in charge of the followin' investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Albert Harebrayne! S-S-Scientist!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You were born in England, but have been carrying out research in Germany in recent years. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes. Yes, that's right. After graduating from university here in Britain, I went to work in Germany...and made an amazing discovery! Which is what brought me back! I had to demonstrate my incredible hypothesis at the Great Exhibition!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">What you demonstrated was incredible alright. An incredible explosion!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But the science! The science was a success! The instantaneous kinesis worked! E-Everyone saw it! They must have done! Yes, there was the terrible accident, but... ...the demonstration of my hypothesis was a success!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well, that much is undeniable. As shown in this photograph taken by the Forensic Investigation Team.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This was taken inside the Crystal Tower, I take it? The centrepiece of the exhibition, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">That's right, My Lord. Seems the victim rammed straight into it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, I see... Very well, submit the photograph as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">As the court's heard, the victim of the incident was Mr Odie Asman. There have been a number of allegations made against the man, but puttin' them aside for the time bein'... ...he was the man who financed the research for the experiment and the demonstration itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So to summarise the situation... ...the defendant is accused of taking the life of the man who funded his work. Would that be correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But couldn't it be... ...that the explosion was caused by some malfunction in the apparatus used for the demonstration?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">That's right! That must be it! My splendid machine... My poor, splendid machine...</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You saw it yesterday, didn't you? We can't even examine the wreckage thanks to the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! The wreckage?! THE WRECKAGE?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that being the case, how can the facts be established? How can it possibly be determined whether this was an accident or a deliberate and malicious act?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Extremely simply, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Isn't that right, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Wha...? Sorry? ME?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No. Your neighbour.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, sir! It was murder, plain and simple. Anyone could state that with complete certainty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! <thought>How can he possibly think that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Inspector. I think we had better proceed to formal testimony. You will explain to the court on what grounds you claim this experiment to have been a front for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The corpse that went crashin' through the Crystal Tower had a broken neck.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I made a minor miscalculation in the angle of the beam projection, that's all! That was my mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">But the post-mortem examination revealed another injury. A fatal wound.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... An extraordinary business... In addition to suffering a broken neck, the victim was stabbed in the heart?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Information I would really like to have heard from someone other than the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The coroner says death would have been all but instant from a wound like that.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You could say, in fact... ...that the victim was killed twice by the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No, no and no! That couldn't be further from the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I have here the experiment plan document that was submitted to the security team. The victim stood himself inside somethin' called 'the birdcage', ready to be 'beamed' instantly... ...to the second level of the Crystal Tower, about twenty-five yards away.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The experiment did not go according to plan, however. As the machine was put into operation, there was a large explosion. The blast caused the beam transmitter to point higher than intended. Accordingly, the kinesis resulted in the birdcage materialising in mid-air... ...from where it subsequently fell, crashing through the glass of the Crystal Tower's large round window.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word... One assumes the victim's neck was broken upon impact with the tower, then?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'm, I'm so sorry! I didn't mean for this to happen! The machine was just too powerful! But honestly! Really! I swear! It was just an accident! A terrible accident!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Unfortunately, that excuse can't save you.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">No, not considerin' the sharp murder weapon that pierced the victim's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">M-Murder weapon?! What are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This is the autopsy report submitted by the coroner. The prosecution would like it entered into the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your request is granted, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I was there in person, you know. I saw the whole ludicrous performance. And the only other person on the stage with Mr Asman was that disgraceful excuse for a scientist!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Then really, by all accounts it must have been him.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Hmph. Hard to think otherwise, really.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Counsel for the Defence...proceed with the cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, yes, My Lord! <thought>I need to focus here... It's been a while!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The corpse that went crashin' through the Crystal Tower had a broken neck.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you suggesting that's because he fell from a considerable height?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Exactly. Which highlights somethin' else about this whole rum business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The fact that the instantaneous kinesis itself was a success.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">After the explosion, the cage with the fella inside suddenly appeared out of nowhere in mid-air.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So although the experiment ended in disaster, the so-called instantaneous kinesis did actually occur.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Remind us, Professor, what was the cause of the fatal disaster?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I made a minor miscalculation in the angle of the beam projection, that's all! That was my mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the angle of projection is critical, is it? And you calculated it yourself? Personally?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Absolutely! The calculation is far too complicated for anyone but me to carry out!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Only, you got it wrong, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! That's right! That's the point! The calculation is so complicated, even I can make a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do people fall for that brazen confidence? ...I should try it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I took into account the subject's height and weight, the wind direction, the ambient temperature... I considered every possible variable! So I just don't understand how this could have happened!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously then, you had to include the weight of the clothes Mr Asman was wearing at the time, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah. Crackling comets! The answer should have been three!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So much for safety first. The three must be for safety third...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">But the post-mortem examination revealed another injury. A fatal wound.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Another fatal injury, you say? That doesn't make any sense!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I didn't think I'd have to spell this out, but here we go... Just because there were two fatal wounds doesn't mean I'm sayin' the victim had two lives to lose, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Too right.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Obviously at first, we thought the bloke had died due to his spine snappin' in half as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you're saying that's not the case?!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You'll get your answer once I've finished my fish an' chips...if you don't keep buttin' in every few seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But we all know that's a bottomless bag...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The victim plummeted thirty feet into a glass tower. It would be reasonable to assume that as the cause of death.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Right. That's what we all thought. But it was a red herring, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">There was a lesion in his chest where he'd clearly been stabbed by somethin' sharp right in the heart!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence knew nothing of this crucial information!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution received this report from the Forensic Investigation Team only this morning. That was the first we knew of it as well. I can only apologise for the impossibility of informing the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sarcastic AND insincere? Thanks...</thought> So, what was the nature of this sharp object?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Among the accused's tools that were in use at the demonstration, one is of particular interest. This.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, that would appear to be some kind of screwdriver, wouldn't it, Couns-</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AHAHAHAHAAAAAAAAAH! There he is! My trusty little companion, Andrew!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Andrew. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, do you know each other already? He's one of my dear friends...like all my tools! I've named them all, you know. We're one big, happy family!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Andrew is my flat-head screwdriver, of course. His brother, Michael, is a cross-head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that your beloved 'Andrew' has a red stain on his shank.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! That, that isn't...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's blood, beyond all reasonable doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">And that's not all. The long, sharp shape of this Andrew fellow is completely consistent with the victim's wound.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! The court will enter this 'friend' of the defendant as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So one of Professor Harebrayne's tools is the murder weapon...? Great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence knew nothing of this crucial information!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution received this report from the Forensic Investigation Team only this morning. That was the first we knew of it as well. I can only apologise for the impossibility of informing the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sarcastic AND insincere? Thanks...</thought> So, what was the nature of this sharp object?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Among the accused's tools that were in use at the demonstration, one is of particular interest. This.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, that would appear to be some kind of screwdriver, wouldn't it, Couns-</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AHAHAHAHAAAAAAAAAH! There he is! My trusty little companion, Andrew!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Andrew. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, do you know each other already? He's one of my dear friends...like all my tools! I've named them all, you know. We're one big, happy family!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Andrew is my flat-head screwdriver, of course. His brother, Michael, is a cross-head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that your beloved 'Andrew' has a red stain on his shank.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! That, that isn't...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's blood, beyond all reasonable doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">And that's not all. The long, sharp shape of this Andrew fellow is completely consistent with the victim's wound.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This...is blood. Mr Asman's, no doubt. This is the problem with looking at murder weapons...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've seen this unusually shaped handle before. It's the same screwdriver that was lodged in the grille on the floor of the kinesis machine. <thought>Which could be important information, so I should definitely make a note of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no question considering the unusual shape of the handle... This is the screwdriver that was poking through the floor of the kinesis machine. It looks a little bit like a capital 'A'. <thought>For 'Andrew' I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">So the victim was killed before he went anywhere. And this fella's the only one who could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What grounds do you have for saying that?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Hah! D'you really need to ask? There were only two people on that public experimentation stage, in front of the whole crowd.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The victim, Mr Odie Asman, and the accused, Professor Harebrayne. And we know for certain that before the experiment, the victim was alive.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">That's right. I saw him with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Furthermore... ...following the explosion and 'kinesis', nobody went anywhere near the body.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">In other words, only someone else on stage with the victim could possibly have done it. And Albert Harebrayne is the only bloke who fits the bill. Unless you've got some other bright idea, sunshine? In which case, let's hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne! Do you have some information that may be relevant here?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah! Sorry! SORRY! I was just calculating the optimum coefficient of electrolysis to separate molecules in the human body...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And the witness stand is the best place for that?</thought> It seemed as though you might have something to say? About Inspector Gregson's last remark.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah! AHAHAHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Yes! Yes, that's right! Of course! He just said that nobody else could have done it, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yeah, that's right. Who else could have stabbed the victim, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I DON'T KNOW! ...But! There's no way that I could possibly have stabbed Mr Asman as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Explain, please, Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Of course. This cold-hearted policeman may not be aware, I suppose... ...but humans are warm-blooded mammals, with blood running continuously through their veins.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I had heard...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Then surely you see! If I'd plunged something the size of Andrew into the man's chest... ...the whole stage would have been a bloodbath! No, a blood swimming pool!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aah...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But thousands of Londoners were watching me at the time. And yet not one of them claims to have seen a swimming pool of blood!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Well, no...I suppose not...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">You see?! Not one!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Hm... True, I didn't see anything like that...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well done, Professor! That was a great counter-argument!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Pray forgive the discourtesy if I savour a drop from my hallowed chalice to accompany my old friend's adducing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Here's to you, Albert!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, you're too kind, Barok! But I'm really not a patch on you...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, you're not.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You've neglected to mention one crucial possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I have?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A particular situation in which very little bleeding would result from a stab wound.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Inspector, enlighten the court, please.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where are they going with this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You will amend your formal testimony now, Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My learned friend's silence is your answer, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>Can't a man have a moment to think?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">The weapon the victim was stabbed with must have been left in his body whilst he was beamed through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why would you think that, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">With any wound, it's only when you pull the weapon out that profuse bleedin' occurs. Whilst it's still lodged in the body, it acts as a stopper of sorts, for want of a better word.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You don't need a medical degree to be aware of this fact. It's common knowledge for any investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, where's Susato-san when you need her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gregson">If you ask me, this bloke masked what he was doin' from view with his body before stabbin' Asman in the chest. Then he beamed the victim off the stage with his fancy device, the screwdriver still where he planted it.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I, I would never do such a thing! Not to my precious tools! I would never use them for such dirty work! You only use tools for their intended purpose! That's common knowledge for any scientist!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...The fact remains, the lack of blood at the scene can easily be explained. As the prosecution has demonstrated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's all the testimony I have to work with... I had no idea the victim had been stabbed. That changes everything... Did van Zieks keep that to himself until now on purpose, to gain the advantage? Oh well...I suppose all I can do is press these witnesses for as much new information as possible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You say that while the weapon remains in the body, there's very little bleeding... Is that unequivocal?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Look, there was no blood on the experimentation stage, even though that's where the fellow was stabbed. The only explanation for that is if the screwdriver was still in his body, stoppin' any heavy bleedin'.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's common medical knowledge, my learned friend. Even on your side of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Yes, but about this screwdriver... The thing is, we actually saw it at the scene ourselves. On the experimentation stage.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was on the floor by the wreckage of the machine, poking through a metal grille. I went to pick it up, but the detective here stopped me. Isn't that right, Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah, well, um... Now you come to mention it, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Inspector, are we to understand that you permitted the defence counsel to investigate? That you contravened the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Eh? No! Not at all! I, I wouldn't do that! I just let him look, nothin' more! I was very clear he wasn't to touch a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's true. This screwdriver was in plain sight on the stage. But it shouldn't have been, should it?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Wh-What are you gettin' at?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If this tool had still been in the victim's body when the victim was beamed away by the machine... ...then it shouldn't have still been on the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right! It should have been beamed across to the Crystal Tower along with Mr Asman... ...and been found still lodged in the victim's chest!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ugh... UWAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! ...How do you explain this, Inspector?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I...well...um... I don't...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks as though everything that the victim had on his person moved with him when he was 'beamed'. If the screwdriver was still in his chest when the instantaneous kinesis occurred... ...obviously that should have been beamed to the destination as well!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">You...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is a strange situation... Even though people are saying that this instantaneous kinesis is a scientific impossibility... ...we're still basing arguments on the assumption that it did actually take place. Alright. Time to tighten the screws here...</thought> My Lord! If the prosecution is unable to explain this inconsistency in its argument... ...we can only conclude that the testimony given in support cannot be relied upon!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Lord van Zieks is stumped!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Do you have something to say, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes...I knew it... It bears out... The equations hold... Mr Naruhodo! ...DON'T WORRY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...About what?!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Without delving into the details, there is no inconsistency!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Even if Andrew had been lodged in Mr Asman's chest... ...my trusty tool wouldn't have moved. Andrew remaining on the stage is consistent with my calculations!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It would seem your illusions have been...shattered. Clearly we should hear the accused's explanation. ...Or should I say, this brilliant scientist's explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Just when I'd found an inconsistency in the prosecution's argument... Scientists...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! The defendant will testify again. Provide us with the scientific explanation as to why the inconsistency asserted by the defence fails to hold!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">In the name of Apollo, I will, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">To be clear, I'm still at the stage of gathering data in my research.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... So, the thrust of your testimony, Professor, is...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...That based upon his hypothesis, metal objects cannot be moved by this method of instantaneous kinesis.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In other words...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words, since the screwdriver is made of metal, even if it remained lodged in the victim's chest... ...its subsequent discovery on the stage despite the victim being found elsewhere is not an inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And therefore...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And therefore Professor Albert Harebrayne could still have been the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">My great hypothesis holds, you see! We, we had to make the cage used to contain the subject from wood for that very reason.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was not addressing you, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...Professor Harebrayne...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whose side are you on here?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I don't take sides, Mr Naruhodo! No no no! My only interest lies in upholding my hypothesis! I'm a scientist, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Is he working for us or against us? It's very hard to tell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let's see how you cross-examine this testimony, my Nipponese friend.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, fire away, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">To be clear, I'm still at the stage of gathering data in my research.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yet your retort to my argument wasn't lacking in confidence in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">'No scientist can find the truth without first finding self-belief...' Those were the words of a certain scientist I hold in the very highest esteem!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you realise that disproving my argument puts you in a very precarious position, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">'No scientist should strive to protect himself more than he strives to protect the truth...' More words of the same great scientist, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Words that are causing me a lot of trouble. Who is this scientist?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'm afraid I couldn't tell you, Mr Naruhodo. But, but as soon as I remember the magnificent genius's name, you'll be the first to know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It...might be worth keeping the names of your idols to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You're wasting your breath, my learned friend. This scatterbrain even forgets my name at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So Lord van Zieks really did have a friend once. But I didn't notice Hell freezing over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">My hypothesis states the kinesis cannot transport metal, though. Hence the metal weapon would have stayed put.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your 'hypothesis' states it? So this isn't proven then?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No, no, of course not. It's merely a hypothesis. But a good one! Based upon thousands of calculations! But it is widely known that metals can't be decomposed by electrolysis. ...Yes! Of course! So I AM right! My hypothesis is clearly correct!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What is it about incriminating himself that makes this man so happy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">It's the whole reason that the birdcage is made of wood, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry. The birdcage?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, that's what I call the C. obtusa cage in which Mr Asman was placed for the kinesis.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, the jail cell in which the victim was detained. It does indeed seem to be made of a timber of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'll thank you not to refer to it as an instrument of incarceration, Your Lordship...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In short... ...any weapon lodged in the victim when he was beamed away by instantaneous kinesis... ...would have been left behind on the stage if it was made of metal. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! That's it! Yes yes yes! It all fits perfectly with the mathematical model!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the ultimate conclusion then... ...is that the defendant alone had the opportunity to inflict this fatal injury on the victim, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">'Ah!' indeed, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Someone beam me out of this nightmare...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">In other words, the point just raised by Mr Naruhodo isn't an inconsistency at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You seem to be pleased by that.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! Another example of my hypothesis holding true! But I sense some sarcasm, Mr Naruhodo. Are you not pleased?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I knew it. At the end of day, I'm the one responsible for Mr Asman losing his life. The advancement of science is no excuse! I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, you're quite right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell the court, did you have a close relationship with Mr Asman?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh, well no, not really. I mean, I'd only met him two or three times. And we only ever discussed my hypothesis and the project...and the research grant, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Mr Asman was the patron of my research. Without him, my work wouldn't have been possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How did you come to know Mr Asman in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">...A year ago now, a small provincial science journal published a little paper about my work.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a scientific journal? Good gracious, I should need new spectacles!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I might have had an extraordinary hypothesis and great promise, but at the time, I had no money. I, I had to eat tiny little meals at a tiny little café and drink watered-down water out of a tiny little glass... But...Mr Asman read the paper and came to visit me at my tiny little laboratory!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And offered you money to help fund your work?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Exactly! That's exactly what happened! I handled the theoretical side of things, and Mr Asman provided me with an engineer for the practical. ...And the three of us produced that fantastic machine together!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The machine that you brought to the Great Exhibition to demonstrate.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">We, we had to apply to the government for some sort of inspection to be allowed to exhibit, I think. I didn't understand all that side of things. Mr Asman took care of all of it. He was a wonderful man! Really, I owe him everything.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Now I have a duty to protect the incredible machine that we built together!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say that you built the machine together, does that mean that you were involved in its construction?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes! ...W-Well, not exactly... I'm not good with the practical side of machines myself. So the physical construction was done by an engineer.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Little remains of your creation now, though, following the explosion. Repair will no doubt be impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, yes, I realise that. But still... If, if someone were to gather all the broken parts, they could discover the secret of my hypothesis! But Mr Asman and I toiled over that machine for so long. We put our hearts and souls into it! I have to protect our work. So what's left of the machine must be kept safe! That's only fair! Because what happened was an accident!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's the extent of the testimony then... Thank goodness for that. I don't want him doing any more damage. He's already basically proven that he could have been the culprit. But it seems as though all he really cares about is defending his hypothesis. Still, I wonder... What if his hypothesis is just fundamentally flawed?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne, you say that according to your hypothesis... ...nothing made of metal can be beamed by instantaneous kinesis using the machine you made. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, that's right. Spot on! Exactly correct!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case...I'd ask you to have a look at this photograph that was taken at the scene. In particular, I'd like you to pay attention to the victim's face. You can clearly see that Mr Asman is wearing a pair of spectacles...with a metal rim.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">What? Metal? No... Metal can't... That's not... M-Metal? NOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've already established that the proposed murder weapon, the screwdriver, was found on the stage. However, if your hypothesis correctly predicted that outcome... ...it should also have predicted...that the metal-rimmed spectacles would be found in the same place!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">AAAAAAAAAAAAH! My hypothesis! MY HYPOTHESIIIIIIIIIS!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne, this isn't easy for me to say... ...but your hypothesis...is clearly flawed!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">UWAAAAAAAAAGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!! Counsel, what is the implication of this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If, on the day in question, the alleged instantaneous kinesis never actually took place... ...then it's entirely possible that the victim was killed somewhere other than on the stage. And in that case...someone other than the defendant could have been the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But, but my hypothesis! My hypothesis is sound! I proved it that day! The experiment was a success! The experiment was proof of all my work!</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If I could say something here, in my capacity as a fellow of the Royal Society...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, juror number four? Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">As a man of science, there's one thing I simply cannot abide... And that's a fraud who PRETENDS to be a fellow man of science!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">What? Wait! Great Scott! Are you suggesting my science is suspect?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It's just been disproved, hasn't it? In front of all of us. In other words, the whole demonstration was a complete nonsense from start to finish! Believe me, my fellow jurors, when I tell you that this man is a heel, a bounder and a fraud!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I say the wreckage of that machine should be stripped down and thoroughly examined!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Nooo! Never! That machine is the essence of my entire hypothesis! It's protected by the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">What the devil is that blasted act all about, eh? Who made up such a daft rule?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't like the way this seems to be going... What's the best way for me to help the professor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe I should watch and wait for the time being...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">My feeling is that the machine requires a thorough examination.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">But what about this 'special dispensation' that's been mentioned? Oh gosh...this is all too much.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If it's determined that the machine itself was the murder weapon, I think you'll find that act won't apply.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Of course it was the murder weapon! Anyone can see that, as plain as day!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">So we're all in agreement, are we? That the machine should be stripped?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>If, if I don't do something, they'll...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne has yet to perfect his invention! That would seem to be the case, yes. But even so...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Even so, what?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Going to such trouble and expense to create a fake machine to display in public... He would have absolutely no reason to do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If the government was foolish enough to have deemed the man's ridiculous notion plausible... ...he and his conspirators would have received a handsome sum indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">C-Conspirators?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">What would be the value of such a grant? Ten pounds?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">You're an order of magnitude out, madam. Five hundred pounds a YEAR!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Ooh arrrrrr! Ya could live 'andsome on that much for years!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The Society's noticed an increase in bogus public demonstrations in the field of science recently. And plenty of scientists arguing with each other to get the largest slice of the funding cake. People's greed is plenty motive enough for murder, I assure you!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">No no no! I haven't deceived anyone! Least of all the government! My hypothesis is sound! The science is sound! Please, you must believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah, Barok!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And therefore... ...the only person who could possibly have committed this murder...is the accused!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah. Barok...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Where is this heading? I have no idea...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My Lord, if I may...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution would like to summon new witnesses to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">New witnesses? What would be the nature of their involvement?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">They were spectators of the demonstration at the exhibition. Who were occupying special seats.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Eyewitnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the court grants the prosecution's request. I should very much like to hear from eyewitnesses to the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution's stance is clear. This experiment was no postiche. The accused killed the financier victim there on the public stage, before the very eyes of the spectators. Now, my learned friend...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! ...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's time for you to make your own stance clear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's clearly a flaw in the professor's hypothesis. I can definitely see that. But where does that leave me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">We shall take a short recess now. During which time, the prosecution will prepare its new witnesses to take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. In that case, court is adjourned for twenty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">M-Mr Naruhodo... ...what on earth were you playing at just now? Or rather... ...WHAT ON EARTH WERE YOU PLAYING AT ALL ALONG?! MY HYPOTHESIS! MY AMAZING HYPOTHESIS! You've been picking holes in it from the start!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But you promised me! You, you said you'd prove that dratted explosion was an accident, not murder. You said you'd keep my precious invention from falling into anyone else's hands! But all you've done so far is try to undermine me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Yes, I did make you a promise, you're right. I said that I'd believe in you and fight for your freedom to the very end. But I also told you I was no scientist. I don't understand your hypothesis. The fact is, there's an undeniable flaw in your logic, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah! But! If I just run through some equations... Yes, you see! It's because my work is incomplete!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps it is. Nevertheless...a man died as a consequence, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Oh. OOOOOOOOOH NOOOOOOOOO! ......... You're right. You're so right. It's all my fault... And I have no right to blame you for my failures. I'm a disaster! Not just as a scientist...but as a human being!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...that might be a little over the top.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">And while we're on the subject... ...wh-what about Barok? He's being awful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Claiming his old university friend to be a murderer, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">He's a disaster! Not just as a prosecutor...but as a human being! Oh! But no! Wait! He's the Reaper, isn't he? Perhaps he's not classified as Homo sapiens any more...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Glad that's cleared up...</thought> ......... Can I double-check something with you?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah. Yes? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The machine and demonstration you prepared... They were based entirely on your hypothesis, I presume? There was no...trickery involved?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I drew the plans for the machine with my very own hands. Every line was painstakingly drawn with the firm belief that science is the only future. So yes, it's true that my hypothesis hasn't reach [sic] maturity yet, but please, Mr Naruhodo...you must believe in it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Alright, Professor, I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel! Defendant! The prosecution's witnesses are ready to take the stand. Court is about to be in session again. Make your way into the courtroom, please!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It all hinges on that demonstration. If the professor's hypothesis is sound as he claims... ...it leaves him as the only person who could possibly have killed the victim. But on the other hand, Mr Sholmes was adamant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A practical implementation, such as was attempted by the professor at the Great Exhibition, is quite impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So really, what should I be trying to prove here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby reconvene the proceedings of this court. Counsels for the defence and prosecution, are you ready for the new witnesses to testify?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As is the defence, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Lord van Zieks... ...I believe these next witnesses saw the demonstration on the day in question with their own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Indeed they did. And as luck would have it, one of them is a police detective. ...So the testimony we are about to hear can be considered highly reliable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perfect. A detective of all people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution's stance remains unchanged. Though it ended in tragedy, the demonstration on the day in question was scientifically sound. And consequently... ...the sole person with the opportunity to have committed this act of murder... ...is the only other individual to have been present on the stage at the time: the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel. The prosecution's position is clear. So, bring forth your witnesses now.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Bailiff, show the witnesses in. The witnesses whose proximity to the incident on the day in question will clarify the truth unequivocally.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Witnesses, state your names and occupations for the court to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">My name is Balthazar Lune. I am...the impresario of all the hot-air balloons in vicinity of the esperimento stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Mein name ist Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond Ormstein. I have come to see ze Great Exhibition all ze vay from my home in Bohemia. ...I'm very rich.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Inspector Gina Lestrade, Scotland Yard. I'm a great detective. Even 'Erlock Sholmes agrees. I was on security duty at the exhibition...and I got to go up in one o' them balloons! It was amazin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gina...again. But she did mention that she'd seen the disaster from up in a balloon actually, didn't she? And she clearly loved every minute of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There were three balloons flying near the public experimentation stage when the incident occurred. Two of these witnesses were in one such balloon at the time, and saw events unfold from the skies above.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">You make it sound like they were in the clouds. It was only an altitude of circa sixty feet. Very low.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well ya can't see nuffin' if ya fly too 'igh, can ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sixty feet... About eighteen metres, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you for your introductions. Now, you will give your formal testimony for the court. Kindly describe exactly what you witnessed...especially those of you who had a vantage point above the stage!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">It was an incidente terribile. I am only grateful that my balloons were not damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">There's this huge bang from the stage, and then the next second, another bang in the sky beside us.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">And from amid ze smoke...a cage appeared out of nowhere!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">The cage, it fell from the sky like a stone. And crashed into the Crystal Tower!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I didn't get a good look inside the cage, but no one went near it after it crashed into the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A most extraordinary collective account, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could I just clarify something? There's a detail in the witnesses' testimony that I've not heard any mention of until now. Specifically, that there were two explosions?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...More precisely, two explosions in two separate places, yes. When the demonstration began, the balloon carrying the two witnesses was around...here. There were other balloons in the air nearby at the time carrying other passengers as well, to be clear. Then, as power was supplied to the machine for the demonstration, the first explosion occurred. The so-called 'birdcage' that contained the victim disappeared from the stage, and a moment later... ...the second explosion occurred, directly adjacent to the balloon carrying the witnesses. The birdcage appeared at the site of the explosion, subsequently to plummet down into the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">I voz very surprised. Suddenly a cage appeared before my eyes viz a person inside. Ze blast voz so hot, but I didn't vant to miss a sing, so I kept my eyes vide! ...I still have lots of money.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Precisely who is this curious infant?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm told he is a young noble of Bohemian royalty. Apparently he disguised himself in order to steal unnoticed into the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, I am here in London on a sightseeing trip viz my elementary school.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We will have the benefit of a child's point of view in the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do we really need that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ven I remove my mask, zis is vot I look like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, I see. A delightful face, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, everybody says so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Great disguise, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...The point is, the testimony of these witnesses further substantiates the facts for the court. Namely, that despite ending in an explosion, instantaneous kinesis was successfully demonstrated. And furthermore, that until the arrival of the police, no one approached the Crystal Tower where the victim fell. Therefore, only the accused, who was with Mr Asman on the stage, could possibly have committed the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, thank you, Counsel. The prosecution's views on the matter are quite clear. So, the defence's cross-examination now, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">It was an incidente terribile. I am only grateful that my balloons were not damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There were three balloons flying above the experimentation stage at the time, I understand?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si, si. All three of them, my bellissimi bambini. They are very popular, signor. Some people will pay ten pounds for one ride.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ten pounds?! That's more than my annual stipend!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Twenty pounds a month. Zat is my pocket money.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Royals have all the luck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">I got up there for free, I did. Played the old 'I work for 'Er Majesty's Police' card, ya know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Detectives have all the luck...</thought> If they're so popular, why would you only be operating such a small number of balloons, though?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Because...if I have too many in the skies, they could crash into each other.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The operators for the balloons were decided by lots, with each operator manning a particular area.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si! And the zone above public sperimentation stage is the most profitable! The other impresarios, they hate me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, witness. I think the court has a clear picture of the arrangements for balloon rides at the exhibition. Perhaps we could hear more about what you actually witnessed of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right! I can fill you in there, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">There's this huge bang from the stage, and then the next second, another bang in the sky beside us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you actually saw the accident happen from up in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yup! Innit amazin' wot a detective gets to do, eh? I'm tellin' ya, 'Oddo, bein' a lawyer's a mug's game. You should join the force an' we can go flyin' together!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You know me so well...</thought> Yes, well, anyway... Could you tell us exactly what you saw, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Everyfin'! We saw everyfin', cos we were up above it all. That dodgy cove climbin' into that cage, an' that dodgy professor pullin' all them levers... An' that's when it 'appened! That's when there was that massive bang an' the cage disappeared! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...you are describing the moment the subject's body was decomposed by the electricity, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I didn't know wot to make of it. But then there was another bang! Right in me ear! I looked round, an' there was a huge great fireball right next to us in the sky! An' there was nuffin' there before! An' wot appears out the flames? The cage, that's wot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, er...Master Gotts! Does your memory of the day differ?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">......... Mein teacher at elementary school said zat ven you meet somevun for ze first time... ...you should alvays use zer full name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, um...what was it again?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond Ormstein.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just the four names then...? The point is, do you have something to say? Something to add in response to Detective Gina Lestrade's last remark, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! Get it right, 'Oddo! It's Inspector Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why does everyone have a problem with how I address them at the moment?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gotts">......... Zat is not vot I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, zere voz a second explosion and it voz right beside our balloon. Zat is true. But I'm sure-</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Which is wot I said, innit? One minute there was nuffin' there, the next a massive explosion!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Mein teacher at elementary school said zat ven somevun else is speaking... ...if you are rude enough to interrupt...you vill have ze most awful life imaginable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are all Bohemians brought up to be so full of joy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Just before ze second explosion happened next to our balloon, I clearly vitnessed... ...a green balloon flying in ze sky.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A green balloon?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? You wot? I never saw nuffin' like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vell I did! I saw it! And you can't say I didn't! I vill complain to ze Consul! I vill cry and scream! My testimony is ze truth! I am Bohemian prince! You cannot say it's a lie! Zat is not allowed!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">...Tsk, playin' the bleedin' royalty card, are ya? Typical.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the orphan who likes to remind people she works for 'Her Majesty's Police'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, young man, I must ask you to amend your formal testimony. In the interests of cordial national relations between Great Britain and Bohemia...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...and that description sounds like the moment after the man was 'beamed' instantaneously through space.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's mind-blowin', innit?! But that's the twentieth century for ya, I reckon!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So the people who actually saw the demonstration with their own eyes... ...really believe they saw something miraculous taking place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gotts">And from amid ze smoke...a cage appeared out of nowhere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you're saying that you witnessed the actual moment that the instantaneous kinesis took place?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">During zis stay in London, I have seen many extraordinary sings. Ze Great Exhibition itself, zis instantaneous kinesis, big explosions, ze British courtrooms and strange creatures.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Strange creatures?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, you. A most unusual creature from ze East.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh yes, but I see princes wearing masks every day of the week.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Did you also see the moment that the cage materialised, Mr Lune?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">No no. I did not see the esplosione myself. However...</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">It voz not ze sky zat exploded. It voz a green balloon zat woz next to ours at ze time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A green balloon, you say? Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Of course I am sure! I am a proud Bohemian prince! All zese questions are making me boring.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think you mean 'bored'.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ach, English is very annoying! Ze language of my countrymen is far superior.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Ragazzo, it is very wrong to lie.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Lie?!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Flying balloons never explode. For the same reason the planets never explode. It is logico!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Please tell me that doesn't mean logical...</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">If you insult me, you insult all of Bohemia!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Ma dai!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">I vill have ze army come and shoot all of your stupid balloons out of ze sky! All of zem!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">......... ...Here you are, Your Highness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If only all international incidents were so easily resolved...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Now that peaceful relations have been restored here in the courtroom, perhaps we could return to the testimony? Did you also see the moment that the cage materialised, Mr Lune?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">No no. I did not see the esplosions myself. However...</line>
<line speaker="Lune">The cage, it fell from the sky like a stone. And crashed into the Crystal Tower!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you see that actually happen?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Eh, no, in reality I did not. I saw after it hit the tower. There was a grande confusione around the stage. I ran to see what had happened. I was terrorised by the idea that one of my balloons had crashed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I suppose they are his livelihood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lune">But when I looked up to the sky, all my precious balloons were still there!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I saw it, though. I saw it slam into the tower! After all, I am a detective now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then tell us what you saw...Inspector Lestrade.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's wot I like to 'ear!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I didn't get a good look inside the cage, but no one went near it after it crashed into the tower.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was it you who gave the order to keep people away?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Use yer 'ead, 'Oddo! 'Ow could it 'ave been me? I was up in a balloon, weren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So cos I weren't available, it was the boss who 'ad to leg it over there. 'E was gettin' shoved an' kicked all over by the panickin' spectators as 'e tried to seal off the scene. It was a real sight to behold, I can tell ya! Amazin'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Inspector Gregson...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">So anyway, I couldn't see the cage that well cos of all the smoke. And I didn't really wanna see, to be honest. I was scared out me wits...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Keep it together, Inspector...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The prosecution really is asserting that the demonstration was genuine... But what if it was actually some kind of switch-around trick instead? That would mean that the victim was never actually on the stage in the first place. The two explosions would have thrown everyone watching into a panic for sure. I think I need to find out more about what exactly people saw at the time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Lune, in your testimony... ...you said that all three of the balloons you had operating at the time were undamaged.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si. That is correct. If they had been caught in the esplosiones, it would have been terribile.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder...if you might know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Ah...I think it may be... Si, part of a balloon. A burnt piece of the fabric of the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? The envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Pardon. That is the large, round part of the balloon which becomes filled with hot air. It is made from very thick fabric lined with rubber. You do not want it to rip when you are in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Just as I thought...</thought> This piece of cloth was found near the experimentation stage. In other words, as Master Gotts testified... ...a green balloon did indeed explode that day.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If all the balloons in the sky above the experimentation stage belonged to you, Mr Lune... ...then your statement that they were all undamaged clearly contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">NOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Causing the balloon to explode? Yes, eminently plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">An unfortunate traffic accident, as it were. But it changes nothing about the pertinent facts.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lune">This, I cannot accept!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not, Mr Lune?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">You are suggesting that I am a liar! That persons died in a balloon incidente!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There's no need to get 'fired up', Mr Lune. The victim was the sole fatality that day.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">That's right! And I prove it! Balthazar Lune is not a liar! There was no such balloon in the sky! It is non possible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're saying it's impossible? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This court has more important matters to discuss than the number of balloons that were operating that day.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">AIIIIIIEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we can't ignore the fact that nobody appears to have known anything about this other balloon until now! My Lord! The defence calls for further testimony from Mr Lune!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur. There is clearly more to the truth here than meets the eye. It's imperative that we clear up the issue of this phantom balloon, I feel. Witness, you will give supplementary testimony about the balloons you were operating at the exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Ah...grazie, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">As I said, Balthazar Lune is no liar! Every balloon I had in the sky landed safely!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But ya can't get away from the fact that a burnt-up bit o' cloth was found at the scene, can ya?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">This stupido ragazzo is mistaken! My balloons have the red and blue zigzag stripes anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...so your assertion is that the balloon this child saw was not one belonging to you?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si! Exactamente! If he even saw a balloon in the first place. I do not like the sound of it. It is very bad for business! I have a good mind to sue the land of Bohemia!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">If you attack us, ve vill fight back! It vill be vor! All out vor!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...What happened to 'all out war'? Mr Lune certainly doesn't appear to be lying. But that doesn't change the fact that the testimony and evidence are contradictory here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If the defence is unable to find fault with the witnesses' statements, the court must consider them the truth. ...Think long and hard on that, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The situation has clearly changed now. I have to get to the bottom of what happened here, no matter what it takes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, you may now cross-examine the witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">As I said, Balthazar Lune is no liar! Every balloon I had in the sky landed safely!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You couldn't just...have forgotten one, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">......... Signor... ...I might not notice if I was given one hundred lentils and one was missing. But! We are talking about three enormous balloons! Do you believe I could make a mistake about something so grande and expensive?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I took the liberty of having Inspector Gregson check this gentleman's warehouse. I have the report here. It clearly says 'a total of three balloons.'</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It would appear no mistake has been made, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely Miss Lestrade could have been sent for such a menial task!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">What? Me? I'll tell you wot I told the boss! East End kids like me can only count up to two! ...Obviously that ain't true, but the boss bought it an' said 'e'd 'ave to go 'imself in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Lune">All three of my balloons were carrying passengers. If they fell to the ground in an esplosione, what a catastrofe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It would be quite a catastrophe if they fell to the ground for any reason, I think. On that note, Mr Lune, tell me...what is it that keeps these balloons in the sky?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Are you an idiota?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">That is like asking why does a candle burn bright? It burns bright because it burns bright. And a balloon flies because it flies! ...What else?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... <thought>That must be Italian for 'I don't know'...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There are two types of flying balloons: hot-air balloons and gas balloons. Hot-air balloons work on the principle of hot air being less dense than cold air. Whereas gas balloons derive their lift by using a gas that is lighter than air.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si. And my balloons are filled with the magic gas, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Hydrogen. Lighter than air, but highly explosive.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">I do not permit smoking of the cigarettes in any of my balloons. The magic gas does not like fire.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Even a small spark of static electricity could cause the entire balloon to explode.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">What is the matter with you, signor?! All that comes out of your mouth is esplosione, esplosione! I tell you, my balloons are perfectly safe! They have to be! Or I cannot eat! None of my balloons esploded that day! I am completely sure! But if you still say that is what happened, you must show me the proof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, so Mr Lune had three balloons in the air that day. If none of them were damaged, then what was the one that exploded?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">But ya can't get away from the fact that a burnt-up bit o' cloth was found at the scene, can ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was surprised to find the piece of fabric still at the scene, actually. Didn't you search the area surrounding the stage for clues?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nah...I'm not into pickin' stuff up off the ground, me. Always works out way better divin' into people's pockets instead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...So much for the new career path...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Mind you, the boss was on 'is 'ands an' knees pickin' up all kinds o' rubbish from the floor. Thing is, though, the cage went crashin' into the Crystal Tower, didn't it? So that's where most o' the investigatin' was goin' on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even so, I would have thought someone from Scotland Yard would have gathered it up as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Cor, listen to you! Ya stumble across a bit o' balloon an' suddenly yer the best investigator in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well you ain't got a badge, 'ave ya? Like this one! I could arrest ya wiv this if I wanted to!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wouldn't put it past her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Come to think of it, there was talk of some scorchin' on the ground at a meetin' we 'ad about the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The coppers at the Yard reckoned it was prob'ly some debris thrown from the explosion on the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was considerable damage to the stage and surrounding area, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah. Some o' the coves wot were watchin' the experiment were caught in the blast an' injured. Good job the 'ole contraption didn't keel over, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I hadn't even considered that!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It seems there was great panic after the incident occurred. Nevertheless, the police shouldn't have missed a torn piece of the envelope from a balloon. ...Inspector Gregson can expect repercussions.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Like me swipin' all 'is fish an' chips, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The man's sole pleasure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lune">None of this matters! That scrap of balloon envelope means nothing! Niente!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">This stupido ragazzo is mistaken! My balloons have the red and blue zigzag stripes anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...the colour is wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si, signor! I do not have any green balloons in my warehouse!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yet, a piece of green cloth was found at the scene... and it's unmistakably from a balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Well, well I do not know how that can be...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">For the sake of argument, let's say that a green balloon did explode above the stage. You couldn't therefore conclude that it happened on the day in question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There have been recreational balloon flights over Hyde Park operating from before the Great Exhibition. One could have exploded on some earlier date. Unfortunate...as I'm sure you'd agree.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You, you believe it may have been from some earlier balloon accident that predates the exhibition?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si! Exactamente! As the signor says, it is not from one of my balloons. Clearly this little ragazzo from Bohemia is mistaken about what he saw. If you come to my warehouse, you will see my three bellissimi balloons, all present and correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is something wrong, Master Gotts?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">It's Master Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond Ormstein!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was on the tip of my tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, somesing is very wrong! I know vot I saw! Zere voz a green balloon zere! I svear it! I svear all over Bohemia!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">You can speak as much bad language as you like, but it changes nothing. If you do not have evidence, ragazzo, then I must tell your parents to punish you, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps we'll let the judge decide when it comes to punishments.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">'Evi-dence'? Vot is zis 'evi-dence'?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To give a simple example, young man... ...a photograph, for instance. Some tangible proof of what you claim.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vell vy didn't you say so sooner? I have ze photograph here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">I had not been up in a balloon for a little vile, so I voz very excited. I took lots and lots of photographs! Of ze Crystal Tower, of ze Bohemian exhibit, of ze streets of London, of ze hot eel seller, ze balloon...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the instantaneous kinesis experiment? Did you take a picture of that?!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, vun picture.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? You did take one?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">But all I vanted voz a ride in a balloon. I voz not interested in boring experiments.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Never mind that! Can you show us that photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Of course. And zen you vill see! You vill see zat I am not lying! Zat I really did see a green balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vell? I see you are all too shocked to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I think shocked is indeed the word, young man.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja, perhaps you cannot see zat it voz a green balloon from zis photograph, but... But... BUT ZAT IS NOT MY FAULT! ZAT IS ZE FAULT OF ZE STUPID PERSON WHO MADE ZE CAMERA! Wäääääääääh! Wäääääääääh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That is one very Bohemian-sounding cry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Wäääääääääh! Wäääääääääh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-Very well! The court will accept this photograph as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">It's not my fault. It's ze fault of ze person who made ze camera...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, never mind. I'm sure you have plenty of wonderful sepia memories to take home with you! In any case...when exactly did you take that photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vell...it voz on ze day of ze big explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't say...</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ven I pressed ze shutter release, zere voz zis very loud bang... ...and a hot vind rushed over my face.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>That means... ...this photograph was taken a split-second before the explosion occurred.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lune">Well, if you ask me, this black-and-white photograph changes nothing. I could not give the flying fig!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Lovely language you've picked up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I've already verified Mr Lune's annual business reports, and he's had the same number of balloons for a year now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, as thorough as ever, Lord van Zieks. Disarmingly so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In that case... ...is the young boy just imagining things?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the prince took a photograph as proof.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">It's Prince Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond Ormstein.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">...Your royal blood will not help you here, ragazzo. Si, it is a balloon! But there is nothing more you can see from this black-and-white photograph! Just look on my head! THAT is a Balthazar Lune balloon! The best in the business!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's try not to get over-inflated... The point is this! Here we have clear photographic proof that in the sky above the experimentation stage... ...there may very well have been a balloon operated by somebody other than you, Mr Lune!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Who was it?! I want to know! Who was this mongrel with no respect for the boundaries?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As I thought, Mr Lune's testimony just doesn't quite add up... The young Bohemian boy claims to have seen another, fourth balloon. But Mr Lune vehemently denies the possibility. And it's hard to imagine the man in charge could be mistaken about the number that were in the air... Still, this inconsistency must tell us something, I'm sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unfortunately, the photograph Master Gotts took can't tell us the colour of the balloon. But it can tell us something else. Something crucially important.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It shows that the pictured balloon...wasn't carrying any passengers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! My goodness, you're right! But surely all the balloons would have been carrying passengers? There would be no sense in it otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">S-Si! They are for pleasure! For seeing the view! MY balloons only fly with passengers!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which tells us that the pictured balloon isn't one of them. So when the incident occurred that day... ...there WAS a fourth balloon in the skies above the experimentation stage! The mysterious green balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">I, I know nothing! Niente! I, I can only tell you one thing... If this balloon was not carrying passengers, then it was not one of mine!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Si... Si! The competizione...trying to steal my profits! I did not notice because of the esperimento that went wrong on the stage!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This fourth balloon exploded at the very same moment Mr Asman was 'beamed' from the stage below.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right...so them scraps that fell to the ground after, an' left them scorch marks... They didn't come from the stage at all! It was bits o' the balloon rainin' down! But cos no one was in it, it didn't get no attention.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A mysterious fourth balloon carrying no passengers, silently floating over the experimentation stage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Its relevance does elude me, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The court has seen sufficient evidence and heard ample testimony already. The prosecution calls for this trial to be concluded!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Really? Have we really got to the truth yet? No, I can't let this opportunity slip away. The jurors' minds are made up...and not in our favour! What else can this photograph tell us? Is there nothing more we can learn from it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I'm really not sure that there is, but if I say there isn't, it's all over. I'm just going to have to assume some other clue exists here somewhere, and stall for time. If only I could find something more... Anything at all that this picture can tell us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Your face has turned a similar shade to the photograph, my learned friend. You've seen the writing on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, wait! Please don't give your decisions yet! The photograph from Master Gotts... ...may well be hiding one more vital clue!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What's that?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">A vital clue?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The owner of the fourth balloon! That's what this photograph tells us!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">How can this be possibile? Si, all of my balloons have red and blue zigzag stripes... ...but this photograph is black and white! It is useless!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, at the very least we can see that the balloon doesn't have any stripes. And consequently...we know that it can't belong to you!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Congratulations. You've narrowed the field of everyone in the world...by one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hardly what you'd call proof of the balloon's owner, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Don't I at least get points for a logical argument...?</thought> I'll...I'll come up with another possibility then!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Leads back to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The balloon's colour! That's what this photograph tells us!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You have to clear your mind of all the extraneous information that's clouding your judgement. Then look at the photograph and focus. Now tell me... ...what colour do you see?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Sepia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite. I believe the defence's overly colourful imagination needs toning down a little.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Am I the only one who sees a green balloon...?</thought> I'll...I'll come up with another possibility then!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Leads back to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We can reasonably assume that the pictured balloon was destroyed in the searing heat of the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Ja! Zat's right! Ja! It voz not my fault!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Evidently. Because the birdcage from the kinesis machine materialised in the sky where it had been flying. And the balloon, being filled with flammable hydrogen, instantly and explosively ignited.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No, that's not what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that this photograph requires closer examination. Counsel for the Defence, you will highlight the location of this alleged 'clue' in the photograph for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, My Lord. <thought>If you look closely, it's plain enough to see. And what's shown is linked to another piece of evidence we have. In a way that leads to an unbelievable conclusion!</thought> The clue that heavily suggests the real reason the balloon exploded is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I'm afraid it's still not clear to me, Counsel. Perhaps it's a matter of age.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes, probably!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, one thing is abundantly clear.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Namely, that only one as immature as you could give such a rash answer, my learned friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So without a doubt, that wasn't it, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Remember, Counsel: due consideration, if you please. Both in your answers...and toward your elders. Now then, perhaps you would like to try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The timing of this photograph can only be described as miraculous. If you look, you'll notice there's a bright white line that appears to point directly at the balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Most likely a ray of light caught incidentally on the film.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm afraid I can see nothing of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you look with a magnifying glass, My Lord, it becomes clear what the nature of this bright line really is.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Undeniably some flash of light, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh golly. Do, do you think it might be lightning?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">But it couldn't have been a finer day.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I believe we may be looking...at fire!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">A bolt of fire, heading straight for the balloon...like an arrow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Even to my ageing eyes, it would appear to be a flame of some sort. My word! Are, are you suggesting this flame struck the hydrogen gas that filled the balloon?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, it's my opinion... ...that a particular piece of evidence found at the scene reveals how that is exactly what did happen.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If such evidence exists, Counsel, then for goodness' sake present it, man! Which evidence explains this mysterious streak of flame that appears to be headed directly for the balloon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A curious answer. With a slim chance of being the correct one, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It looks somewhat like a piece of firework. But whereas fireworks dazzle their audience... ...you fizzle out in a remarkably disappointing way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...insults dressed up in colourful metaphors are still insults. But anyway, this firework display isn't over yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This was found hidden at the foot of a small ornamental tree near the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Is that a crossbow?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An arrow dipped in oil and set alight could have been shot from this weapon... ...sending a flaming arrow straight into the hydrogen-filled balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Are you suggesting...that crossbow was used to deliberately...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Blimey, yer right! That streak o' light in the photo looks just like an arrow, dunnit?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Then...the esplosione of the balloon, it was...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Very likely the result of a flaming arrow from this crossbow igniting the hydrogen gas inside it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Nooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Counsel, this is an extraordinary supposition!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the aim was to cause the balloon to explode, the shooter could have used a gun of course. However, there's an obvious reason why that would have been out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The noise of the discharge? Of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. By using a crossbow, the projectile could be fired at the balloon silently.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well yeah, if someone 'ad shot a gun off in the exhibition grounds, it would've caused a real panic.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">But with the big esplosione, there was a very big panic anyway, no?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I don't like this. I should be pleased to have found a plausible new explanation for all this, but something feels wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If a flaming arrow did indeed hit the balloon, then obviously it would have exploded. And if the birdcage appeared from the cloud of smoke that ensued...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot? Wait a minute! Wot are ya really sayin' 'ere? I don't get it. Was, was the birdcage beamed up into the sky after all, or...wot?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My goodness me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Ah, now I understand. That's what that sinking feeling is about...</thought> I think there's a good chance... ...that the birdcage was actually concealed inside the balloon all along.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Did, did I just hear that correctly, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's no going back now. The horse has bolted...</thought> Let's assume, as I said, that the birdcage was hidden inside the green balloon from the start. On stage, when the experiment was started... ...the birdcage in the instantaneous kinesis machine disappeared in a cloud of smoke. At that moment, the flaming arrow was fired from the ground... ...causing the green balloon to explode and drawing the attention of the spectators to the sky above their heads. From amid the smoke, the hidden birdcage then appeared, to fall down and crash into the Crystal Tower. I think you'll all agree it's entirely plausible... ...that what I've just described is the real truth behind the 'miraculous' experiment carried out that day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This... I......... GOOOOOOOOOD GRIEF!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Both Mr Sholmes and Iris said that the experiment was a scientific impossibility. In which case, this is the only way to explain what happened that day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And in any case...the victim's body was found inside the birdcage in the Crystal Tower. If the instantaneous kinesis didn't take place, how do you explain that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Um...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">If I may put in a word...as a man of magic myself... Such apparent discrepancies can easily be explained by some simple deception.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">J-Juror number three!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">All that would be needed is a doppelgänger - someone who looked very similar to the victim, Mr Asman... ...and having this other man appear on stage to front the show...as a body double!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...yes! Of course, so in fact... ...Mr Asman must have been inside the birdcage that was concealed inside the balloon right from the start!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not necessarily. The explosive force of the balloon gas would very much depend upon the mixture ratio.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">J-Juror number four!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Flying balloons are rarely filled with pure hydrogen, but a mixture of other gases such as helium as well. Helium on its own doesn't explode, but by controlling the gas mixture ratio, the explosive force can be altered.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The mixture ratio...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Obviously, the victim's body would have suffered some burns. That would be unavoidable. But not to such an extent as to render this whole obscene charade impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So everything that happened can be explained. Logically and scientifically. The explosion that engulfed the stage at the start of the 'experiment' was no accident. It was all part of an elaborate deception...to make it appear that instantaneous kinesis had occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...goodness me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And if we accept that this is what happened... ...it means that the victim, Mr Asman, was never present on the public experimentation stage to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Nrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In short... ...he couldn't have been killed by the defendant, who was on stage in full view the entire time!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">AAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This will be very hard for the prosecution to counter. Lord van Zieks can't credibly maintain that Professor Harebrayne is a suspect now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Mr Naruhodo...I appreciate your efforts. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">P-Professor?!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But you can stop now. Just keep your mouth shut, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's all this about...Mr Harebrayne?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... I, Albert Harebrayne, hereby confess... ...that it... That it was... That it was me who stabbed Mr Odie Asman! Yes! It was me! With my faithful friend and partner... Andrew the Screwdriver!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha......... WHAT ARE YOU DOIIIIIING?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!! Defendant! Explain this sudden confession!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne! What are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">It's...it's what I've said all along! I must protect my hypothesis! And my precious machine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">You stand there and claim it was all a trick! All an elaborate prank! But where's your proof?! No, y-you'd have to examine the machine if you wanted to prove it. But then it would all be over! My beautiful hypothesis would be laid bare... I mean, the indignity of it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's clear that you drew the plans for the experiment, but you didn't actually build it. It's quite conceivable that you were duped, Professor. If you'll just let me, I can prove-</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Barok!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'll cooperate. I'll do whatever you say. I swear it. So, so please... ...ensure the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act is adhered to and protect my creation!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Pray forgive the discourtesy of filling my hallowed chalice at this critical juncture... Here's to my learned Nipponese friend...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...and his upcoming attempt to clarify the defence's position in the light of the accused's confession.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Do you intend to formally assert that the experiment was nothing more than a conjuring trick? Because the moment you do... ...the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act that protects the professor's invention will cease to apply. The prosecution will then demand a rigorous examination of the machinery involved in order to establish the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">However...if you acknowledge that the machine is genuine and instrumental in the victim's murder... ...any chance of investigating will be crushed...and the confidentiality of the professor's hypothesis preserved.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Counsel...what is the defence's official position on this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What Professor Harebrayne - my client - actually asked of me... ...was to prove that the explosion on stage was an accident and protect the secrecy of his hypothesis. But there's no way to do that without implying the professor's guilt! Do I protect my client's life by asserting his innocence, or do I uphold my client's request but see him condemned? Either way, I can't avoid betraying his trust...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">You've been silent long enough! Isn't talking your trade, my learned friend? Or has all knowledge of English escaped your confused Nipponese mind?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's no escape here! I have to make a choice! But it's an impossible one! I have to give up on something...but what?</thought> The defence asserts...that the defendant's instantaneous kinesis machine was in fact...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... .........Agh! <thought>No! I can't say it! My client placed his faith in me... I can't just let him down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hello again...Mr Naruhodo. It's been far too long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Su... Susato-san! But, but what are you-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Haiiiiii-YA!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAGH! <thought>My first Susato Takedown in six months!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">There'll be time to talk later, Mr Naruhodo. For now...we must concentrate on the task at hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Which is working out not what I have to give up on, but what I can protect!</thought> Professor Harebrayne!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah! ...Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yesterday you told me that science is the pursuit of truth. Well...my job is to pursue the truth too.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Yes, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And personally, I believe...that you didn't stab Mr Asman. I think you've come to realise something yourself too, haven't you? That your experiment and the machine you built with the victim are questionable! The truth behind that is what we must both pursue now!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...So...you've finally opened your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And as for you... ...Albert. You can't ignore this any longer.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Having heard my learned friend's assertion... ...don't you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... B-Barok...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, I've never heard him speak that way before.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... In truth...there is one thing. Something I've remembered that's of relevance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">On the day it happened...just before I began the experiment...I saw a man near the stage. A man holding that crossbow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor! Did the man have any distinguishing features? What did he look like?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Uh...tall. Taller than me. And, and thin. Thinner than me. With straight hair. Straighter - and whiter - than mine. Let me see... One less lens than me, too. A monocle. A rather stylish, black monocle. But one thing in particular will help to positively identify the man. You see, I know him very well. After all...he's the engineer who built my invention!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He...built the machine?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">That's right. Mr Asman introduced him to me a year ago. He's, he's a man by the name of... ...Enoch Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Enoch?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Drebber?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does this name mean something? Members of the jury seem flustered...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Not a name any scientist wishes to hear. The man's an abomination!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not a name any conjuror wishes to hear, either!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who on earth is he?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I'm afraid this isn't the first tale of this nature that I've heard in scientific circles in connection with that name. There's talk of other flamboyant experiments that turn out to be nothing but stage trickery in the end. Obviously the rascal is after the government's research grant money.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">When magicians are in need of money, I have heard of them resorting to these underhand tactics. Some acquaintances of mine with...experience of such things have mentioned Enoch Drebber's name before.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">The man is both an engineer and a magician. Yes, we're dealing with an unparalleled confidence trickster here! That's Enoch Drebber for you!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">So it's true then... My invention... My great machine... It was just a grand illusion?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Considering what we've just heard about Mr Drebber's character... ...I'm sorry to say that sounds increasingly likely.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Even though no one else believed it...I wanted to. I wanted to believe to believe that machine would function exactly as my hypothesis predicted.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which is why you were so opposed to it being investigated, I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I knew that if the machine was examined in detail, its construction would give away my hypothesis. Obviously, I didn't want that to happen. But at the same time... ...I knew that if it was found to be nothing more than a trick... Than a work of deception... ...then everything I'd worked towards...all my research... all my dreams...my whole life would be over! I was terrified at the prospect.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you really had no idea, then, did you? About the true nature of the machine that was built. And the true nature of Mr Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I never questioned anything. I, I didn't want to question it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's entirely possible that Mr Asman and Mr Drebber... ...were working together to use you as a means of fraudulently acquiring the research grant money.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">.........</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">But I really don't know how the whole illusion was made to work. I...don't know anything any more...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let me confirm one final point with you, Professor. Do you now consent to the prosecution submitting the necessary paperwork... ...to release your invention from the protection afforded by the Special Dispensation for Scientific Equipment Act?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Yes, please go ahead. I'm...very sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that we shall have to suspend proceedings for the remainder of the day now. Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court has newly been made aware of another party whose involvement in this matter is critical.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, Mr Drebber...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gather information about the man. If possible, I should like him served with a subpoena.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">With pleasure, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Counsel for the Defence...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... When we reconvene, I shall be looking for one thing and one thing alone from you. Evidence...that the defendant is innocent of the crime for which he presently stands accused.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. In that case...this court is adjourned until tomorrow morning!</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... ...Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I'm...I'm...I'm... I'm so sorry! I was wrong! You were right! I tricked you! You trusted me! I dragged you...into my mess! Oh h-how did it ever come to this...? I'M SOOO SOOO SOOO SOOORRY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you really have no idea, Professor? About what Mr Drebber was really up to, I mean? About what he was really constructing.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">Naturally! That machine was the embodiment of my hypothesis! Of all my hopes and dreams! I had complete faith in it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright. In that case, I won't say any more. Now, sadly the murder accusation against you still stands. So we must do as much investigation as we can before the trial resumes tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Well, thank you for doing so much for me!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so sorry for arriving late this morning, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A-Arriving late?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Didn't you receive my postcard? I wanted to let you know when I'd arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Postcard? What postcard?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I hid it from you, Runo! So it would be a surprise! ...Well? Did it work?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was surprised alright! Especially when she threw me to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear! I'm so sorry! I, I was just so happy to see you again that...it sort of slipped out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe we could stick to more traditional displays of emotion in future...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Susie's train was late into London Victoria this morning, you see. But we made the coachman really whip the horses hard so she didn't miss the whole trial!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I was watching from the gallery for a while, but in the end...I'm afraid I couldn't contain myself...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I'm glad you didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Having you at my side in court gives me the strength I need to win. So...I'm, um, delighted to see you...back in London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, you're too kind, Mr Naruhodo! I'm delighted to be here! I hope I can continue to be of service to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course. So...what's brought you back? Did Professor Mikotoba not protest?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Let's save all that conversation for when we're back at home, shall we? You know I've made one of my most special blends ever for this special occasion!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Iris, how wonderful! I can't wait!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Susato-san was back in London. It's hard to describe how happy that made me feel at the time. But despite my elation... ...our tale was about to take yet another extraordinary turn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely something about that last statement seems odd, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you care to mull over precisely what you find odd about it on your return journey to Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I wouldn't be back to give the court an answer for about four months, though.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Rest assured, we should be happy to carry proceedings forward in your absence, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He sounds serious! I have to prove my worth before he really does send me back home!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement would seem to be at odds somehow with the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is your task, Counsel, to explain the 'somehows' to the court, not the other way around.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It just seems to jar, though. Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What I think, is that this whole exchange has been extremely jarring, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps I need to reconsider this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence would have to object to that last statement, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I would have to overrule your objection, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence...would have to accept the penalty given.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Glad to hear it. And you would also have to think again, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Harebrayne! Are you hiding something from the court?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">......... Ah ha! It's four! AAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Um, what was that?</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">I was calculating the neutralisation coefficient of electrical charge required for electrolysis of a human subject. I have to keep the result a secret at all costs, you see. That's why I ate the paper I did my working on. But now I've completely forgotten the number! Dear me, I am a scatterbrain sometimes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...moments before you ate the paper, you did yell out the number four...</line>
<line speaker="Harebrayne">NOOOOOO! You, you know it? You know my secret coefficient! Oh dear! Oh no! This is bad! Oh my goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps...you could just focus on the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector! Did you have something to add?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Didn't that last statement set off a train of thought in your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well...I was ponderin' somethin' that pops into my head from time to time, yes. I was thinkin' that there probably are one or two things in life more important than a bag o' fish an' chips.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">But you can't deny they're bloomin' useful when you feel like bitin' someone's head off!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'No, nothing to add' would probably have sufficed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I may, Mr Lune!</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Ah! You like one of a balloons, eh? Prego, prego. Ten shillings for one!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, I was going to ask you if that last statement bothered you for some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Lune">......... People say things to me all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Lune">They say avaricious, they say money-grabbing, they say cheat, full of hot air, stripy swindler! If I let what the people say bother me, how can I fly my balloons, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I think you just need to fill them up and the gas does most of the work, really.</line>
<line speaker="Lune">Allora! That is why I refuse to listen to what the people say! Why should I?! It is nothing good!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well...if he doesn't listen, that explains a lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A balloon with arms and legs, but no faculties with which to hear...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...There's no need to get carried away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Master Gotts, do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something that struck you about what you just heard, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vot I just heard voz you failing to remember my full name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Vich is Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond Ormstein.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uh... Vil...um...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">My learned friend's powers of recollection are clearly abysmal. Perhaps he has forgotten where he is...</line>
<line speaker="Gotts">Mein teacher at elementary school said zat if you are rude enough to forget somevun's name... ...you vill have ze most awful life imaginable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Are all Bohemians brought up to endure a life of such great pain?</thought> Well...well it's important to listen, too! So please pay attention to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh? Blimey, wot's up wiv you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did that last statement strike you as odd in some way, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... You're the expert on bein' odd, ain't ya, 'Oddo? So why don't you tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no...I'm the one asking the questions here, Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Hah! Askin' other people wot ya don't even know the answer to yerself! I don't believe it! An' I'm INSPECTOR Lestrade, an' all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She just had to drop that title in somehow, didn't she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel, that will do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but, My Lord, wait! The defence is still in the process of establishing its argument...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No further analysis is necessary, I feel. As such, I shall be requesting the final decisions of the members of the jury.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It's been an honour to serve, My Lord. And we know exactly what we think now. Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Albert Harebrayne, in accordance with the findings of this court, I pronounce you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I applaud the jurors for doing their civic duty and for finding a swift resolution to this matter. That is all. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>