<xml>
<title>The Memoirs of the Clouded Kokoro</title>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is it then, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It's time to put an end to this now. To the miserable 'curse' that has been plaguing Mr Natsume... To everything!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And in my own small way, I shall do everything I can to help you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I always appreciate your help, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Suffering Soseki Selfishly Sidelined!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good...morning to you too, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">'GOOD MORNING'...? 'GOOD MORNING', LOCUM STUDENT MR NARUHODO ESQUIRE?! LISTEN TO YOU TWO CHATTING AWAY HAPPILY AS IF THE MAIN PLAYER OF TODAY'S TRIAL ISN'T HERE! WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT? WHY?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... We didn't mean to cause offence, Mr Natsume. I thought perhaps that because you had your eyes shut so tightly, you were meditating. Finding inner calm. It seemed wrong to disturb you.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I was waiting! 'What's the matter, Mr Natsume? You seem...different somehow today...' 'Why naturally. That's because I've attained spiritual enlightenment. The path of literature, you see, is a journey to discover one's own death!' ...Or suchlike. That's the sort of morning conversation I was hoping for! That's why I had my eyes shut!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...missed the signs, I'm afraid. Somehow. You'll have to forgive me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And you mustn't talk of your path leading you to death, Mr Natsume!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">THAT WAS JUST AN EXAMPLE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Oh yes, there it is. Inner calm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You, you barely came to see me at all yesterday. I, I was sure you'd abandoned me and returned to our beautiful, long-lost homeland!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've not even been in Great Britain a week yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, well, anyway... ...I intend to set everything straight in court today. I'm determined to uncover the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">...! I've actually reached an important decision myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? What sort of decision?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">I shall fill you in after the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem... ...Mr Sholmes isn't coming today, after all. It's a very clever message, I think! 'My dear fellows, you must win this battle on your own merits!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a very clear message, I think. That he's overslept again.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">The 'great detective'? My arch-nemesis... LONG MAY HE STAY AWAY! ...If you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Defendant! And your legal representative! The trial is about to begin. Make your way into the courtroom immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Today, once again, we face the Reaper. And when the Reaper stands for the prosecution, the defendant's fate is sealed. But I don't believe in that legend any more than I believe in Soseki-san's curse. The truth is hidden here somewhere. And I won't let it escape me. I have to keep believing in my client, and keep fighting to the very end. That's all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session. I call upon the counsels for the prosecution and defence to declare their willingness to proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the defence is ready!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. And now I call upon the six ladies and gentlemen of the jury... ...chosen by lot to represent the will of the people in this trial. Are you ready to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Absolutely! Justice will be done, you mark my words!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I feel obliged to say...I feel especially ruthless on days when my hat is sitting just right.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh...well I wonder if you could adjust my hat for me. And please, be as ruthless as you like...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Thieves deserve to die if you ask me. Especially gas thieves! I've no sympathy for the man at all!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Look! I said it yesterday and I'll say it again now. I don't have time for this! I've got my own problems!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Oh, may the Lord show us all the light here, and lead His flock to a righteous verdict again today...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now...Lord van Zieks, what can you tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution's report, please, for the court. In relation to the theory expounded by the defence yesterday...regarding the defendant's tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>So he does have the results...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Before the prosecution delivers the black news about the black tea belonging to the blackguard in the dock... ...pray, allow me a moment to savour a liquid of a more sanguine hue. In fact, I'll defer to the good detective for the report. ...Here's to you, Inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Yes, sir! Thank you, sir. As indicated by the defence, we found a bar of soap just outside the victim's window in the snow. And there was indeed a frozen reddish liquid in a little depression on the top of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! That's the tea! That's what Mr Natsume brought with him that night!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well the brains at the Yard analysed it, and yes, you're right: it was tea. And there wasn't a trace of strychnine or any other toxic substance in it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...! No poison at all!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">In other words...the tea that the defendant brought with him to the victim's room...is innocent. It's in the clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a revelation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As I suspected...</thought> This makes it quite clear! The defendant, Mr Soseki Natsume, is blameless here!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, it's true, no poison was found in the few drops of liquid recovered from the soap on the window ledge. But! What logic is that? Would you take a drop from the Thames and conclude that the water in the ocean isn't salty?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My word! The water in the ocean is extremely salty, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Exactly! Unfit for drinking! Just as the victim's tea was on the night in question, as the court has already heard. 'Bitter' was the precise word from the lips of Mr William Shamspeare... ...whom the prosecution now calls back to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I will uphold the prosecution's request.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it sounds like we're going to have another confrontation with our theatrical friend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Show Mr Shamspeare to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Mr William Shamspeare...the victim of this despicable crime.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'O Heaven! O Hell! Do you command me to remember?' Forsooth, 'twas I, Shamspeare, did have a bellyful of the foul fluid giv'n! In mine innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...but as was revealed in yesterday's proceedings... ...the witness is not as innocent as we had perhaps first been led to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">By using bars of soap such as this, he has been stealing gas from the supply company, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'One may smile, and smile, and be a villain...' Forsooth, 'twas I, Shamspeare, did have a roomful of the sweet fuel giv'n!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">That's right! Fellow jurors, don't forget...this man is a rotten thief!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I haven't forgotten! Kept all that about the ice coins a tidy secret, didn't you? You should've owned up sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Arrest him, I say! Arrest him at once! And let him feel the sting in my tail!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">O, indeed! By dint of vile and cowardly means have I plotted to further mine own ends. I confess! Thou wouldst not pardon my sins, of that I am sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you acknowledge your wrongdoing, what exactly are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Cowards die many times before their deaths.' And for a coward such as I...death be well deserv'd. But! Would it that a still greater crime passeth unpunish'd? For lo! The hairy-faced gentleman of farther East than Verona did contrive to poison me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But there was no poison in the tea found in your room! The police have attested to that.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What the defence would assert as an inconsistency will quickly be cleared up by the witness's testimony. Is that not so, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Verily, my liege! I would most gladly speak!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let the witness testify to explain this inconsistency. Tell the court why it is that poison apparently entered your body, though none was found in the tea!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">The Japanese man did come to my chamber with tea brew'd in a pot.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The poison was slipped into the cup after the tea had been poured. The normal way for poison to be administered...in my experience.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite. Otherwise it would be disastrous if the poisoner were to mix up the cups, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But no poison bottle was found at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Because, quite simply, the Nipponese took the bottle back to his own room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The absence of a vessel containing the poison only becomes problematic when considering suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>I knew that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">By now it should be perfectly clear. A bar or two of cheap soap... ...is wholly insufficient to was the deep stains of guilt from the accused's hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Sirs! Madams! 'Tis true that I, Shamspeare, be a common thief of gas... But... BUT! Listen here, ladies and gentlemen... Wherefore would I lie? Verily, I have no cause! I have nought to lose!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I do declare...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you for your testimony, witness. Counsel, proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">The Japanese man did come to my chamber with tea brew'd in a pot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I understand that you were already acquainted with Mr Natsume. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'I know thee not, old man. Fall to thy prayers.' Do I know thee, or know thee not? Methinks 'tis all I can know that thy destiny mingles with mine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You lost me at the first 'thee'.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Zounds, sir! Thou must learn the English tongue afore thou turns thy hand to lawyering!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I did. But I must have missed the Archaic Elizabethan lecture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Verily and in truth, 'twas a fine-flavoured brew. Though a drop of poison did barb its sweetness. As the thorn doth barb the sweet rose. That, dear friends, be the simple truth.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Listen to Mr Shamspeare... He seems in even better form than he was yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Either that, or I'm in worse form...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">That fated evening, after I did dine... ...at Grub's Grubbery - a local alehouse of good report... ...nought did pass my lips but the tainted black tea. But behold! The poison was not in the tea at first!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Twas in my cup alone that the wicked miscreant secretly pour'd his wicked poison.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you saying that you saw the moment when the poison was added to your tea?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...To have witness'd the act and then drank the tea? Thou dost describe the actions of a fool.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite so, quite so.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">But no one likes going thirsty, do they? Sooner would I die quench'd than parch'd...would I have the choice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, on the night in question, the water main was frozen, I believe, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Were it not for the tea, in sooth I would sooner have died frozen than quench'd or parch'd.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right... No ice coins means no heating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The witness had more than one brush with death on the night in question, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Remind the court,  Mr Shamspeare...as to whether the accused drank any of the tea which he brought with him.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">With the greatest of pleasure, my liege...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Whilst feigning distraction in our debate, ne'er did a drop of his own drink pass his lips.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the teacup Mr Natsume drank from was found completely empty at the scene! And let's not forget the defendant's maxim: 'Drink tea while it's hot!'</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...I did gulp from the poison'd cup that night. And in mine agony did I writhe uncontroll'd. In fits of pain I did knock the fellow's cup and its contents spilt as blood from a gaping wound...methinks. ...Though certainly, 'twas after I had made the coins of ice from his tea.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">An upset cup was found on the table that the victim was slumped over. There is no contradiction here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's true, there was no tea left in either cup that we found at the scene. But still...something about this statement is troubling me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Of course! I know what it is! It's Mr Natsume's wise 'drink tea while it's hot' maxim, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... No, I'm not sure that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, witness. Now reiterate for the court what it is that occupied you after your guest had left and before you drank your tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">When he departed by and by, I did use the tea that remain'd in his cup to make my coins of ice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, so that you could cheat the gas company, in fact. ...Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">To cheat...or to die... 'Tis life's only choice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yeees.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Faith, to cheat be the wise choice! And mine occupation be not an ugly one! Prithee, dost thou not see beauty in the simplicity of the ruse?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">No, I don't. And be very sure, sir... ...once this trial is over, Altamont Gas will take you to ask over this! Legal task!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I shall not run! I shall not hide! Sooth to say, I have nowhere to run nor to hide... But my lady! What wouldst thou with this pitiful player?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Oh, I'll tell you what I'd like to do with you. Starting with the shoddy shirt on your back.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... ...'Tis time for a Shamspeare dance!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a harsh world we live in...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The thieving of the gas was addressed in yesterday's proceedings. The prosecution calls on the defence not to muddy the waters with irrelevancy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Consider that a warning, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord! <thought>Why am I the one in trouble here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Mr Shamspeare, after the accused returned to his own lodgings, you used his tea to make your...coins. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">To cheat or to die... I did make my choice many moons ago.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Thus 'tis no surprise that poison be not found in the tea I did pour into the moulds of soap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If, having first made your special coins, it was after two in the morning when you collapsed... ...that would mean you can't have drunk any tea yourself until around that time.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Once ensnared by literary debate, nought else be found in the furrows of the mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The debate about Romeo and Juliet, you mean? And who was the stronger of the two.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Rightly did I pay no heed to the tea as I wrestled with the abominable fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't remember debates like that when I was studying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you suggesting that neither of you actually drank the tea whilst it was hot that evening?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My Lord, wouldst thou be privy to some Shamspearean wisdom? 'Husband, wife and tea ought aye tepid be!'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah yes, so very true. Everyone has different preferences when it comes to tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think you might have interpreted that wrongly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... So it's been proven that there was no poison in Soseki-san's tea. That should be hugely in our favour. But the atmosphere in this courtroom today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It feels as though everybody is against us, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It must be the Reaper's poison.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid that if we don't find a significant flaw in this testimony somewhere... ...the jury will pounce and find Mr Natsume guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It really feels like we've jumped into the fire here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You claim that Mr Natsume didn't drink a drop of tea on the night in question... ...but that's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">How, how, how, choplogic? What is this, ye dark yclad fiend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The two teacups from the scene - one used by the victim and the other by the defendant... ...have a clear difference between them...one that represents incontrovertible proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Incontrovertible?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What difference?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at the inside of the cups. Just here...there's a clearly visible ring.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes... A tea ring. Commonplace enough.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Such stains occur all too readily when one leaves tea in the cup for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And yet...Nr Natsume's cup has no such ring.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! You're right! It's completely clean...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">And prithee, sir, what mak'st thou of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly what Mr Natsume told the court yesterday. The Japanese saying he quoted!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Drink...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...Tea...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...While it's hot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right! Yes... ...the jittery Mr Natsume was true to his usual self that night, and drank his tea in no time.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If, as you claim in your testimony, he didn't touch a drop of his tea... ...a ring would have developed on the inside of his cup as well, after the several hours the tea was left standing.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">But...erm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In short, Mr Shamspeare... ...you clearly lied to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Get...thee...to a nunneriiiiiiiiieeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You might want to keep that information to yourself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yet on occasion, tedium distracts me and I pour more times than I intended until the bottle is dry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your drinking habits are fascinating, but...irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">On the contrary. They illustrate the fickleness of human memory. To William Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Y-Yes...my liege...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...though you previously stated that you made the coins of ice from the leftover tea in the accused's cup... ...could it be that you were perhaps mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Could it be that...yes. Perhaps there was some tea remaining in the small teapot left at the scene. A fact that had vanished from your memory until now...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Faith, my liege, thou art a magician! For verily...'tis as though thou hast seen with thine own eyes that night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Forsooth! I was mistook! I did plan to use tea from the Japanese fellow's cup, but lo! When I looked, 'twas empty! And thus did I use the dregs that fester'd in the teapot, as my liege did suggest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you've just suddenly remembered now that you made a mistake before? Are we supposed to believe that?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But in any case, it makes no difference. The victim's most recent testimony tells us two things of note: Firstly, that the poison was put into the victim's teacup only. And secondly, that this spoilt cup was not the source of the insipid 'ice coins' that have bewitched this court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... The prosecution makes a fine summary of the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Furthermore, that testimony remains valid and in full support of the established facts. In other words... ...the inconsistency claimed by the defence simply does not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My lords, ladies and gentlemen of the jury! I do solemnly swear... After I did dine at Grub's Grubbery alehouse that night... ...nought did pass my lips but the black tea giv'n me by the Japanese, whose back be stoop'd as low as death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And on what did you dine, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Why, I did partake of my favourites: a broth as wouldst be call'd soup and a leaf as wouldst be call'd salad...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As insalubrious a menu as the establishment where it was served...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'But you gods will give us, Some faults to make us men.' Willingly would I suffer what punishment 'tis seen fit to serve a wicked thief of gas. But! I pray ye wise and noble fellows, ne'er forget the simple truth...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Jurors all, your humble servant Shamspeare doth entreat you: punish the Japanese fellow for his sins!</line>
<line speaker="???">My Loooooord!!!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">If I may speak, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I believe we may have been duped by that rotten defence lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By me?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do declare you may be right!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">We all know the waif there was making coins of ice to keep himself warm...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...But this lawyer lad says if he's stealing gas, he deserves a dose of poison, eh? He's been leading us up the garden path, that's what he's been doing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I really never said anything like that.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">But what we just heard from the victim there has opened our eyes again! We've reached a decision this time, and we won't be swayed from it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court acknowledges the position of the jury foreman... ...and will duly hear the jury's findings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? No! You, you can't yet...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ladies and gentlemen of the jury...you will state your decisions now!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby declare the jury to be in one accord.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">O happy day!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How is this happening?</thought> My Lord! The defence asserts its right to carry out a summation examination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court upholds the defence's right.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Typical... My learned friend is unable to accept the obvious truth...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial will therefore enter its second summation examination immediately. Jurors, the court calls upon each of you... ...to state the grounds upon which you find the defendant guilty of the crime of which he is charged.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I'm a man of logic, me. And having considered all the evidence, the defendant must logically be guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do agree that gas is far too expensive. I can quite understand why the man would want to avoid paying.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">The stuff explodes and it can poison you! It's absolutely lethal, gas is!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Gas doesn't come for free! It costs a fortune to deliver it around the city and maintain the pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Truth be told, the tea my wife serves up for me is a little...sketchy at times.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">If nothing else passed the victim's lips that night, there's no other explanation, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, I do feel that perhaps personal opinion about gas and its supply has influenced decisions somewhat... ...but never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No no, you really should mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The truth is, our counter-argument wasn't as unassailable as we'd hoped. And Mr Shamspeare WAS poisoned. There can be no doubt of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then how are we supposed to turn this around?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think... ...we need to establish the method by which Mr Shamspeare was actually poisoned. Our only hope is to demonstrate that to the court incontrovertibly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but that's surely almost impossible at this stage!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...If we don't manage it, though, Mr Natsume will...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Will be found guilty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">No delays, Counsel! Proceed with the summation examination!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I'm a man of logic, me. And having considered all the evidence, the defendant must logically be guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All the evidence, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">That's right. And there's no room for doubt. It's all pointing at that Japanese man with the big moustache!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the Englishman with the bigger moustache...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which means we need to show the man some new evidence to make him change his mind!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...If only we had that kind of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't worry. This summation examination has barely started really. Perhaps there'll be a shift in the situation that shows an existing piece of evidence in a new light!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's hope so! <thought>To start with, though, I need to find some way out of this deadlock...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All the evidence, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">That's right. And there's no room for doubt. It's all pointing at that Japanese man with the big moustache!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the Englishman with the bigger moustache...</thought> But the defence just demonstrated another possible explanation for the events on the night in question. What do you make of that?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What, your so-called 'skin prints'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's an exciting new forensic investigation technique... developed by the great detective himself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The numerous handprints on the wall are clearly out of the ordinary. And if Mr Shamspeare had indeed put his mouth to the gas pipe on the night in question... ...it can't be denied that there's a possibility that's where the poison was!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Well, yes... I won't deny that it's playing on my mind. But as the prosecution rightly says: we should pay no heed to unacceptable forms of evidence. And besides...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Even if the fellow has been up to some mischief with the gas pipe dozens of times before... ...it doesn't mean he got up to the same shenanigans on the night in question, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">If you can't make your case better than that, I'm afraid I can't change my stance.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Hm, you do make a very valid point, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Hm...that's true. Perhaps I was a little hasty...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Look, you've got your chance here, haven't you? So it's time to prove your theory. If you and your Japanese cohorts can, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Just leave our nationality out of this, please!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! If we can't substantiate our position... ...I'm afraid the jurors that changed their minds before may very well change them back!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What can I do...? Is there any more proof I can give here? Can I show that Mr Shamspeare really did blow down the gas pipe on the night in question?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I'm not in a position to prove it...yet.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">As I thought. I had a feeling that would stump you Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We ARE capable of independent thought, you know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we need to gather some more material to bolster our position, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. That's what I was trying to imply by saying we can't prove it 'yet'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel. On with the examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Naturally, I can provide evidence to support the defence's position.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You will present the evidence now, Counsel. The evidence in support of your claim that the victim blew down the gas pipe on the night in question!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Oh yes, it's evidence alright. No question about it. Evidence that this ripe little lawyer thinks he can make a fool of us all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You heard the man, Counsel. Don't get too big for your boots!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you getting too big for your boots, do you think, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not likely. In fact, I wish they'd swallow me up at the moment. <thought>It looks like I need to take another tack here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">On with the summation examination, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, in truth I don't have evidence to support my theory. However... ...there is witness testimony that substantiates it.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What's that? Testimony?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">This is incredible! Whose testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes...it's all connected. Everything is linked.</thought> A person whose testimony revealed details about the gas in the Garrideb residence that night. Namely...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Whew. I don't think he was listening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Rest assured, Counsel, I shan't let such nonsensical answers go without penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I thought I'd got away with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">A witness who spoke about the gas on the night in question... Yes, there was someone...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's what I thought, too. <thought>But I obviously chose the wrong person!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do agree that gas is far too expensive. I can quite understand why the man would want to avoid paying.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This isn't the time or the place to be discussing the price of gas, madam!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">But really! Think of the injustice! Air is a gas, and air is free! Why should Altamont gas cost money? It, it makes my blood boil! I can feel myself becoming more ruthless than ever!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This isn't the time or the place to be ruthless either.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">If I might interject here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, yes, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It seems my fellow juror takes issue with the price our company charges for gas. But it's precisely because of thieves like this man that the cost goes up!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh, what a beastly man! That unkempt moustache, those hunched shoulders... Poisoning tea and stealing gas... Utterly unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! Mr Natsume isn't the one who's been stealing gas! I'll thank you NOT to go adding on more crimes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Natsume hasn't been poisoning tea either!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well anyway, I've quite made up my mind. It's as made up as the price of gas!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I'm very interested in the results of this great detective's investigation at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">The stuff explodes and it can poison you! It's absolutely lethal, gas is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could we please talk about the poison rather than the gas, do you think, sir?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Well, if you like. I mean, to be honest, I'd take poison over gas every time!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd 'take poison'?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">What I mean is, poison can only poison you. It doesn't explode, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Goodness me! What are you talking about? Set him straight, please, lawyer man!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it's certainly true that poison isn't prone to exploding... ...but I think you'll find poison also can't light or heat up a room.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Ah! You're right! I hadn't considered that at all...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">......... Young lawyer man...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">You have a good head on your shoulders. We could use someone like you as our company's legal representative.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, I wasn't expecting to pick up more business in the middle of a trial, that's for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Anyway, the point is, I haven't had the best experience with gas companies in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Blow too hard into a gas pipe, and you extinguish everything in the house. And then you're in real trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say 'extinguish everything in the house', do you mean even on different floors?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh yes. All floors are connected to the same pipe, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">That's true of every building, because gas supply contracts are issued for whole properties.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I had no idea that it was possible to extinguish gas appliances simply by blowing down the pipe.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It's not something we like to publicize, to be honest. But we have to carry out these investigations, as I'm sure you can appreciate.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. It has been mentioned on more than one occasion in the papers, even.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is that so? <thought>It's been mentioned to me, too. Very recently. An incident involving the gas stove going out inexplicably, almost leading to someone's death...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, I think perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It's finally starting to fall into place. The secret link that joins all of these strange occurrences.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number six! Did you hear what juror number three just said?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Eh? What? Yes! Of course! I, I heard him mumbling about something or other.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There IS another explanation here, I believe. Something besides Mr Natsume's tea did, in a manner of speaking, pass the victim's lips on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">What? What explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder...did the police check the mouth of the gas pipe feeding the wall light at the scene? To see if there were any traces of poison there.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was curious to see what your floundering would result in this time...but the mouth of a gas pipe? Scotland Yard have enough to do without exploring such irrelevance.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'What a piece of work is a man!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you trying to say, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">What speakest thou? Prithee, is it not strange and strange? That is what I say to thee, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought I'd been quite clear. But let me put it another way... The strychnine could have been on the mouth of the gas pipe that feeds the wall lamp in your room. And that is how the poison came to enter your body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good... Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Are they tasty, then, gas pipes? Is that what he's saying?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Or is the gentlemen suggesting that the poor man was so desperately hungry, he tried to fill his belly with gas?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Perhaps no actress would perform a kiss scene with him, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">For shame, madam, speaking thy fancy! I assure you, I'm not such a buffoon that I have to kiss pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">To begin with, the lamp in the victim's room is high on the wall. In order to have placed his lips to the pipe that feeds it, he would have to be a contortionist. These are empty assertions. There is no possible proof that the man did as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's true...I have no proof that Mr Shamspeare put his lips to the pipe. However, I can say with some certainty...that on multiple occasions... ...Mr Shamspeare has been doing something in front of that lamp on his wall. ...And I have evidence to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...Alright, you've got our attention, lad. I'd like to see how you can be so sure of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">So would I! Let's see this evidence then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Now that I've got the jury's ear... ...I need to make this opportunity count!</thought> This is the proof that, time and time again, Mr Shamspeare stood in front of his gas lamp!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I don't know what you think that 'Well' was for.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do declare I should be the one saying 'Well'. As in: 'Well, it's meaningless.'</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I don't know what you think that 'How's that?' was for either.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I should be saying 'How's that?' I think. As in: 'How's that relevant?'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They make a formidable pair of double acts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough, thank you. It would appear that not one person present was moved by the evidence you produced, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Proof that Mr Shamspeare stood in front of that gas lamp many, many times... I'm sure there's a piece of evidence we have that makes my point perfectly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The mystery we uncovered when we investigated Mr Shamspeare's room is about to be solved, I believe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. And this time I'm going to show the court evidence that's irrefutable!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">What the...?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These are... Wait, what are they called? ...Yes! Skin prints that were found at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Skin prints, Counsel? I've never heard of such things. The justice ministry is currently assessing whether or not to permit fingerprints as evidence in court, however.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My Lord, this is an exciting new forensic technique developed by the great detective, Mr Herlock Sholmes! It reveals all of the places that Mr Shamspeare touched in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I've never seen anything like it! I mean that's black magic, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm... Well, if anyone could invent something like this, it's that great Sholmes fellow, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I agree. This month's edition of 'Engineering Thumbs' was quite fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We found skin prints in many places that you would expect. On the table...on the costumes... However, Mr Shamspeare also appears to have been touching some very unexpected places in his room. For example, here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Around the hanging picture there? Indeed, multiple handprints appear to be visible.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well, I wonder... Could he have been appreciating the artwork, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first, my colleagues and I thought the same. However... ...imagine standing with your hands where those prints are, and you would find yourself directly in front of...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">In front of... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Though the reason why isn't immediately obvious, it's clear that Mr Shamspeare... ...has regularly been standing with his hands to the wall in front of that lamp.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Right! What have you been up to, you nut?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd ask the court to recall juror number four's earlier statement.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Me? What did I say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You said that blowing into a gas pipe would make the lights in the entire building flicker. And now, if you'll recall juror number three's statement...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">What? Me now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When the gas worker who visited his home blew with too much force into the pipe... ...it caused all the lights and the gas stove to go out, and gas to start leaking into the rooms. Obviously, that incident was an accident. However, the simple fact is... ...if Mr Shamspeare were to have blown hard into the gas pipe here in his room... ...he could have extinguished every other light and gas stove in the building at will.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Crikey!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Are, are you suggesting that the man purposefully caused the gas to...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This curious photograph - or whatever it is - presented by the defence... The so-called 'skin prints'... Clearly, that cannot be accepted as any form of useable evidence in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">But, but it's an exciting new forensic technique! Developed by a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's nothing. A mere toy developed by an amateur sleuth with too much time on his hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Certainly, even research of this nature by the esteemed Mr Sholmes... ...cannot be recognised by the court as formal evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please, My Lord, if I may...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was not the defence's intention to submit the skin prints as formal evidence. We merely wished to present the results of the great detective's investigation of the scene... ...as a tool by which to explain a possibility to the ladies and gentlemen of the jury.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And, if the trial were to come to an end now... ...we should never learn the truth behind these mysterious handprints that everyone has now seen. I don't believe we can allow that to happen! And I'm sure the jurors would agree!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">...!</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">You're right! Whether those strange handprints are a significant clue or not...it's down to us to decide!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number three!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh yes! I do declare that the great detective's investigation results sound absolutely fascinating! And I want to hear what that shady actor fellow has to say about those shady handprints!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What's the matter with you two? That was foolhardy!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Well, I did say it, didn't I? And I don't like to break a promise.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">No! Wait! You heard His Lordship! It's not fair dinkum evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, well done, Mr Naruhodo! If just one more juror changes his or her mind... ...Mr Natsume's trial will have to continue!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Miss Susato. But I couldn't have done it without you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, it was you who identified the clue, after all. This is very much your success.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why, Mr Shamspeare...you seem to be losing your composure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just one more juror, Mr Naruhodo! You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Continue, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">We're the ones who decide if the evidence is worthy of consideration or not! Us. The jury.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Gas doesn't come for free! It costs a fortune to deliver it around the city and maintain the pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can we please refrain from all this talk of gas?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">There's an all-out attack underway here in case you hadn't noticed. Against my company's gas. And I'm supposed to sit here and take it, am I? I don't think so!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's really buzzing now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">All I've heard about our wonderful fuel is explosions and poisonings! What about electricity, hm? What about getting electrocuted? What about that? A little explosion here and there is nothing in comparison!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Any explosion...could hardly be described as 'nothing', madam. Nevertheless, the theft of your gas is deplorable.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">My point exactly. But the gas thieves aren't even the worst of our enemies. We have far more devious reprobates to contend with on a daily basis, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">More devious...? Who, madam?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Other gas companies, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Other...gas companies...? <thought>Not quite what I was expecting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">We generate gas and we deliver it to our customers fair and square.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Nobody is questioning that, madam. Altamont is an exemplary gas company.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">But there are other, unscrupulous gas companies here in London that don't even have any gas at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But if they don't have any gas, how do they go about selling it to people?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">You wouldn't think it possible, would you? But they steal our gas, you see. And sell that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They steal your gas? How on earth is such a thing possible?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Gas companies like ours deliver gas to people's homes via a network of pipes. But these devious reprobates...secretly disconnect our pipes and divert our gas into their own rotten pipes! Then they make a contract with the households supplied by those pipes... ...and take money for the precious gas that's rightfully ours, without us even knowing!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're diverting gas into their own pipes illegally... What a brazen form of theft!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">When we visit customers' houses to collect the money from their meters... ...we always have to check whether or not one of these devious companies has been up to its tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say about that, juror number three?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh golly! You mean me? I'm, I'm terribly sorry! I was just thinking to myself...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I really did catch him off guard there...</thought> Thinking about what the lady next to you was saying, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Well, yes. I just...got a little riled about it recently, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">An Altamont Gas worker visited my house the other day. To investigate the pipework. 'We need to ask for your cooperation while we carry out a secret check of your property, sir,' the fellow said. So I let him in...and do you know what he did?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm, um...afraid I have no idea. Please tell us.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">He proceeded to take one of my lights off the wall. Then he grabbed the exposed mouth of the pipe...and started blowing into it!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">What do you think you're doing, young man? You're giving away company secrets there!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh please! Everybody knows! But it was very nearly the death of me, I can tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I'll explain, if you don't mind. As I said before... ...these unscrupulous other gas companies connect their customers to our pipe network.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, but how does blowing into the pipes come into it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Obviously there's gas in the pipes. And it's at a fairly low pressure. By blowing air through the pipe, you can make the pressure drop temporarily. And if you do that, any lights connected to the same pipe will flicker for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see! In other words... ...if, upon blowing into the pipe, the lights of an adjacent property that has no contract with your company flicker... ...you can know that these devious scoundrels have been meddling with the pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Exactly, My Lord. That's it in a nutshell. It's the reason why we have teams of workers going around neighbourhoods to investigate which lights flicker.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">The trouble is, the particular worker who came to my house didn't know the strength of his own breath! He blew down the pipe with all his might! And you can guess what happened, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if he blew hard, then... Wait! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">That's right. The lights didn't just flicker; they went out! Along with the stove! Gas started pouring into the house!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What a disaster...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The gas supply must have been interrupted briefly because the man blew too hard, so the flames went out.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I'm afraid I yelled at the fellow. 'Are you trying to kill us all?!' I said.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>So by disconnecting a lamp and blowing into the exposed gas pipe... ...it's possible to extinguish lamps and stoves connected to the same network of pipes... And then when the gas starts flowing again, it just silently seeps into the room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, I think perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. This is almost certainly the clue that we've been hoping for! Juror number three! The defence requests that you amend your statement to include that information!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Oh, well, if you like. I don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Well I DO! That's our company's secret method of identifying the rogues that try to diddle us!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Like I said, madam, it's widely known already.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Juror number three, you will amend your statement accordingly.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Yes, My Lord. ...Although I'm not really sure what the point of all this is...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I had no idea... It's almost unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">It might seem unbelievable to you, but it's happening. All the time. Right here in the capital. It's very difficult selling something you can't see, you know. Very difficult indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, that will do! Clearly this is a very involved subject, but I feel we have digressed rather too much already.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I concur. Though if my learned friend wishes to become an expert in gas, I believe the subject will suit him well. To your new career in nothingness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you so much...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will turn your attention to the next juror's assertion, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Truth be told, the tea my wife serves up for me is a little...sketchy at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you mean it's poisoned?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">That's right. It's happened a tidy few times now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most troubling indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">It's always days like this one when I don't get any wages. I get in at tea time, see... ...and I see her doing it. My wife. She gets that devilish look on her face and she slips some white powder into my cup!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...and you drink it anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I was brought up proper, I was. If someone gives you a cuppa, you drink it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what happened to you? What did it taste like?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">It was God-awful, believe you me! Salty as hell!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then I think perhaps what your wife put in your tea...was salt.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">No! So...she doesn't even care enough to poison me properly, eh? Unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's move on, please!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">If nothing else passed the victim's lips that night, there's no other explanation, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Does that mean that if the victim could be shown to have ingested something else, you'd change your leaning?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? Sorry? What's that now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um...I was just saying, if the victim did actually eat or drink something else on the night-</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">What's the matter with you?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I said, 'If nothing else passed the victim's lips that night, there's no other explanation, is there?' Haven't you been listening to me at all?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I feel there's an English expression about a pot and a kettle that's appropriate here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Compared to the other jurors who don't even appear to have anything to say about the case at all... ...it would seem that this elderly gentleman has been listening to the proceedings far more intently!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I-I suppose. The trouble is...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...He has selective hearing?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Exactly. But still...</thought> This juror may well be the key to the breakthrough that we so desperately need!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements clearly contradict each other!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! To whose statements do you refer, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number six! Did you hear what juror number three just said?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Eh? What? Yes! Of course! I, I heard him mumbling about something or other.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There IS another explanation here, I believe. Something besides Mr Natsume's tea did, in a manner of speaking, pass the victim's lips on the night in question.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">What? What explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder...did the police check the mouth of the gas pipe feeding the wall light at the scene? To see if there were any traces of poison there.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was curious to see what your floundering would result in this time...but the mouth of a gas pipe? Scotland Yard have enough to do without exploring such irrelevance.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'What a piece of work is a man!'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you trying to say, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">What speakest thou? Prithee, is it not strange and strange? That is what I say to thee, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought I'd been quite clear. But let me put it another way... The strychnine could have been on the mouth of the gas pipe that feeds the wall lamp in your room. And that is how the poison came to enter your body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good... Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Are they tasty, then, gas pipes? Is that what he's saying?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Or is the gentlemen suggesting that the poor man was so desperately hungry, he tried to fill his belly with gas?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Perhaps no actress would perform a kiss scene with him, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">For shame, madam, speaking thy fancy! I assure you, I'm not such a buffoon that I have to kiss pipes!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">To begin with, the lamp in the victim's room is high on the wall. In order to have placed his lips to the pipe that feeds it, he would have to be a contortionist. These are empty assertions. There is no possible proof that the man did as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's true...I have no proof that Mr Shamspeare put his lips to the pipe. However, I can say with some certainty...that on multiple occasions... ...Mr Shamspeare has been doing something in front of that lamp on his wall. ...And I have evidence to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...Alright, you've got our attention, lad. I'd like to see how you can be so sure of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">So would I! Let's see this evidence then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Now that I've got the jury's ear... ...I need to make this opportunity count!</thought> This is the proof that, time and time again, Mr Shamspeare stood in front of his gas lamp!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">I don't know what you think that 'Well' was for.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">I do declare I should be the one saying 'Well'. As in: 'Well, it's meaningless.'</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">I don't know what you think that 'How's that?' was for either.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I should be saying 'How's that?' I think. As in: 'How's that relevant?'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They make a formidable pair of double acts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough, thank you. It would appear that not one person present was moved by the evidence you produced, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Proof that Mr Shamspeare stood in front of that gas lamp many, many times... I'm sure there's a piece of evidence we have that makes my point perfectly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The mystery we uncovered when we investigated Mr Shamspeare's room is about to be solved, I believe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. And this time I'm going to show the court evidence that's irrefutable!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">What the...?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These are... Wait, what are they called? ...Yes! Skin prints that were found at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Skin prints, Counsel? I've never heard of such things. The justice ministry is currently assessing whether or not to permit fingerprints as evidence in court, however.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My Lord, this is an exciting new forensic technique developed by the great detective, Mr Herlock Sholmes! It reveals all of the places that Mr Shamspeare touched in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I've never seen anything like it! I mean that's black magic, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm... Well, if anyone could invent something like this, it's that great Sholmes fellow, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I agree. This month's edition of 'Engineering Thumbs' was quite fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We found skin prints in many places that you would expect. On the table...on the costumes... However, Mr Shamspeare also appears to have been touching some very unexpected places in his room. For example, here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Around the hanging picture there? Indeed, multiple handprints appear to be visible.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Well, I wonder... Could he have been appreciating the artwork, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At first, my colleagues and I thought the same. However... ...imagine standing with your hands where those prints are, and you would find yourself directly in front of...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">In front of... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Though the reason why isn't immediately obvious, it's clear that Mr Shamspeare... ...has regularly been standing with his hands to the wall in front of that lamp.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Right! What have you been up to, you nut?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd ask the court to recall juror number four's earlier statement.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Me? What did I say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You said that blowing into a gas pipe would make the lights in the entire building flicker. And now, if you'll recall juror number three's statement...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">What? Me now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When the gas worker who visited his home blew with too much force into the pipe... ...it caused all the lights and the gas stove to go out, and gas to start leaking into the rooms. Obviously, that incident was an accident. However, the simple fact is... ...if Mr Shamspeare were to have blown hard into the gas pipe here in his room... ...he could have extinguished every other light and gas stove in the building at will.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Crikey!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Are, are you suggesting that the man purposefully caused the gas to...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">This curious photograph - or whatever it is - presented by the defence... The so-called 'skin prints'... Clearly, that cannot be accepted as any form of useable evidence in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">But, but it's an exciting new forensic technique! Developed by a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's nothing. A mere toy developed by an amateur sleuth with too much time on his hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Certainly, even research of this nature by the esteemed Mr Sholmes... ...cannot be recognised by the court as formal evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="Susato"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please, My Lord, if I may...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was not the defence's intention to submit the skin prints as formal evidence. We merely wished to present the results of the great detective's investigation of the scene... ...as a tool by which to explain a possibility to the ladies and gentlemen of the jury.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And, if the trial were to come to an end now... ...we should never learn the truth behind these mysterious handprints that everyone has now seen. I don't believe we can allow that to happen! And I'm sure the jurors would agree!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">...!</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">You're right! Whether those strange handprints are a significant clue or not...it's down to us to decide!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number three!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Oh yes! I do declare that the great detective's investigation results sound absolutely fascinating! And I want to hear what that shady actor fellow has to say about those shady handprints!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What's the matter with you two? That was foolhardy!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Well, I did say it, didn't I? And I don't like to break a promise.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">No! Wait! You heard His Lordship! It's not fair dinkum evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, well done, Mr Naruhodo! If just one more juror changes his or her mind... ...Mr Natsume's trial will have to continue!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Miss Susato. But I couldn't have done it without you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, it was you who identified the clue, after all. This is very much your success.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why, Mr Shamspeare...you seem to be losing your composure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just one more juror, Mr Naruhodo! You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Continue, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">I don't believe in breaking promises. We can't come to a decision whilst so much is up in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, this is hopeless... There's no way for me to appeal to these people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do think that the only way we shall overcome this difficult situation... ...is by exposing the way in which Mr Shamspeare was really poisoned. We have to prove that it happened some other way, and not via Mr Natsume's tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. The trouble is... ...I have absolutely no idea how it did happen.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...I wonder if perhaps there's something...you might have forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's important to watch everyone involved and pursue people if they react to something someone else says. If you'd like me to remind you exactly what I mean, I'd be more than happy to, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Once again, Soseki-san's fate is entirely in my hands here. I probably owe it to my client to hear any advice my assistant may be able to offer. So perhaps I ought to let Susato-san remind me. Then again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">When a particular juror is talking, the other jurors will be listening, naturally. Most of the time, when people are speaking themselves, they are careful not to give away more than they want to. But when they're listening to others speak, they tend to be less guarded.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, that's very true. </line>
<line speaker="Susato">So, if you see people reacting strangely in an unguarded moment, you must 'Pursue' them to find out why! Here, take a look at this, Mr Naruhodo... When you press jurors about their assertions, a marker appears in the centre of the screen. By using [D-pad / A D], you can move the marker and see how other jurors are reacting to what's being said. And if you find a particular juror seems to be reacting oddly, you can 'Pursue' him or her about it. By catching people off guard, you may be able to glean new and potentially useful information!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Alright, I've got it. <thought>Press, and then if something seems odd... ...slide the marker with [D-pad / A D] to see if one of the other jurors is having an unusual reaction. If so, 'Pursue' that juror!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Actually, I don't think there's any need. It's vital that we start trying to change these jurors' minds as soon as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course. I'm sure you're right. But if you decide you would like your memory refreshed, you need only ask, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, this is hopeless... There's no way for me to appeal to these people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do think that the only way we shall overcome this difficult situation... ...is by exposing the way in which Mr Shamspeare was really poisoned. We have to prove that it happened some other way, and not via Mr Natsume's tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. The trouble is... ...I have absolutely no idea how it did happen.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Are there no clues at all that might help us?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All we can do is keep pressing these jurors for more information, I suppose. <thought>Because we simply have to find some way to turn this situation around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Or Mr Natsume will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously I'm talking about the defendant, Mr Soseki Natsume himself!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">The defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the very beginning of the proceedings here in court yesterday, Mr Natsume said the following:</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">MY LODGINGS! THERE'S BEEN A WHOLE SERIES OF STRANGE HAPPENINGS IN MY LODGINGS!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Even on that fateful night, it happened. When I returned from Mr Shamspeare's room... ...I lit my gas stove and climbed into bed, but before long... ...the stove went out, AND SOMEBODY TRIED TO KILL ME!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the night in question, the gas in the defendant's room went out. So I ask the court...was that a mere coincidence, or not?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Good golly!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">So that Shamspeare fellow blew air into the gas pipe to make the man's stove go out on purpose?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Now hold your horses there. What would he do that for?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Foreman!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What the...?! What is it, man?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We cannot allow judgement to be passed whilst this doubt remains. It's true that I don't have conclusive evidence yet. However... ...you must surely agree...there is more to this case than meets the eye!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Agh! ......... ...Fair enough. Like I said at the outset... ...I'm a man of logic, first and foremost.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's four jurors leaning towards not guilty, My Lord. We've overturned the decision. Therefore...the defence calls for the trial to continue!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As the defence has rightfully indicated... ...the summation examination has concluded with a majority of jurors altering their decisions. Two jury members now call guilty. Four now call not guilty. Therefore, the jury's opinion is conflicted, and, in accordance with the law of this land... ...I hereby order the continuation of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr William Shamspeare!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My Lord! How can thy humble Shamspeare serve thee?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What say you in response to the various revelations made during the summation examination?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">So God mend me, I do solemnly swear... ...I recall aught of either the lamp or the pipe!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">But your handprints have made a tidy mess all over the wall there. How d'you explain that, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I am done with this. The dignity of this great courtroom has been sullied enough already...juror number five.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Who, me?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As I went to some pains to point out already... ...a print from the self-professed detective's toy has no place in a British court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As such, whether or not this man did indeed stand before the gas lamp with his hands against the wall... ...remains, at this time, unestablished conjecture. You would all do well to remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Ah.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the prosecution must concede that it would be extremely simple to verify! Just order the mouth of the gas pipe feeding that lamp in Mr Shamspeare's room to be examined! If there are traces of poison there...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Therefore it shouldn't be beyond your wit to imagine that even if poison were to have been spread on the pipe... ...it would have completely evaporated by now, making any analysis impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! <thought>I didn't think of that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, Counsel...I fail to see what could possibly have motivated the man to do as you describe. Why on earth would this fellow have wanted to blow air into the gas pipework where he lived?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... There's only one possibility that I can think of. And that is... ...to use the leaking gas to commit murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! ...Counsel! Precisely whose life do you propose this man was plotting to end?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The answer couldn't be simpler. Now we've unravelled the mystery this far...</thought> Mr Shamspeare wanted to end the life of...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. The nature of cases like these is that they're full of wild twists and turns!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UWAAAGH! <thought>Alright, keep calm... Just try to think... I know there's someone who's been complaining of troubles with the gas supply recently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If a gas lamp were to go out, it would be noticed immediately, of course. But a gas stove, on the other hand, could be silently extinguished by the killer without anyone noticing.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I live round those parts myself, so I know what it's like. I can tell you, trying to sleep without the stove lit is pretty much suicide. You'd freeze to death in no time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Garrideb, the landlord, has a large fireplace in his part of the residence, on the top floor. In other words, it wasn't the landlord, but a fellow lodger whose life Mr Shamspeare was trying to end.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Outrageous!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm talking, of course...about the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Natsume isn't the villain in this case... ...he's the victim this man was trying to murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? How can you still claim that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let us indulge your fancies for a moment and assume that there was indeed poison on the mouth of the gas pipe. The question that then arises...is who put it there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Who DID put it there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The only logical conclusion is that the person responsible... ...was aware of this man's trickery with the gas supply and his intent to kill.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that would indeed seem logical. If the assailant were unaware, how would he or she have known to lace the end of the gas pipe with poison?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So now we must ask...how could anyone have known of Mr Shamspeare's murderous designs?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! You mean to suggest...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Naturally, the sole possible answer to that question couldn't be more obvious. Only the man whose life was being threatened could possibly have known.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words... ...the person who put the poison on the gas pipe, in what was a clear retaliatory attack... ...can only have been the accused, Mr Soseki Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Whatever Mr William Shamspeare may or may not have contrived to do... ...he was nevertheless the victim of a potentially lethal poison attack. And the only person who could possibly have perpetrated that attack...is the accused, Mr Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">...!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The defence counsel's theorising has failed to avert suspicion from the accused. Far from it. In fact, now that a clear motive for the poisoning has been successfully established... ...that suspicion is greater than ever. Would you not agree...my Nipponese friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah......... AAAAAAAAAAAARGH!!! <thought>How did he manage to turn that around on me so rapidly?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, you must respond! Otherwise the members of the jury may very well change their leanings against us again. And this may be our last chance to gain the advantage!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What advantage?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it would seem that somebody put poison on the gas pipe in Mr Shamspeare's room. So we must name that person now and absolve Mr Natsume of guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...name the true culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I know it might sound impossible. But if we fail to do that... ...I have no doubt that Mr Natsume's fate will be sealed once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>As it happens... ...one possible culprit does come to mind. The evidence... The poison... It's all pointing to a particular person now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution calls for the jury to consider their leanings again. I trust you'll make the correct choice this time... Mr Foreman.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Hm? What? ...Oh, don't you worry! We know exactly what-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There is one other person who I believe could have been involved in all of this. The true culprit of this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The, the true culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A term found only in second-rate novels featuring third-rate 'great detectives'...my Nipponese friend. But why not? This farce has gone on for so long already, I see no reason to cut it short before its disappointing climax.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Tell us, my learned Nipponese friend...what is your latest theory? Who is the so-called 'true culprit' of this crime?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Highly suspicious, I would say, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Perhaps, my learned Nipponese friend, you should turn those wide eyes of suspicion on yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">For it seems to me that your reckless reasoning makes you, far more than anyone else you could name... ...a very dangerous man indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, please! You must concentrate!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I was trying to!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then you must concentrate harder!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh. Harsh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The name of the person responsible for the poison that afflicted Mr Shamspeare is, I believe... ...Miss Olive Green.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Miss Olive Green... Miss...Olive Green... I do feel as though I've heard that name in the recent past, Counsel. But I don't recall where...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Miss Olive Green? The woman from six days ago... The victim in the recent case of stabbing on Briar Road. An incident for which Mr Natsume was arrested, I hasten to add.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Of course, yes! Miss Green. She was left comatose for some three days, I believe. But I hear she regained consciousness two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And I hardly need remind the court that Mr Shamspeare's poisoning took place three days ago. Given that the woman was lying comatose in a hospital bed at the time, she appears to have a rather fine alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>True, on the night that the incident occurred, Miss Green was in hospital, unconscious. So on the face of it, it would seem that she couldn't possibly be responsible. But still...</thought> My colleagues and I visited Miss Green in hospital yesterday. And we found her to be in possession of a bottle of poison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! She had poison?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And there is another fact that links Miss Green to this case as well. The defence requests that she be brought to the witness stand in order to explain the details to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Tell me, Mr Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My Lord! Pray, what be thy bidding?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you acquainted with Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh? N-No, never heard of her...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Judging by the look on Mr Shamspeare's face... ...I think perhaps he genuinely doesn't know her. At least...not by name.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...As the voice of Her Majesty's prosecution here, I adhere to my word. We will see my learned Nipponese friend's farce through to its conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I appreciate that!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The prosecution requests a short recess, My Lord. In order to subpoena the witness and bring her here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Miss Olive Green...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Indeed, My Lord. One hour should be sufficient.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I grant the request.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Excellent...I hope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defence has made a most extraordinary accusation, I must say. But at the present time, I feel the prosecution's argument remains largely uncontested. Accordingly, I'm afraid the defendant and his culpability remain the sole subject of this court's attention. Thank you, Counsels. We reconvene in one hour. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Joyful, Jubilant, Jumping Jacks!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Natsume! I'm so pleased for you!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Locum Student Mr Naruhodo Esquire! And Non-Locum Judicial Assistant Miss Mikotoba Esquiress! Now, finally...at long last, there can be proof... Proof that I'm innocent, and...proof that my tea is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah! Good morning, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">ARGH! HERR LOCK SHOLMES! May you drink my tepid tea and fall forever silent!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I thought the tea was innocent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Sholmes, you came! How wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Please, save your derision. I know what you're all thinking. '"Good morning," he says? When it's very nearly time for luncheon...' Your scorn is written clearly across your faces.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nobody said or thought anything of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The truth is, I was determined that today would be the day. As sleep seduced me last night, I thought... ...'Tomorrow for once I shall not oversleep! I'll rise early and be present in court to support my companions!' Such spirited determination has a beauty all of its own, does it not?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And then I began to muse on the subject. 'Why do people oversleep?' I queried. 'Why, time after time, do they make the same foolish blunder?' And the answer came to me at once. It's so delightfully simple: people oversleep...because they sleep! Well? Is that not an astute insight into the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...yes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Upon which realisation, I attempted an experiment. I didn't sleep a wink all night! And the results... By first light, I was exhausted and began to be assailed by fits of drowsiness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shocking...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And so, the conclusion of last night's experiment is this: a good night's sleep is quite simply essential!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think most of us probably knew that already.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What others presuppose, I prove by experimentation. That, my dear fellow, is the scientific method! Ah yes, and one more thing... Do you remember this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course. It's the poison that Miss Green was about to drink at the hospital yesterday. Oh! You didn't manage to...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was a laborious task, as the bottle was near empty. But such inconveniences do not hinder Sholmes. I managed to confirm that it contained strychnine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...So I was right.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps. Though of course such circumstantial evidence doesn't prove Miss Green's guilt. I shall leave the bottle in your care now. But licking the inside of the neck is not recommended!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah...could I have a word?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is the poison we've been hearing so much about. Strychnine... There are a few remnants on the bottom of the bottle here, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You mustn't be tempted to try it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course not. ...As long as we don't lose this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... No! Even if we lose the trial! ......... No! We mustn't lose the trial in the first place, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Make your mind up, Susato-san...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Gregson! How good of you to come!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">......... Forget it. Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait a minute, Inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I, um...don't wish to make a nuisance of myself...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>From the look on your face, I'd say it's someone else who you think is making a nuisance of himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear inspector, please, speak freely. Pretend that I'm not here.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Believe me, if I could do that, life would be a whole lot simpler for me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you have the results, Inspector? Of the investigation of Mr Shamspeare's room?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Not yet. Shouldn't be long now, though. No, I'm here about somethin' else. That dead convict, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, you mean the man from this newspaper article we discovered yesterday in Mr Shamspeare's room?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A man by the name of... Ah yes, Selden.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I went through the archives at the Yard and dug out the fellow's file. There's somethin' in there that... Well, it caught my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Something caught your eye? What, Inspector? What?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">I've copied out the relevant parts for you. So you can read it for yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">These documents... ...include the details that were in the newspaper cutting we found in Mr Shamspeare's room. I'll rearrange everything in the Court Record so we don't have duplicate information!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why are you giving us a copy of this important file, though?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Well...you're the ones who turned up the clue in the first place, aren't you? I'm just makin' sure things get handled in the proper fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Scotland Yard's workings are so wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, my dear fellows! And the inspector here is a shining diamond in its crown!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A shining diamond...in the rough, maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Look, I just don't wanna be beholden to a lawyer, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel for the Defence! And the defendant! Court proceedings are about to resume. Make your way into the courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, I shall leave you then. I'll be listening with interest from the public gallery. Not nodding off at all! Certainly not!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm rather tired of seeing Mr Moustache in floods of tears, personally. So...the best of luck to you!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">LOCUM STUDENT MR NARUHODO ESQUIRE!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Mr Natsume?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">It's, it's time, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...this is it. Miss Olive Green and Mr William Shamspeare... This is going to be the final battle. <thought>I won't really have saved Soseki-san... ...until I've exposed the whole truth of everything that's been going on. But it's all coming to a head now. You can do it, Ryunosuke. You have to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session again now. Before the recess, we heard a most startling accusation from the defence. Namely, that the victim of the case we heard here only a few days ago is the true perpetrator of this incident.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A reckless, rash and prejudiced charge of wrongdoing in my opinion, My Lord. However... ...the prosecution has tried to extend every courtesy to this amateur newcomer from dubious Eastern shores.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you! <thought>...For that backhanded consideration.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A rather cold assessment from the honourable British prosecutor, I must say. So, Lord van Zieks...is the new witness present and ready to take the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ready and waiting in the witnesses' antechamber, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff! Bring the witnesses in!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Witnesses...state your names and occupations for the court, please.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">William Shamspeare, my liege. For mine occupation, I can say only... ...that I be a tragic victim. To be pitied.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Currently unemployed, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm Olive Green. I'm a fledgling artist. ...Well, no... ...not a fledgling, really. A hopeless failure who's too weak-spirited to admit she has no talent, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Also currently unemployed, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What a coterie...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">My Lord, I am thy humble servant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that you are no longer merely the victim in this affair. The possibility has been raised that you are in fact the assailant, intent on taking the life of your fellow lodger. The part you have played in this whole business will be thoroughly scrutinised, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...I would for nought else, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And Miss Green...</line>
<line speaker="Green">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are aware of the reason you have been summoned to this courtroom today, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Yes, the officer did explain. He said I poisoned...this ridiculous buffoon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And? Do you accept the charge, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... I don't know anything about any poisoning. And...I don't know anything about this man.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Come, lady, die to live.' Verily, I know not thy prickly, pea-pigmented personage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let us proceed with the matter at hand. That being to ascertain whether or not Miss Green has any involvement in this affair.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It's all very strange. Very strange indeed. Why would you suspect me? I barely ever go to the East End anyway. It so happens that I passed by that neighbourhood six days ago, that's all. And on the night that this man was poisoned, I was still in hospital, fighting for my life.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, having been unfortunately caught up in the incident on the street outside the Garrideb household. An incident that rendered you unconscious for some three days.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I was struck in the middle of my back by a knife, through no fault of my own, and now I'M under suspicion? What other irrelevant things might I be suspected of? It's all very disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm, your energies may be better spent worrying about random knife attacks, I feel, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At this point in time... ...all that appears to connect you with Mr Shamspeare's lodgings is the Briar Road incident of six days ago. That's why... ...we would like you to testify formally now about exactly what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh no! The incident six days ago? You, you mean you want me to relive that awful accident?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unfortunately, yes. Please tell the court what happened that day. And of course...we will be interested to hear from you about your movements that day, too, Mr Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh? But, but what happened six days ago is nothing to do with me being poisoned!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us proceed, then. The witnesses will present their formal testimony to the court... ...on the subject of the incident that took place on Briar Road the evening of the seventeenth of February!</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was six days ago, at about 5 p.m. I was walking along in the snow when I was suddenly stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I was at the tavern on the eve of which thou speak'st, for I had bespoke my supper.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was the first time I'd been in the area. I had a little matter to attend to, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, a second incident inside a week at what I believe to be aptly described as 'the haunted lodgings'. One can only presume this is a most unfortunate coincidence...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Meanwhile, you say you were not in your room, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Twas the following morn when I did awaken that I learn'd of the dire events. Marry! What a commotion did the officers of the law make on the floor above mine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>When Soseki-san was arrested on suspicion of attempted murder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As suspected, there is nothing connecting these two witnesses but happenstance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's true, it does seem as though they're unrelated at first glance. But I'm not so sure... There's something lurking in the shadows here. I feel certain of it. And this is my one and only chance to expose it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, you may now cross-examine these two witnesses if you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was six days ago, at about 5 p.m. I was walking along in the snow when I was suddenly stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm well acquainted with the case. ...I'm sorry you had to go through that.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was awful. I still can't believe I was unconscious for so long. And I woke up to find that the case had been solved and the culprit arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes. The incident has been resolved already. Perhaps it would help you to consider it a bad dream that ended with your wakening...and should now be forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, I...I suppose so. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But before you put it completely behind you, Miss Green, I need you to remember the details one last time. You must tell the court exactly what happened that day... for us to arrive at the truth about this new case.</line>
<line speaker="Green">The trouble is, there's nothing to tell, really. I was just walking along the pavement.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Coincidentally, it happened to be just outside the house where the men in this case have their lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What were you doing there that day, though?</line>
<line speaker="Green">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The art school you attend... What's it called?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah...yes... It's the Thorndyke Academy of Fine Arts.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">According to Mr Sholmes, that's just in the vicinity of Brixton Road... ...which is some ten stops away from the scene on the Underground.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I believe you mentioned before that you also live on Brixton Road. Isn't that right? So why, then, would you have been walking along Briar Road in the middle of the East End?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Well...um... It's because, um... Oh yes, of course! I thought it might make a nice picture!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The witness is a student of art. City-dwelling artists can't all paint grand urban vistas.</line>
<line speaker="Green">That's, that's right! I happen to like the crumbling look of that part of town.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps 'quaint' would have been a less...grating term...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The point is, she's definitely hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. It seems she's not going to be forthcoming with the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If she's trying to hide why she was there that evening... ...it must mean there's a reason for her not wanting us to know. That's the key to this!</thought> And you, Mr Shamspeare... On the evening of the incident six days ago... ...would you tell the court what exactly you were doing?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Twould be my pleasure, sire.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I was at the tavern on the eve of which thou speak'st, for I had bespoke my supper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A tavern, you say? Which one?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">'Twas the Slug and Salad where I did tarry. 'Tis a jewel in the East End.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... And a little unexpected, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Slug and Salad offers unusually fine dining...for the locality, at least. Not an establishment you'd expect to be patronised by a man with not even a crumb of bread in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's true. The menu lists premium crusts of bread and glasses of water...in different levels of cloudiness.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I would have expected Grub's Grubbery in the local vicinity to be more...appropriate for your means. Watery soup and mushy peas. Or rather, soupy water and pea-like mush.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All equally appetising...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I, I just wanted to try some water in a different pub for once! What's wrong with that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How different can water really be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or perhaps...there's a more plausible explanation. A specific reason why he had to go to that particular establishment...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agreed. The fact that on that day of all days, he dined at a place he wouldn't normally... It does stand out. <thought>So Mr Shamspeare's own actions on the day of the incident six days ago were slightly suspicious... I wonder if we have some evidence that can explain those actions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Y-Yes, sire?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the day in question, is it not the case that you visited The Slug and Salad, a place you don't normally patronise... ...for a very particular reason?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I, I don't know what you're talking about. Pray, if thou hast some purpose, speak'st!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Very well! I will present the court with evidence. Evidence that explains why you had to be at The Slug and Salad that day. Namely...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Miss Green's card, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. It reads: 'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross. Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th. Don't tell anybody else about this letter or the meeting. It is a matter of utmost importance.' Mr Shamspeare... Your actions on the afternoon of Miss Green's stabbing... ...are exactly as described in this note.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Personally, I find it hard to believe that's a coincidence. Don't you, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Um...well...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Excuse me...can I say something?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">That card was delivered to me. It doesn't have anything to do with THIS odd man, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, well you'd think so, yes. But it's hard to believe it's merely-</line>
<line speaker="Green">My Lord, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May you what, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'd like to make something very clear about that card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, you may amend your testimony... ...to include details about the peculiar note.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Miss Green's card, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. It reads: 'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross. Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th. Don't tell anybody else about this letter or the meeting. It is a matter of utmost importance.' Mr Shamspeare... Your actions on the afternoon of Miss Green's stabbing... ...are exactly as described in this note.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Personally, I find it hard to believe that's a coincidence. Don't you, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Um...well...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Excuse me...can I say something?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">That card was delivered to me. It doesn't have anything to do with THIS odd man, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, well you'd think so, yes. But it's hard to believe it's merely-</line>
<line speaker="Green">My Lord, may I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May you what, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'd like to make something very clear about that card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, you may amend your testimony... ...to include details about the peculiar note.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shamspeare:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Horatio?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe it's a line from Shakespeare's play 'Hamlet', Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Be it a line from the great Shakespeare or from this... Mr Shamspeare, the message is the same: My learned Nipponese friend is wide of the mark.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hardly surprising given this witness's obtuse literary quotes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do wonder if there isn't perhaps some evidence that would explain why it was The Slug and Salad he visited...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think we have discussed this issue enough. Let us return to the witnesses' testimony, please...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Gladly I would thy bidding do, Horatio...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wish we did...but sadly I can't think of anything at the moment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If we find a clue that could explain why Mr Shamspeare went there, we must present it to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, absolutely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is all on this matter, Counsel, I would ask Miss Green to reiterate her next statement.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Remind me, which tavern was it?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Why, The Slug and Salad, sire. As I said to thee erewhile.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So on that particular evening, and no other, you chose to visit a different tavern to normal. And the reason for that is written in this card, isn't it? 'Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th.'</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">No! ...Nay! The green woman already told you! The note is nothing to do with this odd man!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's one admission, at least...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the undeniable truth is that the torn-off end of the envelope was found in Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words... ...one or the other of these witnesses is lying!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Let's return to the testimony, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was the first time I'd been in the area. I had a little matter to attend to, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What 'little matter', Miss Green? Please elaborate.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was nothing, really. It's not worth mentioning.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you remember, you mentioned it to us yesterday at the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was related to the card you were holding.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green! <thought>What was that?! She clearly just hid something behind her back!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">From memory, I believe the card contained a note that read: 'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross.'</line>
<line speaker="Green">Wh-What does that matter? This has nothing to do with Duncan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare! Do you have something to share with the court?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... 'To be, or not to be, that is the question...' ...Ah, pray, forgive me. The great bard's words springeth from within me with ne'er a thought.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Don't tell me... It's because you're possessed by Shakespeare's spirit, right?</thought> Hearing Miss Green's words a moment ago seemed to make you think of something. Something of relevance perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh?! Um...well... Nay nay, sire! 'Twas nothing at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Presumably you know the name, though? Mr Duncan Ross, I mean. After all, you were both lodgers in the same house.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I would it were so, but sadly nay. Lodging be a lonely occupation, sire. My lodging fellows be rarely known to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you haven't heard of him...even though he passed away in the room just one floor above yours?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Me, My Lord? Have I done something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The card that was mentioned before...containing the note. Do you have it upon your person?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I do, yes. But I don't need it any more. In fact, I should throw it away, really.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Before you dispose of it, the court will take it as evidence, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course... That's what links Mr Shamspeare and Miss Green! It's Duncan Ross!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, continue with your testimony, please, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Duncan Ross...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please, Miss Green. Tell us more about that note!</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... I'm sorry... ...there's really nothing I can tell you. But I can assure you, it's unrelated to all of this. Completely unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The truth is, you went out that day because that's what the note told you to do, isn't it? The instructions were for you to come to Briar Road at five o'clock that afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... I didn't think I should go at first. But then... ...I thought it might be a good opportunity to see what the East End looked like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Very well, if that's your final word on the matter. Continue, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The envelope has been ripped open rather carelessly, hasn't it? Miss Green strikes me as the type to open correspondence more neatly than that. ......... Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The way the envelope is torn... I'm almost sure I've seen that exact same shape somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh! You don't mean... Were you thinking of this piece of evidence, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! That's it. Try to match them up...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They go together perfectly... This torn-off end of the envelope clearly belongs with this card!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The envelope that contained the note to Miss Green and the torn-off card we found fit together perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! There's no question that they're from the same letter!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...that means... <thought>Something doesn't quite add up here, does it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you remember where we found this torn-off piece of envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, of course. It was in Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For some reason, it's suddenly started to bother me. ......... The way it's been ripped... I feel sure I've seen the same pattern somewhere else...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Ah! I wonder if it could be this you're thinking of! The envelope in which Miss Green's card came.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! That's it! Try putting them together now and let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They go together perfectly... This torn-off end of the envelope clearly belongs with this card!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The envelope that contained the note to Miss Green and the torn-off card we found fit together perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! There's no question that they're from the same letter!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...that means... <thought>Something doesn't quite add up here, does it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">Anyway, I was admitted straight to hospital, so I knew nothing about all of this business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you didn't regain consciousness until the day after the trial, did you? In the early hours.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Exactly! So how could I have had anything to do with it? And yet you still haul me in here to court like this. Honestly...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So at the time of the poisoning, the witness was unconscious in her hospital bed. Could there be a more airtight alibi, I ask you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Green">And yet, in spite of that, you claim that I was the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I, I, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Green">But you certainly haven't produced any evidence to support your wild claim, have you? None at all!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There you have it. The good lady has yet to see evidence...my learned Nipponese friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm working on it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, I will point out here that the jury's next decision will be final.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We're really up against the wall here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">This note was delivered to me at my address. It's nothing to do with the odd man next to me here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think you said that you received it the day before the incident, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There appears to be no indication of the sender's name or address on the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Green">It was in my letterbox and that's all I know, I'm afraid. I've no idea who sent it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross.' Who is this Duncan Ross, please?</line>
<line speaker="Green">A friend of mine. He attended the same art school as I do. He, he passed away in a tragic accident a month ago now, though. I wasn't sure what to make of that note, to be honest, but in the end I decided to go.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you found out what the information was?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Of course I didn't. You're not thinking straight.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Whilst on her way there, she was stabbed in the back. ...As my learned friend hopefully remembers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Yes, of course! <thought>She never made it to the meeting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's all the testimony I have to work with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's certainly no obvious link between these two, or the two incidents.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we can't just turn around and admit this has all been a waste of time! I have some pride you know, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps pride shouldn't come into this, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well anyway, I should at least make sure I've pressed them on all of their statements. ...And hard, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...did you hear what I said about pride?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, did you notice? One of the witnesses reacted rather strangely to something that was said before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. When you see someone reacting in an odd way, it's time to 'pursue'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I need to keep a closer eye on the people in the stand, even if they're not speaking at the time, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo! You pursued Mr Shamspeare wonderfully there!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's worked out well, hasn't it? We have a new clue at last! Alright! Now I need to pull off a really insightful objection somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well... ...as you've managed to expose this promising new angle, I wonder if you should perhaps try to develop that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Yes, of course! <thought>And yelling out objections isn't necessarily the best way to do that, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The day before the incident - exactly one week ago now - this note was delivered to your address. And upon carrying out the instructions in the note...you found yourself in hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, I did! It's terrible, everything that's happened to me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it is terrible. ...If it's all true, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Green">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, have a look at this, please. It's the torn-off end of an envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh...is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it so happens...that it fits together perfectly with the envelope of the note you received.</line>
<line speaker="Green">...! Wh-Where did you find that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh? In, in my room?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare... ...do you perhaps remember this note from somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Uh...well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your actions that afternoon follow the instructions in the note to the letter. 'Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th.' And so that's exactly where you went.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me ask you again, Mr Shamspeare... You already knew about this note, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you, Miss Green!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah! What did I do?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As this torn-off end of the envelope proves... ...the note was originally in Mr Shamspeare's room. So how is it that it came to be in your possession?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I, I don't have the first idea. I'm just a fledgling artist, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There is only one explanation! You broke into Mr Shamspeare's room and stole it!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">You did wha- Sorry- Thou hast WHAT?! You broke- I mean- Thou were in MY ROOM?! What on earth...do you want with me?!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would seem... ...that both witnesses need to testify again.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Urrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Miss Green...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Whilst you have the court's sympathy, I'm sure, for the suffering you have endured in recent events... ...anyone found to be giving false testimony in a court of law...will be duly punished. Please bear that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Yes...I know...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, witnesses. You will give formal testimony again now... ...on the subject of this curious anomaly regarding the note Miss Green claims to have received!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I do remember now. 'Twas a week ago, peradventure, that note was deliver'd unto me.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I don't know what you mean. You think I snuck into this man's room, do you? Why would I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... You now claim to have received this letter, do you, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Faith, 'tis so, My Lord! And I would swear to have set it upon the table in my humble lodgings. Yet...'tis clear to me now that since I return'd from the tavern that night, I have not laid eyes upon it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, that being the case... Young lady, it would appear that your testimony was-</line>
<line speaker="Green">A lie? Is that what you think? How unfair of you to think I'm the one lying!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm just a fledgling artist, as I said, and fledgling artists don't lie. That note was delivered to me at my address! Besides... ...we all know who the liar around here is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If that's true, Miss Green, how do you explain the facts? This part of the envelope was, without question, found in Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I don't see why I should explain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm a fledgling artist. My job here is just to say what happened, that's all. It's your job to give the explanations and the proofs. You, the fledgling lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The fledgling will do his best...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Evidently, my learned friend's cross-examination is our only hope of learning the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm ready, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then! The defence will now proceed with the cross-examination of the witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss Green clearly did break into Mr Shamspeare's room. There can be no question of that. And that's how she acquired the note.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Two facts that are starting to lead me to a possible explanation for all of this... <thought>And it's not a pretty one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I do remember now. 'Twas a week ago, peradventure, that note was deliver'd unto me. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And can you shed any light on the contents of the note at all?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Nay, sire! 'Tis as strange to me as a foreign tongue. Even with a knowledge of literature as great as mine own, verily, 'tis impenetrable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Mr Duncan Ross had lodgings in the same household as you. In effect, he was your neighbour, so surely you knew him, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Alack, if the choices be 'twixt 'I knew him' and 'I knew him not'... ...then 'tis with foreboding that I be forced to declare we were by some small measure acquaint'd.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Despite your claims, though, you followed the note's instructions and went to The Slug and Salad. Presumably that was nothing to do with your knowledge of literature...?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Marry! Nought will have the better of me, sire, save for the lure of curiosity. So 'tis true, I was compell'd by mine own eager heart to betake myself to the tavern. Yet in the end...my curiosity was not satiated.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">On the day writ therein, I did tarry a long hour at The Slug and Salad, yet nobody came. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So even after waiting for an hour, nobody appeared?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Well...um...yes, sire. 'Tis as thou sayst.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Really? You paused for a moment before you answered.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">In truth, when thou asked whether nobody appeared... I did suddenly recall...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? Do you mean to tell the court that somebody did appear after all?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I was not alone that night at The Slug and Salad, My Lord, no. 'Tis returning to me now... I did treat my lips to almost-clear water, and mine innards to a premium crust of bread. And all around me danc'd a great many companions!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Flies, sire! Flies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">In the name of Beelzebub, what were they?! Fairies, perchance, from a Midsummer Night's Dream, come to taunt me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think they were just flies...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I can't help thinking that the flies ought to choose something more wholesome to buzz around. ...Is that wrong of me?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Thereafter, on the evening I shared the company of the Japanese fellow, I did see the note had vanish'd. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When exactly did you notice it had gone missing?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...Such idle thoughts ne'er occupy my mind. I am busied with greater ideas!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In other words, you didn't notice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Several days passed between your outing to the tavern and Mr Natsume's visit to your room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it would appear that the note disappeared sometime in that interval.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...Such idle thoughts ne'er occupy my mind. I am busied with greater ideas!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And yet during that time, Miss Green was comatose in hospital, was she not? Clearly then, she could not have been stealing things from Mr Shamspeare's room.</line>
<line speaker="Green">...! Ah...yes... Yes, of course! It's, it's all some sort of misunderstanding! ...Isn't it, Mr Prosecutor, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... You have so far failed to give a satisfactory explanation as to how you came by the note.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I am not here to advocate for your defence, madam. I won't tolerate inconsistencies in your story. ...You would do well to remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh dearie me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's Lord van Zieks getting at...?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I don't know what you mean. You think I snuck into this man's room, do you? Why would I? </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems that this note was actually delivered to Mr Shamspeare about one week ago.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh...does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But for some reason, it ended up in your possession. I can't think of any way that could have happened except for you breaking into Mr Shamspeare's lodgings.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! I, I, um...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I won't deny that Miss Green's possession of the note would appear to defy logic. However...until and unless her involvement in this case can be proven in some other way... ...any further pursuit of this note is meaningless!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Miss Green could only have come to be in possession of the note by stealing it from Mr Shamspeare's room... And yet, there's no obvious reason why she would have done such a thing...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What if there was some other reason she broke into his lodgings, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! We should pursue that idea, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We're close now... I can feel it. We're so close to a breakthrough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Green">I can point out the villain here! And as for that torn-off piece of the envelope, I don't know anything about it. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you don't want to tell the court the truth about the letter, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm a fledgling artist, remember? Artists are nearly always introverted characters.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Introverted? Fie! This fledgling doth readily cast aspersions about my nature! Yet I am an angel! A seraph! Birds do harmonise with my song! The wind doth frolic on my wing! O pity! Wherefore dost thou accuse one so pure of heart, ample woman?</line>
<line speaker="Green">...Pure of heart? I don't think so. Even a fledgling like me can see you're just a failure.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Tragedy! Thou shalt not know the true heart of an artist until thine instruction hereafter by Death. O the days! O the years! Alas to enlighten thee, thou must wait so long and in vain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Interject with some clever remark! This is your chance to shine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm no Shakespearean actor, Miss Susato. No, as far as I can tell, the only thing that's going to resolve this argument...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Is evidence! Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's clear that Miss Green did in fact break into Mr Shamspeare's room, isn't it? And that's where she found this letter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Two more-or-less foregone conclusions that lead me to one terrifying conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Terrifying?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I'm afraid to say... ...that the outcome of this cross-examination may well change how we look at this case completely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yesterday at the hospital, we saw you with this bottle. And though the contents spilt during the course of our meeting, a small quantity remained.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">According to the defence's independent analysis... <thought>Mr Sholmes's chemistry set...</thought> ...the liquid that was still in the bottle was identified...as strychnine.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?! Strychnine?! The very same poison that afflicted Mr Shamspeare!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, you broke into this man's lodgings... ...for one reason, and one reason alone: To cover the end of the pipe that feeds the gas lamp in Mr Shamspeare's room with poison!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can, can this be...?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">You...broke into my room...to...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It may seem incredible to the court... ...but from the remaining clues, there is only one logical conclusion that we can reach. The person who attempted to take Mr Shamspeare's life with poison...was you, Miss Olive Green!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh dear... Oh dear... Oh...dearie... ...MEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or-Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! Counsel, are you seriously suggesting this woman put poison on the end of the gas pipe with intent to kill?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord. There's no other way to explain the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But if Miss Green did indeed set this odious trap six days ago... ...and the victim had put his mouth to the pipe that very evening as expected... ...the attempted murder would have happened six days ago, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Erm...well... <thought>That's a very good point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Perhaps not, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There was a significant police presence in the area that evening, on account of the incident on Briar Road. Local residents were being interviewed throughout the night as part of the ongoing inquiry. A circumspect criminal would likely have chosen not to carry out any wrongdoing at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord...van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And of course, the following morning, there was more activity at Mr Shamspeare's address.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">More activity? ...Ah! Yes! You mean his fellow lodger, Mr Natsume, being arrested on suspicion of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. And as the defence has already proposed... ...Mr Shamspeare was meddling with the gas in the pipe for a very sinister reason himself: To cause the gas stove in Mr Natsume's room to go out, thereby asphyxiating the occupant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But once Mr Natsume had been arrested, his room was under constant surveillance by the police. In the circumstances, Mr Shamspeare had no reason to blow air into the gas pipe.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">His intended victim being in a prison cell... With the need to tamper with the gas removed, the poison on the pipe lay dormant.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And then...three days ago now, the situation changed again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right! Mr Natsume's trial, which took place here at the Old Bailey, came to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The trial in which the man stood accused of stabbing Miss Green in the back...but was duly acquitted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That resulted in Mr Natsume returning to his lodgings for the first time in two days. And that very night, his gas stove mysteriously went out, and Mr Shamspeare was mysteriously poisoned.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Uhhh... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In conclusion, the poison that was present on the mouth of the gas pipe... ...had been put there in the victim's room some four days earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... MAAAAAAAAAAAARRY!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With that new understanding... ...it becomes clear that this letter was all part of the plan.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What plan?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The court will recall that the note gave instructions to visit The Slug and Salad at five o'clock. And that the recipient should tell nobody else. ...The reason for those instructions are now clear.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">To ensure that the lodger would not be at home at the stated time.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">To...make sure I wasn't home...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. While you were out, Miss Green could safely slip into your room... ...knowing that she wouldn't be disturbed.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">You, you mean to say...that letter...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Was written by Miss Green, yes. And in order to cover her tracks, she took it away with her when she left... ...just after she smeared poison over the mouth of the gas pipe in your room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! What do you have to say for yourself, witness?!</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Just who are you?! Why did you try to kill me?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green's motive should be obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's all tied up with someone whose name we've heard several times already during the course of this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So...that's what's behind all this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will share your apparent understanding with the court, please, Counsel. Which person is behind this woman's motive for the attack on the victim's life?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. The nature of cases like these is that they're full of unexpected twists and turns!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Or rather... ...it's that they're full of total nonsense delivered by wide-eyed imbeciles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WAAAAAAGH! <thought>Well... Surely I'd be more of an imbecile if I went around with my eyes shut...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps...you should keep your eyes on the matter at hand, Mr Naruhodo. It's somebody related in some way to Miss Green, remember. There are very few options!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, alright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Duncan Ross...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. Before the defendant, Mr Natsume, took up residence in the lodgings at Mr Garrideb's... ...somebody else was renting the room. Mr Duncan Ross.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I knew I'd heard the name somewhere else... It was all over the papers a month ago when the man died in strange circumstances at the 'haunted lodgings'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, that does ring a vague... Ah! Of course, yes! I remember now! The young man they claimed was strangled by the 'convict's curse' or some such!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sadly, My Lord, it wasn't a curse of any kind. Nor was it an accident. The man died as a result of Mr Shamspeare blowing into the gas pipe and causing gas to leak into the room. It was murder, plain and simple!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">AAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Hah hah... Hah hah hah... Well...what do you know...? The world...is so unfair... Curses... Curious deaths... That's all people care about... If it's an interesting story...they want to know. It doesn't cross their minds...that real people are involved... And once they're bored... Just one month later, once the story's lost its appeal...everyone's forgotten him...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">You, you mean you...? Duncan was...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Ross was Miss Green's fianc.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">F-Fianc?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You may not have known until now who Miss Green really is, Mr Shamspeare... ...but she's known exactly who you are all along. Because you're her sworn enemy. The murderer who took the life of the man she was to marry!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">MAAAAAAAAARRY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green, is it not the case... ...that in order to exact revenge on Mr Shamspeare, you smeared poison over the end of the gas pipe?</line>
<line speaker="Green">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This, this is all quite extraordinary! Am I correct in my understanding that you now accuse BOTH parties, Counsel? Each on different counts of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, My Lord, that's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Why would Mr Shamspeare have wanted to kill these lodgers as you say? You have completely failed to provide a motive to substantiate your accusation against the man.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Yes... Yes! That's right, Mr Reaper, my liege! I, I have been slight'd... 'Tis lies! All lies! I deny every utterance!</line>
<line speaker="Green">And you'll have to forgive me, Mr Naruhodo, sir... ...but I don't intend to admit to anything, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green...</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'm sure you'll think I'm being very rude, but... ...I'm not going to be sent to the gallows for the likes of this scoundrel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you broke into the man's room! If you didn't do it to smear poison on the pipe, what was your reason?</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... I...thought I'd have a look around, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Green">You're right, I suspected him. So I thought perhaps I might find some evidence or something in his room. Evidence that it was him who took Duncan's life.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">O vileness! O villainy! O tyranny! O rotundity of woman! But in any case, whene'er I leave my room, I do turn the key in the lock!</line>
<line speaker="Green">...That whole place is falling apart. The locks on the doors are no different. Duncan showed me once how to unlock the door with some turps and a piece of wire.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">O awfulness! O artfulness! O tyranny! O profanity of woman!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We will consider your trespassing on some future occasion. But for now... ...tell the court what you found. What evidence your search revealed.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Well...I spotted the note that I'd sent him lying on the floor. When I went to pick it up, I noticed something. One of the floorboards was loose, and underneath it, I discovered a secret hiding place.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we also discovered that hiding place.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Inside we found a newspaper cutting, a photograph and... an empty tin box.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah, yes, well the thing is...when I found it... ...the box wasn't empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! There was something in it?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes. This rather nice key.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! What are you doing with that?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What the...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Every ounce of colour has drained from his face...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Give it here! Give it to me now! It's mine! I inherited it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What was that, witness? What did you say? You inherited it?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah! Um...no, I... Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's all this about? He inherited that key?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Green">It was obviously important to you, since you'd gone to such lengths to hide it. So I took it. I don't know what it's for, but you took something precious from me, so I took something precious from you. So what if it means you can't open something now? I don't care.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Give it back this minute! GIVE IT TO ME!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Calm yourself, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Mr Shamspeare has tried, and in one case succeeded, to take the life of two lodgers now. Yes...his motive for doing so...is the key to everything that's happened!</thought> It's true that there appears to be no motive to support the accusation against Mr Shamspeare...at first. But considering everything we now know, I think there is actually something that could explain it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I need to recall every piece of evidence at our disposal. Everything we've seen and heard... Because I'm sure that I just caught a glimpse of the link that runs through all of these events!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, Counsel, I must demand that you present evidence to the court in support of your claim. What is it that you say can explain the motivation for Mr Shamspeare's alleged crimes?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is what, exactly, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...this is that thing, which... Wait... What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Enough.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... A single word and he puts me in my place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... A single word and she puts me in my place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It may not be conclusive proof that we can provide the court at this stage... ...but sometimes all that's required is something that calls the right idea to mind!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright. Mr Shamspeare is desperate to get that key back in his possession. What does that tell us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's...an official police report, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Selden file? How did you get hold of that?!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">S-Selden...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The now sadly deceased Mr Ross...and the defendant Mr Natsume... ...have only one thing linking them: The fact that they had lodgings in the same room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well yes... We know this, certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A room that was formerly occupied by Selden. Until, that is, he was arrested by Scotland Yard for his involvement in multiple burglaries.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it so happens that the convict Selden left behind one very substantial mystery when he died.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The some one thousand pounds worth of loot that he stole... ...which as yet, remains to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...yes, of course! It's coming back to me now. It's written in his file here.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">'A Thousand Pounds Lost En Route to Hell!' ...That was how the papers summed it up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it seems that one particular fellow inmate was with the convict in his final moments. It's not hard to imagine Selden entrusting that inmate with his most closely guarded secret: The location of the stolen loot. And perhaps a key...to unlock whatever container the valuables were in.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah! You, you mean this key is...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Shamspeare, it was you, wasn't it? You were at the capital offender's side when he died, were you not?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Wh-What are you talking about? 'Tis a false charge, I tell you! A false charge!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The name of the inmate who was with Selden at his death isn't noted in this file. But a simple telegram to the prison where he died would quickly tell us how false the charge really is.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, but even if it's true... ...why would the man be so intent on killing every subsequent occupant of the convict's lodgings?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's only one explanation for that, My Lord. It was in that very room...that Selden hid his loot!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So...it all comes out...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. And having established that... ...all of Mr Shamspeare's subsequent actions start to make perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When he was let out of prison following Selden's death... ...he made immediately for Mr Garrideb's lodgings in the hope of renting Selden's old room. However, the retired army man was unable to offer him the accommodation of his choice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because Selden's old room had already been let to somebody else: Mr Duncan Ross.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which is why Mr Shamspeare subsequently devised his gas-based plot to kill the occupant of the room. And when he was successful, he presumably intended to enquire about switching into the newly vacant room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">However... ...a certain jittery someone had beaten him to it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Soseki Natsume...? The defendant of this case, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you decided to use the ploy with the gas again, didn't you, Mr Shamspeare? This time to oust Mr Natsume. All for one simple and avaricious reason: To get your hands on the thousand pounds of loot left behind by the dead convict!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ugh... You... Agh... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........'S mine.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...? <thought>What did he just say?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...It's mine... ...That...loot...is mine...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Shamspeare?!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">It's all lies! I...don't accept any of it! Why should I?! After all...you don't have a shred of evidence! You can't prove...I killed that fellow! Forsooth! I'm the victim here, remember?! ...Isn't that right, ladies and gentlemen? If I don't admit to it...there's nothing you can do! You can't arrest me...for the time being, anyway. Verily! You can't arrest the victim, can you?! ...Isn't that right, ladies and gentlemen? I'm so close... I just need a few more hours... I swore to myself...that I'd get my hands on it... And I can almost taste it now... Do you really think I'd just give up?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's no question in my mind now. This man is guilty through and through!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But he seems so utterly intoxicated by the idea of that loot. I'm afraid that however hard you press him, he'll never admit to what he's done, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... There is a way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's one way I can finish him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He's already committed the most heinous crimes to get his hands on that loot. Which means all we need to do, is find it first!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A fine plan... ...were it not for the fact that the police thoroughly searched the room following the death of Mr Ross. If it's there at all, it must be very well hidden indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Without conclusive evidence, I certainly cannot rule.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If only... If only there was some way we could find the convict's loot quickly...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>This is the final piece in this complex puzzle. But I think we might have it in our possession already. Or rather, I think we may well have something that can help us find where that loot is hidden!</thought> My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence would like to make a proposal. About how to find the late convict's hidden loot. I believe we are already in possession of something that could give us a clue as to its whereabouts!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's our last chance... So it has to be worth a gamble. Besides...  ...we've used the same technique once already, and it definitely paid off then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, Counsel, let the court hear your idea! What do you propose we can use in order to locate the hiding place of the deceased convict's haul?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! We, we can use that, can we?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Van Zieks:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That is my proposal, my Nipponese friend!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAH! <thought>Ugh...his proposal was better...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've already found one secret hiding place during the course of our investigations, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I suppose we have. Though someone else beat us to it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The findings from the method we used are still in the Court Record, however aren't they? I believe it's worth proposing the same method again now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If I'm not mistaken... ...those are Mr Shamspeare's handprints on the wall of his lodgings...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. Exposed as a result of the defence's independent investigation of the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Based on a wonderful new discovery in the field of forensic science by the great detective, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">A great detective? Is that some kind of joke? Do you really think I'm going to be daunted by a man with such a ridiculous title?</line>
<line speaker="???">I should think the 'great bard' ought to recognise such a title when he hears one, Mr 'Sham'-speare!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps we should compete for the honour of most ridiculous title?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">AAAAAAAAAH! 'Tis Herlock Sholmes himself!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What are you doing here...great detective? You usual haunts are the filthy backstreets of the capital, are they not?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, Mr Reaper! It's been too long. And I see your complexion has worsened since last we met.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Sholmes! <thought>He DOES know Lord van Zieks then... Well enough to say something like that, in any case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Sholmes... ...though you may be heralded as a great detective by the population at large... ...that does not give you the right to come and go in my courtroom as you see fit.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If I may, My Lord... ...Mr Sholmes's newly developed scientific method has helped us to uncover vital clues in this case already.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Clues, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I call them 'skin prints', My Lord. My method identifies every location touched by an individual under scrutiny. It's the method by which we were able to ascertain this gentleman's gas pipe 'activities'.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You need only a small sample of something the individual has previously touched to make an indicator solution. In your case, sir, I used the teacup you had been holding. Elementary! So now...Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What am I to use as a sample to make the indicator solution this time?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you for offering to help, Mr Sholmes! <thought>When the convict was arrested, he was living in what is now Soseki-san's room. We need a sample to help locate Selden's loot that's hidden in his old room. What form will the sample take?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We will need a particular piece of evidence in order to create the indicator solution.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed? And you have the piece of evidence in question?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I believe so.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Upon my word, Mr Naruhodo, your powers of reasoning appear to be on the up. So...which particular item is the one in question? What piece of evidence do you propose that we use to help find Selden's loot?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have a look at THIS!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm... As far as I'm able to ascertain... ...you have very little confidence in your choice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Why, why would you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, once again there is no mystery. Did you really believe that the minute deflection of your left eye would escape my attention?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...but... ...I asked you to look at the evidence, not my eye!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we need to reconsider this from the start, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why do I feel as though Susato-san is studying my left eye now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm ready and waiting, Mr Naruhodo. The rest is in your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We will need something of Selden's in order to create the indicator solution to find his loot. And something the convict owned happens to be...in the possession of somebody listed in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Upon my word, Mr Naruhodo, your powers of reasoning appear to be on the up. So...which particular person do you have in mind? From whom can we obtain a possession of the late convict, Selden, to create the indicator solution?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let's hear your new and improved powers of reasoning at work, my dear fellow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Dear me. Your left eye just twitched. ...Are you currently concocting an elaborate excuse? Not some clever Japanese joke about a wet noodle, I hope.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAGH! You got meeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we need to reconsider this from the start, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Why do I feel as though Susato-san is studying my left eye now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm ready and waiting, Mr Naruhodo. The rest is in your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Green!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Ah! M-Me? What do you want with me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The key around your neck...if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That key belonged to Selden. There will be remnants of secretions from the man's skin on its surface that we can use.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Very true.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That is the sample we need! Using it we can create the indicator solution required for Mr Sholmes's Skin Print Seeker... ...and find out exactly what Selden touched in the room that he used to rent!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">AAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Shamspeare...as one 'great' to another, I assure you... ...if the late convict's haul is hidden somewhere in his former lodgings... ...I shall uncover it in no more than thirty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, Mr Shamspeare... ...the truth is well within our grasp now. And as such... ...you will never get your hands on Selden's stolen wealth!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Ugh...ugh...arrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Green">In that case... ...I'll gladly let Mr Sholmes have this key.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">No! Give the key to me! The detective shan't have it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's over, Mr Shamspeare!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">No... No...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're out of options now. There's only one thing left for you to do: Admit your guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Woe.........</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... I never intended to kill the man. I just... I just wanted to drive him out of the room, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you'd have time to find the convict's haul of stolen goods?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yet after you'd killed the young man, you still didn't move into the room...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I asked the landlord, of course. I pleaded with him. But he refused.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I was three months behind with the rent, for one thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Mr Garrideb really has had a lot to put up with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">And he had the gas repair work done immediately afterwards, putting the room out of action for a while. And then...this Japanese man swooped in at just the right moment to sign the new lease.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Mr Natsume. What unfortunate timing...</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Then five days ago... ...after the incident on Briar Road when the Japanese fellow got himself arrested... ...I thought I'd finally have my chance. But it wasn't to be.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, the scene was sealed off and guarded by the police night and day.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...if I remember rightly... ...Mr Sholmes spent the whole day in there reading books.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I couldn't even enter the room, let alone search for the loot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which is why, on the day Mr Natsume was acquitted and returned to his room... ...you once again tried your trick of blowing air into the gas pipe that feeds the stove in his room.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Unbeknownst to you, however, that action would lead you into a deadly trap.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">.........</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... William Shamspeare... How does it go? 'To be, or not to be. That is the question.'</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">From Shakespeare's Hamlet. Act Three, Scene One.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Well let me tell you, in your case... ...it's not to be. That is the answer. You deserve to die for what you've done.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... Haah... Urrrngh...</line>
<line speaker="Green">At first...I really did think it was just a terrible accident. I'll never forget our conversation the night before Duncan died...</line>
<line speaker="Green">...But that was the last time we ever spoke. That very night, he fell victim to the gas. If only I'd known it was going to happen, I'd have insisted he left that horrible room that instant! But instead, all I've been left with is bitter regret. I stopped going to school... ...but something kept drawing me back to the house on Briar Road. I saw a stooped Eastern-looking man with a moustache coming out of the house one day when I was there. He walked up the road to Grub's Grubbery for some food, so I followed him... ...and I sat myself down next to him. He had some watery-looking soup and started to pick a quarrel with the publican.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">That place is cursed, I tell you! CURSED! The ghost of that convict who used to live there...IS TRYING TO SUFFOCATE ME! I, I wake up in the m-middle of the night, f-freezing to death b-because the stove has gone out. The room is f-f-full of gas and I can h-hardly breathe... But the pipes have been checked. No problem there. It's like I'M THE PROBLEM! That's what they're thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Green">Then I remembered. A rumour I'd heard about how the gas companies go around investigating the gas installations.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A rumour? Ah...you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, everybody's heard the stories, it seems. About how they go around checking the pipes.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">How anything connected to the gas can be extinguished by blowing air into the pipework.</line>
<line speaker="Green">That's when it started. A little flicker of doubt in the back of my mind, that just wouldn't go away.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Once I'd had the idea, it wouldn't leave me alone. It plagued me day and night. So I bought this...at one of the black markets in the East End.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A...black market?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I'd never been. I'd just heard people talk about them. And you really can buy anything you can think of there... In some ways, being able to get my hands on this so easily made me even more determined. I had to find out one way or another. Was Duncan's death an accident...or was it murder?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And your chosen method for establishing the truth was simple...but highly effective. Smear poison on the gas pipe you suspected the man of tampering with...and wait.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If Mr Shamspeare was innocent, nothing would come of what you'd done. But if he was guilty...he would pay for his crimes dearly.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I found out the name of the man I suspected. William Shamspeare. And then I wrote him this little note: 'I have information regarding the death of Duncan Ross. Come to The Slug and Salad on Briar Road at 5 p.m. on 17th. Don't tell anybody else about this letter or the meeting. It is a matter of utmost importance.' If he'd done it, I knew that would worry him enough so he'd be sure to go. So I waited to see if it worked.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And of course, Mr Shamspeare followed the instructions to the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Green">I worked out where the gas pipe was straight away. So I smeared a good amount of the poison I'd bought all around the mouth of the pipe. All the time praying that the devil's work wouldn't be done, and that it was all just some wild fantasy. Actually, no... All the time praying that the devil's work would be done, and that the culprit would get his just desserts!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Three days ago... ...when you were first stood in the dock before me...this whole affair seemed relatively straightforward.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I certainly never imagined the depths of depravity that we should subsequently find lurking behind the scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It has been a long road...my Nipponese friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And one I certainly didn't envisage walking...with you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Nevertheless, together we have reached the light at the end of the tunnel, as it were. Miss Green...</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will henceforth be stripped of your freedom... ...as punishment for the attempted murder of Mr William Shamspeare.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes...I know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you, Mr Shamspeare... You will be tried for the murder of Mr Duncan Ross in cold blood... ...and the subsequent attempted murder of Mr Soseki Natsume here present.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Nrrrngh...</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Um, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Ah, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yesterday...at the hospital...when you and your friends stopped me from...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">From ending your life by drinking what was left in the poison bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Green">I, I wasn't myself. I can't even really remember what was going through my mind. 'To be, or not to be...' I suppose. That's a question that's so hard to answer, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well...personally...I'm glad of your being here, Miss Green.</line>
<line speaker="Green">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I'd like to believe... ...that it's a blessing Mr Shamspeare didn't die when he ingested the poison. For your sake, at the very least.</line>
<line speaker="Green">......... Because of you...I chose life, not death. And now you've made the truth come out at last... Really...I can't thank you enough.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Miss Green...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Soseki Natsume.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court declares that you are exonerated from all blame in this matter. Accordingly, I would call upon the ladies and gentlemen of the jury to present a verdict of not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">We are in full agreement, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, I hereby declare the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh...yes... Yes... At last...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Divine...justice? My dear fellow, if there were any divine justice in this world, you would shave that moustache.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">NO! This...HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH MY MOUSTACHE!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Some say that a luxuriant moustache is a sign of physical prowess, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">LOCUM STUDENT MR NARUHODO ESQUIRE! Once again... Once again... ...you've saved me from doom!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm very happy to have been able to help, Mr Natsume. Congratulations on your acquittal. Your second in almost as many days!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... I was first acquainted with and gained affection for English literature whilst in our great homeland empire. And then, by a twist of fate, I was brought to the land that bore the fruit of that literature. Only... ...the city of bricks and mortar became my prison. Try as I might, I never found my feet here. In the end, I confined myself to my room and lived life through friendly old books...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You've had such a difficult time, haven't you...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, but a week ago now... ...I dragged you out of that dark and dingy room of yours, did I not?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">You did, you did. And I've seen more of life in this week than in all my years to date. And for the first time... ...I feel I've begun to see the true face of the English that's so far been hiding from me behind the wall of fog.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow...there is nothing special about the true face of the English as you put it. Wheresoever one goes in the world, humans are human. There are few genuine differences.</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Yes, I think you're right. I've finally started to see that. And...I've come to understand something. I've worked out why I was attracted to English literature in the first place. It made me see... ...that whatever our nationality, we humans all have the same hopes and fears. We're all just doing our best to live.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well said. I've come to feel the same way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... I've made a decision, too. I'm going to cut short my study tour here and return to Japan!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Just when we'd become friends here in England... What a terrible shame!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh, I know. That does tug at my heartstrings, it really does. But I've decided I'd like to take everything I've learnt here in Britain and write something of my own. A...novel of sorts, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! So you'll be creating your own literature, Mr Natsume?! How wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">Oh! Well! No! I mean... I WOULDN'T PRESUME TO CALL IT LITERATURE!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why not? When that is precisely the definition, Mr Moustache?</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">.........I suppose you're right, yes. It will, in a way, be literature... But as of now, all I know is that I'd like to try my hand at writing. I have no delusions of grandeur.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I for one would love to read your work!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, all things considered, it may be for the best. After all, you have once again emerged victorious... ...from a battle with the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>That's very true...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And there is no salvation for a person in the dock when the Reaper is the prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The desire to return posthaste to the perceived safety of your homeland...is one I quite understand.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My goodness, yes! Faced with such a terrifying prospect... ...nobody would consider that cowardly, I'm quite sure!</line>
<line speaker="Soseki">......... ...But... But that's... THAT'S NOT WHY I'M LEAVING! I MEAN IT!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, well done, Mr Sholmes! How simply marvellous of you! To uncover the secret hiding place in just one day...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Wasn't it supposed to take thirty minutes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As I believe I told you, my dear fellows...skin prints are extremely useful in such situations. Wouldn't you agree, Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">.........</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Gregsy's been happily munching in agreement this whole time you know, Hurley!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Happily? I think perhaps 'humourlessly' might be closer to the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, it transpires the man fashioned a hiding place in the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what's in it? What exactly is the 'loot'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Let us look then, if you're ready. Let's examine the late burglar's haul...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What the...? What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It...looks to be some sort of neckband or collar...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A collar?! It's huge, though!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And look at all the gemstones set in it! I can see why it was claimed to be worth a thousand pounds! ...Perhaps I could have it as a belt...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Have you noticed on the inside there? There are some dark stains.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... You, you don't think... ...they could be blood, do you? <thought>I mean, there's quite a lot of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...On second thoughts, perhaps I won't have it as a belt.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then of course there's this emblem here... A large letter 'B' and a small crown...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What does it signify, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! I, I hadn't noticed that! Hm... I feel as though I've seen that emblem somewhere before, you know... Where could it have been...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That's enough of that, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>What's the matter with Mr Sholmes? All the colour has drained from his face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, Inspector, I believe you ought to be taking this, oughtn't you? It could be valuable evidence, after all. It must be kept safely under lock and key.</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Ah... Yes... Get your grubby hands off that, you lot! And hand it over. NOW!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well, that was a funny case, wasn't it? But it's all buttoned up now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you look very pleased, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I am! Because I was starting to wonder what I could use as the basis of this month's story in the magazine. But this case will be perfect! It's been so fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're talking about the latest instalment of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', I presume.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">'The Mystery of the Knife in the Mist' and 'The Moustached Man and the Convict's Curse' perhaps. I could make it a two-part story!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I can't wait!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Um...a word, please, Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes? What is it, Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sorry, but you can't write about this case. It's out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What? Why not? It's a great case!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then I shall have to insist that you limit yourself to the first of your two titles. The second must never be written. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...! ...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement was contradictory in a number of ways, I think you'll find!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In a number of ways, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. In a number of ways!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it would serve you well to concentrate your efforts on one contradiction at a time, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I made a bit of a mess of that. In a number of ways, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The witness's last statement is clearly contradictory when you consider this piece of evidence here! Yes! Undeniably!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say it's undeniable, Counsel, but I fail to see any contradiction here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think perhaps that itself is the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Time for a rethink...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! There are clearly grounds for being suspicious of that last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Counsel, but I fail to see why.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you know...I was just playing devil's advocate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes. You do appear to have something of the devil in you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the man merrily dishing out penalties...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number one! Do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Eh? Wha-What the blazes? What's the matter with you, you young hooligan?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! I'm, I'm sorry, it's just... You seemed to be lost in thought. Did something that was just said ring any bells with you, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">What are you trying to do? Make me look like a galah? Maybe my mind wandered for a moment, but it hardly warrants being victimised like this!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do think that as foreman of the jury, you should try NOT to let your mind wander...sir.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">It was only for a moment!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Even a moment is too long!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Tsk! Fine! It won't happen again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he was just daydreaming then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is there something you'd like to share with the court, juror number two?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Agh! Wh-Whatever do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. I'm sorry. I, I didn't mean to startle you. It just seemed that something that was said a moment ago maybe gave you pause for thought?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">......... When I'm startled, I become startlingly ruthless.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty! I do declare they're both guilty! This black-suited lawyer and the other Japanese man!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! I'm, I'm not on trial here, madam! <thought>Maybe I need to pursue these jurors with a little more care from now on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number three! Is everything alright?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Quite alright, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. No, I mean... ...was something that was just said significant to you in some way?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">No, not really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Oh, well, sorry then.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Not at all. Don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right. Thank you. <thought>Why is it that the more normal this man's responses are, the more I feel on edge?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid it's an occupational hazard, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...didn't think that being a lawyer was a particularly hazardous job... <thought>Maybe I need to watch more carefully before I pursue jurors in future...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is everything alright...juror number four?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Yes. Why?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, well...did something that was just said trouble you in some way, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Everything that's being said here is troubling me, if you must know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Is it any wonder? I've not heard a good word said about gas since the trial started! Really, my head's full of gas at the moment. Absolutely full of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That might be a little unhealthy, if you ask me. <thought>And if I'm not careful, I have a feeling I might cause some kind of gas explosion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Juror number five! Is something troubling you?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Is something troubling me?! Of course something's troubling me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Thanks to you, I very nearly died last night!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nearly died?!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I couldn't get that five bob I needed, could I? So the missus wouldn't let me in the house! I had to sleep out in the dog's kennel. I very nearly froze to death, I can tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear. That sounds awful.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">I spent the whole night dreaming that scrawny dog of mine was watching me as it sat there trembling!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gosh, you need that five shillings more than ever now then, don't you? For your wife and your dog.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">So can we please get this trial over and done with?! Either me or the dog might not make it otherwise!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll do my best for you both...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say about that...juror number six?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">THAT LAST STATEMENT! DID IT MEAN SOMETHING TO YOU?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">......... Hmph, must have misheard, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? <thought>Well done to whoever had the good sense to pick someone like him for jury service...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Oh! So you think the elderly should be confined to their bedrooms and left to fester among books, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I didn't say anything!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Hm? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, if there's a juror to watch, it's this man. He's dangerous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those two statements are fundamentally at odds with one another.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">My Lord! As foreman of the jury, I must object!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Being their leader, it's my duty to stand up for all jurors here present. And stand up for them I will!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur with the foreman. Counsel, I warn you, I shan't abide any pettifoggery!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Until you've got your facts straight...keep your pointy fingers to yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I thought I did...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We're trying to find inconsistencies in these jurors' statements, Mr Naruhodo. The key to it is comparing the different things they say before attempting to pit them against one another.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright. I'll have another go!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to say about that, Miss Green?</line>
<line speaker="Green">This is a very critical moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Green">No no, don't move! It's a very rare sight to see an Eastern gentleman in a British court, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Are you drawing me?</line>
<line speaker="Green">Yes, of course. Now, could you go back to that same expression you had before? With the cold sweat?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Let's just focus on the trial, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to add, Mr Shamspeare?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">......... 'Twas but a few sunrises ago...I got me to the nunnery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Forsooth, I could not rightly recommend the place so oft to my fellows without having seen it mine own self.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">Though, upon mine arrival, I was forbidd'n entrance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The clue was in the name, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Shamspeare">I did tarry a while outside the building, in search of some other way inside. But alack! I was arrest'd by an officer!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That was very illuminating, but perhaps you could just focus on the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Counsel, that will do! I've seen enough. According to the powers vested in me by Her Majesty the Queen, I declare no further examination necessary. I believe the court has been presented with more than enough evidence to pass judgement. As such, I shall be requesting the final decisions of the members of the jury. Are you all ready, Mr Foreman?</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">We're all ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, you will announce your findings to the court in turn, please.</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 1">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 3">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 4">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 5">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 6">Guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr Soseki Natsume, in accordance with the findings of this court, I pronounce you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I applaud the jurors for doing their civic duty and for finding a swift resolution to this matter. That is all. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>