
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Countdown</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are dark times, where the law has been reduced to rubble. And it's up to us to restore it to its former glory. "Yeah, I know what you mean. It looks like your target finally decided to make a move. Don't you worry, I got a trusty new partner onboard."</line>
<line speaker="Girl">Done!</line>
<line speaker="Robot necklace">Ready to go?</line>
<line speaker="Girl">You bet, let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"She's been with us for half a year, though I can hardly believe it. Anyway, her power will be our greatest weapon."</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Are you alright, miss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Yeah. It's for this very reason I returned. Time to bring it to an end."</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh heh heh! The best thing about bombs is how they erase and destroy... without discretion. Now all I have to do is pin everything on that little girl!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... Nope! Not feeling nervous at all! It's amazing what a girl can get used to! Even a tense atmosphere like this is no biggie!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You doing okay, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Apollo! Y-Yeah, doing great! Like, hum-a-little-tune great!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, yeah? Well, that's good to hear. Although... I could've sworn I heard your voice crack for a second there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oof! I'm THAT transparent, huh?</thought> Cracking? N-No, my voice isn't cracking! Nerves of steel, here, I tell you! <thought>This is Apollo Justice. He's a fellow lawyer at the office I work for. Apollo is the lead for the defense on this case. But I'm going to be there at the bench with him, doing what I can to help out. I'll do whatever it takes to defend Junie!</thought> Speaking of steel, how are you holding up? That explosion really did a number on you...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm just happy that you're okay, Athena. Although... I can't pretend I have no connection to this case. That's why I'm gonna see to it that Juniper's name is cleared! And I'm sure you feel much the same way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got that right! I won't rest until Junie is completely cleared of all suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="???">Apollo, Thena... Thank you... for doing this for me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...... *cough* *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Sorry about that. I always seem to go into coughing fits whenever I get nervous. This kind of thing never happens *cough* at home in the forest, though. *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>This is Juniper Woods. She's my dear, dear childhood friend, and she's also our client for this case. The news keeps repeating that Junie is the "alleged bomber"... But that's ridiculous! There's no way Junie would do anything like that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I brought you a little snack, Thena... Just a little something from my garden.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, thanks! So, um... Is this an orange or a tangerine?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It's an orange! My grandma says... ...that orange is the color of strength and endurance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it! Strength for the trial, right? <thought>Junie... You're always so good to me. Geez, look at me! Standing here clutching an orange to my chest with tears in my eyes...</thought> Well, don't you worry! We'll be so powerful in there, they won't know what hit them! Right, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... that's right. Come what may... this is one trial... we just can't lose...!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Apollooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ungh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Blood is seeping through his bandages! One of his wounds must've reopened. All this time, he was trying to put on a brave face, but he was really overdoing it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to start, sir. Please proceed to the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What?! Now?! But Apollo's in no state to defend!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*huff, huff*... Aaaaargh! I... I have to... defend Juniper!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What are we gonna do?! The trial is about to start, with or without us! There's only one other option I can think of at a time like this... But even if I called him now, he'd never get here in time! .........No, wait! There's something else I can do!</thought> Apollo, give me all the evidence for the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? What are you gonna do?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Bailiff.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Y-Yes, Miss?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The defense would like to submit a substitution of attorney petition.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're not seriously--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You just concentrate on getting better. I'll defend Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All by yourself?! Athena, stop for a sec and think about what you're saying! You've never once taken a case on alone before, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">¡No hay problema! I can handle it! <thought>I think.</thought> But I guess it's really up to you, Junie. Would you be okay with me taking over?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Um......... Sure. I believe in you, Thena, and that's enough for me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're worried for me, aren't you? To be honest, I'm pretty nervous, too. I think my heart might just burst out of my chest! But you're in no shape to stand at the bench now. So you'll just have to leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ ...All right. I can see your mind's made up anyway. I hate it that I can't be there... but I know you'll give your utmost to defend Juniper!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You bet I will! Rest assured of that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>My name is Athena Cykes. I'm still just a newbie, but I'm a lawyer. This is... only the second time I've taken the lead in a defense case. It'll be the first time I stand up there alone, though. But I have to do this! And I'm definitely not about to let anything bad happen to Junie!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is also ready, Your Honor. Uh-huh... And what is the meaning of this? I was under the impression that Mr. Red Monkey would be my opponent today.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, a substitution of attorney petition was submitted just a few moments ago. Due to the explosion in the courthouse yesterday, Mr. Justice is unable to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I see, I see. Not at all surprised he used that as an excuse to run away. With me as an adversary, who wouldn't want to feign illness in order to escape?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What?! The nerve of that guy! I'm going to give him a piece of my mind! W-Well, I would if I wasn't so nervous... Argh! This arrogant jerk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">You arrogant jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No! Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Is my hearing getting worse? I could've sworn I heard the defense say something just now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-N-No! You didn't hear anything at all! Especially not from me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How odd. I could have sworn I also heard something...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh, that would be my indispensable partner, Widget. He... sometimes blurts out what I'm thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. Well then. If that's the case, then it's a clear contradiction to what you just stated!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>A contradiction?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You just stated that you said nothing. However, if that device of yours says what you're thinking... ...then you indeed said I was...what was it? Elegance at work?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeep! <thought>Actually, it was arrogant jerk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">At any rate, what does it matter if it's a red monkey or a yellow monkey facing me? No fresh-out-of-law-school ROOKIE can defend this witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, I believe that's enough. Let us get back to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Of course, Your Honor. I'm more than ready to show this little girl why they call me the "Rookie Humiliator."</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I knew it. He really is an arrogant jerk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">Arrogant jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes. If you continue to insult the prosecution, I will remove you from this court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ack. I'm very sorry... <thought>It was just a knee-jerk reaction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then... Mr. Payne. Your opening statement, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Thank you, Your Honor. Now then. The incident occurred yesterday here at this very courthouse, in Courtroom No. 4. At that time, the trial for a certain bombing was being held in Courtroom No. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. I was presiding over that trial as well. And Mr. Justice was there as the lawyer for the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A bomb that was being presented as evidence suddenly went off during the trial. It was a terrible incident... and Courtroom No. 4 was completely destroyed. Fortunately, we were able to start evacuation procedures before the explosion occurred. Just a few more seconds and it would've turned into a horrific loss of human life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But there was, in fact, one death, was there not?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That is correct, Your Honor. When Courtroom No. 4 was examined after the blast... ...the body of Detective Candice Arme was discovered. She was to take the stand as a witness later in the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose she wasn't able to evacuate in time. What a terrible tragedy. I must admit, I stumbled at least ten times myself before I was able to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Maybe the court should see to getting you even shorter robes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim's body was found near the entrance to the courtroom. I suspect she stayed until the very end to help guide the others out safely. Your Honor, allow me to submit as evidence the victim's autopsy report... ...and details about the bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Okay, I know how this works. All evidence for the trial is filed in the Court Record. When I want to check something out, I just touch the Court Record Button (R</thought>. I'd better take a peek later.)</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Please call the accused to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............ *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defendant, are you feeling all right? You're looking a bit pale...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I'm so sorry! I was feeling a bit weak when I first arrived here at the courthouse... *cough* But I... I'm all right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie's really giving it her all! I'd better make sure I do the same!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. If we could please proceed. Your name and occupation, defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Juniper Woods... I'm... a h-high school student.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Woods, can you confirm you were in the courthouse on the day in question?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. I came to know Apollo Justice through my friend Thena... *cough* And so... I was there yesterday... to watch his trial and lend my support.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Something's wrong. Junie's really scared.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Did you know I'm also known as the "Defendant Humiliator"? It looks like I have yet another chance to show everyone how I earned that moniker!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Grr... Does his arrogance know no bounds?! I have to protect Junie no matter what!</thought> Hey you arrogant je-- Er, Prosecutor Payne!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmm? What is it? Do you want me to demonstrate why I'm known as the "Rookie Humiliator" instead?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Deep breaths, Athena. Don't let him get to you.</thought> P-Prosecutor Payne! Junie is telling the truth! Mr. Justice also backed up her claim when we saw him in the Defendant Lobby. And, Junie, he said that he was glad to get the lotus root you gave him, too.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">He was? My grandma says lotus root is good for your eyes. She says they can even help you see into the future!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They can? Then that's the perfect present for a lawyer! <thought>And if that's true, I guess he must not have eaten them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A sweet, meek girl like this, blowing a courtroom to bits? I must say it's very hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-That's not true...! I don't have any kind of motive...! A-And I-I didn't even know the lady who was killed...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I admit the investigation didn't turn up any connection between the victim and defendant. However, that doesn't matter. The only thing that does is that her objective was the destruction of Courtroom No. 4 itself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, what's that supposed to mean?! Why in the world would Ms. Woods want to do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mm-hmm. That's a very good question, coming from a novice such as yourself. But first, a question for the defendant. Have you ever been brought up on false charges?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What?! Wh-Why, yes... Yes, I have...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And did that experience cause you to harbor a grudge against the court system?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a valid point. We would have a single courthouse left standing in the land.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I concede the accused isn't the only one who might bear resentment against the courts. But Ms. Woods is the only person who could have committed this crime. Why? Because we have some decisive evidence that proves the defendant's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Decisive, huh? I'll believe it when I see it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It involves a very unique aspect of the bomb itself, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what exactly was so unique about it?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmm... Why don't we have Ms. Cykes answer that question?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mm-hmm. I notice that you appear to be very nervous. And, well, gentleman that I am... ...I'd like to offer you the chance to gain some confidence with such an easy question.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Could he BE any more condescending?! Really! What a thoroughly unpleasant man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">"L" is for "Loser"!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Harrumph! What did it just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Nothing. Not a single thing... <thought>Now, let's see... What was I supposed to do at a time like this...? Oh, I know! The Court Record! The information I need is somewhere in the Court Record!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, Ms. Cykes. Let's hear your answer. What was unique about the bomb that blew up the courtroom? Was it because it was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see... I believe it was because it was... ...in Mr. Justice's briefcase?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't tell me you intend to claim that it was Mr. Justice who committed the bombing?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? No! Of course not! I just thought maybe... he brought it to the courtroom by mistake...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What kind of person makes a mistake like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh... What in the world am I blathering on about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Let's try that again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The bomb was... In Your Honor's pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms Cykes! What in Sam Hill are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I tried to picture myself as the bomb... If I was in your pocket, you'd surely bring me into the courtroom, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The only things in my pocket are pictures of my grandchild! I would hardly have a bomb in there!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah ha ha... No of course not... That would be silly, now, wouldn't it? <thought>I think I'd better take another good look through the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Let's try that again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Payne! What kind of simpleton do you take me for?! It was stuffed inside a stuffed animal! Its evil intentions covered up by a cute exterior!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. Very good. Have a cookie. The bomb that went off in the courtroom was indeed hidden inside a stuffed animal.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There, how do you like that? Not bad, huh? I AM fine, just like I said from the start! I can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, as I recall, the bomb was stuffed inside a stuffed animal the whole time. I never even got to take a look at it. But what connection does this impish elephant have with the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The answer to that question lies in another piece of evidence, which I have here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what, pray tell, is this? It appears to be a little singed.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's a tail, Your Honor. The tail of a poor victim of the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is incredible! Are you saying it's Detective Arme's tail?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor is so very close, but no. It belongs to this stuffed animal. It's called the Phony Phanty. A rather unpleasant name, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's the mascot for a campaign to eliminate false evidence and false charges, is he not?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly. His motto is "Phony Evidence is just Trunked Up!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's so wrong on so many levels.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The Phony Phanty's tail is made of vinyl cloth. And we found something very interesting on its surface... the defendant's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>WH-WHAAAAAT?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The Phony Phanty provided the prosecution with all the evidence we needed. It clearly proves that the accused handled the bomb!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I... Uhhh... Eep!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But that doesn't make any sense! Why would Junie's fingerprints be on it?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does appear to be pretty irrefutable evidence... The court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Woods, do you have an explanation for this?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...I... I don't understand... I... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">How about you, Ms. Cykes? Do you have any plausible explanation to refute this decisive piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, I... uh... <thought>I-I can't do it! I can't think of a single thing! But I'd better come up with something... for Junie's sake!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">If you can't produce an answer, we could always go straight to the ruling, if you prefer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ack, no! I have to say something -- fast! Oh, no! I can't get my voice to work! Why now, of all times...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">As you can see, there is no room for debate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, it's you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry it took me so long to get here, Athena. Apollo explained the whole thing to me over the phone. He asked me to come help you out in his place.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Thanks for coming. I hate to admit it, but I was having a real rough time on my own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I don't know. I think you were doing just fine, all things considered. And you hung in there, giving me enough time to get here. Now, let's turn things around!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. Look who showed up out of the blue. If it isn't Mr. Phoenix Wright. You always manage to surprise me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Mr. Payne has called for an early ruling... ...but I believe there are still many things that need to be deliberated. How did Ms Woods's fingerprints wind up on the stuffed animal tail? How was the bomb even detonated? Until these questions are answered, I assert it's impossible for a fair ruling to be made!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You are absolutely right. Let us continue from where we left off. I assume you have no objections, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. None at all, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough, cough*............ ......*cough, cough* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Woods really looks like she's having a hard time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie's really struggling, Mr. Wright. I get the sense she's afraid of the courtroom itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah. It was understandably very traumatic for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Poor thing. And here she is, back at the courthouse again, being so brave. I'd like to make a request, Your Honor. If at all possible, I'd like to have Ms. Woods rest in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Given the defendant's condition... Very well, I grant special permission.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You go get some rest, Junie, and leave the rest to us!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Okay... Thank you. Sorry about this... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Phoenix Wright... I've been looking forward to meeting you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's been a while, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. You're more clueless than I'd heard. I do believe you mean, "How do you do?" For I... am Gaspen Payne! I am the younger brother of your longstanding rival, Winston Payne!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAT?! <thought>"Longstanding rival"...? When were we ever rivals, let alone "longstanding"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You'll see, Mr. Wright. I will cleanse Winston of the disgrace he met with at your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* Looks like this royal Payne is going to be as thoroughly unpleasant as the other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Your Honor! The prosecution would now like to call a decisive witness to the stand. This witness will testify as to how the accused detonated the bomb in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please call your witness, Mr. Payne!</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, your name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NAME: TED TONATEOCCUPATION: BOMB DISPOSAL SPECIALIST</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! What a strange, robotic voice you have!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SPEECH SYNTHESIS VIA TYPING. IT IS THE SAME AS ME TALKING.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He sounds exactly like a robot...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can't you speak in a normal manner?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He can!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BUT I DO NOT LIKE TO SPEAK. SPEAKING IS INEFFICIENT. ENERGY EXPENDITURE: SPEAKING &gt; TYPING UNDERSTAND?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm.. What an odd witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Tonate was in charge of the bomb for that trial and was there when it went off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Being a bomb squad specialist, do you have any relation to the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NEGATIVE. I FIRST MET THE GIRL WHILE ON THIS JOB. MANY PEOPLE ARE EMPLOYED BY THE POLICE. I KNOW ONLY A FRACTION OF THEM. HOWEVER, I WAS SHOCKED WHEN I FIRST DISCOVERED THE BODY OF THE VICTIM.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Shocked?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WAS THE FIRST ONE ON THE SCENE AFTER THE EXPLOSION. I WENT THERE TO ENSURE SAFETY, BUT I ENDED UP DISCOVERING A DEAD BODY.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So he was the first to discover the body, was he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">He is here to testify about the circumstances surrounding the moment of the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will hear Mr. Tonate's testimony. But at the very least, show this court some respect and remove that faceguard, Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE BOMB WAS ORIGINALLY DISARMED BY ME, THEN TRANSPORTED HERE AS EVIDENCE.BOMB NAME: HH-3000 OPERATED BY TIMER OR WITH A REMOTEI WAS WATCHING FROM THE GALLERY WHEN I SUDDENLY BECAME ALARMED.I SAW THAT THE BOMB'S TIMER WAS COUNTING DOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So even though the bomb was supposed to be disarmed, it somehow got switched on?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">PRECISELY. ACTIVATING THE TIMER IS VERY SIMPLE. 1. CONNECT WIRES 2. SWITCH ON TIMERA MONKEY COULD DO IT. I AM SURE EVEN YOU WOULD BE ABLE TO, MR. WRIGHT.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh, I guess this makes you the Blue Monkey in this barrel of fun, Boss...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*ahem* I'd now like to begin my cross-examination-- Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate...! What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">HH-3000... AKA: A BOMB.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A B-BOMB?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Great googly moogly!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yeeeaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate! I-I demand that you disarm it this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Disassembly complete. HMPH. 5.3 SECONDS. 0.2 SECONDS SHORT OF MY PERSONAL BEST.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you trying to give me a heart attack?! I'm not exactly a spring chicken, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THIS IS AN EXACT REPLICA OF THE HH-3000. IT IS USED TO PRACTICE DISARMING BOMBS. DISARM = SUCCESS. EXPLOSION = FAILURE.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An exact replica of the bomb that exploded, is it? So that's what it looked like.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SUBMITTED A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE REAL BOMB TAKEN JUST BEFORE THE TRIAL. DIMENSIONS: 10" H x 10" W x 10" D WEIGHT: 12 LBS... A PERFECT REPLICATION.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your bomb does appear to be a very good copy, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YES, HOWEVER I COULD NOT REPLICATE THE DETONATION MECHANISM. IT HAS A VERY PUZZLING WIRING SETUP. IT IS REGRETTABLE I COULD NOT REPLICATE IT.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, that's enough! There's no need to replicate anything here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And now if the defense would begin their cross-examination-- Hm? Where has Ms. Cykes gone to?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, you can come out now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, Mr. Wright! Let's get to work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you were pretty scared, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What?! I don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">She was about to bolt!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, put a sock in it, Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* As transparent as ever...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now, let's see... Where were we...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were at the "cross-examination"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! Cross-examination! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems disoriented. I wonder if she's all right... Maybe I should ask Athena if she remembers how to cross-examine... to help her focus.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Athena, you remember how to conduct a cross-examination, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Of course I do! What kind of lawyer would I be if I didn't?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now! Don't get upset! But what do you say to humoring me with a little review...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it! Basically, we examine a witness's testimony... ...and compare it against the Court Record, searching carefully for any inconsistencies. This green text represents a witness's testimony. Touch the right arrow to advance to the next statement of the testimony. Touch the left arrow to go back to the previous statement. Pay close attention to the testimony, and when you've found an inconsistency... ...touch "Present" <thought>R</thought> to open the Court Record! The Court Record contains information on all the evidence we have at our disposal. You can use it to look for facts that conflict with what the witness has said. When you find something, "Present" <thought>X</thought> that evidence to refute the witness's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what if nothing conflicts with the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's when you "Press" <thought>L</thought> the witness for more information. Find any inconsistencies or lies in the testimony and reveal them to the court. That's what cross-examination is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you remember it just as I taught it. <thought>And it was a nice refresher course for me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nah, no need for that right now. She'll be fine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll do everything I can to help!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you can't find any contradictions... ...and you flub up too often, don't be afraid to ask me for help! Press X to consult with me when the Consult panel appears. I'll let you know where I think the suspicious statement is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds good. I'll be counting on you if I get in a bind. All right. It's cross-examination time!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE BOMB WAS ORIGINALLY DISARMED BY ME, THEN TRANSPORTED HERE AS EVIDENCE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ABSOLUTELY. I CAN DISARM ANYTHING. IN A FLASH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, that looks more like "dismantle" than "disarm" to me...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Oh. Pardon me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see. Is there any chance you could have forgotten to disarm the bomb?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IMPOSSIBLE! I DO NOT MAKE RUDIMENTARY MISTAKES LIKE THAT.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They say "to err is human." <thought>Although the jury is still out on this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. If you must know, Mr. Wright, according to the court's own records... ...the fact that the bomb had indeed been disarmed was officially confirmed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess I can rule out the possibility that he forgot to disarm it...</thought> Could you talk about the bomb in a little more detail for the court, Mr. Tonate?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">CERTAINLY.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BOMB NAME: HH-3000 OPERATED BY TIMER OR WITH A REMOTE</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DIMENSIONS: 10" H x 10" W x 10" D WEIGHT: 12 LBS. THIS INFORMATION IS ALSO WRITTEN ON THE PHOTOGRAPH.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. Here it is, on the back. According to this, the case is made out of alloy plating five-sixteenths of an inch thick. That certainly sounds like one thick and very heavy bit of metal.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet if I dropped that thing on your foot, you'd be hoppin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you dropped that thing anywhere, I'd be "hopping" for the nearest exit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I believe the court has heard enough about the bomb itself. So, Mr. Tonate, you were keeping an eye on the bomb? Where were you watching from?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WAS WATCHING FROM THE GALLERY WHEN I SUDDENLY BECAME ALARMED.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">MY DUTIES MAY HAVE BEEN OVER FOR THE MOMENT, BUT I WANTED TO KEEP WATCH. EVEN THOUGH THE BOMB WAS DISARMED, YOU CAN NEVER BE TOO CAREFUL. EXPLOSIVE DEVICES ARE VERY DANGEROUS THINGS.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, how admirably responsible of you. A model to be emulated.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I PRACTICE DISARMING BOMBS EVERY DAY. I practice assembling them, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The disarming part, I get, but assembling them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'll have you know that I practice presenting evidence every day myself!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SEE. BUT DO YOU EVER PRACTICE HAVING EVIDENCE PRESENTED TO YOU?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Presented to me? What...? No, I...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THEN YOU CANNOT VERY WELL CALL YOURSELF A PROFESSIONAL YET, CAN YOU?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! That does it! I'm gonna start practicing having evidence presented to me every day! And you'd better drink some coffee, Boss! We're gonna be pulling an all-nighter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I don't think that will be necessary... <thought>...Or worth either of our time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Tonate, what did you witness from the gallery?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SAW THAT THE BOMB'S TIMER WAS COUNTING DOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THESE GOGGLES HELP ME SEE VERY SMALL THINGS CLEARLY FROM VERY FAR AWAY. I CAN EVEN SEE WHAT YOU HAD FOR BREAKFAST BY LOOKING AT YOUR TIE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I suddenly feel like a bug under a magnifying glass?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I guess it's possible he saw the timer if he was wearing those goggles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure. There's something that just doesn't sit right with me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? I don't think I follow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bomb was completely hidden inside the stuffed animal. So well concealed, in fact, that it didn't even look like a bomb at all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you're trying to find testimony that conflicts with the evidence, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Listening carefully to Mr. Tonate's testimony is just the first step. After that, it's a matter of taking a look at any evidence that seems relevant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Remember that you can touch "Present" <thought>R</thought> when you want to open the Court Record! If you find evidence that conflicts with the testimony, "Present" <thought>X</thought> it! Let's see... This testimony is about when the bomb went off... So I'd think what state it was in at the time would be pretty important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... A bomb that didn't look like a bomb because it was inside a stuffed animal, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you say you saw the bomb's countdown, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">OF COURSE. I CLEARLY SAW IT COUNTING DOWN TO ZERO.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I say... that you are CLEARLY lying!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way you could have seen the bomb's timer. After all, the bomb was concealed inside a stuffed animal.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate! How can you claim to know the bomb was about to go off... ...when you couldn't even see the timer?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">AAAAAAAGH! BUT THAT IJLS KDSOI EDJMB9I A LAJ72Z OIQE AKCXW!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What?! NOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That does seem like a glaring inconsistency, indeed! Witness, how do you explain this?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL... I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! That was great, Mr. Wright! You found a contradiction right off the bat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Always remember, Athena. When you find an inconsistency in a witness's testimony, there's always a reason behind it. It could be a lie, a hidden meaning, a secret... Whatever it is, it's up to us to dig it out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And pointing out every contradiction we find is the best way to do it, right, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now the question is, what can we dig out of Mr. Tonate?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL, LET ME SEE... I... UH... NO, NO, NO. THERE MUST BE SOME MISTAKE... OH, YES! YES, OF COURSE! I REMEMBER NOW! THE SOUND! I KNEW BECAUSE OF THE SOUND!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sound? What sound?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHEN THE TIMER OF THIS TYPE OF BOMB IS SWITCHED ON, IT BEEPS SOFTLY. BEEP... BEEP... BEEP... IT IS THE SOUND OF THE BOMB COUNTING DOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A beeping noise, you say? I suppose it would be possible to notice that, even with the bomb inside the stuffed animal.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SIMPLY MADE A MISTAKE. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">LISTENING FOR THE SOUND OF A BOMB'S TIMER IS AN INTEGRAL PART OF MY WORK. I CONSTANTLY UNDERGO TRAINING SO THAT I WILL NEVER MISS IT.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hardly think "training" would help you hear something so soft from so far away... <thought>What now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ARE YOU MAKING LIGHT OF THE FINE SCIENCE OF DISARMING BOMBS? IT IS A SOLEMN MISSION THAT I PUT MY LIFE ON THE LINE TO PERFORM. WHAT KIND OF SPECIALIST WOULD I BE IF I COULD NOT HEAR A BOMB TIMER? It's not like disassembling a toaster, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now he's just showing off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You keep asserting that the sound was too tiny to hear, but the only tiny thing here... ...is your skill as a lawyer! Being suspicious is not an attractive quality you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And you're just overflowing with attractive qualities, are you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Or perhaps you have some proof that Mr. Tonate did not hear the sound?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... no, but... <thought>...it still seems totally suspect... But it's going to be really hard to prove that he DIDN'T hear something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If I have this correct, the prosecution's argument is that... ...someone reactivated the bomb before it was brought into the courtroom. What I don't understand, Mr. Payne, is why you believe that person to be Ms. Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's simple, Your Honor: Mr. Tonate happened to be there when it happened. He was there when the defendant rearmed the bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this, now?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IT HAPPENED BEFORE THE TRIAL STARTED. IT WAS WHEN DETECTIVE ARME AND I WERE TRANSPORTING THE BOMB. WE BROUGHT THE BOMB TO THE LOBBY FOR THE DEFENSE. BOMB = EVIDENCE. THE LAWYER WANTED TO SEE IT BEFORE THE START OF THE TRIAL.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Looking for a chance to get at the bomb, Ms. Woods was already there in that lobby. Her goal was surely to rearm the bomb and steal the remote switch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The remote switch?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YES. THE SWITCH THAT CONTROLS THE BOMB REMOTELY. DUH. IT HAS BEEN MISSING EVER SINCE THE INCIDENT.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I AM PARTIALLY TO BLAME. I LEFT THE BOMB AND REMOTE ON TOP OF THE TRANSPORT CASE... ...AND THEY WERE REARMED AND STOLEN WHILE I WAS TALKING WITH THE LAWYER.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defendant then used the remote from inside the courtroom to start the timer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone other than Mr. Tonate could have opened the case and taken the bomb out.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IMPOSSIBLE. THE TRANSPORT CASE IS ASSIGNED EXCLUSIVELY TO ME. DO YOU SEE THIS NUMBER HERE? THAT IS MY IDENTIFICATION NUMBER. AND I HAVE THE ONLY KEY THAT CAN OPEN THE CASE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nevertheless! Mr. Payne's assertion is nothing more than conjecture! You have no proof that it was Ms. Woods who stole the remote switch!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And by the same token, you have no proof that it wasn't her. But what I DO have is a piece of evidence that proves the defendant handled the bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AH! That TAIL!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">FIVE MINUTES, TWENTY-FOUR SECONDS, TWO POINT THREE DECISECONDS. THE DEFENSE'S ADVANTAGE LASTED A MERE FIVE MINUTES.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk. Talk about a rotten hand... As long as they have her fingerprints as their trump card, I'm at a big disadvantage.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears we will have to hear from the defendant herself once more.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I wholeheartedly agree, Your Honor. I would like to recall Ms. Woods to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I trust you have no objections, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm worried about her condition, but we DO need her testimony. On the other hand... ...I'm not sure I want to make Athena mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I can read your feelings you know, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! <thought>Guess there's no hiding from her, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry. I know we need her testimony. But if anybody picks on her again, they'll pay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess she's already at Anger Level 1...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry. I'll stop the proceedings before I let anything bad happen to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has no objections, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IN THAT CASE, I WILL TAKE MY LEAVE. BUT BEFORE I DO, THERE IS JUST ONE MORE THING. MR. WRIGHT... IS IT?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DISMANTLING BOMBS IS MY JOB. DISMANTLING THE CASE IS YOURS. DO YOU THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT? I LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING YOU TRY.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grrr! This guy is hiding something! I just know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NOW IF YOU WILL EXCUSE ME...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Please go out to the lobby and bring back the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Hi, Thena.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks even worse off than before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Junie! We're here for you!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thanks, Thena. And I'll do my best, too...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You blew up the courtroom because you bear resentment against the courts, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">N-No! Of course not!... *cough* I...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What's that you say? I can barely hear you.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I... I... haven't done anything wrong... This prosecutor's scary...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is getting ugly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You rearmed the bomb because you wanted to blow up the courthouse! Admit it! That's why you went to the lobby where Mr. Justice was, isn't that right?!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Uuugghhh... Ahh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright... Can I go give that prosecutor a smack?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?! Of course not! Do we have to review Courtroom Manners 101 again?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We can't let a creep that bullies innocent girls like this off so easily!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I haven't forgotten about how he treated you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry about me, just help Junie! Her heart's crying out! She's so scared... so very scared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Athena's picking something up with her heightened sense of hearing... And it sounds like this time it's the voice of Ms. Woods's heart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Don't deny it! You stole the remote switch and used it in the courtroom, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Ms. Woods does seem quite frightened. Mr. Payne, I ask that you behave more like a gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, but don't you know, Your Honor? There is no more a gentle man in this world than I.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh, as if a gentleman, or even a "gentle man", would behave like he does! Don't let that rude ruffian win!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Theeena...! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">How dare you call a gentleman such as I a "rude ruffian"?! I'll have you know I attend a manners class every Saturday. I'm more than just a mere gentleman -- I'm a GENTEEL-man!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Not when you're terrorizing a young lady you're not! I'd demand my money back from that manners class if I were you!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should probably be the adult here and stop the two of them, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, that will be enough.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Certainly, Your Honor. No further questions. Let's move on to the defendant's testimony. Ms. Woods, please share with the court what you were doing when the bomb went off.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, that day... *cough* I was watching from the gallery... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie's clearly in pain, being forced to recall the bombing like this... She can't even get her words out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going to work, so what now...? Hey, wait a minute! Even if she can't vocalize what she wants to say, we can listen to what's inside her heart! Yes, now's the perfect time to use Athena's power!</thought> You can hear it, can't you, Athena? The cries of Ms. Woods's heart?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, and they sound incredibly strained. She's so scared... I think she could collapse at any second!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena has a unique ability, you see. With her finely-tuned sense of hearing, she can hear the words of a witness's heart. In essence, she can sense how a person is really feeling from the tone of their voice. Guess it's all up to Athena and her special ability now!</thought> Athena, I want you to use the analytical psychology you studied... ...and listen to the testimony of Ms. Woods's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Okay, Boss! I'll give it a go! After all, this is the whole reason I put all that effort into studying analytical psychology! Auf geht's! Let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your holographic thingamabob can show us how Ms. Woods is feeling, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In a nutshell, yes. The emotions and images that I picked up on just now while listening to her testimony... ...I can enter all of that into Widget and use the Mood Matrix to analyze them. There mood markers here reflect fluctuations in Junie's emotions. When she feels happy or is enjoying the memory, the "Happy" marker will light up. When she feels angry or frustrated, the "Angry" marker will react. When she feels sadness or is frightened by a memory, the "Sad" marker will blink. And when she feels surprised or confused, the "Surprised" marker will let us know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, with your special ability and Widget's Mood Matrix program... ...we can track how Ms. Woods is feeling as she testifies. Talk about the wonders of technology...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! Now, let's give it a shot! I'm picking up on some kind of discord -- or noise -- in Junie's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See here? This is what the noise looks like in the Mood Matrix. It's a result of inconsistencies between her testimony and her feelings. If we can pinpoint their inconsistencies, the noise level should drop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay! It's time to listen to Ms. Woods's true testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, that day... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was watching from the gallery... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">The bomb went off... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough* and rubble started falling...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It fell on top of me... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think I have a good grasp on Junie's emotional state now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This power of Athena's is incredible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'm seeing an unexpected emotion that's inconsistent with the rest of her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Already?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at this! When she says, "It fell on top of me," the "Happy" marker is reacting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, look at that. That IS odd!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There must be a reason for this contradictory emotion! We just need to do some digging! When you find an unexpected emotion... ...touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>... ...and then select the unexpected emotion or reaction from the four mood markers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Widget is registering joy when Ms. Woods recalls the rubble falling on her. There must be a reason for this unexpected emotion!</thought> Ms. Woods! As the rubble was falling, was there also something that made you feel happy?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What?! *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! The feeling of happiness is spreading throughout Junie's heart! Keep going on this point, and I bet Junie will start to calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great! Let's hear what she has to say!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Um... *cough* Just as I was about to escape the courtroom... the bomb went off. I was so startled... I tripped. And then rubble started falling on top of me...! I really thought I was done for... But just then... Apollo came and rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">He used his own body to shield me from the rubble...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's when he sustained those injuries...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">How do you feel, Junie? Did talking about Apollo give you some courage?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. Apollo is... just like the sun -- strong and bright and warm. Just talking about him makes me feel like a leaf undergoing photosynthesis.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And see? Your coughing stopped all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh! You're right! Thank you, Thena.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we were able to draw out some new testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee. Pretty neat, huh? But there's still some noise left, meaning there must still be some discord in Junie's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I guess we'll have to keep going, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let me input this new information and update the Mood Matrix, and we'll be good to go! You remember what to do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I find an unexpected emotion, I should touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! And then you select the unexpected emotion from the mood markers. If we can find the reason for the discord in her heart... ...then we should be able to draw even more new testimony out!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I tried to run, but I was too slow.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Before I could get away, the bomb went off.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was so startled I tripped! Then rubble started falling on me.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I thought I was done for...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But then Apollo came and rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can see some discord in Junie's heart when I listen to her voice. There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere! When you find an unexpected emotion... ...touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>... ...and then select the unexpected emotion or reaction from the four mood markers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were happy when Mr. Justice rescued you, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... I was really happy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But was there also something you felt sad about at the same time?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Sad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The reason I ask is... ...when you were describing how you were rescued, we sensed a little sadness, too.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">......Oh! I think it's probably because of Bum Rap Rhiny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bum Rap Rhiny? <thought>Well, what do you know? Something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's right. I... I brought my stuffed animal, Bum Rap Rhiny, to watch the trial with me. Bum Rap Rhiny and Phony Phanty are brothers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who knew that the legal world could inspire a whole line of merchandise...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I had Bum Rap Rhiny with me while I was watching the trial... But it wasn't until Apollo saved me that I realized I'd lost him as I was running away... My poor Rhiny! A victim of that terrible bomb! Oh, I know! You can see what he looks like in this poster! It's for the campaign to eradicate fake evidence and false charges.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phony Phanty and Bum Rap Rhiny, huh... Nothing against the campaign, but why an elephant and a rhinoceros...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I don't sense any discord in Junie's heart anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I guess that means we managed to draw out all of her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! I'll just make an update with the new info and we'll have the whole picture! So do you think her new testimony will help?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely. I don't know what I would've done without you, Athena! <thought>So Bum Rap Rhiny was in that courtroom when the bomb went off. Now that we know that, it changes the meaning of that other piece of evidence! All I have to do is "Present" it... at the right statement!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was watching from the gallery with Bum Rap Rhiny. I tried to run, but I was too slow.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Before I could get out of the courtroom, the bomb went off.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was so startled I tripped! Then rubble started falling. I thought I was done for...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But then Apollo came and rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's Junie's complete testimony. Not bad, huh, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should focus on the new statements Ms. Woods made... The existence of Bum Rap Rhiny should turn things around in our favor! It changes the meaning of a certain piece of evidence we already have. All I have to do is present it... at the right statement!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods, I know this trial has been very hard for you. But you can relax now. You are, without a doubt, innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! What wild assertion are you making now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My "wild assertion" is simply this: the two stuffed animals were mixed up. The tail the defendant's fingerprints were found on wasn't that of Phony Phanty. It was the tail of her gallery companion, Bum Rap Rhiny!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But are they really so different? Both defense lawyers and prosecutors strive to protect the peace through law.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even elephants and rhinos have some similar characteristics. They're both gray, for example!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, this poster is all I need to prove my assertion to be true. If I may direct the court's attention here, you'll clearly see how the two got mixed up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It's this area, Your Honor! Right here! If you look closely, you should see how the two animals got confused with one another...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Now that you mention it... I think I might see a possible similarity...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. Your Honor. Please don't get taken in by this fellow's bluffing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Are you trying to trick me?! I wasn't born yesterday, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, I'm pretty sure everybody can clearly see that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then you should be able to clearly see that I'm about to give your boss a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urngh! <thought>Think, Phoenix! Which part of the stuffed animal was found at the scene? Once I know that, it should be easy to show how the two stuffed animals got mixed up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! Would you look at that! The two tails are exactly the same!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, exactly. The two stuffed animals are based on entirely different animals... ...but the design of their tails is exactly the same!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! As long as the possibility exists that the tail belongs to Bum Rap Rhiny... ...we can no longer consider it to be decisive proof that the defendant handled the bomb. As things stand, I consider the charges against the accused unsubstantiated. Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oh, um... Y-Yes, of course, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, that was great, Mr. Wright! You turned things right around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's not over yet, but at least we managed to hold out this long.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this brings our proceedings for today to a close. Mr. Payne, I'm afraid you have some serious investigating ahead of you.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let us reconvene tomorrow. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was so exciting, Boss! We did it! True to form, you managed to just barely pull it off at the very last moment!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"True to form"? Gee, I never knew you had such a glowing opinion of me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Thank you for everything you're doing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did great, Ms. Woods. You really stuck it out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And you got really brave at the end, just when we needed you most, Junie! Thanks to you, we were able to turn things around!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, you were the one who gave me that courage, Thena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Heh heh. Thanks. So, be honest -- was I any help at all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! Without you, we would've never gotten out of that tight spot.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's good to hear! I may still have a lot to learn, but you can bet I'm going to give it my all! I'll be so good that, one day, you'll call me your partner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I like to hear! <thought>Analytical psychology... The ability to solve the riddles of a person's heart. Athena's true potential is beginning to really shine through now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, where's Apollo, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Good question... <thought>I almost forgot about him.</thought> I assumed he'd still be here in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, I know! Maybe he's still in Courtroom No. 4...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Courtroom No. 4? What would he be doing at the scene of the explosion?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">When I came out to the lobby to rest, I told Apollo about Bum Rap Rhiny... I told him I dropped Rhiny in the courtroom as I was trying to escape before the blast. And then... ...Apollo said he had an idea where Rhiny might be, so we went to take a look together.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh. I guess Apollo can be pretty nice when he wants to be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you went looking for Rhiny together before you were called back into Courtroom No. 5?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... I'd had some time to rest so I was able to go and look for him. But then they called me into Courtroom No. 5 to testify. Apollo insisted on staying there, though...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">With all those injuries? I wonder how he's managing?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I think Apollo might have figured something out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Wonder what it was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">He told me, "I'm going to look for evidence to clear your name, Juniper."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just maybe, he found some new piece of evidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Anyway, we'd better go and get him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Where are you, Apollo? Trial's over for today! C'mon, I know you're...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>This isn't exactly how I envisioned the second day of this trial to start... ...but given how things ended yesterday...</thought> ............ Good morning...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The mood sure is tense... Not that that's any surprise.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Oh, hey, did you read the paper this morning, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? The paper? That came out of left field.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You didn't read it? Then you don't know the big news! Somebody spotted an abominable snowman waaaay up in the mountains!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tell me you know the difference between a paper and a tabloid, Athena!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It might show up in the forest where you live, Junie. So you'd better watch out! Okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ You really should read the story for yourself. I couldn't even begin to do it justice.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">! "Justice"...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, poor Apollo! And it's all my fault! *sniffle* Theeeeenaaa! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Junie! What was I thinking?! I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What we found yesterday... ...was not Apollo's dead body... thank goodness. He'd been assaulted by someone with a blow to his head, and was lying unconscious. We rushed him to the hospital right away, and it looks like he's going to pull through. <thought>But it was still quite a shock to stumble onto a scene like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is Ms. Woods all right, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I managed to get her to stop crying. Now she's resting on that sofa over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess she really feels responsible for what happened to Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Poor Junie. She believes that the reason Apollo was attacked... ...is because he was helping her look for something in that courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? <thought>Guess I can see why she'd think that...</thought> By the way, how are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you. I know you're concerned about Ms. Woods, but are YOU all right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Me?! I-I'm doing just fine, boss! I mean, yeah, it was a huge shock, but I'm all right! People who've studied analytical psychology are great at times like these. After all, they've learned how to control their own emotions, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, I don't think it's as easy as she makes it sound. But there's no denying she's a real trooper.</thought> Apollo doesn't remember a thing, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... He can't recall anything from the time right before he was assaulted. Nothing about what he was doing in Courtroom No. 4, or who assaulted him. The doctor said it's probably due to that hit he took to the head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Assaulted in a court of law and losing your memory at that... I know how that feels...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But who in the world would do such a thing, huh, Mr. Wright?! Grr! Just WAIT till I get my hands on the coward who hurt our Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now, Athena... I thought you said you were in control of your emotions. Let's just focus on helping Ms. Woods, okay? <thought>But I admit I'm just as upset as you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Okay, Boss! You're right. Apollo's assailant can wait until after we clear Junie's name!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the spirit! <thought>Now, let's see... I'd better check the Court Record one more time before the trial starts. If memory serves, when I have more than six pieces of evidence... I should be able to switch pages with [D-Pad] or [Control Stick].</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Earth to Mr. Wright! I'm ready whenever you are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's get ready to rumble!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You bet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With everything that happened with Apollo, I didn't have time for a proper investigation. I can't let that stop me, though. I have to get this right, for Ms. Woods's sake, and Apollo's, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene for the trial of Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is also ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. I believe I instructed the prosecution to further their investigation. Were you able to locate the remote switch in question?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm afraid the remote switch is still missing, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say I'm disappointed, Mr. Payne. Not angry, just disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I-I apologize, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aha! Looks like the prosecution is just as unprepared as I am!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">There is a separate matter, however, that I would like to bring up during this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A separate matter, you say? And what might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I assume you are aware that another incident occurred during yesterday's trial? I'm speaking of course, of the assault on Mr. Justice in the ruins of Courtroom No. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Why is he bringing THAT up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, what a truly harrowing experience it must have been. Poor Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">At the time of the attack, Mr. Justice was not alone. He was with the defendant, Ms. Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He isn't going where I think he's going with this... is he?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution wishes to indict Ms. Woods on the charge of Mr. Justice's assault!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Mr. Payne! The incident under deliberation here is the courtroom bombing! The assault on Mr. Justice has nothing to do with this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, but I believe there IS a connection between this case and Mr. Justice's assault. Please take a moment to consider these facts. Both events occurred in Courtroom No. 4. This is the location in Courtroom No.4 where the unconscious Mr. Justice was discovered. As you can see, it's quite close to where Detective Arme's body was found.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The question is, why did the culprit feel the need to maliciously attack Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why indeed... What do you believe their motive to be, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I believe Mr. Justice found something in that courtroom while Ms. Woods was with him -- evidence that fingered her as the perpetrator of the bombing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean he found some incriminating evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Precisely! And so, I surmise that the defendant picked up a piece of rubble and... ...hit Mr. Justice on the back of the head in order to silence him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Cykes, please control your outbursts.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">*ahem* It is the prosecution's belief that by deliberating on Mr. Justice's assault... ...we will draw ever closer to the truth of the courtroom bombing itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Ms. Woods is hereby officially indicted on the charge of assaulting Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What?! Why are you listening to Mr. Toupee over there?! Although... considering our conversation yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I think Apollo might have figured something out...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Wonder what it was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">He told me, "I'm going to look for evidence to clear your name, Juniper."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe the two incidents really are related after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I would like to start by hearing from the defendant herself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff, please bring Ms. Woods to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............ *cough, cough* I-I'm sorry. *cough* I can't seem to stop... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ms. Woods... Guess she's still really upset about Apollo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Woods, you went to the ruins of Courtroom No. 4 with Mr. Justice, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Y-Yes... I did...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Good, good. If you would, then, please testify about what happened to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">During the trial yesterday... I was overcome by a fit of coughing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So Mr. Justice stayed by your side while you were feeling unwell...? What an admirable young man! I thought his loud voice was his only outstanding feature...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He may look like a little imp at times, but Apollo can be really nice, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope she didn't hurt her wrist backhanding that one out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But one has to wonder... Why did Mr. Justice stay behind in the ruins?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I think Apollo might have figured something out...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something? What kind of something?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Something to do with the courtroom bombing kind of something, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh ho! New evidence for the case, was it?! That's a very big kind of something, indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I believe so. He mentioned looking for some evidence when I was called away.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What lie is that?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">When she learned Mr. Justice would be looking for evidence, she attacked him. She attacked him to give herself the chance to destroy that evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">N-No...! I never...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What on Earth...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Do you see it? There in front of Mr. Justice's right hand? Witness the message he left us!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It-It's written in blood! "W, O, O, D, S"...? Why, isn't that...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's right, Your Honor, it says "WOODS" in capital letters.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I submit that Mr. Justice left us with the name of his attacker before he fainted!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">N-No! That can't be true... Why would Apollo write my name...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! The NERVE of him leaving that message! Why would he do this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey, don't take it out on me! I don't understand it any more than you do. <thought>When we discovered Apollo yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A-Apollo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">......N-No...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We didn't even have a chance to rush over to him. As soon as security heard Athena's scream, they ran in and cordoned off the area. After that, they were in Courtroom No. 4 with Apollo the whole time. We couldn't investigate anything ourselves, and had to leave everything to the police. Still, I never thought they would find some bloody writing there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, please begin your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">During the trial yesterday... I was overcome by a fit of coughing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Y-Yes... *cough* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please do not make Ms. Woods nervous by pressing her so ruthlessly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But that barely even qualified as a quasi-question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's help her relax with a little small talk before we dive into the cross-examination! You know, ask her about her hobbies and her crushes and stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her crushes?! Really?! I don't know about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Apollo stayed with me and we went to the courtroom ruins together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">We went to look for my medicine... to stop my coughing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your medicine? Why would your medicine be in Courtroom No. 4?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I dropped it in the heat of the moment. Bum Rap Rhiny... He was keeping my medicine safe for me... He has a little compartment that I can put things in, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And Phony Phanty has the same type of pocket. That's where the bomb was inserted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I had put my medicine for my coughing fits inside Bum Rap Rhiny. When I told Apollo about it, he said he'd help me go look for him. There was so much rubble in there! I was worried, but... ...there was no rubble or anything in front of the witness stand. So when we got inside, Apollo went straight there... ...and started looking for my Rhiny in that area. It was so nice of him to do that for me, in spite of all his injuries... Apollo is so strong and kind, just like the trees of the forest...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The way she makes him sound, you'd think Apollo was some kind of ancient god... Oh, wait...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm.. So that's why you went to the ruins. I see. That seems to be quite an important fact. Please add it to your testimony, Ms. Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Apollo started looking for Bum Rap Rhiny near the witness stand, where there was no rubble."</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Apollo started looking for Bum Rap Rhiny near the witness stand, where there was no rubble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I-I'm sorry. Did I say something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. Of course not. I was just... testing my hearing...! <thought>Must not upset her... Must not upset her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... I'm sure that's where we searched first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But then I was called back to this courtroom to give testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. The bailiff came to Courtroom No.4 and brought me back to this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about Mr. Justice? Did he come with you, or did he stay behind?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Apollo insisted on staying behind in Courtroom No. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hobbies...? Oh, well, I love growing vegetables in my garden... And I love to knit. I like sewing, too. I made this outfit myself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Keep it up, Mr. Wright! It's working! Now ask her if she has a crush on anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*ahem* So, um... is there anyone in particular you like right now?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To this case...? Uh... not really...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you will refrain from asking questions unrelated to the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry, Your Honor... <thought>Minus 1 to Brownie Points...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. Ms. Woods, please continue with your testimony. I believe you were telling the court about your attack on Mr. Justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I swear I didn't attack Apollo! Why would I ever hurt such a kind person?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, very kind! He rescued me. He's like the sun, strong and warm. He makes me feel strong, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only adjectives I associate with the sun are "sweltering" and "oppressive."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">But then Apollo got hurt, and... and... It's all my fault! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Junie, Apollo's going to be fine! He's just like the sun, right? Well, the sun doesn't just drop out of the sky!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">You really think he'll be fine?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. But the sun does go down at night...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-Then that means... Apollo could...! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne! I do not think much of men who make young ladies cry!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, it's obvious Junie didn't attack Apollo! I mean, that's just ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. I agree. <thought>They must've gone to look for Bum Rap Rhiny together. But why did they need to find it so badly that they'd go to all that trouble? I'd better try to find out more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Apollo was trying to help Juniper... Who knew that Apollo could be such a sweetheart?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must've been pretty hard on him, too, with all that rubble everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now that I think about it, there's something odd about what Apollo was able to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, considering what Ms. Woods said just now, I think you're right. That courtroom was in a very unusual state, after all. <thought>Which leaves the million-dollar question: what would explain this contradiction? Anyway, let's see what happens when I present what I suspect is our answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he started his search with the witness stand, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's right. I guess maybe he wanted to start from the furthest point in the room. He was being so brave... *cough* and strong... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's odd... Under the circumstances, he shouldn't have been capable of that...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But he WAS! And he still IS! He might not look it, but he really IS brave! And kind, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not the part I was finding fault with. <thought>SOMEONE has a crush on Apollo...</thought> What you are claiming is something that no one should have been able to do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But I should think that anyone can be brave and kind if the wanted to be, Mr. Wright...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, anyone can be brave and kind, but if you would please take a look at this diagram. With the courtroom in this state, how was it possible to walk up to the witness stand?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I see your point. The rubble blocks off access to the area around the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmph. Does such a tiny inconsistency even matter? Perhaps the witness is simply misremembering it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>Great, now I'M not so sure it matters...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">A real man doesn't make mountains out of mole hills, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that's precisely what Mr. Wright does best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I call slander, Your Honor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, was it really impossible to approach the witness stand? I have to say, it's a bit hard to tell with any accuracy from just this diagram. Mr. Payne, do you have any other photos of the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Er, let me see, Your Honor... Ah, yes. I have one more. Here it is. It's a more pulled-back version of the photo I presented before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What's that hunk of metal on wheels?</thought> Mr. Payne, is the metallic object in that photo Mr. Tonate's bomb transport case?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's right. Is there some problem?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. That transport case was there in Courtroom No. 4 when the bomb went off. It must have been there ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh! That's it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods? Have you remembered something?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Y-Yes! I just realized... Its position... It's different from before...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Its position? The position of what?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Um, the position of that big metal thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bomb transport case?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. When Apollo and I went there, it was in a different place. Where the case is in the photo was open space, so it was easy to search the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. So where was the transport case when you and Mr. Justice saw it?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">As I recall, I think it was more to the right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To the right...? <thought>Then that means...! In that case, the case was over there at the time of Apollo's attack...? Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Who cares where the transport case was when? What difference does it make? It has nothing at all to do with what we were talking ab--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What...?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! That certainly sounds very relevant indeed! And you sound as though you know where the case was at the time of the attack.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. This diagram represents the crime scene as shown in the photo. And this is where the transport case was at the time of the assault on Mr. Justice. <thought>All right, I have this! The bomb transport case was here at the time of Apollo's attack!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There...? Hmm... I'm afraid I fail to follow your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh, Boss... I don't think anyone could follow that logic, even with a tracking device.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I'm pretty sure my logic just made a clean getaway, even from me...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps a penalty will help you rethink your "position."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ow. <thought>I'd better take another good look at the evidence... I think there was a clue in there about where the transport case was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Let's try that again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I assert that this is where the transport case was at the time of the assault!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...I-Inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods, was this where the transport case was when you saw it?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... Yes, that's where it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Ms. Woods. I'm sure the court has noted an interesting fact about this position.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The transport case covers up the writing in blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! If the transport case was in that position at the time of the assault... ...then no message could have been written there, because the case was in the way! Which leads us to conclude that Mr. Justice couldn't have left that bloody writing!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What?! And where is this "proof" you're talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here in the crime photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm keen to see this proof, myself, Mr. Wright. What in this photo indicates that the transport case was moved after the assault?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I'm afraid I don't follow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I'm sensing feelings of doubt from you... Which means... you're just taking a wild stab in the dark, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. You're good. I bet you can also tell how I'm about to feel in a few seconds, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just earned yourself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the transport case was moved after the assault, there should be some evidence of it. I'd better take another good look at the photo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suggest you give it another try, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at the mark that runs over Mr. Justice's bandages here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see it, but what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This mark was made by one of the casters from the transport case carrying the bomb. As the case was moved, it ran over his bandages! In other words, the transport case was originally to the right of Mr. Justice! Then, after Mr. Justice was assaulted... ...the transport case was moved!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as Ms. Woods said, the case was covering the writing at the time of the assault! Therefore, it was impossible for Mr. Justice to have left that message in blood!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Boss! It was a real nail-biter, but you pulled it off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. That should bring down the prosecution's claim like a house of cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Mr. Wright, that was a very clever deduction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, it was nothing, Your Honor. <thought>Nothing but pure genius! Take THAT!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss! I'm sensing a definite "smug and braggy" vibe coming off of you...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Uuuuungh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have just one question, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If Mr. Justice didn't leave this message in blood... ..then who did?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">............ Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well... ............ <thought>Looks like I should've taken that train of thought through to the last station...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, well. I've heard a lot about this. So this is Mr. Wright's famous bluffing technique, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, this feeling! It brings back memories of the old days! Back when you carved out a name for yourself by bluffing your way through thick and thin!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, Mr. Wright. The judge kind of makes you sound no better than a two-bit con man...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You made your argument with such confidence, Mr. Wright. Now I'd like to hear your answer with just as much confidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, until the judge asked the question, you didn't catch on, either, buster!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What now, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. I hope you didn't bluff your way into a corner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, Phoenix, think! There must be a way through this! I have to dig my way to the truth somehow! Who could have written that message in blood?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If Apollo didn't leave that bloody writing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it was Apollo's attacker who wrote it, and made it look like Apollo did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That seems like the most reasonable explanation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But wait a minute! I just realized something, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at the amount of blood in the photo. It doesn't look like Apollo bled very much... I wonder if it's possible to write out "WOODS" with just this much?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right! Good thing Apollo didn't lose that much blood. That might be a factor in why he survived the assault.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And since there was so little blood, that pretty much rules out his attacker, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so. But if it wasn't his attacker, then who else could it have been?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who wrote the bloody message... was none other than Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pardon me?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Wright! Didn't you just finish saying that it COULDN'T have been Apollo?! And don't try to blame it on "old age"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah... <thought>I did just say that, didn't I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Not only does your head resemble a bird, but it seems that you have a bird brain as well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please try to think before you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... <thought>I'd better give that another try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If it wasn't Apollo, who could have left the bloody message?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, do I reeeally need to base my claim on something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course you do. Don't tell me you don't have anything at all to back up your assertion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Nothing in particular, really...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That won't do, Mr. Wright. But a penalty will make up for your deficiency very nicely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So it wasn't Apollo or his attacker... When you think about who was at the crime scene... ...there's only one other person who it could really be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh yeah! Wasn't there another person who shed blood at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To be honest, I don't have any real proof of this... But I've come this far. There's no turning back now!</thought> Besides Apollo, there was one more person who shed blood at this crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A person who shed blood...? You don't mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, but I do. I believe it was Candice Arme who left behind this message in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Detective Arme?! Are you sure you know what you're doing here?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, not really?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At first glance, that would seem to be the most reasonable explanation. However... ...Apollo didn't shed enough blood to write such an extensive message.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Uh-oh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see. Even the photo makes it clear there wasn't enough blood to write all those letters. And Mr. Justice did survive. I suppose he didn't bleed very extensively, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But why would Detective Arme write the defendant's name? There is no connection between the two whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">A-And I-I didn't even know the lady who was killed...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I admit the investigation didn't turn up any connection between the victim and defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">They had never even met each other!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's... very true...</thought> Well, then, let's see... Then maybe the intended meaning of the message is not what it appears to be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The "intended meaning"...?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">"Not what it appears to be"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the message was not intended to be "WOODS."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Coming from you, that's quite the bold statement, Mr. Wright. You wish to assert that this bloody writing could have some other meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor! <thought>Hmm... For something I pulled out of a wormhole, it could turn out to be true, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I didn't think of that...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh. You may have tricked His Honor, but you'll never get the best of me. I have a thing for studying on the weekends, as you may have already guessed. And there is no such radio code as "WOODS" in the state, dear Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is that a fact, heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't look at me. I know as much as you do about police codes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough of this! I was quite taken with the defense's new theory... ...but if they can't substantiate it with anything, then I must end things here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Please wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But before we discuss this theory any further, I demand a plausible explanation. So, Mr. Wright, what is the true meaning of the bloody writing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I believe it's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And no stalling! If you can't come up with an answer quickly, I will declare this discussion officially over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm in trouble now... What other meaning could it have, besides the obvious one...? Maybe it means something in another language? Or maybe it's a code? Think, Phoenix! You can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which piece of evidence will tell us what the word "WOODS" really means?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But doesn't it, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you asking me or telling me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I'll let you be the judge of that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I'll do the judging around here! And I judge that you deserve a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. That didn't go over well. But I just KNOW there's something here that looks like the word "WOODS"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Let's try that again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The bomb transport case...? I've about had it up to here with your shenanigans, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at the numbers on this case, Your Honor. "L10015R". Doesn't this string look vaguely familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"L100"... What does that have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmph. What could those numbers possibly have to do with the case at hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now please take a look at the bloody writing shown in the crime photo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! I think I see it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thatta girl! That one's on my side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It says "WOODS."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or, you could say it's a horse of a different color, Your Honor. The first character isn't a "W". It's actually an "L" and a "1". The next two are zeros.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! My goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true meaning behind the bloody writing isn't Ms. Woods's name. It's the number engraved on this bomb transport case!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All you have to do is erase one line from the writing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Erase one line from where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anywhere you like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Anywhere I'd like?! ...All right. I'll erase one of the "Os." "WODS"? And what is that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your state of mind. I believe it stands for "wise, optimistic, dauntless, and serene."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, what in the world?! This is no time for a psychology test!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't say my state of mind is exactly "serene" right now, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urngh. <thought>I guess erasing just one line won't do the trick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please refrain from making things up as you go along! Now, try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I propose we read it backwards. Let's see... Reading it from the back end, we get... "SDOOW".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And what does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe there was someone connected to this case by the name of "S. Doow"... ...wasn't there, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And who in the world is "S. Doow" supposed to be, Boss...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid there is no such person connected to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well, I guess I expected as much.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you knew, then why did you ask?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess reading it backwards was a big bust.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please try again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please erase the third, downward stroke of the "W", and the curved part of the "D."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! Would you look at that! ............ "LIOOIS"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, Your Honor! It isn't meant to be read as a word! It's the number "L-1-0-0-1-5"... ...which, if you take away the final "R"... ...is the exact same number that's one the bomb transport case!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Would you, Mr. Wrigh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only RIGHT spelling is "Wright!" <thought>Okay, I'm doing pretty well here, and I think I've drawn the right conclusion. Detective Arme's real message to us is the bomb transport case number.</thought> Your Honor, the two lines were added by the real culprit to intentionally mislead people!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The original message Detective Arme left behind was the transport case number! But whoever assaulted Apollo changed the message!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you're right, Boss... ...then what do you suppose Detective Arme was trying to tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good question... What DOES this number represent...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DO YOU SEE THIS NUMBER HERE? THAT IS MY IDENTIFICATION NUMBER.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Candice Arme lost her life in the courtroom bombing. Her dying message could only have had one purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To tell us the name of the one responsible for the bombing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Don't keep us in suspense, Mr. Wright! Tell us who she was trying to name!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The culprit that the victim was trying to identify is none other than...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............And how did you come up with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do I really need to explain? I think the answer should be obvious...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There he goes again with his famous "wild guess" tactic. Your Honor, Mr. Wright deserves nothing less than a penalty for wasting the court's time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, I would ask that you not use guesswork to pin the crime on a person. Or else, my "guess" is that you will get a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Drat! <thought>Looks like I guessed wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. My brother Winston warned me about you many times. "Watch out for the shady defense lawyer in blue and his wild guesses," he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that's not very nice.</thought> L-Let me try again, please, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense wishes to indict Mr. Ted Tonate on the charge of the courtroom bombing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">T-Ted Tonate?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently, disabling bombs isn't Mr. Tonate's only specialty. Somehow, the victim must have realized that he was the bomber. So when she was caught in the blast... ...she left his bomb transport case number as her dying message. She used Mr. Tonate's own ID number to finger him for the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got a good point there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you have to say to that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That only Detective Arme would know the answer to that, but allow me to offer a theory. Perhaps Detective Arme couldn't recall Mr. Tonate's name in the heat of the moment. As I recall, this was the first meeting between the two. It's entirely possible they wouldn't have been familiar with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or maybe using the ID number was a way to hide its true meaning from the real culprit! Thus lowering the odds that they would erase the bloody writing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But no matter what the reason, the important thing is the meaning behind her message. The fact remains, she wrote Mr. Tonate's ID number!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate was able to cover the message up because he's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate is quite a nervous person, a stickler for details. That's why the bloody writing bothered him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But wouldn't the bloody writing bother him whether he was a stickler for details or not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I don't know about that, Your Honor. For example, I doubt it would bother Athena here. <thought>She doesn't seem like one for details... I don't think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! I object to his accusation, Your Honor! I object whole-heartedly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I object to your lame explanation, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. <thought>I object to this pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But seriously, I wonder why nobody discovered the bloody writing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because Mr. Tonate was able to do something to hide it. And that was because...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I know how Mr. Tonate was able to cover the bloody writing up! Please let me try to explain one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate was wearing those weird goggles of his! Thanks to them, he was able to notice the bloody writing before anyone else could. That super-extendo binocular vision of his... I mean, how weird is that, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I agree it's pretty strange, but I don't see what it has to do with the bloody writing...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, I don't appreciate careless accusations based on flimsy assertions. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I still think those goggles are pretty weird. I mean, c'mon. Right?</thought> I know how Mr. Tonate was able to cover up the bloody writing, I swear! Your Honor, please let me try to explain one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The first person to discover the bloody writing was Mr. Tonate himself.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WAS THE FIRST ONE ON THE SCENE AFTER THE EXPLOSION. I WENT THERE TO ENSURE SAFETY, BUT I ENDED UP DISCOVERING A DEAD BODY.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Mr. Tonate saw that the victim had written his ID number... ...he used his bomb transport case to cover up the bloody writing as a stopgap measure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so that's why the message in blood was under the transport case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't have enough time to try and scrub away the writing. If he didn't report the body right away, he would look suspicious. So those letters lived on to serve another function... ...when Mr. Tonate used them in another incident!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! The assault on Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. Mr. Tonate hit upon a plan to use the bloody writing for his own purposes. So he didn't clean it away. Instead, he made it look like Mr. Justice wrote it. By adding two lines to the writing that Detective Arme left behind... ...he changed the meaning of the message! He made it look like Mr. Justice was accusing Ms. Woods of the attack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only person who could have altered the bloody writing was the courtroom bomber... ...who was the same person that assaulted Mr. Justice. And that person is Ted Tonate!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order in the court! Order, I say! It looks like we will have to hear from the bomb specialist himself. Mr. Payne, please have Mr. Tonate take the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ungh... Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was great, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just doing what I do best! <thought>Which is flying by the seat of my pants...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DISMANTLING THE CASE IS YOURS. DO YOU THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT? I LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING YOU TRY.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've finally drawn Mr. Tonate back onto the witness stand. Looks like you'll get your wish, goggle-man. Now watch me take your lies apart!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate, I'm afraid we have a few more questions for you.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I UNDERSTAND THE SITUATION, YOUR HONOR. I WAS KEEPING A CLOSE EYE ON THE PROCEEDINGS FROM THE GALLERY. THE ALLEGATIONS ARE ALL LAUGHABLE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SUCH A FARFETCHED THEORY! NO BETTER THAN A TANGLED BALL OF WIRES. I've [sic] have them untangled for you in no time at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were the first person on the scene after Detective Arme left her message in blood. You were the only one who could've hidden the writing, and then used it again later!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SEE x2. BUT THEN, LET ME ASK YOU: DO YOU HAVE ANY PROOF THAT DETECTIVE ARME WROTE THAT MESSAGE?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a very good question. Well, do you, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The best way to prove that Detective Arme wrote that message is to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I request a handwriting analysis be performed on the bloody writing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A handwriting analysis...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sorry, but that's just not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Unlike writing done with a pen, for example, a message written with a finger... ...is difficult to properly analyze for unique characteristics. And with such a small sample, it would be even more difficult to analyze.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... <thought>There's gotta be another way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I request that a DNA test be performed on the blood itself. Once we know whose it is, it will be obvious as to who wrote the message!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff! Please put in a request for a DNA test with the forensics team!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It will be some time before we have the results of the analysis. Until then, let's hear more from the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WOULD LIKE NOTHING MORE, YOUR HONOR. I WANT THE COURT TO HEAR HOW RIDICULOUS THE DEFENSE'S THEORY IS.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I ADMIT I WAS THE FIRST ONE ON THE SCENE AFTER THE EXPLOSION.BUT THERE WAS NO BLOODY WRITING THERE AT THAT TIME.ANYWAY, THERE IS NO WAY DETECTIVE ARME COULD HAVE WRITTEN IT.SHE HAD STRUCK HER HEAD ON RUBBLE AND DIED NEAR THE COURTROOM ENTRANCE.SHE WAS TOO FAR AWAY FROM WHERE THE BLOODY MESSAGE WAS FOUND.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying that the victim's body was nowhere near where the writing was?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">PRECISELY. IT IS AS PLAIN AS DAY THAT SHE COULD NOT HAVE WRITTEN IT.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">It's true that the body was discovered near the entrance to the courtroom. Please have a look at this crime scene photo. As you can see, there is blood on the rubble near the victim's body. She must've died after hitting her head there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. All right, then, Mr. Wright. You may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO TAKE MY INFALLIABLE TESTIMONY APART?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I ADMIT I WAS THE FIRST ONE ON THE SCENE AFTER THE EXPLOSION.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">TO SECURE THE AREA. IT IS REGULATION FOR A BOMB DISPOSAL SPECIALIST TO ENTER FIRST.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, you had the opportunity to alter the bloody writing then, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn. I think he was about to say something interesting, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHEN I WENT IN AND SAW THE AFTERMATH... WELL, IT WAS QUITE THE DISASTER...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BUT THERE WAS NO BLOODY WRITING THERE AT THAT TIME.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WITH THESE GOGGLES, THERE IS NO WAY I COULD HAVE MISSED SOMETHING LIKE THAT. I CAN SEE QUITE WELL WITH THEM. IN FACT, I CAN SEE EVERY HAIR ON YOUR SPIKY HEAD. OH, YOU HAVE A FEW GRAYS, MR. WRIGHT.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Poor Mr. Wright. You're always working so hard, keeping our office together...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a minute! I don't have any gray hairs!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">JUST KIDDING.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate, this court frowns upon untoward comments on a person's hair, or lack thereof!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sensing a great sorrow coming from the judge...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">MY APOLOGIES, YOUR HONOR. MAY I PLEASE CONTINUE MY TESTIMONY?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ANYWAY, THERE IS NO WAY DETECTIVE ARME COULD HAVE WRITTEN IT.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">MR. JUSTICE, OF COURSE. JUST BEFORE DYING, HE WROTE THE NAME OF HIS ATTACKER, JUNIPER WOODS.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A final message from your poor subordinate.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Poor Mr. Justice. I'm starting to get all misty-eyed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, Apollo is not dead, folks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, how can you be so sure it WASN'T Detective Arme who wrote the message.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IT IS VERY SIMPLE.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SHE HAD STRUCK HER HEAD ON RUBBLE AND DIED NEAR THE COURTROOM ENTRANCE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">A BOMB CAN INFLICT DAMAGE NOT ONLY FROM THE EXPLOSION ITSELF... BUT ALSO SUBSTANTIAL SECONDARY DAMAGE FROM THE BLAST WIND.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Detective Arme unfortunately hit her head on some rubble. It's stated in her autopsy report as well. "Cause of death: Trauma to back of head."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, the autopsy report. I'd better take another look at that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NOW DO YOU SEE? DETECTIVE ARME COULD NOT HAVE WRITTEN THAT MESSAGE. THE REASON FOR THAT BEING...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SHE WAS TOO FAR AWAY FROM WHERE THE BLOODY MESSAGE WAS FOUND.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IF THAT WERE TRUE, THEN HOW DID SHE RETURN TO THE SPOT NEAR THE ENTRANCE?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe she crawled back after writing it...?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">HMPH.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, did this guy just "Hmph" me?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Would you like to get down on the floor and give us a demonstration of your theory?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? N-No, thank you...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... The victim's body and the writing ARE several yards away from each other. There's no way she could reach.</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Quite the conundrum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that means something is off somewhere. There must be a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! Maybe the body was moved? But that doesn't explain how blood got onto the rubble...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What if that was done by the real culprit after the fact? If that's the case, then something about that should contradict the evidence we have.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are a terrible liar, Mr. Tonate.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............???</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this autopsy -- specifically, the part about Detective Arme's head injury. "Cause of death: Trauma to back of head caused by impact with a flat object."</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YES? WHAT ABOUT IT?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now take a good look at the bloody piece of rubble. It's sharp and pointed!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ND$OIJH AJ9LS WO&amp;J09 BDSK ^(*&amp;!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Hey, you're right, Boss! It IS pointy! Just like your hair!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That is odd, isn't it? What could be the meaning of this contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe it means the victim did not hit her head on this piece of rubble. The bloodstain you see is just another fabrication. Its purpose is to mislead us into thinking the victim died near the courtroom entrance!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A-Are you claiming the culprit moved the victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly what I'm claiming. The victim hit her head at some location. Most likely on the floor, or some other flat surface. And this location was somewhere near where the bloody writing was found.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In that case, she definitely could have written the message!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Your Honor! I have the results of the bloodstain analysis!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, very good timing. Let's take a look. Hmm... According to this report, the message was written in Detective Arme's blood. And, as the defense claims, only the parts of the message that were added afterwards... ...were written in Mr. Justice's blood. It would appear that the defense's assertion is correct after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes! You did it! You were right, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now I have to drive it home. <thought>I'll have to take a good look at the bloody writing analysis later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NNNNNNGGGGgGHhHhhH!!11!1</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate, it is now apparent that you have told several lies to this court. I hope you have some sort of explanation for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............ FINE. I WILL CONFESS.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You will? ... But then, why are you so calm?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THIS TIME, I WILL TELL THE TRUTH.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IT IS TRUE THAT DETECTIVE ARME WROTE MY ID NUMBER.SHE VERY PLAINLY WROTE "L10015R." I WAS SHOCKED.BUT I DID NOT DETONATE THE BOMB.DETECTIVE ARME MUST HAVE MISTAKEN ME FOR THE REAL BOMBER.NOT WANTING TO BE ACCUSED, I MOVED THE BODY AND COVERED THE WRITING. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So it is your assertion that you merely moved the body, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THAT IS CORRECT. I DID NOT KILL DETECTIVE ARME.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, well, if that's all you did, then... ............Wait a minute! That in and of itself is a criminal act!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glad to see you finally cross that finish line, Your Honor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Your cross-examination, please, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IT IS TRUE THAT DETECTIVE ARME WROTE MY ID NUMBER.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">MY BAD. I SHOULD HAVE SAID SO FROM THE OUTSET.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you are sure it was your ID number?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I AM SURE. IT WAS DEFINITELY MY ID NUMBER. THAT NUMBER WAS ASSIGNED EXCLUSIVELY TO ME BY THE POLICE DEPARTMENT. THE NUMBER IS ASSIGNED TO MY GOGGLES AS WELL.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So those funky things were assigned by the police department...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ALTHOUGH THESE ARE SPECIAL GOGGLES CUSTOMIZED BY ME PERSONALLY.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Speaking of personalized, these sunglasses of mine were custom-made as well. They were specially created to be particularly dark and shiny.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Speaking of special, my gavel is made of mahogany and was custom-made as well. It was specially created to make a particularly loud and resounding sound!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wish I had something to brag about...</thought> B-Be all of that as it may, I just want to reconfirm you saw the bloody writing clearly? And that it was your ID number?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THAT IS CORRECT. MY ID NUMBER WAS WRITTEN IN BLOOD ON THE FLOOR.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SHE VERY PLAINLY WROTE "L10015R." I WAS SHOCKED.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it was written after the bomb went off in the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">CORRECT. I DIDN'T KNOW WHY SHE WOULD WRITE IT, SO THAT SENT ME INTO A PANIC.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Sounds like you were in quite a tizzy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I were in his shoes, I guess it would've psyched me out, too. I can't imagine coming across the message "CYKES!" written in blood!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">If I saw "GASPEN PAYNE" written in blood, it'd certainly make me gasp. Rest assured, Mr. Tonate, I understand how you must've felt.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so you discovered your ID number written in blood at the scene, and...?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THAT IS RIGHT. I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES. IT VERY CLEARLY SAID "L10015R."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BUT I DID NOT DETONATE THE BOMB.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THOUGHTS DETECTIVE ARME MAY HAVE HAD INSIDE HER HEAD. IT IS NOT LIKE I EVER DISMANTLED HER MIND TO CHECK.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright, if you have suspicions about the witness, let's see your proof. Evidence is everything in a court of law. Even school children know that. How many years have you been a defense attorney now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cut me some slack, will you...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Don't feel bad, Boss! You just got your attorney's badge back, after all. In that sense, you're still more of a beginner than I am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>.........I suppose I should be thankful you're not a licensed psychologist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WITH PLEASURE. MY ID NUMBER WAS LEFT AT THE SCENE, BUT...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DETECTIVE ARME MUST HAVE MISTAKEN ME FOR THE REAL BOMBER.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THAT IS CORRECT. THAT IS WHY I WAS SO SHOCKED WHEN I SAW MY ID NUMBER.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim may have suspected Mr. Tonate for no reason other than the fact that... ...as the bomb specialist, he was in charge of the bomb. In other words, a false accusation! It's vocational discrimination, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I do not support discrimination of any kind.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well spoken, Your Honor! If the victim had been found to be killed with a gavel... ...Mr. Blue Suit over there would probably have pinned the crime on you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-He would?! Well! That just wouldn't do! Mr. Wright, if you DARE try to pin anything on me, I will find you in contempt of court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I've never even TRIED to harm a hair on-- er, a strand of your beard, Your Honor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL SAID, MR. PAYNE. BECAUSE I AM SO CLOSELY ASSOCIATED WITH BOMBS... ...I WAS AFRAID I WOULD BE PROSECUTED IF ANYONE SAW THE BLOODY WRITING.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NOT WANTING TO BE ACCUSED, I MOVED THE BODY AND COVERED THE WRITING. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I DIDN'T HAVE TIME. BY THE TIME I FOUND THE MESSAGE, THE BLOOD WAS ALREADY DRY. THE POLICE WERE WAITING JUST OUTSIDE FOR ME TO SECURE THE ROOM. AND I STILL HAD TO MOVE THE BODY. I WAS IN A PANIC. WITH NO TIME TO SPARE, I TEMPORARILY COVERED THE WRITING WITH MY CASE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you think the police would find it during their investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">REGULATION STIPULATES ONLY SPECIALISTS MAY TOUCH TRANSPORT CASES. BECAUSE OF THE DANGER, YOU SEE. I THOUGHT I WOULD CLEAN UP THE WRITING ONCE THEY WERE FINISHED. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"My bad"?! Does he really think that will just magically smooth everything over?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guy is something else. And I don't believe Detective Arme's dying message was just some mistake. He won't wriggle out of this that easily! <thought>What did Mr. Tonate see when he first discovered the bloody writing...? There has to be a contradiction hidden in his testimony somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just want to make doubly sure that "L10015R" is really what you saw written in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YES! IT VERY CLEARLY SAID "L10015R."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's odd. Because that's not what I see.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a good look at the photo in the bloody writing analysis. Now tell me, does it really say "L10015R"?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Eep!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something is missing, isn't it? And that "something" is the final "R."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this, Mr. Tonate?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............ O-OH! OH, RIGHT! NOW I REMEMBER. THERE WAS NO "R" ON THE END. I-IT WAS JUST A SLIP OF THE FINGER. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C-Come back, my beautiful contradiction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I'm not so sure it was just a simple slip of the finger...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have something for me, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sense that he's extremely agitated, almost panicked...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He does look pretty flustered...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright, it appears it was nothing more than a mere mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know... Did he really just make a typo? What about that "R"? Did Mr. Tonate actually see it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess everybody makes mistakes. Even I get Mr. Justice and Ms. Cykes mixed up sometimes...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just don't believe it, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, that I get you two confused?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, not that! THAT I can believe... I don't believe that Mr. Tonate just "made a mistake."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'd better think about this a little more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright, do you intend to continue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe Mr. Tonate really did see the "R"... But there's no "R" anywhere in the bloody writing. What's going on here? Huh? Now that I take another good look at the photo, I think maybe...</thought> THAT'S IT!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it now, Mr. Wright?! Are you trying to imitate Apollo and his "Chords of Steel"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got it! So that's what happened!</thought> "A slip of the finger." Is that really all it was? Because I don't think so. I propose that Mr. Tonate really DID see the letter "R."</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... ...the photo clearly shows that there is no "R"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor. Actually, just the opposite is true. The photo shows that Mr. Tonate actually could have seen the "R."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to make that claim, then you'd better be able to point out what you mean! What part of the photo shows that Mr. Tonate could have seen the "R"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What exactly are you pointing at?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, um, here, Your Honor... Or maybe it's this spot over here...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you deciding what to point at by gauging my expression? Why must you always be so wishy-washy, Phoenix Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My apologies. I'll try to be more resolute next time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please look here, to the right of the "5." Do you see a little bit of red?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I see it! Just on the edge of where the floor is broken up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the "R" that Mr. Tonate saw.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, well, that explains it-- Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Care to explain what you mean...? Because you just proposed that everything happened in the exact opposite order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup, because that's the way it really went down. <thought>The timing of when the "R" was written turns everything about this case around!</thought> Now then, if the floor was damaged by the explosion, when was the message written?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I propose that the bloody message was written after the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... and so, where does that leave us? Does that change things in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I guess that really wouldn't change anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just answered any old thing without thinking, didn't you? Well, here's MY answer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the message was written after the floor was damaged by the explosion... ...I don't think things would've ended up looking the way they do in the photo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I guess you're right. Let me try that one more time, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With the bloody message running off the edge of the damaged floor like that... ...we can only conclude that it was written BEFORE the explosion!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But that's ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that were true, it overturns your own premise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. It does. In fact, it turns everything upside-down! The victim was not killed by the explosion in the courtroom! She was killed before the explosion ever occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What kind of preposterous claim is that?! Have you forgotten that the victim's body was found at the scene of the explosion?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It sounds like we had better look into what the victim was doing before the trial. Mr. Payne, did anyone see Detective Arme before the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Let's see... According to the police report... ...Ah, here it is! One person! One person saw the victim before the trial! And that person was... Ted Tonate... Wait, what?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-No one besides Mr. Tonate saw the victim?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That appears to be the case, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would now ask the court to recall something... Specifically, Mr. Tonate's words from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">IT WAS WHEN DETECTIVE ARME AND I WERE TRANSPORTING THE BOMB.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate! Just before the trial, you were with the victim! The two of you were together at the scene of the crime, Courtroom No. 4!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGHHH! LWOU8 AS;/*7; H98AH&#160;% ^&amp;* 2PQZCX!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense requests new testimony from Mr. Tonate! We wish to hear what he has to say about his whereabouts just before the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Tonate! Your testimony, please!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">MY TESTIMONY? THERE IS NO NEED FOR... WHALJ8 6Y9PO 4XQ*&amp; HBR9Z VE8#!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's completely unnerved, Mr. Wright! You must've hit the nail on the head!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BEcAUszE oPT! ALL I DDDID WAS TRANSPORT THE BBBOMB TO THE3 COURTROOM! I ALREADY TTTOLD YOU! POAOU 2LWJ@ OUOKST! Graaagh! Blast this thing! I was only in the courtroom with the victim because of our work! I swear I was only transporting the bomb here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Payne:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What now, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, Mr. Tonate may have had the opportunity to kill Detective Arme. But an important piece of your assertion is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What important piece?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The murder weapon! What do you claim was used to kill the victim?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Payne has a point! Even if Mr. Tonate had the chance, without a weapon, we can't accuse him of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, Mr. Tonate?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Oh, uh, yes! That's right! I didn't have any sort of thing that could be used as a murder weapon on me. I couldn't possibly have killed Detective Arme!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did he really have nothing he could use as a murder weapon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm. Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just looking over the victim's autopsy report. I'm hoping there's something in here that can point us in the right direction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it does say that she died from trauma to the back of the head with a flat object.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and to inflict that specific kind of injury... ...all you would need is a flat surface, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A heavy, blunt object with a flat surface could definitely be our murder weapon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Can you indicate for the court what was used to kill Detective Arme?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I believe I can. <thought>"Believe" being the key word here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Y-You can?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then please do so now! What did Mr. Tonate have that could have been used as the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Huh? Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aha! You fell right into my trap!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you confirm that this piece of evidence was NOT the murder weapon. That narrows my candidates down by one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope you don't intend to answer by process of elimination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Because if you do, prepare to see me, do more of this to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaagh! <thought>The victim was killed with a blow to the head, so the question is... ...which evidence is connected to Mr. Tonate and could serve as a blunt instrument?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll ask you again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate, you say you didn't have anything that could be used as a weapon. But in fact, you had the perfect thing.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! What the devil are you talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's the bomb. I thought you were trying to prove that the victim wasn't killed by the bomb blast.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bomb blast, no. But I believe Candice Arme WAS killed with this bomb. Because this is the blunt object that delivered the fatal blow to her head!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Graaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please recall the description of Detective Arme's head wound. "Trauma to back of head caused by impact with a flat object." We assumed this injury was sustained when her head hit the floor... ...but a blow from any flat side of this bomb would produce the exact same wound pattern!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Uuugh! Gaaagh............ Ungh............ Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What's with him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Then show me some proof! Where's the evidence that I hit the victim with the bomb?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! He's right. I don't have anything decisive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Did you find any of the victim's blood on the bomb? That would be decisive proof. But too bad! The bomb is blown to bits! It's long gone! Boom! Game over! Yeaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Is there really nothing on the bomb in the photo?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh! I don't see any blood or anything...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! The timer display is a little broken here! Maybe it broke when it made contact with Detective Arme's head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's definitely a distinct possibility. But unless we find a fragment with the victim's blood on it, it's not going to count.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... I guess you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By setting off the bomb, Tonate managed to obliterate all traces of the murder weapon. What in the world do I do now? At times like this, I've got to change gears and look at things in a different way! Instead of looking for the things he wasn't able to hide... ...I should be looking for a way to expose the things he DID hide. Ted Tonate murdered Detective Arme before the trial started... Then he placed her body in the courtroom after the bomb went off. Which means there was something he needed to keep hidden until then. And I think I have just the thing. Time to present the photo that shows exactly what Mr. Tonate had to hide!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm not sure I really understand what you mean by that, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm not sure, either, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ME, EITHER.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Here's a penalty to inspire you to make more comprehensible assertions in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that was a spectacular belly flop. But I can't back down now. I'd better reconsider what Mr. Tonate could have hidden.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! There's something we've all been overlooking! If the murder took place before the trial... ...then Mr. Tonate would've had to hide the body somewhere during the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right! And if we can figure out where that hiding place was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. We might be able to find some evidence we can pin him down with! So where could Mr. Tonate have hidden the body during the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a good look at this, Mr. Tonate!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............ What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops... Did I do it again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sensing a wave of strong anxiety coming from you right now, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, the evidence you have presented appears to be meaningless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I DID do it again... I'd better try again. If the murder took place before the trial... ...then he would've had to hide the body somewhere during the trial!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... A box big enough for a body, a box that was in the courtroom the whole time... A box nobody would touch if they thought there was a bomb in it!</thought> Mr. Tonate!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHAT IS IT? DO YOU FINALLY HAVE SOME DECISIVE EVIDENCE TO SHOW ME?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you're the one who's going to show it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">COME AGAIN?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You heard me. Now, show me what's inside that bomb transport case!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">What?! Why?! No! There's no need!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got him now!</thought> Just before the trial, you killed the victim with a blunt object. And then, you placed her body in the ruins of the courtroom after the bomb went off. Clearly, you were trying to make it look like she died in the explosion. But where was the body hidden during the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I hadn't thought of that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer is right here! Inside a box made of thick alloy plating that can withstand any impact!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Um, no! That's, er, completely false!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it's false, you should have no objections to showing us your transport case. So! Let's open it up and take a look inside, shall we?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Tonate:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What's he up to now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">REMAIN CALM AND LISTEN CAREFULLY. THIS BOMB WILL DETONATE IN FIVE MINUTES.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I REPEAT, THIS HH-3000 WILL DETONATE IN FIVE MINUTES.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's going on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YOUR HONOR, I RECOMMEND YOU ADJOURN THIS TRIAL... ...BEFORE THIS BOMB GOES OFF.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Tonate! Are you... Are you threatening me?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">HEH HEH HEH. I AM THE ONLY ONE WHO CAN DISABLE THIS BOMB. IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO DIE, YOUR ONLY OPTION IS TO LISTEN TO ME.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But Mr. Tonate! Didn't you say that's just a training model? A fake to practice on?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I DID, BUT I ALSO LIED. THIS IS THE REAL DEAL. THIS IS THE HH-3000.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the HH-3000 was used to blow up Courtroom No. 4... wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">HOW DO YOU KNOW IT WAS THE REAL HH-3000 THAT BLEW UP COURTROOM NO. 4?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE BOMB THAT BLEW UP THE COURTROOM WAS A DIFFERENT ONE, ONE THAT I MADE.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Then, are we to take that as a confession on your part?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">TAKE IT ANY WAY YOU WOULD LIKE. JUST BEFORE THE TRIAL... ...I TOOK THE HH-3000 OUT OF THE STUFFED ANIMAL AND PUT MY OWN BOMB INTO IT. THAT WAS THE BOMB THAT EXPLODED AND DESTROYED COURTROOM NO. 4.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">M-Mr. Tonate, please be reasonable! Do you really expect us to believe a crazy story like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE HH-3000... IT IS SO UNIQUE! I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT. IT IS SO UNIQUE THAT I COULD NOT REPLICATE THE DETONATION MECHANISM. SO... I JUST HAD TO HAVE IT. BESIDES, DID ANYONE LOOK INSIDE THE STUFFED ANIMAL DURING THE TRIAL? DID ANYONE CHECK TO SEE IF IT REALLY WAS THE HH-3000 IN THERE?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">! I-I must confess, no one opened up the stuffed animal to check...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">S-So there really is a possibility that the bomb was switched out?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NO, NOT A POSSIBILITY. A CERTAINTY. I DID IT.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's had a real bomb with him this whole time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YOU HAD BETTER GET OUT OF HERE WHILE YOU CAN. YOU DO NOT HAVE MUCH TIME.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Man">I-I'm outta here!!! It's gonna blow! RUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUN!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YOU FOUR ARE STILL HERE? WELL, WELL. AREN'T YOU BRAVE?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I-It just wouldn't do for the judge presiding over this court to run... ...but that horrible explosion the other day...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge looks like he's about to book it for the nearest exit any second... And Mr. Payne...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I-I-I-I-I... That is... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And he's off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Wh-What do we do?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... It'd be pretty pathetic to run now, wouldn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But the bomb might really go off...!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ONLY THREE MORE MINUTES, FOLKS.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that bomb really the HH-3000? What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No! I can't do that! I can't run, not now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-M-Mr. Wright! That look on your face...! You weren't thinking of running away like a yellow-bellied chicken, were you?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss! I never would've expected that from you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I only thought about it for a second!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">U-Unacceptable, Mr. Wright! If you think about running away again... ...I will be forced to throw you out of this courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I wish you would, Your Honor. I'd better reconsider my next course of action...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't run now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL, IT'S BEEN FUN, BUT I WILL BE GOING NOW. WITH MY DEAR, DEAR HH-3000, NATURALLY. OH, AND BY THE WAY. I WOULD ADVISE AGAINST HAVING ME FOLLOWED. EVEN WITH NO REMOTE SWITCH, THIS BOMB CAN STILL BE TRIGGERED MANUALLY. IF I THINK I'M BEING FOLLOWED, I WILL DETONATE IT ON THE SPOT. FAREWELL.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">OH?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, there's no reason to be afraid! That bomb is a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Are you sure, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............HMPH. MORE OF YOUR FAMOUS BLUFFING? EVEN AT THE RISK OF YOUR OWN LIFE?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-M-Mr. Wright! None of your bluffing now! Not at a time like this! Lives are on the line, here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not bluffing. And I have proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, of course, Your Honor. It's right here in the photo of the bomb, clear as day. Proof that Mr. Tonate's bomb is not the real HH-3000!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really?! Out with it, then! Immediately! Where is the proof that what Mr. Tonate is holding is not the real HH-3000?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">MR. WRIGHT! ARE YOU GUESSING AT A TIME LIKE THIS?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, Your Honor! Let me try again! <thought>That bomb is missing something is should have if it were the real thing! That's the proof I need!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... If the bomb doesn't get us, the judge definitely will if you don't get this right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Try again, Mr. Wright! And no guessing this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The display for the timer on the bomb in the photo is broken. Most likely, it broke when Mr. Tonate used the bomb to attack Detective Arme. But the display on the bomb in front of us is not broken.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Therefore, this is not the real HH-3000. Mr. Tonate was clearly lying when he said he switched out the bomb in the stuffed animal! The real HH-3000 blew up in Courtroom No. 4! This bomb is nothing more than a fake, a model used for training purposes!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fear not, Your Honor! I will examine the inside of the bomb transport case myself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, please do that, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NO! STOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOP!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is that...? I-Is that a bloodstain?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as I expected. Your lies have all been blown to bits, Mr. Tonate! I'm confident DNA analysis on this bloodstain will confirm that it's Detective Arme's blood. And that those results will conclusively prove that you murdered Detective Arme!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuungh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about it, Mr. Tonate? Think you can dismantle this conclusive evidence?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">............Dismantle it? Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! You're too late! You missed your chance to run, so now you're out of time! This HH-3000, is about to explode!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't try to threaten us, Mr. Tonate. I've already proved that your "bomb" is a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">It's real! This bomb is the real thing, I tell you! It's real... Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee! HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA! HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA HA!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mad Bomber, party of one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">There's no time left! It's going to blow! I have to disarm it! I have to take it apart! I can dismantle anything! I can take apart evidence! I can take apart bombs! I can dismantle it all! DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE DISMANTLE I'M NOT GONNA MAKE IIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIT!!! ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO DOOOOOOOOOOOOOO! STOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOP!!! M-MADE IT--!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Ha ha ha! It's all over! My life has been blown to pieces! It's all that stupid woman's fault! I was selling the bombs I disarmed on the black market. When I tried to take this one, she just had to notice, didn't she?! She confronted me in Courtroom No. 4 that day. That's why... That's why I had no choice! Before I knew what I was doing, I hit her... It's all her fault! While I was looking for a place to hide her body, she left a message in her own blood! The trial was about to start, so I didn't have time to clean it up. And now all this...! I thought for sure I could disguise her death with an explosion! Then that stupid defense attorney started sticking his nose into my business! After my testimony yesterday, I went to Courtroom No. 4 and... I found that kid all up in my bomb transport case! That's when I snuck up behind him and ...BAM! And when the idiot police arrested that little girl... ...I thought for sure I could pin it all on her! Why... oh, why...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ted Tonate, you are hereby under arrest... ...on suspicion of the courtroom bombing and the assault on Mr. Justice. Your innocence or guilt will be determined at a later trial. Now then, I see that members of the public have returned to the gallery. One person, however, seems to still be running far, far away... Be that as it may... ...I will now announce Ms. Juniper Woods's verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess we managed to pull it off somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So many mysteries cleared up all at once! It was amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It just sort of worked out that way, didn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not the kind of thing that usually just "works out"" You made it happen! And the way that mean ol' prosecutor high-tailed it out of here! That was great!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Mr. Wright, Thena, thank you for everything you did for me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm so happy for you, Junie! Now you can go back home to the forest in peace!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I hope the both of you will come and visit me there sometime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be nice. Thank you for the invitation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I dunno, Mr. Wright... I'm not so sure you could make it all the way up to Junie's house. How high up do you live again, Junie?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Umm... Around 3,000 feet, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! <thought>That's no forest -- that's a mountain!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But, you know, Boss... ...there's something that still bothers me about the case. One little mystery we never got around to solving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that? Yeah, I was wondering about that, too... Is this the unsolved mystery you're thinking of?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah. I wonder where it disappeared to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glad mind reading isn't my day job.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was wondering about the missing remote switch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............! <thought>O-Oh, right! That unsolved mystery!</thought> Ha ha ha. I was just testing you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so you were looking to get a reaction out of me, huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. Always remember: The trial isn't really over until you get back to the office. Even if you get a "not guilty", you still have to remember to stay sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, don't gloat too much over a victory, right, Boss? Thanks for the tip! But I still wonder where that remote switch disappeared to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe Mr. Tonate just got rid of it somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... It is a pretty big thing to leave unsolved, though...</thought> Well, let's leave it up to the police to find. For now, we should be celebrating our not guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess you're right! Hey, I know! Junie, shall we go report the good news? You know, to that certain someone...?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Her grandmother?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, silly! To Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Well, why don't we all go to the hospital together to see him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great idea! I bet he's bored out of his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so, the courtroom bombing case came to a close. But the next trial was just over the horizon. There's never a dull moment with so many lawyers in the office. That's for sure. Apollo Justice, Athena Cykes, and me, Phoenix Wright. Between the three of us, there's no case we can't solve! When our powers combine, we're an unstoppable team. ...At least, that's what I believed. But all of that changed with what Apollo said to us that day. It was something that would put my faith in us to the ultimate test.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, but I'll be taking a leave of absence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, what do you mean by "a leave"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you at least give me a reason why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can only say... that this is something I must settle on my own.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh why, Apollo? Why are you shutting us out?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What happened to you, Apollo? Ever since you put that jacket on, you've changed. ............ And now, for whatever reason, all my mind keeps doing... ...is returning to the day I met you. We had tackled our first case together, he and I, this past spring. And as we did, I came to know who he is and how he thinks. It was a very peculiar case, one in which the victim was killed by a mythical creature...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it clearly contradicts the statement... er, doesn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't see anything particularly contradictory here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! Well, it can't hurt to try, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a penalty for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouchies... I guess it can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe you should take a deep breath and re-think things, Mr. Wright. I'm sensing that you've got the wrong evidence AND the wrong statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you're right. I've got that nagging feeling about Mr. Tonate's last statement.  </line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know what? That's how I feel about the stuffed animal bomb, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. The last statement and the stuffed animal bomb, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm sorry, Mr. Wright... ...but the only thing "odd" I find here is your objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go so well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just don't understand it. I was so sure that the correct evidence to present was this stuffed animal bomb. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Then I guess we presented it at the wrong statement.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet that's it! Why don't we take another good look at the other statements? There must be one in the testimony that contradicts that bomb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Must we be so cut and dry, Your Honor? They say it pays to keep an open mind about things.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's true. And lucky for you... ...I'm very open-minded about giving people the penalties they deserve!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You honor me with your open-mindedness... <thought>Guess I should've seen that one coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I agree there's definitely something off about this statement. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Wonder if I presented the wrong piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet that's it! Why don't you take another look through the Court Record? There must be something in there that contradicts the statement: "I saw that the bomb's timer was counting down."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I think I have something here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sensed something wrong with the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Let me show you which statement I thought was strange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. That would be a big help! <thought>Now I just have to compare the evidence with the statement she points out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I don't see any inconsistencies in the testimony. This might be a good time to--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Press for more information? I think you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just can't help but feel that there's more to these statements than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll put my faith in Athena and press them for all their worth, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we view your emotions alongside your testimony, we find the unexpected emotion-- <thought>Wait a minute... There really isn't anything strange here.</thought>    </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but I think maybe we made a mistake, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I think maybe you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's take another look! There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It does?! I... I'm so sorry! I had no idea... *cough* *cough*...... *cough* *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, are you all right?! Mr. Wright, why are you badgering Junie like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh? <thought>But I was trying so hard not to...</thought>  </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, if you could refrain from badgering your own client, please. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you know, with the new facts we learned from Junie's revised testimony... ...I'm sure we can find an inconsistency with a piece of evidence we already have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess I'd better take another look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! I got it wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I'm forced to give you a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm sorry, Mr. Wright... ...but the only thing "odd" I find here is your objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go so well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I apologize, Your Honor. I seem to have made a slight miscalculation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You never change, do you? Let this be a lesson to always take every factor into account, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. <thought>Guess I should've seen that one coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Juniper Woods...</line>
</xml>