<xml>
<title>Turnabout Trump</title>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Panicked... Palms sweaty... I can admit it. I'm nervous.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">G-Good morning, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You look tense, Justice. Wound up tight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wound up, sir? No! I'm loose! I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That screeching noise... Is that your voice? I suppose it's to be expected... Your first trial, and it's a homicide. I guess "Justice" doesn't start small, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm fine! I got up at 5 AM to do my "Chords of Steel" voice workout! I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, that explains it. I did detect a certain rasping quality to your screech.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...*cough* <thought>I overdid it again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As you know, your client today is a good friend of mine. I wouldn't want to let him down... if you get my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Drift gotten, sir! I-I'm all over that drift!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As it happens, I dined with him the night of the murder. We can't let this case fall through.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. Yes! I'm fine, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">One more thing. Don't say you're fine quite so much. People might take you the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I'll be preparing our case. You might want to introduce yourself to the client.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My name is Apollo Justice. If it isn't clear already, I'm a new attorney. And today is my first trial. N-Not that I'm worried or anything! The defendant has been accused of... murder. My boss wants to help him out, of course... and so do I! I mean, there's no way he did it. Not him! No way!</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa!</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good uh, morning!</line>
<line speaker="???">... Morning. It's all up to you today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>First trial: nervous. Meeting him: cardiac arrest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... <thought>I think I'm supposed to say something... Uh... help?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">So, you're...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine! I-I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah... Mr. Fine, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh.</line>
<line speaker="???">I did remember you having an odd name.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, we're off to a great start.</thought> Um... Are you sure you're OK, I mean, with me?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin is a top-notch defense attorney. And he's your friend! So why...</line>
<line speaker="???">... You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh?</line>
<line speaker="???">You can do it. Be confident.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I... I'm really sorry this happened to you. I mean... I mean, I...</line>
<line speaker="???">It's time. Shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir! <thought>...OK. I need to focus. First trial, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a number inscribed on the back of the badge. There are many numbers like it, but this one is mine. Proof that I'm an attorney. To tell the truth, I get a happy feeling inside just looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, the defense is, uh, fine! I mean ready, Your Honor! <thought>Mind going blank... Don't panic... Ack, too late!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your name was... Mr. Justice? And this is your first trial?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor! But I'm fine! Really!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you quite sure? Your voice sounds a bit strained.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...*cough*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was under the impression that you would be heading up this case...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That was my intention, yes. However... A defense attorney must always cede to his client's wishes. And my client specifically requested Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, of course he wants justice! But to entrust his case to this greenhorn... Why? I do not exaggerate when I say that you're the best defense attorney in town, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, so Gavin's got trial experience, fine. But does he have Chords of Steel!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's begin. The defendant may enter the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is truly an unfortunate turn of events. I'm sorry we had to meet again under these circumstances. Long time no see, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's put the past behind us, shall we? These days, I'm merely Phoenix Wright, piano player.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Wright... How could this have happened?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I won't speak of it further then. If the prosecution would be so kind as to explain the charges. Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">To think, I saw you enter this room a fresh attorney, and now I'll see you leave in chains.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, Winston Payne. Subtle as ever, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ahem. The crime occurred at the Borscht Bowl Club... a Russian restaurant. The defendant, Phoenix Wright, took the victim, a customer... ...and he hit him! Wham! On the head! Smack! Killed him cold.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A customer at the restaurant, you say? And the defendant, you say he was...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The pianist for the club, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Phoenix Wright... A pianist?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is the weapon that took the victim's life. A bottle of grape juice. Grape juice is apparently our defendant's drink of choice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts the deadly bottle as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grape juice... How long has it been since I drank grape juice? Apparently, it's Mr. Wright's favorite drink. I wonder how well it goes with borscht?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The bottle is completely empty.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Something to note, Justice. All evidence is filed in the Court Record. Make a practice of checking it frequently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Court Record... Right! I've heard of that!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Use the Court Record Button to look at the evidence so far. I'm confident in your ability to handle this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right, the Court Record Button. Sounds like it's time for some hands-on action!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the victim was a customer at this restaurant. But just who was this, erm, "Shadi Smith" fellow?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We believe he was a traveler, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... traveler?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">According to his passport, he had been out of the country for a number of years. He had only returned to this country recently, though his place of residence is unclear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And he had some sort of connection with the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...That, too, is unclear at present, Your Honor. We believe they first met at the Borscht Bowl Club on the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If they had only just met, then why murder? Perhaps the victim slighted the defendant's piano playing?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That doesn't appear to have been the case. No, the motive had nothing to do with the defendant's lack of playing skill. At least not piano playing. I'll let this photo explain what I mean. As we can see, a game of poker was in progress at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait a second! Isn't poker gambling? That's a crime in and of itself!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Indeed. It appears our defendant... ...has fallen to become the basest sort of criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It is true that the defendant was engaged in a game of poker with the victim. Yet it was only that: a game, in the purest sense. A competition, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A... competition?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes, a test of wits, a silent clash of passions... Only the cards, their backs wreathed in blue flame, know its final outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Er, come again?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The cards on the table had blue backs, Your Honor. I believe the defense was waxing poetic in an attempt to mystify those present... ...and impress women.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will be our first order of business here then: To find out more about this fatal game of cards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will testify to the court about the poker competition held the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...My pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it, my first trial! Here goes nothing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am a pianist by trade... yet I can hardly play at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmm. A pianist who can't play piano?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Better than a defense attorney who can't defend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Very well. The defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right, Your Honor! <thought>My first cross-examination! Don't blow it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Are you alright? You're sweating bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bullets...!? Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's a figure of speech, Justice. Your voice sounds strained and raspy, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My brain feels strained and raspy, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You've watched me perform cross-examinations many times. Though you've never done one yourself, have you? Care for a refresher?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What to do? Should I ask Mr. Gavin for a refresher course in cross-examination?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Better safe than sorry, especially this early in the game!</thought> Yes, teach me! I know nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Indeed. Your job, Justice, is to be mindful of the Court Record and the testimony. Look for inconsistencies in the testimony with what the Court Record tells you. When you've found an inconsistency... That's when you present the conflicting evidence from the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I didn't hear anything strange at all in the testimony just now...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">A good sign that you need to press the witness for more information.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Press... him?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't let the fact that he's a remarkable man hold you back. Get more information!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh... But isn't Mr. Wright my client?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well? Think you can do it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! Thank you, sir! I think I can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I think you'd better, or we're going to have a problem. Just remember...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No need for help here, sir! I think I've got this one covered!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I think you'd better do more than think. You know it, or you do not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm fine! The Chords of Steel are ready for battle! My weapons: press and present...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Find any inconsistencies, any lies in the testimony, and reveal them to the court. That is cross-examination. Learn it. Know it. Do it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Inconsistencies"? "Lies"? Phoenix Wright...? As if! Phoenix Wright would never lie, and it's up to me to prove it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am a pianist by trade... yet I can hardly play at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can hardly play...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I play sometimes. When customers demand it. So I play them one song. That's usually all they want.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Was that supposed to be a boast just now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The title of "pianist" is a mask -- a respectable face I wear for the world at large.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then why are you really at the Borscht Bowl Club?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My real job is to take on interested customers over at the poker table.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They pay you just to play poker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would seem to be the case. I am a professional, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Bah! Do I detect pride in that statement? It's just hard for an honest, hard-working member of society like me to imagine...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Your imagination was always a bit limited, Winston.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've played poker for seven years in that little room. And I've never. Lost. Once.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You see why the customers come now? "Defeat the undefeated poker champion"... It's quite a draw. That is, I'm quite a draw.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you've never lost once? Not even one time!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I said, I'm a professional.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's played poker for seven years and not lost once... Is that even possible!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This competition you're talking about... I believe the court understands the nature of the game sufficiently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right! It was a simple game, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">People are not murdered over "simple games", Mr. Justice. Defendant. You were in the room the very moment that the crime occurred... Yet you claim no connection to the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Now that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was testifying about the competition that night. Asking me about the crime at this point is against the rules, Your Honor. Of course, I expected to hear a cry of "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" from the defense...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Argh! I completely let that one slip by!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't despair yet, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wright. There's something I'd like made clear. Namely, your connection to the case at hand. And I'd like to hear it from you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sure, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defendant will amend his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just one little press... ...and I've got myself a whole new testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The room where we play and the competition in there are the club's main attractions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The room in the crime scene photo... is an attraction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has quite a history, actually. The Borscht Bowl Club used to be a gathering spot for black market types back in the day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-Black market?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All in the past. Things like the black market are only on the silver screen nowadays. Suffice it to say that there were a lot of deals being made under the table. Right there in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A smoky room, gambling hoods. You know... Just looking at this picture makes me feel "bad"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bosses gather around the table, cutting deals, safe from the eyes of the law... Meanwhile, a goon keeps watch through the small window... I can practically picture it now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That window does look like it would be good for keeping a look-out but little else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The room had a few other tricks to it... Though it was common knowledge to our regulars. At any rate, they come to play poker in a room steeped in history. Despite the dark past, it was all just good, clean fun.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This competition you're talking about... I believe the court understands the nature of the game sufficiently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right! It was a simple game, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">People are not murdered over "simple games", Mr. Justice. Defendant. You were in the room the very moment that the crime occurred... Yet you claim no connection to the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Now that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was testifying about the competition that night. Asking me about the crime at this point is against the rules, Your Honor. Of course, I expected to hear a cry of "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" from the defense...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Argh! I completely let that one slip by!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't despair yet, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wright. There's something I'd like made clear. Namely, your connection to the case at hand. And I'd like to hear it from you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sure, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defendant will amend his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just one little press... ...and I've got myself a whole new testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The rules are simple: we play a game of poker using two decks of cards.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Two decks of cards?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A simple measure to prevent cheating. If you alternate two decks, no one can slip in cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's something else I noticed... In addition to the cards on the table, there are some lying scattered on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Precisely. Cards on the table, cards upon the floor... Each one forming a complete deck. A crime scene painted blue by a sad sweep of cards... It's poetic, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Incidentally, we used two types of cards at the club. One deck of cards was red. The other blue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... As I recall, in poker you make five-card "hands". I can see how it would be easy to cheat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh... Yes. A game of "hands".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This competition you're talking about... I believe the court understands the nature of the game sufficiently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right! It was a simple game, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">People are not murdered over "simple games", Mr. Justice. Defendant. You were in the room the very moment that the crime occurred... Yet you claim no connection to the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Now that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was testifying about the competition that night. Asking me about the crime at this point is against the rules, Your Honor. Of course, I expected to hear a cry of "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" from the defense...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Argh! I completely let that one slip by!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't despair yet, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wright. There's something I'd like made clear. Namely, your connection to the case at hand. And I'd like to hear it from you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sure, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defendant will amend his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just one little press... ...and I've got myself a whole new testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all it is... a game. And our customers are happy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you claim you weren't gambling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. It was simply a game.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't bet any money? Not even a little?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only thing at stake in our game... was pride itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! Well put, Mr. Wright. I've got a mind to play a hand of poker myself... The stakes: your fate!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um... Can we get back to the trial now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I plead silence regarding the murder. But I will say I never touched the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Silence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant has the right to refuse to testify. ...I haven't forgotten everything about the law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But why? That clearly puts you at a disadvantage...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it's your job to turn that around in our favor, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great. Like I didn't have enough to do already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice. Didn't you detect anything odd about that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? <thought>Wait... Something he said did ring a little strangely. Just one thing... Now what was it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">When you figure it out, I'd suggest presenting evidence. Evidence that contradicts the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A contradiction in Mr. Wright's testimony? But why!? I'd better check the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't imagine Mr. Wright lying in a testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Isn't it a little early to be jumping to conclusions? This is your first cross-examination. Take it slow. If you need more information, don't forget to press.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right! I got it! I'm fine! <thought>Time to listen to that testimony again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you say you didn't touch the murder weapon... this grape juice bottle? ...Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something the matter, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee hee hee... Too bad our new defense attorney never learned how to play dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I examined the bottle in question, you see. And it was covered with the defendant's fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">No need to shout, Mr. Justice! I can hear you just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Excess yelling can damage the judge's ears... and our case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>B-But what about my Chords of Steel...?</thought> Any... Anyway! What's so strange about fingerprints on a bottle in a restaurant?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that's true. The prints alone don't prove he did it--</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oh, they wouldn't prove a thing... if they were normal fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But the fingerprints on the murder weapon were upside-down!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Upside-down"? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">It means he was holding the bottle inverted! And there can be only one reason for that! ...Yes. To brain someone with the bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Auuuuuuuuuuuuuugh! M-Mr. Gavin! I think things just took a turn for the worse!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Oh? I see no problem, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The only thing that matters is the truth. There's a good reason for everything. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defendant! Can you explain your fingerprints on this bottle to the court!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I stand by my plea of silence regarding the murder. ...For now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Not very cooperative, are you? This could hurt your case.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sure he's uncooperative because he's hiding something! There must be some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Your Honor. You seem to have forgotten something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what might that be, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">On the night of the crime, who was it who reported the murder to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Reported...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, that was the defendant, Mr. Wright. But still, that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Erm, yes, well. According to the case file... The murder was reported from near the scene, by a call from the defendant's cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Near" the scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Let's take a look at a diagram of the murder scene, shall we? The victim was murdered in a small room in a basement two floors down from ground level. Of course, cell phones can't get reception so far down. The defendant used the stairs in this hallway to go above ground... The call came from the first floor of the restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... And this is the phone that made the call?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. The batteries are held in with a piece of tape... He should just buy a new one. Maybe he can't afford it... or he just doesn't care.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The defendant could have just fled the scene of the crime if he so chose. Yet, he fulfilled his duty as a citizen and reported it to the authorities. And you claim he is being "uncooperative"...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nice save, Mr. Gavin! I'd better not waste this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I think the prosecution has toyed with our client enough for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">T-Toyed? I assure you, no one is more serious about...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What was it you said? The defendant was "in the room the very moment that the crime occurred". How can you possibly know this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a good question! How indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The answer is simple, Your Honor. The prosecution has a decisive witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee hee hee. You're as good as they say you are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So someone else was in the room the night of the crime! That must mean they witnessed the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Everything up till now has been a warm-up, Justice. Are you ready?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The prosecution may call its first witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The witness will state her name and profession.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hold on just a moment! Where's the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I surmise that she has been frightened by the defense's demonic-looking horns.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So I used a little hair gel! Relax, people!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Have no fear! If any horns point in your direction this court will cut them off.</line>
<line speaker="???">... You... are sure?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I swear it on my gavel! Please, come out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't violence against hair a crime, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, if you are sure it is OK...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Now, the prosecution... W-W-Wait a minute! Would the prosecution care to explain the witness's... erm... paraphernalia?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Er... yes. She is a professional, Your Honor. Those are merely the tools of her trade.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">My name... is Olga Orly. I am employed as waitress in Borscht Bowl Club restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... why the camera?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Of course, it is my pride to serve borscht that is naming restaurant. But I also perform -- how it is said? Other service.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I take it one of these other services is taking the customers' pictures?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, dah. Like, for example... this one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's... the defendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Indeed. On the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Man in white hat... is one who has gone kaput.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... That is the victim. Order! Order! This is quite a piece of evidence to casually drop into our laps!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It is same way as I drop cold bowls of borscht on laps of customers... casually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then the court will casually accept this new evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now, witness. Where were you at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">I was in room. The Hydeout, we call it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me? The Hydeout?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It is room where famous gangster "Badgai" was arrested. Is room where murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Your look of utter surprise... It is lovely. I will post by courtroom door later for you! Dah, dah, photos will be numbered, and you will write which ones you want copy of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So there were three people in the room at the time of the crime... The victim, Shadi Smith, Mr. Wright, and... ...Olga Orly, our witness! ...And if Mr. Wright isn't the killer, that means...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Witness! You will testify to the court about that night's events!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That night, customer asked me to deal cards for game.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Incidentally, who won the game?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Isn't it obvious? The winner was the victim... Mr. Smith!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's ridiculous! Um, because... Because Mr. Wright can't lose!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ahem. Justice? Maybe you can come up with a more legitimate objection?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But! He hadn't lost in seven years!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Take it from me kid. It happens. I didn't lose a case my first seven years as prosecutor, either. Incidentally. I have some evidence here. These are the poker chips as they lay the very moment of the crime. The hand and chips on this side belong to the defendant, Mr. Wright. Those on the far side belonged to the victim, Mr. Smith.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Chips... you say?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Dah. I mean yes! Imagine that poker is war... Your hand is your army, and the chips are the spoils.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I know that. After all, in my youth I was known as... ...the "Poker Head of Courtroom No. 3"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think he means "poker face"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Looking at this picture... ...it does seem that most of the chips are on the victim's side of the table.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That night, customer asked me to deal cards for game.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were dealing cards... Do you do this often?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, I am doing this. If customer wishes it, I serve anything. Borscht, cards, more borscht... It is my work.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's good to hear of a place that hasn't forgotten the meaning of service!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Welcome you to Borscht Bowl Club, where borscht is as warm as the waitresses!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank you for NOT handing out flyers during the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It was cold... Both players played with hats on, dah.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's already April. How could it be cold?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">At Borscht Bowl Club we have pride on authentic rustic Russian restaurant theme. Outside it is city in Spring, but inside it is always as cold as Mother Russia!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No way am I going there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">When it comes to hot borscht, cold is best seasoning, dah?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The victim, he plays whole time with his hand on locket at his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His "locket"...?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">I believe it was good-luck charm, dah? He gripped it many times as he played that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, he must have felt as though it might carry him to the moon and the stars! Though if it were small enough to fit around his neck, it wouldn't have much lift...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... The defense would like a clarification: this is a locket we're talking about? I mean, a pendant with a picture in it, right? Not a "rocket"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course! I knew that! It was probably a pendant shaped like a rocket. That's why she called it that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, a locket's a locket! It doesn't matter what shape it is.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's considered bad form to poke fun at the hard-of-hearing in our society.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hard of hearing, or hard of understanding?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">So, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Olga">Then, last hand is done! But something terrible has happened, dah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something terrible!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will refrain from needless shouting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, sorry. <thought>I need to seriously reconsider this vocal training thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now, Ms. Orly, can you tell us what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Oh, I was so frightened! Dah, I trembled with fear!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That man flew at victim, and is strangling him to death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the defendant would never do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well now, I can't say I've ever heard the defense try this tactic.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">If possible... Please... Refrain from embarrassing me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Still... Why would anyone do something like this over a game of poker?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Perhaps it is because defendant has lost game?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes! A crushing defeat for a man undefeated! So it always is with men like him. Winners make sore losers. Oh, how the mighty fall!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh really? "Strangled", you say? That's odd.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, normal customers only choke on borscht.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I mean this report shows that the victim died of a blow to the head!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Aaack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly! Really now... Did you witness the crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Looking at the picture, it doesn't seem like he was hit. He's still wearing his hat and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yet, it is a fact that he was hit, Your Honor. Here's a photo we took of the victim with his hat off during our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that's quite shocking, isn't it? This head certainly was hit.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">B-But...! I have seen it happen!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The defendant, he lunge at victim, his neck...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh really, Ms. Orly? I think I've caught you in your own lie this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Justice. I admire your enthusiasm, but perhaps you should think this through once more.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What do you mean? I found a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There's one thing in her testimony that... troubles me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. It seems we should continue the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's such a thing as thinking too much... This horse is dead, let's stop beating it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There's such a thing as thinking aloud too much, too.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">After defendant tried to strangle victim, he hit him with bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't say anything about hitting before!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">S-S-S-S-So sorry! I must be forgetting this, dah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! You will take greater care with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Oh dah, dah. I'm sorry, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And that clears up the discrepancy with the autopsy report, I believe. The defendant made to strangle his victim, then changed his mind... ...and chose a simpler, blunter means to do the job. Yes, that sums it up nicely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he strangled him, then hit him...? Something's fishy about all this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Go ahead. I believe you know what it is you need to do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, sir! Leave it to me! <thought>There were only three people in the room at the time of the murder. The victim, Shadi Smith, Mr. Wright, and... And if Mr. Wright isn't the killer... I've got you now, Orly!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You know, there was one curious part in her testimony just like Mr. Gavin said. But what does it mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, would you care to explain what it is you're thinking so intensely about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall the testimony, Your Honor... The victim played with "his hand on locket at his neck", I believe she said?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I hope you aren't about to raise an objection to the witness's grammar!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, but look at this photograph. Do you see a locket on the victim's neck?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well done, Justice. I'm impressed. I knew you'd be able to handle this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But what does it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If we are to believe this witness's testimony as-is... Then the locket "disappeared" following the victim's death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lockets don't just "disappear", Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's quite simple when you think about it. If the locket is gone, someone must have taken it off, no?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Taken it off... Wait, you don't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The defendant wasn't strangling the victim at all. He was taking off his locket! ...Wouldn't that explain it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Defendant! What do you have to say to this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I just noticed this, but... You have something hanging around your neck, don't you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? You mean this? Yes, it's a locket... with a photograph inside. A photo... of my daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C-Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! You have a daughter!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">We confirmed it at the time of the arrest. The picture in the locket is indeed Mr. Wright's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Mr. Wright has a locket, too...? Why don't I buy that this is just a coincidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well now, if the results of this poker game led to the murder... Perhaps we should hear a bit more about the outcome of the game?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Further testimony won't really be necessary. It's clear the defendant lost. Badly.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Orly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will testify to the court about the game played between the victim and the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">D-Dah...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The game began with 3,500 point in chips for each man.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... Looking at this picture... It does seem to be a one-sided game.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">As the court knows, poker was the defendant's life! Failure must have been a bitter pill to swallow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, how many times have I heard these words: "I done it in a fit of anger, Yer Honor, and now I regret what I done". ...A common tale, but true.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Methinks the judge watches too many old court movies. Mr. Wright said he hasn't lost in seven years, so this testimony must be wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">The game began with 3,500 point in chips for each man.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are those the usual starting points? Were any special rules used...?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">No, not special. Usual game, usual rules.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If each man began with 3,500 points, then the total would be... Um... Exactly six, no, 7,000 points!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Please, this isn't calculus. It's not even long division!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Olga">House chips come in two size: small and large.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are the chips in this photo all the chips that were used?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Da... Dah! Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...? <thought>Something's fishy with these chips. Should I press harder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Nah. ...It's her nature to be jumpy and suspicious-looking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you could explain a bit about these "chips"?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">E-Explain? What is there to be explained?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Poker chips are poker chips. They're not fish and chips, not a chip off the old block, not a motorcycle cop, not a...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thanks. <thought>Now that I've pressed her I'd better ask something...</thought> What are these chips worth? Are they in dollars? Or rubles, even?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...Nyet. As I have been saying before, it was game, not gambling. Hard perhaps for capitalist to understand. Two types of chip: 100 points chip and 1,000 points chip. It is not money, dah.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't you find her comment... interesting?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In more ways than one, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I'd have it added to her testimony, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Does the defense want the witness to add to her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Very well... It's your trial, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Way to fill me with confidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will resume her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I do think this deserves further scrutiny. Add it to the testimony! <thought>I wish I knew where I was going with this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness, if you would be so kind?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">D-Dah, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">One kind of chip is worth 100 points, other kind is worth 1,000. Two kinds in all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Gavin said this testimony is important! ...To be honest, I have no idea why.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Justice? Do the court a favor and think of what you want to say before raising your hand. We are not in kindergarten.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Sorry! I'm fine! <thought>I'd better think of something to ask... and quick!</thought> Um... The two types of chips...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um. The small ones are 100, and the big ones 1,000... Uh? Right? Right. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hah! Don't waste our time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that all?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Yeah. *gulp* <thought>Great. Mr. Gavin made me stop her, and now I'm the one who looks dumb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh, Justice? Please try not to embarrass me like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Who? Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There's a clear contradiction in the information you have in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's a simple matter of calculation. Go on, try it. We're not in kindergarten, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Calculation"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Olga">The one who was winning... dah, it was victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're telling me that Mr. Wright, undefeated for seven whole years, was losing?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah. It must have been most unlucky day for him. I am glad I did not take other picture of him. It would break camera, certainly. The chips, they went always to victim's side of table.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">So you're telling us it was a one-sided game?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah. One-sided, and...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Olga">For last hand, defendant play with all chips on table and lose.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Last hand"?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It was largest points of any hand. The defendant's hand, it was excellent. He try to use it to take victory from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears that both the defendant and the victim's hands are in this picture. That is truly an excellent hand. However, so is the victim's...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">One with highest number wins, so defendant loses.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The victim, Mr. Smith, had a stronger hand than the defendant and crushed him. I believe that explains what occurred next.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Once cards laid down on table, it happened...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The moment loss was decided, defendant grabs bottle from table and...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And...? What happened next!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...Even to think of it now, I shake and tremble, dah! I did not believe such thing would happen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What "such thing"!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Please, you must believe! I had no idea... How could such thing occur!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What "such thing"!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...Ny-Nyet! ...Nyet, nyet, nyet! The defendant had been hitting v-victim!!! Dah, I saw it all happen, right before me... I saw bottle coming down on victim's head!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Decisive, isn't it, Your Honor? My witness saw the very moment of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Remember, your first goal is to gather information!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, sir! <thought>Look out contradiction, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're sure it was the victim who won? Absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">It seems our new attorney is a bit confused... A glance at the picture is enough to tell you who won! If you're not in kindergarten.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... Just for safety's sake, could you explain the problem to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course, Your Honor. In this photo I see small chips and I see large chips. Tell me.. which were worth 1,000 points?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Why, the big ones of course! Duh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I thought so too... but then the totals don't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-The totals...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's review what the witness told us: Each man started with 3,500 points in chips. And the combined total value of the chips was 7,000 points.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... if my calculations are correct! Let's see, three plus one, carry the five...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, they are, Your Honor. Now! Look at this photo that allegedly shows all the chips. If the big chips are worth 1,000 points, and the small chips are worth 100... And you add them up...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">How much is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Do it yourself... You aren't in kindergarten, are you?</thought> ...10,600 points. The chips don't add up! This clearly contradicts the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But why!? How could this be!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Exactly... Justice. Now that you know the "what", you must determine the "why".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right... There's only one possible way to explain this contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This calculation makes the answer clear! If the total combined points at the table was 10,600... Then each man started the night with 5,300 points!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Five thousand three hundred... That's a rather half-baked score at which to start a game.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice... Would different starting points really change anything?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the defense's objection was even more half-baked than the score!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh... Time to head back into the kitchen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The odd thing here is the number of chips... Right, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Why are you asking me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Just in case?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice... It's your case I'm concerned about. If you're wondering about the chips, just look at the photograph. It's all there. Even our judge with his failing eyesight could count them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's not the only thing failing the judge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Let me ask you again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Each man began the game with 3,500 points. If all the chips are indeed shown in this photograph... Then there can be only one answer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The value of the chips... was the other way around!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Want to know what I think? The small chips were worth 1,000 points, not the big ones!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Madness! Utter madness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Show me that photograph of the chips again! ...There are six small chips, and ten large chips... Why, that does make 7,000 points when you add them up!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Excellent work, Justice. It's almost as though you figured it out by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... I'm just glad I was the one who said it.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But wait! The value of the chips may be different, but that changes nothing!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed.. The victim did have the larger number of chips still. ... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly. If the small chips are 1,000 points, and the large chips are 100... Let's do a little math. Add up the points for each side of the table!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah... Auuuuuuuuuuuuugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim, Mr. Smith, had 2,900 points, and the defendant had... 4,100 points!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well now... It seems that Mr. Wright was winning that night after all!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's... impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My client had even less reason to kill the victim! After all... he was winning!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yeeeaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now... Ms. Orly. You must have known the true value of the chips. Since you were there at the scene of the crime... weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ah... Eeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! It appears our defendant has lost his "motive". And Mr. Wright's supposed defeat... never happened.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nnn... nunngk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We must now ask ourselves whether we can trust the witness's testimony at--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Excuse me? What is it, Ms. Orly?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">I... I did not want to be saying this, but... Actually, you see, erm...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">See what, Ms. Orly!? What do we see!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">In the last hand, there was cheat!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A ch-cheat? You... You don't mean... ...a trick!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait, or do you mean... ..a scam!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They're all the same thing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">Yes, there was cheat in last hand... That is why game ends with chips as they are!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great... Just great... First we have lying... now cheating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well, this case certainly has taken a turn... ...for the interesting!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! You will please testify to the court! Tell us about this cheating in the final hand!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The last hand... both men had "full house".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly! Why did you not tell the court about this from the very beginning!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I thought I smelled a cover-up here... Well folks, it's time to throw back the covers!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A full house is a very high-scoring hand. Not easy to make, in my experience.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That alone is enough to suspect less-than-scrupulous tactics.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Mr. Gavin? What's a full house?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Lawyers these days... You don't know your poker?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't say this bodes well for your case... or career.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is this, some kind of secret court poker ring!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Justice. You know the terms "one pair", "two pair", and "three of a kind", yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, yeah! No problem! Two cards with the same number makes a pair, and three makes a three of a kind!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Good. Now picture a hand with one pair, and one three of a kind. That's a full house.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... That doesn't sound very easy to make, does it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You can see each player's hand in this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow... They both have full houses!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">We forget, there's an easy way to make a full house... and go undefeated for seven years. You cheat.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If he did cheat in the last hand, that still leaves one important question... Mr. Wright lost that hand. Who's ever heard of a professional con man losing when they cheat!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">The last hand... both men had "full house".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just how hard is it to make a full house, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It is quite hard, dah. It is making a pair and a three of kind at same time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... I guess that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very difficult, to be sure. You can take my word as the "Poker Head of Courtroom No. 3"!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Very difficult, dah. But is not impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK. Full house: Hard. This line of questioning: A waste of time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">There is four of each card in deck, from ace to king.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Four of each card, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah. There is one spade, one diamond, one heart, and one club for each card. It is interesting fact that this number "four" comes from number of seasons!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, you don't say.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, and did you know that the cards are numbered 1-13? Add all the cards in a deck and you get 364... a year!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, you don't say. <thought>Isn't that one day short?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's why each deck has two jokers. They say the second joker stands for the leap year. Thus you have a perfect representation of the year... all in a deck of cards!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, you don't say. <thought>We're going to be in this courtroom for a year if it keeps going like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">If you look at both men's hands, cheat is more obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How was it "clear"?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, well... the defendant... ...he played a fifth ace!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A f-fifth ace!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">I still remember both hands very well. Mr. Smith's hand has three aces... ...and Mr. Wright's two.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Obviously, cheating was afoot! Or perhaps I should say... a hand!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Your Honor... perhaps this can be added to the testimony? Without Mr. Payne's joke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will add this detail to her testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Mr. Smith's hand has three aces, and Mr. Wright's two. ...It is five aces in all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A fifth ace...?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah! It should not exist, no? I still remember both hands very well. Mr. Smith's hand has three aces... ...and Mr. Wright's two.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, where did this card come from then?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...Perhaps we should ask the defendant that very question! Adding cards to a deck is no less serious a taboo than... Than forging evidence in a court of law!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnnk...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Now... Perhaps it's time for you to say something, Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You bet! I've no intention of staying quiet! Not me! No sir! <thought>...I'd better find some contradicting evidence fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Olga">The next moment, game becomes argument, dah! The defendant's trick was exposed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you recall what the men were arguing about?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah, I believe so... The victim, he shouts, "you are cheater!" and then... ...the defendant shouts something like, "I have objection!"</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Shouting objection, eh? Old habits are hard to break! First he bluffed his way through the courtroom, now he bluffs his way through life!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">However! Mr. Wright lost the hand! That seems to cast the shadow of doubt on Mr. Smith!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Humiliation from losing even when cheating... That is what set fire to defendant's heart!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So what did the flaming defendant do next?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">He took bottle in his hand... Poor Mr. Smith!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By bottle, are you referring to... this?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...Dah. The defendant uses this bottle to... to... *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This behavior is an admission of cheating by the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But why use a grape juice bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You'd be surprised at what can be used as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">This juice is recommended drink of Borscht Bowl Club, dah. This year's vintage is remarkable for its hefty flavor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hefty enough to brain a grown man, apparently.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>First she says it was a serious competition, now she says there was cheating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice... Notice anything odd? Her testimony keeps changing. Now she says the defendant cheated.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, yes! I had noticed that!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Let's get the truth about this "cheating" first, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! Leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It appears the witness is mistaken...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Miss... Taken? But my name...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, this piece of evidence clearly contradicts what you said in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's... the photo of the chips, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice. Perhaps you ought to explain your point in a way that the judge can comprehend... In other words, use your finger to "point" out your point!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... Please point out the contradiction in this photo. What particular "point" contradicts the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why, it's here, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's... where?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Where is that you're pointing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where... Uhm... Good question!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We've already heard today on the dangers of bluffing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, sorry, Your Honor. <thought>I'd better rethink this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think you'd best point out your point again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly, in your testimony, you made the following claim: "Mr. Smith's hand has three aces"... But as you can clearly see, the victim's hand only held two aces!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well... Well maybe the witness was simply confused! Perhaps it was the defendant's hand that held the third ace in question...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take another look at the evidence! As you can see, the defendant also had two aces in his hand. Where's this fifth ace? I see cheating alright, and it's going on right here in this courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Two aces in each player's hand does make four aces total. Hardly proof of cheating...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Wait! Please! It is true... I have seen it! The fifth ace! There was cheating, I swear to you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's odd... She must be lying, yet she's the most sincere I've seen her all day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You're right to trust your instincts...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Who knows what lies in store for us in the trial ahead... Your Honor, if I may. I have a suggestion...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What might that be, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">If you don't mind... ...perhaps we might examine the actual cards?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The cards...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk. Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The players' hands that night were set aside as evidence, were they not? The defense would like to request that the cards be shown to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the prosecution will submit this evidence! Which will you examine?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim's cards... or the defendant's cards?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If these cards don't prove cheating was going on, nothing will! Now... which of these hands is more suspicious?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was the victim's hand that "changed" over the course of the witness's testimony...</thought> The defense requests time to examine Mr. Smith's cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Payne, if you would...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well, time's a wasting. Get to it, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">When examining evidence, be sure to view it from all sides and angles. Try using the dials on the evidence viewer. That should give you a better perspective on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK... Let's do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The card backs are red... For some reason I thought that they were using blue cards in that final hand... Didn't you, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Huh? Oh, hmm. Which was it now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, has the defense found anything of relevance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh... I think I found out that I found nothing out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps you'd best examine the defendant's cards... before leaping to any conclusions. Or maybe you'd rather examine these cards one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well? Do I examine the other hand of cards?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I'll examine Mr. Wright's cards.</thought> Your Honor! The defense requests time to examine Mr. Wright's hand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Granted, but make it quick, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't worry, Justice is always swift!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No... According to the testimony, it was the victim's hand that changed. Better take a closer look!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's start with Mr. Wright's hand.</thought> The defense would like to view the defendant's hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Payne! Your evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well now... Let's see what we have here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Right, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">When examining evidence, be sure to view it from all sides and angles. Try using the dials on the evidence viewer. That should give you a better perspective on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK... Let's do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The card backs are red... For some reason I thought that they were using blue cards in that final hand... Didn't you, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Huh? Oh, hmm. Which was it now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, has the defense found anything they would like to share with the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh... Not unless you count utter confusion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps you'd best examine the victim's cards next? Of course, you can always give these cards another look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well? Do I examine the other hand of cards?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I'll examine the victim's cards...</thought> Your Honor! The defense requests time to examine Mr. Smith's hand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Granted, but make it quick, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't worry, Justice is always swift!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe I missed something the first time... Better check them again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh-What...!?</thought> Your Honor! Look at this! One of the victim's cards... The back is a different color!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The card backs are red... For some reason I thought they were using blue-backed cards in the final hand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only one of cards has a blue back... I'm much more of a red guy myself. Blue is so... not red, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Eh...? Ehhhhhh!?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Th-That's impossible! But I put that card in Wright's hand... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...What was that, Ms. Orly?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">No... Ny-Nyet! Er, I merely said, eh... Dah, I have, eek!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Gavin, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Tell me, what is the easiest way to cheat at poker?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To... cheat?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I'll tell you. One merely needs a friend, a "comrade", shall we say... The dealer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, so you mean... This witness... Ms. Orly...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">She's the cheater. A professional, I'd wager.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Nyeeeeeeaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Focus, Justice! Time to take advantage of her! ...I mean, of her mistake!</thought> Your Honor! Please recall the testimony we just heard!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Th-That's impossible! But I put that card in Wright's hand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ergo! Ms. Olga Orly conspired to cheat, not with my client... ...but with the victim, Mr. Shadi Smith!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ooooooogh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not only did she cheat, she cheated poorly! Therefore! It's not hard to imagine an altercation between her and the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait, you don't mean... The defense isn't accusing the witness, Ms. Olga Orly... are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time for Justice! There were three people in the room at the time of the incident. And if Mr. Wright isn't guilty, that means...</thought> ...I am! The defense accuses the witness, Ms. Olga Orly, of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Payne. Where is your witness, Ms. Olga Orly?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Erm, it appears she has lost, eh, consciousness, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems you've presented a new possibility to the court. One suggesting a connection between the witness and the victim, Mr. Smith.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that means...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court cannot pronounce a verdict for the defendant at this time!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nnk...! What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I did it! I held out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see no point in prolonging the trial this day. The prosecution will need to make further inquiries...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You can't end the trial here, Your Honor. Not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What nonsense is the defendant spewing now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think. One of the cards had a different colored back. Don't you wonder what it means?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What are you doing, Mr. Wright!? Raising objections right when you're about to get off the hook!? Ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne, you of all people should know... Mr. Wright has a talent... for the ridiculous! Perhaps we should get to the bottom of things. Let's clear up the facts about the game that fateful night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As was said before... We alternated between two decks of cards that night.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That was said before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The two decks at the club have different colored backs: Blue... and red. One color per deck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why use different colored backs?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we used the same color, the two decks might get mixed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um, you used different colors and they STILL got mixed up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We used the red deck for the last game.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. But... that's odd. For some reason... I have this impression that you were using the blue cards!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, me too... I'm sure someone said something about blue cards...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Whatever. In the end one card of the wrong color got into the mix... Which means there was cheating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, a card slipped into the deck would seem to indicate cheating... Yet... this card raises two serious questions. ...Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's consider the first question, shall we? Think. In the last game... when was the card swapped?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"When"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are three broad possibilities here. It could have been swapped before the murder, during the murder... or after the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, yeah! Thanks for the news bulletin, Mr. Wright! Of course it was swapp--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? It might be as simple as you think, Mr. Payne. Or it might not be.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nnnk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to hear what Apollo thinks first... When do you think the cards were swapped?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>When was the card swapped into the deck?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it must have happened before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean, during the game?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think. When you're playing poker... ...which side of the cards face your opponent?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! The back...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not something the "Poker Head of Courtroom No. 3" would be likely to miss!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, let me think about this some more...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... weren't they swapped during the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"During" the murder? Tell me, exactly when is that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Well, the very moment of the act, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would that be the moment the cards were shown?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Or perhaps the moment when the cheater was revealed?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or maybe the very moment the bottle came down on Mr. Smith's head?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Uh... could I have a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That "moment" could cost you this case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry... Let me rethink this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Perhaps it happened... after the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What's that? Ridiculous! What's the point of cheating after the hands have been shown? That's silly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! But tell me... How do you swap cards during the game!? I'll take "silly" over "impossible".</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Take it from me, son. There's a lot of silly in this world, but very little impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? Even when the backs of the cards are a different color!? If you pulled that during the game, you'd be caught in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite true. That would mean that the blue card in question... ...was swapped after the hands were shown, after the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">OK, this is going past silly and straight on to crazy. I ask again: what's the point of cheating after the game's over!? Who would do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who indeed. That's one of the mysteries before us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-There's another?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. A simple, yet decisive question must be asked: Who swapped the red card for a blue card?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Who?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The game, and murder, is done. The victim is dead. Only two remain in the room. Alive, that is. The defendant, Phoenix Wright, and our witness, Olga Orly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, so who was it that swapped the red card for a blue?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The one who swapped the cards was... Mr. Wright! It was you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why would I do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Uh, well, because, uh... ...maybe you were trying to hide the fact that you'd cheated?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would make sense... but the swapped card was in the victim's hand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry... I'm a nice guy, but I'm not that nice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it, he would lack a motive for helping his opponent to win...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why, it must have been Olga Orly who swapped the cards! She was trying to cover up evidence of the cheating.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That.. does make some sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry... But there's a problem with that explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The swapped card was from the wrong deck.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, a blue card was stuck into a red hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mixing a card from the wrong deck... when the backs are different colors? Remember that you're talking about Olga Orly... She was the dealer. Do you really think she would make such a novice mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Actually, I have trouble imagining even the judge making that mistake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Give it a little more thought, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The one who swapped the cards wasn't Mr. Wright, of course. And, well, it doesn't seem like it could have been Olga Orly, either...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you suggesting!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That's hardly a logical conclusion, I'll admit. As the defense, I think it only makes sense for you to name Ms. Orly at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, yes, I know! But... But she was the one who dealt the cards, right? I... I just can't believe she would make the mistake of swapping the wrong color card!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And if the card was swapped during the game, it'd be obvious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh. Heh heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something you'd like to share with the court, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, my apologies, Your Honor. I was just thinking how much fun all this is.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Fun!? How about confusing!? I've no idea what the defense is claiming, Your Honor. If the one who swapped the card wasn't the defendant, and it wasn't Ms. Orly... Then who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, yeah, well, that is the question, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe we're about to see this case take... a new direction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A new direction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll find that, indeed, after the murder... ...someone swapped one of the cards in the victim's hand. And that someone made two critical mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I'm sure you're going to tell us that the first was swapping the wrong color card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because the one who did the swap didn't know two colors of cards were being used. The other mistake... was the number on the card.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... The person replaced the fifth ace with a king.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure whoever swapped it wasn't expecting there to be a fifth ace, after all. All they knew was that the game had been won with a full house. So they picked up a king from the table, and swapped it in.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But! There's one problem... According to our case record this person doesn't exist!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, not until now. But you have to admit the possibility of a fourth person. Though it's more than a possibility. There was someone else there that night at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I believe the judge spoke truthfully earlier. You do make trials... ridiculous, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial has proceeded on one central assumption: namely, that, at the time of the incident, there were only three people in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe this new evidence, shall we say... overturns that assumption?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The problem is that you chose to conceal this information from the court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I suppose that is a problem, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned for a brief recess! Mr. Gavin, I'll see you in my chambers during this recess.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Certainly, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! The trial will resume in twenty minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That was quite... unexpected, Mr. Wright. To suddenly claim there was another person at the scene of the crime like that... I must ask... is it the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well now... I'd think you would know the answer to that?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, being mysterious, are we? Sadly, I've no time for mysteries. I'd only ask that you leave the defending to your defense, in the future. Otherwise... I cannot guarantee the outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see you haven't mellowed out one bit, Kristoph.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The judge has summoned me to his chambers, so carry on without me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did well, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um.. Can I ask you something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That locket you wear... Is that really yours, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, you're wondering about the victim's disappearing locket? Here, you can take a look at it. That's a picture of my daughter in there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm... just surprised to hear you had a daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Most people are. Perhaps you'll meet her one of these days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One more question.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The one who cheated that night... Was it you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know what happened seven years ago... What I did. It's not unreasonable for you to think I might cheat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I never! Honest! But... <thought>It IS odd that he managed to go undefeated for seven whole years...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Want to know something? There's only one game where you can be dealt bad cards all night and still win. Poker.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You see, poker is all about reading your opponent. In that way, it's a lot like a court case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Poker.. is like trial law!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Figure out what your opponent is thinking, and you win.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, yeah, but that's harder than it sounds.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try as they might to conceal it, everyone reveals their true thoughts in the end. Their body language can become a valuable source of information.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That witness, for instance, Ms. Orly. She would touch the back of her neck during certain parts of her testimony. Did you notice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... No. <thought>C'mon, who'd notice that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Words, habits, twitches... It's all information for the reading. That's the secret to winning, Apollo. Someone taught me, and now, I pass the secret on to you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But, I'm not worthy! I mean, there's no way I'll pick up on these "signals".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. You can do it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just don't know it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's he talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you will. Soon. Ah, almost forgot. One more thing. About this case... You should know, I haven't told the truth to anyone yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaaaaaa--!? <thought>I knew it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have my reasons, of course. All shall be revealed. And Apollo... I need you to be there, defending me. I need your power.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My, um, power? <thought>I had no idea my Chords of Steel were that special...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's time. The real trial begins now. Do your best.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Has our witness, Ms. Olga Orly, recovered?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, Your Honor! Er, well, she's regained consciousness.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps we can hear her version of the events again?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's the thing... You see, she's quite fatigued.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're looking a bit fatigued yourself, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Sadly, fatigue is insufficient grounds for refusing to testify... or prosecute. The defense would like to request that Ms. Orly take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps you could repeat your name and profession?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Or perhaps you'd rather admit that you're a poor liar, and a poorer loser.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ny-Ny-Nye-! ... Not. Name's Olga Orly. That's the truth. I'm a pro dealer. People call me... Olga "Quick-Fingers" Orly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Oh really?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Want to know something else? I'm not really Russian! And my last name sounds like "Oh really"! There, that's the truth! I hope you're satisfied.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Witness! You will tell the court what you were really up to that night!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Fine, I'll talk. We had a plan, see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me remind you that you are currently under oath. Any further fabrications will have serious consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">... Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Like I said, I'm a pro. That guy, Smith, hired me to do what I do best. I was planted at the Borscht Bowl Club several days prior to the night of the game. As a waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you were in cahoots with the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Not that he needed my help. Smith is a well-known poker player in some circles. But winning wasn't the main purpose of this game. It was about destroying a legend: the unbeatable Phoenix Wright! The plan was simple. Elegant, really. You see, we set up a trap of sorts... I was to plant a card in Wright's pocket beforehand... ...and then deal five aces during one of their games. When their hands were revealed, Smith would call him out and search Wright. He would then pull out the planted card and the trap would snap shut!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Exposed as a cheater and losing on top of it! It would have made a great double play. Just like that, the legend would be dashed to pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... Getting caught red-handed at cheating would cast doubt on all his prior wins...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">A seven-year legend, destroyed by one little card... That was the plan!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">"Oh really, Orly"? How droll. But... it appears you made quite the mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I agree, the trap was elegant. Yet, what happened to that planted card?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">He's lucky, I'll give him that. You'd have to be to slip free from a trap laid by Olga "Quick-Fingers" Orly!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh really? The witness would be much cuter if she dispensed with the evil mastermind shtick.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Cute...? Who wants to be cute? I'm not cute! I'm bad! You hear me? Bad!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When you're through being bad, perhaps you could testify to the court? Tell us about this "trap"... and how it was sprung.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That night, I planted the card like I was supposed to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A surprisingly frank testimony that still leaves us mostly in the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The trap was perfect I tell you, perfect! If that rotten cheater hadn't messed it up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look who's talking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, the testimony, for what it's worth, is all yours, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With witnesses like her, who needs criminals? ...And with defendants like Mr. Wright, who needs prosecutors?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">That night, I planted the card like I was supposed to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This planted card... which card was it, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The trump card... the Five of Hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me guess. Mr. Wright was to have switched the Five with the Ace to make a full house. At least, that's what you were going to accuse him of doing, thereby ruining his legend.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">I slid it into Wright's pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When was this...?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Why, before the match, of course. While he was eating. At the Borscht Bowl Club, we serve borscht... and suckers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Remind me never to go there.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Of course, the card was to make its grand debut during the game... Like a good borscht, a good plot must be cooked up early and allowed to thicken.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">And Wright lost the last hand, just like he was supposed to. Then Smith searched him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, everything went according to plan...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Exactly. The fifth ace came up, so it's obvious the switch went off without a hitch. Once the extra card was found in his pocket... ...Wright would be forever known as a cheat and a fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are worse things to be known as I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell us what happened with the search.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">But the planted card was gone! The trap failed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The card... disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Yeah! My trump card, the Five of Hearts! Gone! Without a trace! Poof! Zippo! We searched every nook and cranny... Even inside his cute little hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the card was nowhere to be found, is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Never in my long, storied career... Never has "Quick-Fingers" Orly been so readily duped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh really. So, what did happen to that Five of Hearts?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Don't look at me. Why don't you ask that cheating, lying, two-faced defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the Five of Hearts is still missing in action...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">The next moment, Wright picked up a bottle and swung it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... Isn't that a little odd?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Wh-What's odd!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You searched Mr. Wright, er, thoroughly, and found nothing? Which means he didn't cheat... Which means he had no reason to strike the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh-What was that just now!? I... sensed something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something wrong, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... nothing, Your Honor. <thought>What to do? Should I press her a little harder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly...! You're hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Wh-What are you talking about!? Y-Y-You! M-M-M-Me? "Quick-Fingers" Orly, hi-hi-hide something?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defense will refrain from baseless accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have one question for the witness then. You say you saw the moment the defendant hit the victim. ...Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">O-Of course it's true! I d-did see it, honest! I saw it when Wright hit him. </line>
<line speaker="Olga">With my own eyes, I saw it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's this weird vibe I'm getting!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That witness, for instance, Ms. Orly. She would touch the back of her neck during certain parts of her testimony. Did you notice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Touching her neck, was it? Whoa! What's going on? This sensation... It's coming into focus! There! That twitch! It's so clear! It's like I could perceive her habit like I couldn't before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly... Perhaps you are unaware of this yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Un-Unaware of what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whenever you get to a certain part of your testimony... ...you touch the back of your neck with your left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...! My... My neck? So... So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What indeed, Justice? I hadn't noticed anything of the sort...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When she says that part of the testimony... She's subconsciously recalling something... Her body reacts to the memory, and she touches her neck! I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A memory? Would someone care to explain what he's babbling about?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is highly unusual... but let's ask the defense. You claim the witness is remembering something. Maybe you have evidence of this "memory" to show us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her habit is scratching her neck whenever she talks about the moment of the crime... So, what would remind her most of the moment of the crime!?</thought> Ms. Orly. Whenever you recall the crime that night, you scratch your neck. I've noticed it happens when you think about the moment of the crime. There must be some reason behind this "habit" of yours. I believe the weapon that left an inerasable "impression" on your neck is this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Olga">... Sorry to disappoint, but I don't have any particular memories of that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh... That must not have been it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmph! Of course not! You want a habit, Mr. Justice? I'll show you a habit!!! Ah ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better get this sorted out before I develop a habit of my own...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whenever she talks about the moment of the crime, she touches her neck... And what reminds us more of that moment than this bottle, the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... something doesn't fit. If you were only the witness to the crime... ...why would that make you touch your neck like you're in pain?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What's he talking about now!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was Mr. Smith, the victim who was hit... not you!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Uh... Uhmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is a cross-examination, not a cross-wild-conjecture! Th-The witness's... "habits"!? They're completely irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice... I'll admit, I'm a bit confused myself. This is certainly a... unique cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll explain later! Just, trust me. Now's our only chance to break her! Ms. Orly! Please testify, in detail, about the moment of the crime. The very moment!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ny-Nyet. I am knowing nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Um, we know you're not Russian.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will testify, please. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Bah. Fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nah... I'm just seeing things.</thought> Sorry, it's nothing. Please continue the testimony. <thought>What was that? A dizzy spell? I gotta relax...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're hiding something, and that habit of yours proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Hah! Ludicrous! I'm not h-hiding anything!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You touched your neck again.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's no use trying to hide it. I can see right through you.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">It wasn't me who hit Smith! It was that no-good, cheating defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let me ask, how's your eyesight?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Just who do you think you're talking to? They don't call me "Quick-Fingers" for nothing. I'm a pro. Which means my dealing's pro, and my eyesight... is pro!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Honestly, she'd have to be blind as a bat to miss something in that small room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, but Mr. Wright didn't have a motive to hit the victim! Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">He's the one who did it! I didn't let him out of my sight until the cops got there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You seem... uneasy.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">You try sitting up here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her eyes are darting all over the place... I must be getting warm!</thought> Tell me... After the crime, what was the defendant like?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Uh. Well... He must have been stunned by the weight of his crime! He sat in a daze at that table ...until the cops came.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Intriguing... I believe you've gotten all the testimony you're going to get out of this witness. So, what do you think about her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll tell you what I think! Her testimony is..</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...pretty good, really. I'd be upset too at the scene of a crime like that. Yeah, I can picture my mind going blank, staring listlessly...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes, I am picturing you doing that right now. As for our defendant, he is an experienced trial lawyer... He's seen a lot in his day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...is basically bogus. It contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What's that!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... Show us this evidence, Mr. Justice! This evidence that you claim contradicts the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She didn't let him out of her sight until the cops got there... I know there's some evidence that contradicts that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This, Your Honor, is the evidence that contradicts her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Tsk. Who would have thought that Justice could be so wrong! He's the guilty one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Gah! Me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Justice. You might want to think about your future before doing that again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch. That one hurt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Different personality... but the same testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I believe you have her where you want her, Justice. The circumstances have changed yet her testimony has not. That means...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's got to be a contradiction in there!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Quite.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Orly! We have a record here that clearly contradicts what you said! It states that the police were alerted by a report from the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And we know that the defendant left the room, climbed the stairs... ...and made that phone call from the first floor of the Borscht Bowl Club!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, explain how you kept your eyes on the defendant... ...when he left the room entirely!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Eeeeeeeeek! ...The man who picked up a bottle and swung it that night... wasn't the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Just then, Smith grabbed the bottle from next to Wright... ...and he hit me!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">When I came to...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim was already dead... Is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That's why I couldn't reveal who I really was. If it came out that I was in league with Smith, I'd be a suspect for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well. Where does this leave us?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">M-Madness. Th-This is madness! I'm dreaming! It must have been me who was hit with a bottle and I'm imagining all of this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears our prosecution is at his wit's end, and frankly, I can't blame him. Mr. Gavin, what do you think about this turn of events?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mr. Gavin? Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I believe that, as the defense in this case... ...we are compelled to call Ms. Orly a "big, fat liar".</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Wh-Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Three were in that room the night of the murder: the defendant, victim, and her. ...And she has a motive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A motive?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Her plot foiled, the witness got into an argument with her client, Mr. Smith. And the denouement of that argument... was murder!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">What!? I didn't... I'm no killer! It's a trap! Someone's trying to frame me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh heh heh... What tangled webs we weave when we practice to deceive. So tangled, we catch ourselves in the process.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Such a hasty conclusion... It's not like you, Kristoph Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What are you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not consider the other possibility? ...That there was another person in the room at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right, like Mr. Wright was saying before recess!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A single card was swapped into the victim's hand after the murder. And the one who swapped the card didn't know two colors of cards were being used. ...A fourth person.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hah, this theory again! Your "fourth person" doesn't exist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed. That's why I decided to bring this case to court. Here, where there's no escape, and no chance for deception... The perfect place to catch the real criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The r-real criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, we're in luck. A clue to the real criminal's identity was kindly provided for us. And right at the beginning of the trial, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo... perhaps you know what I'm talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember what I said. The fourth person who swapped the cards made one critical error.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He or she wasn't considering the color on the backs of the cards...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. But how could such an obvious mistake occur? The cards used for the last game were red. Yet, there is one person, here, in our court... ...who thought those cards were blue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, I had that impression, too... But why?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Apollo? Think you can figure out who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I-It's not me, I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this fourth person!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why do I always get put on the spot like this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's hear what the defense has to say. Who was it? Who thought the cards used in the final game were blue?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... As I expected. Your eyes and ears are as sharp as your hair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I was right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Apollo, do you seriously think that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think I'm seriously confused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I'm seriously sorry. <thought>*gulp* That didn't go well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it can't be helped. I almost missed it myself... But it doesn't do anyone any good to turn their eyes away from the truth. Does it... Kristoph?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eh? Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Kristoph Gavin. You were the fourth person that night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But of course Mr. Gavin knows the color of the cards!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...How would he? As you can see, the photo of the crime scene is black and white. You can't tell which of the cards are blue: the ones on the floor, or the table.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But look! You can see the colors in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but when he said the cards were "blue"... ...it was well before this evidence came to light!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It is true that the defendant was engaged in a game of poker with the victim. Yet it was only that: a game, in the purest sense. A competition, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A... competition?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes, a test of wits, a silent clash of passions... Only the cards, their backs wreathed in blue flame, know its final outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Kristoph?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr.... Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin! I-Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Hmm? N-No, nothing. Excuse me, it was just so... sudden. Wright. You aren't seriously accusing me... are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Kristoph? You know even I'd never take a joke this far.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This has gone beyond ridiculous, beyond dumb... This is insanity! The defendant accusing his own defense attorney of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I assure you, I'm quite sane.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But what possible connection could Mr. Gavin have to the victim!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wasn't aware that I had a connection to Mr. Smith, either.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, but Mr. Gavin and the victim have never even met!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... What if they have?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a possibility, after all. They may have met that night, before the game started.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you suggesting!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is this the truth Mr. Wright was staying silent about!? Well, only one thing to do!</thought> Mr. Wright! The defense would like to request that you testify to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The defense would like to request no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Testimonies must relate to the case. How could anything happening before that game of poker be related?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure I follow, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As I explained before, the defense believes that Ms. Orly...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Am I to assume you speak for Mr. Justice in this? He is the defense, not you.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. The matter of Mr. Wright's testimony is up to you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... OK. *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the court, in your opinion, need to hear Mr. Wright's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This was Mr. Wright's strategy! He was planning this all along! And I intend to see it through.</thought> ...The defense would like to request that Mr. Wright testify to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Et tu, Justice? You would betray me, your teacher?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, Mr. Gavin. This isn't about loyalty... This is about the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defendant... Mr. Wright will take the stand, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>As much as I'd like it to, I guess the testimony isn't related to the case, per se.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You heard what the judge said, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's your decision. Yours.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice! You aren't seriously considering...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, Mr. Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But now that we've gone this far, we might as well go all the way!</thought> The defense would like to request that Mr. Wright testify to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defendant, er, Mr. Wright will take the stand, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That evening, Kristoph and I had dinner. We sat at the table in the photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin! You were at the Borscht Bowl Club the night of the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dine with him rather frequently.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A-And he talked to the defendant on the phone directly after the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite against my will, I had become involved in a murder. I thought I might be in need of a lawyer, so I called him.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You were planning this all along, weren't you, Wright? Just because you wanted to drag me into your little murder trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only thing I want... is the truth. As I did back then... and now.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I thought my office was doing you a favor when we took on your defense. It appears that I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The defense may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">He's lying, and you're going to expose him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Understood, sir. <thought>Mr. Gavin vs. Mr. Wright... This can't end well. Why can't I have a normal trial!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That evening, Kristoph and I had dinner. We sat at the table in the photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You had dinner with Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, he dines with me at the Borscht Bowl Club quite frequently. We were enjoying a usual dinner at our usual spot... as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Usual"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I always eat at the table closest to the piano.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Where Mr. Smith was sitting!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">So, the plates and such on the table were from your dinner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Indeed. The remnants of my meal with Kristoph. We dined for two hours, then Kristoph left. After that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shadi Smith walked in five minutes after Kristoph left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Five minutes? So, the two of them could have passed in the restaurant during that time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would have been a "fateful encounter" to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee hee hee... Oh, Mr. Wright... What was it you said? Kristoph Gavin and Shadi Smith "may have met"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe I did say that.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Here I was all nervous about this "meeting"...And now we hear they just passed in the hall?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does seem a little weak as a pretense for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh it would be. If that was all that really happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, Mr. Wright... What are you hiding this time!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When the "trap" failed, Smith hit the waitress.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About this failed "trap"... This is the same "trap" that Ms. Olga Orly mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">The plan was simple. Elegant, really. You see, we set up a trap of sorts... I was to plant a card in Wright's pocket beforehand... ...and then deal five aces during one of their games. When their hands were revealed, Smith would call him out and search Wright. He would then pull out the planted card and the trap would snap shut!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Just like that, the legend would be dashed to pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... A harmless prank, in essence. It was by a quirk of fate that I happened to discover it...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A "quirk"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I happened to put a hand in my pocket... and found a card.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The card she planted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I snuck a peek at it and found it was the Five of Hearts. I had a feeling something might happen so I disposed of the card... before the game.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Disposed... Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was an empty bottle of grape juice I had been drinking right beside me. I threw the card inside the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">An empty bottle of grape juice...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder weapon!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I rolled it up and shoved it in. The colored glass makes it hard to see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A battle of wits between the deceiver and the would-be deceived! That sounds like terrific drama...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A card inside the murder weapon? That's strange... Did the police miss it in their investigation? Maybe I'll take a look...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! The "Poker Head of Courtroom No. 3" approves of this battle of wits! Please revise your testimony with this new information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I discovered the "trap" during the game, and disposed of the card in the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why in the bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I perceived my opponent's intent immediately. I'm used to entrapment, you see. I knew what was coming.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hoh hoh... So you struck first! I like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know every trick in the book. They don't work on me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>At least, when you get lucky and stick your hand in your pocket they don't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Mr. Wright, if I may?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've examined the bottle, and I don't see any card in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? No? ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What, Mr. Wright? Surely "..." isn't all you have to say for yourself!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say that I know what happened to the card. I did put it in that bottle, however.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps a fifth person came and took it out? Oh, and a sixth person could've helped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin... Mr. Wright is your client!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...My apologies, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I won't have you disparaging our investigation, either! We looked inside that bottle. There was nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...So what's going on? Is Mr. Wright hoodwinking us again? Or did the card just... disappear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, please continue the cross-examination. I'm afraid decisive contradictions call for decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Push him harder, Justice. Break him! It's just you and the witness in the ring. Go for the KO!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. Why do I get the feeling we're not on our client's side anymore?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Mr. Wright, if I may?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've examined the bottle, and I don't see any card in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? No? ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What, Mr. Wright? Surely "..." isn't all you have to say for yourself!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say that I know what happened to the card. I did put it in that bottle, however.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Perhaps a fifth person came and took it out? Oh, and a sixth person could've helped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin... Mr. Wright is your client!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...My apologies, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I won't have you disparaging our investigation, either! We looked inside that bottle. There was nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...So what's going on? Is Mr. Wright hoodwinking us again? Or did the card just... disappear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The girl was knocked out cold, and Smith was uncontrollable. I left to call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You made the call to the police from the first floor of the restaurant, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. Cell phones don't get a signal down in the Hydeout.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was anyone else on the first floor at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a soul. It was the middle of the night, after all. So there, in the darkened restaurant, I called the cops. After making the call, I returned to the Hydeout. It didn't seem right to leave the injured waitress alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I returned, he was dead, blood streaming from a cut on his forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And when you returned, the victim was already...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dead, yes. I'll admit, I was a little startled when I walked in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... "little"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was bleeding from his forehead, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess I'd be startled, too, if I walked in on a scene like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at this photograph of the crime scene. See the victim here? He's wearing a hat. ...I wouldn't think you could see blood on his forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Good point.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice! Next time you point out an inconsistency, put a little more "oomph" into it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Can you explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... I forgot to mention something. I was the one who put that hat on his head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You put the hat on the dead man's head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wore it through our entire poker game. After calling the police, when I returned to the scene, his head was in full view. Shining bright... Just like in this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I picked his hat up off the floor and put it on his head.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Wh-Why'd you do a thing like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I can say is... I'm sorry. But that's the only thing I touched at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... Ms. Orly didn't see it? "It" being the victim's... er, his head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd think not. She was out cold. I believe I was the only one who witnessed his head.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, here we go again...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ahem. Pardon. It just seems that our client is determined to lie his way through this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>H-Hey, he's still our client! ...Isn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, please continue the cross-examination. I'm afraid decisive contradictions call for decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Push him harder, Justice. Break him! It's just you and the witness in the ring. Go for the KO!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. Why do I get the feeling we're not on our client's side anymore?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at this photograph of the crime scene. See the victim here? He's wearing a hat. ...I wouldn't think you could see blood on his forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Good point.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice! Next time you point out an inconsistency, put a little more "oomph" into it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Can you explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... I forgot to mention something. I was the one who put that hat on his head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You put the hat on the dead man's head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wore it through our entire poker game. After calling the police, when I returned to the scene, his head was in full view. Shining bright... Just like in this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I picked his hat up off the floor and put it on his head.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Wh-Why'd you do a thing like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I can say is... I'm sorry. But that's the only thing I touched at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... Ms. Orly didn't see it? "It" being the victim's... er, his head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd think not. She was out cold. I believe I was the only one who witnessed his head.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, here we go again...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ahem. Pardon. It just seems that our client is determined to lie his way through this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>H-Hey, he's still our client! ...Isn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's when I made another phone call... To Defense Attorney Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you explain why you called Mr. Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd obviously gotten involved in a rather... sticky affair. And I figured Kristoph's law offices would give me a friend rate for my defense fees...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, glad to hear you intend to pay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'll pay in full, Kristoph. It was I who got you involved, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...You may find the price of your defense quite high, my good friend. Quite high.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is this the "truth" that Mr. Wright was talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice, you know what you have to do.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">He's lying. Expose him. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir... <thought>I have to think! What's Mr. Wright trying to tell me with this testimony? The truth has to be in there somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I believe that's enough of that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">This witness's "testimony" is more like a "travesty". It's riddled with lies. I'm beginning to see how you came to lose your attorney's badge seven years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well. You certainly have a unique way of treating your clients, Kristoph. I never knew.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I believe it was you who threw the first stone...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright! If you intend to ever tell the truth about this case... It's now or never!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be misled... I haven't told a single lie here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I noticed the "trap"... I put the card in the bottle to dispose of it. And when I put the hat on the victim's head... Let's just say I had a reason for doing that as well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... reason?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That reason... is right here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your... cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That night... Recall that I spoke with Defense Attorney Gavin after calling the police. Just in case, I recorded our conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that we're all here, I see no reason why I shouldn't play it back for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Kristoph. I seem to be in a bit of trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What's this? Game not going well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That gentleman who challenged you... He turn out to be good?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He turned out to be dead. Someone hit him. Hard.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You mean someone cracked that flawless bone china pate? It... wasn't you, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me? Please. The cops should be here any minute. I'm in your hands... Should it come to that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Bone china plate"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A kind of porcelain, very smooth and shiny. And not "plate", but "pate". I believe he was referring to a certain gentleman's balding forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The court appreciates the defendant's discretion in not indicating my forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait a second... Something's not right about that phone call!</thought> So, after Mr. Gavin ate dinner with you... ...he left the Borscht Bowl Club?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Most certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then... Then how did he know? When did he see this "bone china pate"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... That was when I began to see my good friend in a different light.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Troubled, I returned to the crime scene. And when I spotted Mr. Smith's head again, I realized exactly what was wrong. Well, Mr. Gavin. The stage has been set. Perhaps you would like to explain this to the court? Exactly how did you come by your privileged knowledge of the victim's head?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">... So, this is your "reason". The reason why you put the victim's hat back on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your point, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...It's come down to this, has it... Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! I will have order!!! Mr. Payne!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this court has been left with no other choice... Are you prepared to hear Defense Attorney Gavin's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Eh? Ah... Urk? Ahem! Well, as the prosecutor, I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well! We'll break for ten minutes. After which Mr. Gavin will take the stand for a cross-examination! ...Are we all clear on that?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Crystal clear, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! This will be the final recess for the day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Gavin and Mr. Wright are both in the judge's chamber! Who'd have thought today would turn out like this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...May I?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello, sir. Please, pick a card.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh-What's all this about?</thought> Uh... Is this one OK?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Excellent. I have a message for you. "The last hand is about to be played. You'll need a trump card to make it."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A trump card...?</line>
<line speaker="???">"The card you have chosen is magical. Use it wisely, and the game is yours." That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>An ace... Where do I remember that card from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Olga">Mr. Smith's hand has three aces, and Mr. Wright's two.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...It is five aces in all. It is true... I have seen it! The fifth ace! There was cheating, I swear to you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The missing fifth ace! Wait... This blotch of red... Is this blood?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You have your trump card. Now it's up to you to cut the deck and draw... the truth. My father's fate is in your hands. I know you can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This blood-stained card... is my trump card for finding the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I fell deep into thought as my mind raced to understand what this all meant. That girl... I'd seen her recently... But where? That's when I made the connection...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Defense Attorney Kristoph Gavin, will you please take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A single drop of blood marks the front of the card.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, if you would, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Y-Yes, Your Honor! Erm, will Mr.... er, the witness state his name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Is this farce necessary, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Believe me, far stranger things have gone on in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Fine, I'll play along.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">First, there's one thing we need to have made clear. How did you know about the "secret" beneath the victim's hat?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>By "secret", I'm guessing he means the fact that Mr. Smith was bald.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Forgive my curiosity, but what is it about this fellow's head? Your Honor seems to have an inordinate interest in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't call it inordinate, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What do you think you're doing, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, things sure look different from the other side. You know what I mean, Apollo? Speaking of "looking from the other side", let's consider something for a second. The victim wore that hat all night, never once taking it off, except for that one time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That one time... being the instant he was hit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When Mr. Wright returned from reporting the crime, the hat was lying on the floor. Mr. Wright picked it up, and placed it on the victim's head... In other words, in order to have seen Mr. Smith's bald head... ...you would have had to be at the scene of the crime... at the time of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">In other words, you'd have to be the real killer... is what you're trying to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Not bad, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Eh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I'm afraid that I haven't been entirely honest with the court.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Oh, I assure you, I had the noblest of intentions. I did it all... to protect my client, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yet, I'm afraid in the current situation I see little reason to hide anything. ...Very well. Allow me to tell you the truth of what happened that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Finally! You may begin your testimony. Tell us... How were you involved in the events of that fateful night?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The rage I sensed in that man that night troubled me... So I returned to the club.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">So... you witnessed the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">For better or worse, I missed the actual moment of the deed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin, may I remind you that you are on Mr. Wright's defense team... Your testimony is clearly disadvantageous to your client!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What else could I say? I'm standing on the witness stand, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So you are, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you had to testify as you just did... You had to tell them you saw the scene of the crime through that little window...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had to say that... ...because that was the only probable window of opportunity. Right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, the defense should do the cross-examination, not the defendant! Mr. Justice, are you prepared?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor... <thought>I can't believe I'm going up against Mr. Gavin... This trial is getting weirder and weirder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The rage I sensed in that man that night troubled me... So I returned to the club.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"That man"... You mean Mr. Smith?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">He was different from the other customers... His aura, shall we say. I knew he was a serious poker player... but it was more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">So then, you knew the true nature of your client's job!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Of course. But I also knew he wasn't engaged in gambling, which would be illegal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, it makes sense that he'd know. They were friends, after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Worried for my friend, I returned to the club. You see, I feared this Mr. Smith might be someone coming to settle an old score.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. What happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I went down to the basement and peeked in through the little window to the Hydeout.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The little window... You mean the one used to keep watch up the stairs?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes, a relic of the ancient past. The black marketeers used it, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why did you go through the trouble of peeking in through the window? Wouldn't it have been easier to just open the door and go into the room?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">... I didn't want to upset Wright, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Upset Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes. What if my fears had been unfounded? I'd be walking in on their match! Bad form, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... So far, everything he's saying makes sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It must have been right after the murder took place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How do you know it was "right after" the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Really, no need to shout, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I was just getting to that part in my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, there he is! The "Coolest Defense in the West" we know and love. Even when you're standing up there on the witness stand... Some things never change.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I was afraid you'd changed, too, Wright, but you haven't. You and that overbearing personality of yours...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With friends like these, who needs enemies...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The victim was dead, as he appears in the photo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "photo" you mean the second photograph of the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Precisely. You see, he wasn't wearing his hat then. I saw his head... when he was dead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And then Mr. Wright came along and replaced his hat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Can you describe the scene of the crime for us?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">A bald head, an unconscious girl... and Wright, holding a bottle in his hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those were the only three at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Yes... As far as I saw, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...Then we're back where we started. The killer was the defendant, Phoenix Wright! Who else could it have been? But... why didn't you talk to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Two reasons. First, I didn't actually witness the very moment of the crime... Second... My office was asked to defend Wright. Even after seeing what I had seen... I couldn't abandon my friend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There must have been someone else there at the moment of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Justice... I just said I saw no one. Not a soul.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But, that goes against what Mr. Wright said!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah yes, this mysterious "fourth person"... ...who would conveniently be the "real killer", I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glad to see we agree, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Let me pose a question, then. Tell me. What possible reason did the "real killer" have to swap cards in the victim's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Hmm? Perhaps you can show us a reason why such a thing would be necessary?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How can I show something I can't find myself!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember, Apollo. The card that was swapped out was the fifth ace...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The fifth ace... right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? The question of why the killer would swap out a card has been raised. Can you point to a reason?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...It's now or never!</thought> The defense would like to present evidence to the  court... Evidence showing the reason why a card was swapped out!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then go ahead and point out your reason, Mr. Justice. Why did the killer take the fifth ace!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The reason is made clear by... this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm not sure how that piece of evidence makes anything clear, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I see now it was wrong of me to field you in a trial so soon, Justice. Wild bluffing, and even wilder accusations... You're almost as bad as another defense attorney I know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh, I'm sure my office's reputation will recover, given time. Once you learn you can't bluff your way through life. Or court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Unnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you... like to continue, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor! <thought>I sure can't let my first trial end like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No. Not yet, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Not yet"!? Hah! Pathetic! Not yet? Try not ever!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh, I'm willing to wait for as long as it takes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great! I don't even know what the heck I'm looking for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't forget... You already know the answer. You just don't realize it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... already know the answer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a moment to think it over again... OK?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I sensed that was not the best place for me to be at the time and so I left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wouldn't it have been better to wait for the police to arrive?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Remember though. By that time, I was already Wright's defense attorney. It wouldn't do for me to become part of the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That makes sense... or does it? ...I'm confused.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That's when the call came from Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where were you when the phone call came?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I had already left the Borscht Bowl Club by that time. On the phone he asked me to defend him. Naturally, I was surprised. I accepted, however. I couldn't abandon him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So kind of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... So far, everything jives with Mr. Wright's testimony... I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it going to be a problem for you to cross-examine your own boss?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I'm fine! <thought>Who was it that taught me never to pull punches in cross-examination? It was you, Mr. Gavin! I learned it from watching you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My reason is... uh... This!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Is that an... ace?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why... Why, it's got blood on it! Right next to the spade!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wh-Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This is insane! Why wasn't I told about this!? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Could... this be...!? Could this be the missing fifth ace!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">In-Inconceivable! How could you... What are you doing with that card!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well, that's the thing... <thought>Why's Mr. Gavin so upset? It's just a fishy card from some fishy girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that card? It's mine. That is, I picked it up at the Borscht Bowl Club that night after the murder had occurred. I gave it to my daughter. Cards are her stock and trade, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">N... No! Impossible! Unacceptable! The court can't accept this evidence! It's a fraud!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fraud? How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would think the only person who could claim it was a fraud... ...would be the one who took the real card from the crime scene... The real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Allow me to elaborate. What if this trace of blood was the reason?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The reason for...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For the killer to take the card from the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where are you going with this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take another look at the photo... and at the victim's head. At the moment of the crime, his hat fell to the floor... ...and a trickle of blood ran from his forehead down the back of his head. Couldn't a drop of that blood have fallen on one of the cards?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The killer then took the card to hide the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">R-Regardless! That evidence is non-permissible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wright! Regardless of how you wasted the last seven years, you used to be a lawyer! You know what a serious crime it is to conceal evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, we can discuss the finer points of our legal system later... What's important now is that I've answered your question.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wanted to know why the killer would have taken a card from the crime scene. And now, I've told you. That one drop of blood would have been decisive evidence, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Th-This is... baseless conjecture! Baseless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I assure you it's quite based.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's amazing, really. How a single drop of blood on a single card can lead us... to the truth. It's quite simple. Well, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try picturing the scene of the crime in your head. The murder took place in the Hydeout... The body of the luckless victim was found at the poker table. And, before the killer swapped a card out... ...there was a single card with a drop of blood on it in the victim's hand. Given this... ...there is one, decisive problem with this scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, what is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's keep it simple, shall we? Given that there was a drop of blood on a card... ...whose position in this diagram doesn't fit? The victim's? The killer's? The witness's? The second witness's? Whose position doesn't fit with the bloody card?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, for one thing, the killer's in the wrong place. I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You "think"...? Mr. Justice, your job here is not to think, but to know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, just looking at you reminds me of the old days. Not the good old days, per se.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How does a good old penalty sound? Let's try that one more time. And, Mr. Justice, think before you sink.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness's location is clearly at odds with... something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By witness, you mean Ms. Olga Orly, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. When it comes to cards, it's "Quick-Fingers" Orly or no one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see. And...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Uh, was I supposed to say something else?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... A meaningful observation would help your case considerably.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet, do you not sense a great feeling of "potential" in his silence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Potential for a whopping penalty, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Please, give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* Very well. Give it some thought, this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The second witness's position is the problem!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The second witness... That would be Mr. Gavin, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The second witness's position is far less problematic than yours right now, Justice. Or perhaps "perilous" is a better word.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uggh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I cannot see what the blood-stained card has to do with the second witness's location. I'm afraid you're more than in peril of a penalty this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! One more chance! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose. Do think it over, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The problem with this picture is... here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, what exactly is  supposed to be "here"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Er, ack! My h-hand must have slipped. Sweaty, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oops! I just gave you a penalty. Hand must've slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Please tell me this farce has a time limit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It will soon if the defense cannot come up with something of substance. So, please wipe the cold sweat from your hands, and show us again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor! <thought>I'm going to need a beach towel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, isn't it the victim's position that's the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't follow your logic here, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... Look, the victim was struck on the head, sending him back in his chair. You'd think any blood would fall behind the body, not onto the table in front of him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at the photo again. If he bled in this position... The blood would fall on the floor, not on the cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, that's right! So... what does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Incidentally, we were sitting in swivel chairs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Swivel chairs!? Oh man...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, try turning the chair around.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The chair was facing the other way!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would have to be. So, we have to assume that at the time of the murder... ...the victim's chair was facing away from the table!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When Mr. Wright returned from informing the police, which way was the chair facing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I came back to the room, the body was facing as seen in this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would mean... the killer turned the chair back around.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take the next step. Look at the diagram once more. We know now the victim was facing away from the table at the time of the murder. But... this creates another significant contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A-Again!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's test your reasoning skills again, shall we? Apollo, whose location on this diagram contradicts our new understanding of the crime? The victim's? The killer's? The witness's? The second witness's? Whose location creates a contradiction if the victim was facing away?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the contradicting position here is the victim's!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Again? How many contradictions can one man have!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Though you're certainly giving him a run for his money.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh, I missed again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will refrain from contradicting itself out of a case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, give him another chance, Your Honor. As you can see... ...he quite clearly regrets his mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm not sure I see that, but, very well. One more time, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The contradicting point is the location of the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Exactly what does the witness's location contradict?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That is unclear, even to me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Generally, one does not announce one's own ignorance with such... aplomb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I have to take pride in something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you would be kind enough to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What doesn't make sense... is the second witness!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You mean to say I don't make sense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh! Um, no, of course you do, er, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Help...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, I'm a little hard of hearing... Did you just say something? Would you be kind enough to show the court one more time what you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The problem with this picture is... Here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, what exactly is supposed to be "here"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Ack! Darn sweaty hands! My finger must've slipped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hope you didn't do that on purpose... For your sake. This court does not look favorably upon those who waste the court's time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Eek!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, Apollo. One more time, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim was struck from the front, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, wouldn't it be hard for the killer to hit him from the front? Sitting where his indicator currently is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would think it'd be quite hard, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, but what you're saying makes no sense! Why would the victim suddenly turn to face the wall... in the middle of a game!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe a sufficient reason will soon come to light.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something in this diagram that makes far less sense, actually. Look again at the diagram. Apollo, if the victim was struck while he was sitting as shown here... ...where would his assailant be standing? Try marking it on the diagram.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--!? B-But...! <thought>There's no room to put a mark where the killer should be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry... Let's think it through and see what we find. We know the victim was facing toward the wall at the time of the crime. That's the only thing we know for sure. Try to forget about everything else... Where would the killer have to be standing to strike our victim from the front?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess the killer would have to be, uh... Here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anything to say, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Um... Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A little late for that, I'm  afraid. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, give me a little hint!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Try not to overthink things, Apollo. What does your instinct tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The killer had to be standing, well... uh... Here!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">You get points for flair, but that's about all you get.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack... <thought>I thought I was on to something there, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I hardly need to point out that standing there would be impossible. The victim is facing a solid cupboard! Or are you claiming the killer climbed the cupboard and hit him from above? Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple logic, really... If this was the only place the killer could have been standing... ...then that means that, at the very moment of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! I know! At the moment of the crime, the cupboard... wasn't there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I mean, that's the only explanation! Right, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I have a suggestion for the defense. We should arrange to examine the cupboard in the Hydeout immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Send a team to the crime scene immediately! Have them try to move the cupboard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one more thing your men should look for. Please give this to the bailiff.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...? Mmm, yes... I see. You do belong in the courtroom after all, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do my best. But let's forge ahead here while we wait. Look at the diagram once again. It's been changed. If the killer was standing here at the time of the crime... ...then this cupboard wasn't here. Which means... Apollo, try moving the cupboard. Thank you. As you can see, the cupboard was the problem. At the time of the murder, it has to have been as shown here. Now everything is in place to reconstruct the moment of the crime... Oh, my! What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the diagram of the crime scene once more. It appears we've found yet another contradiction... What I believe to be the final contradiction, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? Oh dang!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Notice something, Apollo? Our line of deduction is rapidly approaching its logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Mr. Justice, please point to the new contradicting indicator! Is it the victim? The killer? The witness? The second witness? Which indicator in this diagram contradicts what we know about the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The indicator in question is... the victim's!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... see no particular problem with the victim's location.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, good. That's good to know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it's not! Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once more, if you would. Correctly, this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The indicator that doesn't make sense here is the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh really!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah really! Well, maybe really...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would behoove the defense to be really sure before wasting our valuable time! Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe if I just came clean and admitted that I'm totally lost he'd go easy on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! The court will have your answer one more time! And for the love of all that is right and good, please think before you point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What doesn't make sense is the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Olga Orly? Wasn't she unconscious at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Erm, yes, I suppose she was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I fail to see how an unconscious witness could contradict anything. Yet this conscious judge can penalize you, and he just did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! One more chance, please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose. Do give it some thought this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This indicator has to be wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which indicator is that? I'm not sure I see anything there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Um... Look closer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh yes, I see something there now... Why, it's a penalty! Mr. Justice, once more with feeling, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about this cupboard... Are we all OK with assuming it was moved?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if it was... something really doesn't fit. The cupboard would completely cover up the window to the stairs!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! Someone standing outside wouldn't be able to see in. Someone... like Mr. Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What... What did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Is the "Coolest Defense in the West" losing his cool?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Nnk...! Don't expect me to play along with your little game, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's only a game until someone gets killed, Mr. Gavin. And someone was... while the window to that room was blocked by a cupboard.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Mr. Gavin. Perhaps you'd like to explain to the court. Exactly where did you witness the crime scene from?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Nnn... Nnnk!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Excuse me, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order!!! This is a court of law and I will have order!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">We... We just now received word from our investigative team at the Borscht Bowl Club! They've examined the cupboard in the Hydeout, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...? And what did they find?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Well, Your Honor... It turns out there is a secret passage behind it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah yes. I believe I mentioned something of the sort before. This is one of the tricks to the room many of our regulars know about...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I do remember him saying something about that, now that he mentions it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A secret passage is a handy thing to have when you're engaged in illegal goings-on. Never know when you might need to duck away from the eyes of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the room has a secret passage. Where does it go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The other side connects to the restaurant above. The underworld bosses could get away from the cops... And enjoy a cold bowl of borscht, no doubt. Just like our killer. You see where our line of simple deductive reasoning has led us, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I see it, but I don't believe it. That girl wasn't kidding when she said I needed this trump card for the last hand.</thought> At the time of the murder, the window was blocked, and the victim's hat... ...was only off his head for the few minutes between Mr. Smith's murder... ...and Mr. Wright's return from calling the cops. In other words, the only place anyone could've seen the victim's bald head... ...was from inside the Hydeout! ...Well, Mr. Gavin? <thought>Come on, say something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Dare I ask what really happened that night?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, I think we can probably figure it out ourselves at this point. That night, for whatever reason... Our killer had a date with Mr. Smith... A date with destiny. There he crouched, hidden in the secret passageway behind the cupboard... Holding his breath, waiting for just the right moment... Then the chance came... and he took it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Olga Orly was out cold, struck by Mr. Smith... But his time was soon to come. Mr. Wright went upstairs to call the cops. Leaving Mr. Shadi Smith alone in the Hydeout with the unconscious dealer. Then our killer stepped out from the secret passage and into the Hydeout.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim must have heard the cupboard sliding aside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He wheeled his chair around to look, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...After the deed was done, the criminal must have seen the blood on the card. He would have, of course, realized the need to destroy the evidence. That single spot of blood told the whole story of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Too bad for him he didn't linger any longer in the Hydeout that night. If he had, he might have noticed the cards on the floor... And the fact that they were all red!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Nnnrgk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it seems this trial... ...has taken yet another turn. I'm truly, truly sorry I had to see this day come, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne!!!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yeeeearrrk!? Ahem. Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution will continue its investigation! As for Mr. Phoenix Wright, the defendant, he is hereby cleared of all suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gwwaaaarrk!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Believe me when I say that I don't believe this is happening, Mr. Gavin. But, I'm afraid circumstances call for me to issue a warrant for your arrest. Immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh, no need to apologize. I rather enjoyed myself. It's not every day you get to witness a legendary attorney's dirty tactics first hand...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your point, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Frankly, Your Honor, I'm shocked. That a person of your caliber would be taken in by such a low-grade parlor trick...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Erm... Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The defendant is "cleared of all suspicion"...? This is hardly the time for jokes, Your Honor. Mr. Wright hasn't proven anyone's guilt or innocence here. What he has done is use illegal evidence to put the blame on someone else! And not just anyone else, but me, his own defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Illegal evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me ask you, Mr. Gavin... Is there still any reason, at present, to suspect me of wrongdoing?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Of course. This bottle, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The bottle of grape juice Mr. Wright was drinking...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">How do you intend to explain away the fingerprints on the murder weapon? And not just any fingerprints, am I right, Mr. Payne?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Er, a-actually, yes. The fingerprints on the bottle were, erm, upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>I seem to recall this being an issue earlier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The court, and this case, demand an explanation. I can think of only one reason why one would hold a bottle upside-down. ...And that is to hit someone with the bottom of the bottle. Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, see how the caught fish squirms to the last... Well, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your boss seems awfully concerned about this bottle still... But I'm sure you can come up with a suitable explanation... Just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Yeah. <thought>Just like what!? Why would anyone grab a bottle upside-down, other than to... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't let him trick you into thinking his explanation is the only legitimate one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Is there really another?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take another look at the Court Record. I believe you'll find a simple answer there... In plain sight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um, how about you just say the answer in plain words?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It... would be hasty to deliver a verdict with unanswered questions, indeed. Well, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Gavin said that the court, and this case, demand an explanation... Don't worry. Justice won't leave until justice is done.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps the defense would care to enlighten the court? What evidence do you have to explain why the fingerprints on the bottle are upside-down?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now seems like the perfect time... for a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What do they expect!? I have no idea how to explain it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You're thinking too hard, Apollo. The answer's right in front of you. Just reach down and pick it up. ...Or try picturing situations in which one might grab a bottle upside-down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's actually easier to show you than explain, Your Honor. Place that bottle on the floor, next to your chair.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Excuse me? On the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. Now, reach down and pick it up. ...Without getting out of your chair.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">See? You naturally go to pick up the bottle by its neck... ...with your fingers upside-down! Look at this photograph taken on the night of the murder. The defendant, Mr. Wright, sat here... ...playing piano, bottles of grape juice on the floor to the side of his piano bench. He would have naturally picked up the bottles upside-down several times.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wow! I can't believe it was that simple!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Recall our dinner that evening, Kristoph.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was drinking my usual juice then, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Basically... you used the bottle on the table to do the deed... But then you must have remembered! So you went and picked up one of the bottles from under the piano... And you switched the bottles! You took one of Mr. Wright's bottles and made it look like the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! What do you have to say to these charges, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Fascinating... So this is the legendary attorney's famed tactic of misdirection...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You claim that I switched the bottle? Where is your proof?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Proof!? Well, that's, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As I thought. More baseless conjecture. I'm afraid your "bottle" of proof is quite empty...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't be so sure about that.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honor. When you initiated the investigation of the Hydeout earlier... ...do you recall I requested an additional investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, I have your memo about that here. "Retrieve the bottles from under the piano at the Borscht Bowl Club." And here's one of the bottles in question.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Hmph! What, are you going to dust that for fingerprints, too? I would be surprised if any were on that but his.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Gavin probably wouldn't make such a novice mistake, true... That bottle won't bear a trace of anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you go ahead and examine that bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just humor me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That bottle will solve this case once and for all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What!? <thought>That's some bottle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! There's something inside the bottle! Wh-What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Th-That card...! It can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Recall that unpleasant woman's testimony for a moment...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, Ms. Olga Orly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, our little swindling devotchka.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">That night, I planted the card like I was supposed to. And Wright lost the last hand, just like he was supposed to. Then Smith searched him! But the planted card was gone! The trap failed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait, this isn't...! You're telling me that this is the planted card you "disposed of"? The one you mentioned in this piece of testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I happened to put my hand in my pocket... and found a card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I snuck a peek at it and found it was the Five of Hearts. I had a feeling something might happen so I disposed of the card... before the game.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Disposed... Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was an empty bottle of grape juice I had been drinking right beside me. I threw the card inside the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Five of Hearts... This is the card! The bottles were swapped. And the only one who could have done that was the fourth person in the club that night. You, Mr. Kristoph Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Is... this your idea of revenge, Phoenix Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Revenge...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Revenge for the events that took away your attorney's badge seven years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... My past is like my logic, straight and true. Nothing's changed. All I did was point the finger of justice in the proper direction.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">... Fine. I'm glad we could have this little tte--tte, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This... This is insane! What about me!? Don't I get to prosecute anyone!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this time we've finally come to the end of our trial. Mr. Payne... do you have a report for us on Kristoph Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...He's admitted everything. We're processing his arrest now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Still, one has to wonder why he would do such a thing... He didn't even have a connection to the victim... did he?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Er... None that we know of.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, have you anything to add?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm afraid I can't shed any more light on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">About this victim, Mr. Shadi Smith... His occupation was listed as "traveler"... An odd profession to be sure, and that's all we know about him!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...I'll arrange a follow-up investigation, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Seven years... and you still haven't lost your touch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Kristoph Gavin... ...was a man with much significance for me. Both as a friend... and a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He was extremely talented, to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I needed two things before I could confront him: The first was a place where no injustice would be tolerated... This courtroom. The second was a man who would tolerate no injustice... In other words, a defense attorney. You, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dark time is coming for our legal system... A twisting of justice brought on by our very own court system. We have to set it right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Our work lies ahead of us... and I, for one, am looking forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this seems like a good time to announce a verdict. This court finds the defendant, Mr. Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Apollo. You came through, just like I thought you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm pretty sure I didn't do a thing in there! It was you who cornered Mr. Gav... the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I couldn't have done it by myself. You sensed it too, today, didn't you? Your... ability.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ability?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... a sensitivity I lack. You'll come to understand it soon enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, I wonder if he means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have one question for the witness then. You say you saw the moment the defendant hit the victim. ...Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Olga">O-Of course it's true!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's this weird vibe I'm getting!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What... What was that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll have to find the answer to that question yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The answer... Right... Today was full of questions without answers... Most of them about Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What possible reason could he have had to commit murder? Perhaps you'll learn that in the days to come...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Wait... You don't know, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This locket is the key...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, that reminds me, I met the girl whose picture is in your locket. Your... daughter, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. She's my daughter. You know, you were right about this locket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I took this off his neck the night he died. ...But it looks like our dear "Russian" scam artist saw me. So the truth is, this locket really did belong to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! But that's perjury!!! You testified! You said that locket was yours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I said no such thing, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I merely said that it was "a locket" with my daughter's picture inside. A subtle distinction, but a distinction none the less. And it's the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, but then... why!? Why was the victim wearing a locket with a picture of your daughter inside it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sometimes the straightest path to the truth isn't the best one... Give it time. You're still just getting started with your career.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Speaking of which, I may be out of a job. I work for Gavin Law Offices, after all. <thought>I still can't believe I just saw Mr. Gavin get led away in handcuffs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about coming to work for me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh!? You mean... at the Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices!? I mean... there's not a single attorney in my generation that doesn't know it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't imagine that to be true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait.. but didn't you... You're not a...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I turned in my badge, yes. I'm not an attorney anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That incident seven years ago... That legendary trial... And at the middle of it all was one man... Phoenix Wright! The case reached its sad conclusion.. and he left law for good.</thought> Have you ever thought about coming back to the courts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... not qualified to stand in a court of law, I'm afraid. Didn't you notice in today's trial? There was a single piece of forged evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Forged evidence!? Wh-What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about evidence that shouldn't have existed. A naughty magician's trick...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... One piece of evidence struck me as odd, it's true. It just seemed, well, too perfect. I'll bet this was the forged evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean this, don't you? I got this from your, erm, your daughter, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... That card couldn't have been found at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Or maybe you didn't notice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter, I'll tell you. It was this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ah. <thought>The card that girl gave me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Frankly, this couldn't have been found at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? Because the killer took it with him when he left. Leaving the wrong card in its place... luckily for us.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The court can't accept this evidence! It's a fraud!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fraud? How can you be so sure? I would think the only person who could claim it was a fraud... ...would be the one who took the real card from the crime scene... The real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My verdict was already handed down... seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then... You really...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I forged this card. One look at the crime scene should've told you it wasn't real.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... But you can't do something like that and call yourself an attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who's calling themselves an attorney, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So it's true... The rumor is true! Seven years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... None of that matters much now, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Nnngh... Grrrraarrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I... I punched him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... ...It's your story from here on out, Apollo. Perhaps I can help you turn the next page... My office's address. Drop in, if you like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, about your uppercut... Try yelling, "<cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>>" next time. I find it packs a little more punch. And Apollo, thanks for today. I had a good time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And with that, Mr. Wright walked out the door. ...And that's how my first trial ended. A lot of mysteries went unsolved... And, at the time, I had no idea they were all related. Every mystery that day... ...connected by a single thread of logic... I'd find that out soon enough. My name is Apollo Justice, attorney at law. And this is how my story begins...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>