<xml>
<title>Turnabout Visitor</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's hard to believe that I've been away from my office for a whole month. I hope Detective Gumshoe has been keeping an eye on my office. And keeping it clean. Hm...? The door is unlocked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe...? <thought>Hm? What's this smell...? It's very familiar... Blood? Wh-What the!?</thought> What's the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Freeze.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Identify yourself.</line>
<line speaker="???">.................. Shut up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You've got some nerve, committing murder in a prosecutor's office. Is that a threat?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Let me make one thing very clear.</line>
<line speaker="???">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No one gets away with committing murder in my office. No one.</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My name is Miles Edgeworth. And I work as a prosecutor in my local district. Little did I know that upon my return home after a month abroad... ...I would be thrust into a multitude of cases, and some very frantic and busy days.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I've finished photographing the victim's body, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Please continue your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="???">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Mr. Edgeworth, sir!! Are you OK, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Keep it down, Detective. This is a crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="???">When I heard that a murder had taken place in your office, I ran up here straight away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is Dick Gumshoe. He is a detective with the local precinct... ...and the one they assigned to handle this murder case for the time being.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're looking a little pale, sir! Are you hurt!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I'm perfectly fine. However...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! Look what they did to your office! It's totally trashed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll say. The culprit sullied my floor with dirt rather well. No one gets away with tracking mud into my office.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa! Sounds like you're getting really burned up over this whole thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This crime was committed in my office, so it is my responsibility to solve it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho! That's just like you, Mr. Edgeworth! OK! Time to do some investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agreed. Our first course of action is to gather relevant facts and leads. <thought>We must not overlook anything, no matter how small, if we are to find the truth. So I'll keep any leads or information we find etched in the forefront of my mind.</thought> Speaking of things that pique my curiosity... Why of all places did the murder occur in my office <thought>Crime scene: My office – Is it really coincidence that the murder took place in my office?</thought>? <thought>Hmm... I get the nagging feeling that this is something important to keep in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I was wondering that myself, sir... I mean, you can't really say it's just a coincidence, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not really. Especially because of this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The key to your office <thought>The office key – For security reasons, this office's door has a lock built into it.</thought>? What do you mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you think about it carefully and use Logic, it should become clear to you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Logic...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By finding the connection between two pieces of information... ...and connecting them, new information is born. That is the end result of using Logic.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So how do you use it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I recall information through the Logic Button, and then Connect them together. <thought>Now, to touch the Logic Button and recall the facts.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For security reasons, all prosecutors' doors are outfitted with locks. Which means it would have been hard for the murderer and the victim to get in here. Ergo, it's impossible to dismiss the location of this crime as mere coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, that's exactly what I was thinking, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must be a reason why someone infiltrated my room... What was the killer after? (The killer's goal – Why did this happen in my office? What was the killer after?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're really on the ball today, Mr. Edgeworth! That's some beautiful Logic, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... When you follow leads to their conclusion, only the truth remains. <thought>However... If the information doesn't line up properly, I may stray far from the truth as well... But if I think carefully before piecing leads together, the Logic should flow.</thought> Well, let's get started with our investigation, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The basis of any good investigation is to examine everything, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that. And when I want to examine something, I simply touch the Examine Button.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, if you ever feel lost and want to talk, just touch the Partner Button, OK!? I'll give you great, precise advice as an Ace Investigator, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* Something to try later if I have free time, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How is it coming along?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Please, I need absolute silence. Fingerprint lifting is a delicate art!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Well, I never!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have anything to report?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir, yes, sir! Nothing out of the ordinary right now, sir! And yet, there's something out of the ordinary right in front of my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Talk about a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something out of the ordinary, huh... I should look around a bit more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is this... yet another batch of fresh flowers...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The ones that come with a card attached every month like clockwork for you? Yup. Speaking of that! Let's see what's on the card this month, sir!"All will be resolved.--Wendy"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Oh, Ms. Irony... How painful are thy thorns.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wendy... Isn't that the name of that old lady with the whiny voice that's stalk--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's enough, Detective. You need not remind me further. *shudder*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it's a good thing my Steel Samurai doll was spared any harm.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Speaking of which, I still haven't actually sat down and watched any of that show. What's it about again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I don't know much about it myself, but... ...the hero of "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo" is the Steel Samurai... ...and his goal is to defeat the Evil Magistrate. It's a show geared towards kids... ...however its high production values and riveting plot draws in a number of adults as well. Spin-offs like "Pink Princess: Warrior of Little Olde Tokyo" and "The Nickel Samurai"... ...along with the deluge of merchandise, and even a new stage show, gives it presence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You... sure know a lot. Are you sure you're not some sort of rabid fanboy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! O-Of course not! Anyone that keeps up with society know at least this much! And that conversation lasted longer than expected. Let us return to the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, it's your trophy! The um... Knight of Prosecutors, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...King. King of Prosecutors. And it's not a trophy; it's a shield.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They only send this to the winning prosecutor, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, but I have no real interest in the perceived worth of other people. As for my own worth, that is something only I can determine for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-that's so slick, sir! I'm gonna have to try saying that sometime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Unfortunately for him, his monetary worth is tied directly to his worth to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Watch out for the tea cup fragments there, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Nnngh... That killer is going to pay! This tea set...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yikes! You're really mad over this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This tea set is very dear to my heart and can only be bought in England. It cost more than your whole month's paycheck.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh...Whaaaaaaaat!? Now I feel like the killer's wasted one of my monthly paychecks!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been a while since I've sat at this desk. Oh, how I've missed you. ...Hm? It's so tidy that it looks newer than when I first bought it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho, yeah! That thing's so polished that it makes mirrors jealous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me you had no other work the entire time I was away, Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My job is to protect your office, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And you did such a good job protecting it that a murder occur in it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............ That's harsh, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have to admit the desk has never looked better, so I guess I can't dock his pay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope we can solve this case quickly. I'd like to return to relaxing on this sofa.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That thing looks a billion times softer than my mattress at home! C-Can I sit on it, too? Just for a little while, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. You know I can't allow that. Until this case is solved, neither of us has time to spare, let alone rest.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...! You're right, sir! I'm gonna work hard and be a real trooper to the end!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even once this case is over, I don't think he can afford to take any time off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What have we here...? <thought>Could this perhaps be the murder weapon? If so, it would mean that the killer made their escape after disposing of their gun here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I think I've seen one of these before... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Care to enlighten me as to where?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! I know! I was issued the exact same model! .........I think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't really like guns all that much. I mean, they're really dangerous! But now that I think about it, you do see this model around the precinct a lot, sir. I don't use mine much, except in emergencies, so that's why I didn't recognize it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So it's the same type of revolver (Revolver - Found at the crime scene, it's the same model as those used by precinct detectives.</thought> as the ones used by this precinct's detectives...)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, I seem to have gathered a few pieces of pertinent information. Now to calmly use some Logic and figure out if any of them are connected to each other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the detectives of this precinct all use this same model of revolver?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess. I don't really like guns, but at least I do know the different types out there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At least he knows SOMETHING related to his job.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Your files are all over the floor, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They probably fell during the struggle between the victim and his killer <thought>Signs of a struggle - My files are a mess, pointing to a struggle between the victim and the killer.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, and I tried so hard to keep this place spotless while you were away... I mean, this just rendered all the time and effort I put in pointless!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't recall ever asking you to clean my room!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I watered the flowers every day, just like you requested, sir. I just added cleaning to the list as a weekend special! For about half a day every Saturday, I'd come in and clean this place until it sparkled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does he have a life...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch, they even knocked over your chess set! I had it all set up, ready for when you got back. I figured we could play a few games.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had no idea you were interested in chess.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm actually pretty good at checkers, so I thought I'd give chess a try.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... In that case, I suppose I can set some time aside after we solve this case. <thought>Though I don't expect the games to tax my mental acuity much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>They finished photographing the body, so it should be alright to examine this area. I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Your files are all over the floor, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They probably fell during the struggle between the victim and his killer <thought>Signs of a struggle - My files are a mess, pointing to a struggle between the victim and the killer.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, and I tried so hard to keep this place spotless while you were away... I mean, this just rendered all the time and effort I put in pointless!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't recall ever asking you to clean my room!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I watered the flowers every day, just like you requested, sir. I just added cleaning to the list as a weekend special! For about half a day every Saturday, I'd come in and clean this place until it sparkled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does he have a life...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't believe it! I packed those files on these shelves so tight... ...that not even an earthquake could make them fall off, but just look at them! At this rate, the rest of the files won't be able to withstand an earthquake at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...A-A problem to be sure. Well, once the investigation is over, we'll put them back up on the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's see here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's give the body a once over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, there's blood all over his lower abdominal area.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like the bullet passed clean through his stomach area, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. And until the autopsy's done, I don't think we'll know much more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please have the body sent to the morgue once they're done processing the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you going to be OK with keeping track of the evidence we find, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. This is the safest way I know to keep track of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright, if you say so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I keep all the evidence I find either in or with my Organizer. When I want to re-examine a piece, I have but to touch the Organizer Button. But the Organizer isn't only for evidence; I keep people's profiles on hand in it, too. It's probably a good idea to make a habit of checking the facts often.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's see here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's give the body a once over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, there's blood all over his lower abdominal area.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like the bullet passed clean through his stomach area, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup. And until the autopsy's done, I don't think we'll know much more than that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please have the body sent to the morgue once they're done processing the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faith's holster... I bet he never thought he'd be killed by his own gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... Shot down by the very thing that's supposed to protect the people. I just can't get over that, sir! It's not right! We're gonna get the killer for this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe it's because the victim is a fellow detective... ...but for a second, Gumshoe sounded even more detective-like than usual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's some blood on the back of his pants... Which reminds me of this one time... Back in elementary school, I accidentally flopped onto this chair that had a tack on it... And oh man, that thing stabbed me good! It even drew blood! Hurts just thinking about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That story was so painful, I spaced out in the middle of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do we have here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I think I've seen one of these before...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a police badge, Detective...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, hey! I have the exact same thing, actually! What a coinkidink!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... Let's take a look inside. Mr. Buddy Faith... It would appear that our victim was a detective <thought>Victim was a detective - According to his badge and ID, Buddy Faith was a precinct detective.</thought>, just like you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, I seem to have gathered a few pieces of pertinent information. Now to calmly use some Logic and figure out if any of them are connected to each other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To think that it's so easy to take a life with just the pull of a trigger...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, I can't ever see myself really liking guns. Oh! But I love the ones they use at track and field meets to start races! If you take off before it's fired, everybody always ends up following your lead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...To chase you down for a false start, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you mention it, even when I finish last, I always wind up in last place...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like only one round was fired from this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, so the killer killed the vic with just one shot after wrestling the gun from him? Sounds like the guy knew how to handle a gun, huh, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have no proof for now, but that is a distinct possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The revolver, the standard model used by detectives... Could it have belonged to our recently departed? Detective Gumshoe, could you please thoroughly check the victim's body one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! On it now, sir! 'Scuse me, pal... Let's see... What have we got here... Mr. Edgeworth, sir! This guy's wearing a gun holster!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, so it appears that our killer somehow managed to take the victim's gun from him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you going to be OK with keeping track of the evidence we find, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. This is the safest way I know to keep track of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright, if you say so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I keep all the evidence I find either in or with my Organizer. When I want to re-examine a piece, I have but to touch the Organizer Button. But the Organizer isn't only for evidence; I keep people's profiles on hand in it, too. It's probably a good idea to make a habit of checking the facts often.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let's see what else we can find out about this revolver.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As I always say, you've gotta look really carefully at each piece of evidence! You can use the Scroll Wheels to rotate an object. There's no such thing as a bad angle! Use the Slide Bar or the X and Y Arrows to zoom in and out to get at the nitty gritty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To think that it's so easy to take a life with just the pull of a trigger...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, I can't ever see myself really liking guns. Oh! But I love the ones they use at track and field meets to start races! If you take off before it's fired, everybody always ends up following your lead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...To chase you down for a false start, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now that you mention it, even when I finish last, I always wind up in last place...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like only one round was fired from this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, so the killer killed the vic with just one shot after wrestling the gun from him? Sounds like the guy knew how to handle a gun, huh, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have no proof for now, but that is a distinct possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You called, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there anything you noticed that you'd like to share, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just that I rushed over here as soon as I heard there was a murder in your office, sir! The investigation's just gotten started, so I guess there's not much else to say. So, uh, were you the one that found the body, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately. Upon my return, I found my office door to be unlocked. And what awaited me inside was this whole messy affair.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch, that's rough...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even though I left the security of this room to a "certain detective"...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Sorry, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume you understand how to conduct investigations, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, sir! Examine things by tapping them or by touching the Examine Button! By checking various things out, we gather evidence and information. You can see the evidence we've collected by touching the Organizer Button. For information... information... um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For information and leads, it's the Logic Button.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it! Great job, sir! Deductive reasonable is the way to go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's called "Deductive reasoning", Detective... Clearly, something you lack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I seem to have picked up a few good leads.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! So now you're gonna do that thing you do with all that information, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you babbling about?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The brainy thing you were talking about just a few minutes ago, sir! Um... Logic! You said that you can look at all of your leads and info by touching the Logic Button. Then you pick the pieces you want to connect by touching them and hitting Connect. That's your way of investigating, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, which is why this exercise in explaining my own method to me was unnecessary.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, then how about I explain MY Logic to you next!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is even more unnecessary!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Your Prosecutor's Badge is really tiny compared to my police badge. Oh! But, um...... It's really cool, sir! Much, much cooler than my badge could ever be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...There's no need to suck up to me, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim's gun, huh. It's the same model as mine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A tool used to protect lives, yet one that can also take lives away. Those who take a gun in hand wield a great responsibility. I hope you understand that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't really use my gun at all, sir. The only time I would use this baby is... ...when I'm fighting a hot duel with a convict to look ultra cool!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* You were doing so well until that last bit.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm just a lowly detective, so... ...I'm not sure what I should do with that other than to arrest it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that the only talent you have...? Oh, wait...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Jim! Why, oh why!? How could this have happened to a guy like you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... Are you alright?</line>
<line speaker="???">Don't touch me! Leave me alone! Just let me be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but I can't do that. The investigation is still ongoing, so please refrain from touching the body.</line>
<line speaker="???">The "body"? The "BODY"!? Don't talk about him like he's just some lump of flesh! Look at him... Jim looks like he's just turned in for the night.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, sure. Just in a blood-stained suit, pal.</line>
<line speaker="???">Where are my manners?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aren't you that prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Why, yes, I am! I'm Jacques Portsman, Prosecutor. Jim here was my partner in crime busting...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm Miles Edgeworth, and like you, I am also a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Dick Gumshoe, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So you're Miles Edgeworth... I guess this is your office...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Then it was you! You're the one who killed Jim!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't go around jumping to conclusions, pal! Just calm down, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I will not! I know how things work around here! High prosecutors' office doors all have locks built into them. And only the owner of the office has the key to his or her own office door!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is correct. However, I was not the one who killed your partner.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! Mr. Edgeworth has been overseas on a business trip this whole time, pal. And the key to the door was with me the entire time, OK!? So the only one who could get in here was me! Ho ho ho ho. ...Wait, that means... ......... I'm not sure what that means.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So it was you, then! You're Jim's killer!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way, pal! You've got it all wrong!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Everyone calm down!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman, correct? If you are a real prosecutor, you should know to stay collected. The investigation has only just begun. Isn't it too early to be drawing conclusions?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...Alright, I get the point. You're right, my mistake. I tend to get a little too hot-headed sometimes. You sure are one cool customer, though, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I've heard all the rumors about you. You're the great "Genius Prosecutor". You're something of a legend, you know. Anyway! Let's call a truce and work together, OK? Now, how about a handshake to seal the deal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ A pleasure to work with you.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You guys were conducting your investigation, right? Sorry for barging in like that. Carry on, then. It's your room, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, I intend to.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I just want a little more time to say good-bye to Jim... You there!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I want you to capture this scene on film for me. My final farewell to my partner Jim...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>I should probably give them some space...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How is it coming along?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Please, I need absolute silence. This picture is too important to mess up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll just leave the man to his art.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman. A word, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Jim... I swear I'll find your killer and bring them to justice! You wait and see. It'll be for the both of us! Now then! You wanted to talk to me about something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Um, no. That's alright. <thought>I feel like I'm interrupting their... conversation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Your jacket, sir! What's it doing on the floor!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It must have fallen off the wall when the killer tried to threaten me by firing a round.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So the killer not only shot the victim, but they shot your jacket as well!? They dared to shoot the ultra-special jacket that you made your prosecutorial debut in!? What if they had shot through it!? It would've been a disaster!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not worth getting worked up over, Detective. Not when there's something more here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I take it you haven't noticed it yet, Detective. There is a giant contradiction right here in front of us.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did I say "contradiction"? He must be rubbing off on me. I'm starting to sound like him... But I have my own methods and I will conduct this investigation my way. When the scene before me contradicts a piece of evidence or seems off... ...that's when my deductive skills come into play. First, I have to find the spot that holds the contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like your sofa was spared! Talk about good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And just what is so lucky about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'd hate for my napping spot to have a huge hole in it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Napping spot?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">J-J-Just joking, sir! Honest! I wouldn't dream of sleeping on such a nice, comfy sofa...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He just keeps digging himself deeper and deeper with each passing word...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This jacket sure brings back memories! I remember you used to wear this around the time you became a certified prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was a present from my mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Prosecutor Manfred von Karma, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I don't wear it anymore, yet I can't bring myself to throw it away...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It must mean a lot to you... Even with the little bittersweet memories it holds... Ah, but you know, I've got an old coat of mine hanging up in my room too, sir! ...Yesterday was laundry day, so it's just drying off, but you get the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is it. This bullet hole is where the contradiction lies! When I spot something that's off, I should touch the Deduce Button with conviction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And when I have found sufficient proof to prove the contradiction, I Present it! This is how I do things.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is clearly where the contradiction lies!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't really see what's so wrong with that spot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah. You don't understand? You see, therein lies the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir... It'd be nice if you'd just admit when you're wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That wasn't a mistake! That was me keeping you on your toes, Detective! <thought>When the crime scene and the evidence don't add up, I Present proof to show where!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This bullet hole is the contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's elementary. Two shots were fired in this room. The first felled the victim... ...and the second felled this frame.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, this gun was only fired once.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's true, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means that one of these two bullets was fired from a different gun. <thought>Did the killer have another gun (Another handgun – Other than the victim's gun that I found, could there be another gun in play here?</thought> prepared for tonight...?)</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">By the way, I noticed something, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's that thing sticking out from behind the frame?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, that. It's a secret safe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A s-secret safe!? Oh, I smell money!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll spare us the trouble and just say it. Nothing like what you're imagining is inside. Now, if you could kindly move this frame out of the way.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger that! *achoo* *achoo* Talk about dusty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose that's what happens when I'm not here to dust it once in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I had no idea there was a safe here, or I'd have kept it clean for you, sir! So when did you put this thing in?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It wasn't something I had installed personally. Every prosecutor's office has one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really!? I had no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, only prosecutors are supposed to have knowledge of their existence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So... what's inside, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right now? Nothing. We only use them to store especially important evidence when a trial is in session.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's it...? Talk about squashing my hopes and dreams...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I never knew there was a safe hidden back here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, if detectives knew about them, then they wouldn't be "secret" now would they?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are there any other secret, hidden things in this room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if there were, it would defeat the purpose of them being "hidden" if I told you. So don't bother looking for them.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-So there's no, like, hidden camera around, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? And what if there was...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-Ah! No, it's nothing! Forget I said anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Do I even want to ask what he's been doing in my office while I've been away!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the victim's gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and I guess there's one more, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We certainly can't discount the possibility. However, we must then ask ourselves, why would the killer leave evidence behind?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not exactly something you'd put down and forget about...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Not unless we're talking about you, Detective. <thought>There's something unusual about the killer's actions. And none of it is adding up. What does it all mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I had no idea you had one of these things! I mean, I thought I knew everything there is to know about you, Mr. Edgeworth! I feel like I've caught a glimpse of the hidden side of Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's a great deal you don't know about me... At least, I hope so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm...? Now this is odd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You found something, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This keypad... Don't you find it to be a bit too clean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! There's a thick layer of dust all around it, but not on the keypad itself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there, the forensic scientist!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please dust this area for fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">You got it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I couldn't find, let alone lift, a single print. Looks like it was wiped down well <thought>Wiped fingerprints – All of the fingerprints on this have been wiped clean off.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought... <thought>It appears that Logic is the only way around this setback. Time to rationally and calmly play connect the dots with the information we have.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've already finished examining this area, but it never hurts to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's dust on the rest of the safe, but not here on this keypad.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">According to the forensic scientist, he couldn't find a single print, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That the keypad to the safe was wiped down this carefully... Hmm... Perhaps I should take a good look at all the information we've collected so far.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe I have figured out what the murderer was after.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, what is it, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fact that the safe was wiped clean of fingerprints suggests... ...that the criminal had at least attempted to open my safe. Making the culprit's motive for breaking and entering, theft <thought>Motive: Theft (?</thought> – The culprit tried to open my safe. Was the killer's motive theft?), I believe. <thought>I wonder if knowing that the motive behind this break-in was theft... ...changes what the other pieces of information can tell me about this crime?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a possibility that the files splayed on the floor... ...are not the result of a struggle between the victim and his killer.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! You mean like it could be from when the killer tried to find something, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. We need to figure out if any of the files have been stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! I'm gonna shelve files like you've never seen before, even at a library!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, sure... Let's give that a try...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Why do all the good ones always die young? Surely you must ponder that every once in a while, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... No matter how much we lament, the dead will not come back to life. All we can do is search for the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">......... And? So what are we supposed to do? How do we go about finding the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, we calmly restore the files to their rightful place.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You got it! Here, let me help!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, so this file goes here, and that book goes there...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You sure know a lot about where things go, despite it being Mr. Edgeworth's office.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Because I'm the one who keeps it tidy, pal! OK! Done!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that the murder was definitely committed here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Unnngh... The bloodstains on the bookshelf are still fresh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspect that the victim was killed in a standing position, hence the prints on the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And then the guy fell onto the floor, right? The blood on the floor's kinda grossing me out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective, I don't have the time to deal with your weak stomach right now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nnngh... But you know I'm no good with blood, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm certain there's something wrong with this picture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim's handprints...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He must have tried to support himself with his hands here after being shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There are prints on the floor, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those must have been made when, unable to stay standing, he dropped to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I put them all back, just as they should be, sir! Doesn't look like anything's missing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Although, it does look like the killer moved the body to flip through my shelves. <thought>I wonder if they found what they were looking for...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So this is where the bullet lodged itself after it went through the victim, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the bullet to be lodged so squarely in a file spine... ...indicates that the files were ransacked after the shooting had occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then I guess the victim was moved because he was in the killer's way...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that the victim was in a sitting position here after being shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! So that's why the seat of the victim's pants has blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would be the logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer moved the body because it was leaning against the bookshelf.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The blood on this guy's pants proves that pretty well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In a sense, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">See! I'm not completely useless, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is clearly where the contradiction lies!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't really see what's so wrong with that spot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah. You don't understand? You see, therein lies the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir... It'd be nice if you'd just admit when you're wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That wasn't a mistake! That was me keeping you on your toes, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">May I have a word with you?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Please, I need absolute silence. Dusting for prints at a crime scene is a most sacred process.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The man loves his job... Maybe a bit too much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have anything to report?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir, yes, sir! Seeing Mr. Portsman tearing up like that... ...has brought an unstoppable torrent of tears to my own eyes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Were you good friends with Mr. Faith, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">No, sir! But I can't help myself. I'm sympathetic to other people's tears!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If I may make a suggestion, I'd clean myself up so as to not give the wrong impression.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman. A word, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Oh, Jim... Your laugh, your smile... I'll never be able to joke around with you again... But don't you worry, Jim! I'll joke around for the both of us! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...He's not listening at all. <thought>Mr. Portsman is off in his own little world, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So? Any keen insights, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I noticed that you... haven't found anything odd about the crime scene yet! That's unlike you, sir! If you spot something that seems off, you should check it out! All you have to do is line the cursor up with where you see a contradiction... ...and hit the Deduce Button. But after that, you've still gotta back up your hunch. Pick the piece of evidence that does the job and Present it, sir! It's that easy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I suppose you've spotted something already, which is why you explained all this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, not really... But hey! That's what you're here for, Mr. Edgeworth! To find them all in a jiffy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Beaming with overconfidence as he none too subtly cries for assistance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is clearly a contradiction here with this bullet hole!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't see? Quite simply, the bullet hole itself is too low. If the victim was shot in the stomach, the hole should be much higher up.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But what if the guy was shot while he was sitting or lying down, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would be illogical. The victim leaned against this shelf here after being shot. Which suggests that he was standing when he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then that means...! ............Wait, what does that mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It means you need to use your brain every once in a while instead of mine, Detective. In any case, it means someone made a faulty assumption. And it was from this mistake that our current contradiction was born! What is the faulty assumption that caused this problem with the bullet hole's position?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the victim was shot while he was lying down...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait... Didn't you just say that line of reasoning is illogical, sir? You said, "The victim leaned against this shelf here after being shot."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I was trying to be nice and explain my complex logic in an easier way for you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, really!? Thanks for thinking of me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Good, I don't think he noticed my mistake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The position of the handprints is what's causing this problem. We wouldn't be in this dilemma if the handprints were closer to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But the handprints are where they are... Up top.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, you are quite perceptive! Which is why this is not a viable hypothesis.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, so it was just a "what if"? Then what's the right answer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You still can't figure it out? Then allow me to explain.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, please, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Guess he didn't notice the slip-up. Although, at this point, I shouldn't be surprised.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the order of the files is a bit off.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean I put them back in the wrong order just now? Hey! Actually, I think the labels on the files are wrong, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! You see here how the files that were shot begin with the number 0? What are those doing all the way down there after 1, 2, and 3!? That's really weird!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, the way they are organized now is the correct order. They are exactly as I see them in my mind's eye.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But the numbers are all out of order.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Those white binders are special, so they are arranged a little differently. But from this, we know that the files were not in this order when the crime occurred. <thought>Aha! So that's it!</thought> I believe the killer made the same incorrect assumption as you just did, Detective. Let's re-arrange the files in numerical order and see what we find out.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you think it'd be OK to prop the body back up to how it was before it was moved?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They've finished processing the crime scene, so I don't see why it wouldn't be. If you please, Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I suspected... The bullet hole is now where it should logically be. The killer went through my files first before shooting Mr. Faith.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And then put the files back in numerical order, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. And then proceeded to shoot the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why would someone kill a man and then look through your files one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Puzzling indeed. The files were thrown into disarray twice <thought>Files in disarray - The culprit re-arranged my files twice, once before and once after the murder. Why?</thought>, once before and once after the crime. But why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now the crime scene is as it was at the time of the murder. Time to give it another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There must be some reason as to why the victim's body was moved. But there is no time to ponder that now. Let us continue with our investigation, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger that, sir! I'm raring to go!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">These handprints belong to the victim, right? They make sense with the body position.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he must have left them when he was trying to support himself after he was shot. <thought>However, the final position of the body shows that it was moved... I need to go over this crime scene with a fine-toothed comb one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I suspected... The bullet hole is now where it should logically be.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And we figured out that the killer went through your bookshelf twice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... There are many things the killer did that don't make sense. But to figure out the whys, we need more information.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-This...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What is that!? Why does it say "Gumshoe" on there in blood!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I'd say it's some incredibly incriminating evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, indicative of criminal activity, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No! Wait! There's gotta be some mistake! Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Help me! Say something, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... It appears that one of my files was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is that all, sir!? What about me and my situation!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this what the killer was really after?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Looks like Jim was able to leave us the name of his killer in the end. And this most important message managed to reach us.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm telling you! It wasn't me!!!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You can't be terribly pleased to hear that your beloved partner is the guilty party.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you are going to accuse Detective Gumshoe of being the culprit... ...I sincerely hope you have some proof to back it up.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Jim's words... They're more than enough, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's how you want to play it, then at least allow me to understand your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't like this one bit. There's something strange about this man's attitude. And there must be some sort of flaw to his logic waiting for me to dig out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! Wh-What are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What I always do in court; I'm going to cross-examine him. One way or another, I'll expose the flaw in his logic with this technique.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! How do you do that!? C-Can you explain it to me, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. First, I listen to the witness's testimony. If I find a flaw in the testimony, something that contradicts the evidence... ...I open the Organizer and Present the piece of contradictory evidence! <thought>To Present something, I simply touch the Present Button, but that's old news.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it's not like there's gonna be a flaw in their testimony every time, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct, and at those times, I need to Press the witness by touching the Press Button. Sometimes by pressing, I can draw out new information, and new or modified testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I think I get it, sir! I'll be sure to try this technique out during investigations, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. I'll even show you how it's done. Now watch carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman... If you are ready.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Aww, if you don't have time, you could just say so, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Detective Gumshoe. You stole Jim's gun from him and shot him dead.Further, you messed up the files to make it look like you had committed theft instead.That's when you moved Jim's body that was sitting in front of the bookshelf!But thanks to that, you didn't notice the bloody letters his body was hiding.And it will be by his final words that you will be brought to justice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You intend to argue that the victim's dying message points to his killer...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I can hear Jim's voice, and he's calling for his killer's arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Are you sure you're not mishearing his words, Mr. Portsman? <thought>There is no way Detective Gumshoe is the culprit here... I will find the flaw in this man's logic... ...and expose it with credible evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Detective Gumshoe. You stole Jim's gun from him and shot him dead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You know, there's something I've been meaning to ask...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hm? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you call the victim "Jim"... ...when clearly, his name is "Buddy Faith"...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Isn't it obvious? "Jim" is the perfect name for my companion. "Jacques and Jim". Don't those two names go together like peanut butter and jam?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But "Jim" isn't even close to the guy's real name...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, "Jacques and Buddy" just sounds... off somehow. Besides, he was the third of a bunch of guys I decided to nickname "Jim".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. He talks about the victim like he was his pet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Further, you messed up the files to make it look like you had committed theft instead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think it was necessary to dishevel my shelves twice to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That's true... Ok, then maybe his real intent WAS theft.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Are you accusing me of stealing something from Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's a possibility. Maybe your salary's been cut so much that life is getting a little too rough to handle...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll have you know that I eat three square meals every day, pal! ...OK, so all three of them happen to be instant noodles, but...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Poor thing. What an evil prosecutor you were paired up with. And what a motive, no?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That's when you moved Jim's body that was sitting in front of the bookshelf!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why would Detective Gumshoe do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Because the body was getting in his way. He had to mess up your bookshelf somehow, right? Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">But thanks to that, you didn't notice the bloody letters his body was hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you think that the killer didn't notice the bloody letters?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">The body was covering it quite well, wouldn't you say? That's how he missed it. But judging by what I've seen, it doesn't take much for your detective to miss something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Who do you think you are!? You know nothing about me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">There's a lot a person can understand about another from first impressions alone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't say I disagree with him on that point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why don't you say something, sir!? ...*gasp!* N-Not you, too, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Despite his lack of attention to detail, I don't believe the detective to be the culprit. Nobody could've overlooked the bloody letters, and I can prove it... With evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I couldn't ask for a better set-up... ...for the game-finishing spike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And it will be by his final words that you will be brought to justice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying that those letters were intended for you?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yup. Jim was an outstanding detective. I would expect no less from my former partner.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like Mr. Portsman still doesn't understand... He has yet to figure out the true meaning behind the bloody letters.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">What are you sputtering over there? Can't you just admit my logic is perfectly sound?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Actually, there's a gigantic flaw in his logic... A gap so wide that even the good Detective can spot it. Now to clue Mr. Portsman in by presenting him with some evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps you're not aware Mr. Portsman, but there is a serious flaw in your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Heh, bringing a bit of the courtroom into this, I see. No problem, I'm game!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't help but find it odd...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Odd that a fellow prosecutor would be brought down by the power of his own office.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wh-What are you talking about!? ...Oh, you're joking, I get it...! Ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you have the time to laugh, then you have the time to take another, closer look at this. Do you still not see? If not, may I direct your attention to the missing file...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wh-Whaaaaaaat!? That's impossible!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's "impossible", Mr. Portsman?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Um, uh, nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The files on that shelf are all about a certain case. When the killer went to take the file after murdering your partner... ...I highly doubt they could've missed the bloody letters written on the spines.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's possible that they could have taken the file before committing the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think it's pretty obvious that the file was stolen after it was written on. The missing letters in the detective's name where the file should be is proof.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! I mean, the "s" is gone, and there's only half an "h"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If Detective Gumshoe really was the culprit of this case... ...I highly doubt that even he could overlook his own name written in blood on the files. Especially as a detective who can't stand the sight of blood!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">*gasp!*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Which means... what exactly? What does that make this dying message...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It makes it the work of a criminal intent on tampering with the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's so low! I can't believe the criminal tried to pin this whole thing on me, sir! I'm gonna get 'em, sir! You'll see! I'm gonna have them under arrest in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Portsman?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Brilliant! Absolutely splendid! Logic deserving of Olympic gold!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I appreciate the praise, but it doesn't change the fact that your reasoning is flawed.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Meh, you win some and you lose some. That's how life goes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Glad everyone's so cheery... even though I feel more dead than alive.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, but you know, it really is a shame... I really didn't want to have to bring this up, however...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-What is it this time!? Are you still after me, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Humor me for a second. Who has the key to this office?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That would be me! But Mr. Edgeworth just proved that I'm innocent, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That's absolutely right! And I acknowledge your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then why do I sense that you still have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, I was thinking. Did you know there is one other person with a key to this office?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>One other person...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hey, you there!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, sir! What is it, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Would you kindly fetch and escort that lovely young lady here for me...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A lady...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">The girl is a member of this building's security. Think of her as a "material witness".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Security!? Did you say, "Security"!? No, stop it, pal! Don't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's wrong with him all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I believe she needs no introduction. I have called upon Ms. Maggey Byrde, a member of security.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">D-Detective Gumshoe, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maggey!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ms. Byrde is the security guard on watch tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. And your point is?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">My point is that she could very well have used it. And by "it", I mean the master key, which can open all the office doors in this building.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">If you are not the guilty party, Detective Gumshoe... ...then the only other person with access to this room is Ms. Byrde.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">How dare you!? I would never sneak into someone's room!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! I refuse to believe that Maggey's the culprit, pal! Um... It was me! That's right, I did it!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Can we take that as a confession, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, well, it wasn't really me... But it definitely wasn't Maggey, pal! So, yeah, it was me! If it was, you'd have no problems with that, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please refrain from flying off the handle, Detective. There's no need for such theatrics.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Listen to your boss, Detective. He understands what I'm saying here. That girl is the only one who could've committed the crime, and for one simple reason!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's pretty obvious that Ms. Byrde snuck into your room using the master key.I mean, if Detective Gumshoe isn't the one who opened the door......then that leaves only Ms. Byrde as our prime suspect.On top of which, she knows our good detective, doesn't she?Making it all that more probable that she was the one who faked the dying message.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that she used the master key...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Incredibly incriminating evidence, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the master key to every office in the building.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's what you claimed about the evidence earlier as well...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That was then, this is now. The flow of a good match always changes during a rally. It's all about your reflexes and reaction time, especially for an athlete like me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if there was anyone else other than Ms. Byrde who could've used the master key? It seems that the only way to get Mr. Portsman to give me more details is to Press him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's pretty obvious that Ms. Byrde snuck into your room using the master key.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure Ms. Byrde is the only member of security who could've used the master key?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">There's only one person on staff at this time of night. And tonight, she's it. Isn't that right, Ms. Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's, um... true... But... But I wasn't able to use the master key at the time of the crime, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Wasn't able to"...? What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yes, yes... Moving on. I'd hate to get sidetracked by something unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaddaya mean, "unrelated"!? I wanna hear what she has to say, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">But you can't really trust her not to tell lies. Plus, I hate wasting time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, should I hear Ms. Byrde out...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not so fast. I, too, am interested in hearing what Ms. Byrde has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Didn't I just say it'd be a waste of time? We don't need to hear her lies.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be the judge of that. Ms. Byrde, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I discovered that the master key was missing at around 1 AM, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by "missing"?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">As in "it wasn't anywhere in the security booth", sir! The killer must've stolen it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman, I believe this to be an important piece of testimony. Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">*sigh* I can't believe that someone like you would be taken in by such words.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm not lying, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">If that's the case, then I'd like to know... why you have the master key now?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I... I don't quite know. It just reappeared all of a sudden, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hah, a likely story. And where is your proof that the key was stolen to begin with? I bet you just forgot where you put it and then "found" it again.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I never lose things! I can practically guarantee that! With me, if something disappears, it's usually because someone stole it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal! Trust me, you don't want to test just how bad her luck is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Unfortunately, I can't deem this piece of testimony as conclusive.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Glad you agree, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Unnnngh... But! But! You still haven't established Maggey's motive for breaking into Mr. Edgeworth's office!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Her motive? Didn't we already establish that it was theft? I mean, the culprit clearly went through the bookshelves and at least tried the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is as Mr. Portsman says, Detective. <thought>I can't ignore the fact that all the evidence points towards a motive of theft. But I'm done taking blows. It's time to counterattack with a few facts of my own.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, maybe I should pay more attention to what Mr. Portsman is saying for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure Ms. Byrde is the only member of security who could've used the master key?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">There's only one person on staff at this time of night. And tonight, she's it. Isn't that right, Ms. Byrde?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's, um... true... But... But I wasn't able to use the master key at the time of the crime, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>"Wasn't able to"...? What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I discovered that the master key was missing at around 1 AM, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by "missing"?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">As in "it wasn't anywhere in the security booth", sir! The killer must've stolen it!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hah, a likely story. And where is your proof that the key was stolen to begin with? I bet you just forgot where you put it and then "found" it again.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What do you know, pal!? Besides, Maggey doesn't have any reason to want to sneak into Mr. Edgeworth's office!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You mean her motive? Didn't we already establish that it was theft? I mean, the culprit clearly went through the bookshelves and at least tried the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is as Mr. Portsman says, Detective. <thought>I can't ignore the fact that all the evidence points towards a motive of theft. But I'm done taking blows. It's time to counterattack with a few facts of my own.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Her intent? From the messed-up shelves to the wiped-down safe, I'd say thievery.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I concur that the culprit's motive appears to have been thievery, however...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Glad to hear that the great Miles Edgeworth is in agreement with little ol' me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, with regard to the investigation of the bookshelves and safe...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hey! Good thinking, asking for my opinion on the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Would it be too much for you to allow me to complete a full sentence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I mean, if Detective Gumshoe isn't the one who opened the door...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought we had established Detective Gumshoe's innocence pretty thoroughly.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It was just a theory, one hypothesis among the many possibilities. I mean, I had my doubts about Ms. Byrde from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, then why didn't you mention her first?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Now, now. Don't make that face. See! There goes the truth, running the other way! Let's pick up the pace and see if we can't catch up to it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think you're catching my drift...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, but we are in agreement that the detective isn't the killer, right? If so, then I hope you'll understand when I say... ...that since she is the only one who could've open [sic] your office door...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...then that leaves only Ms. Byrde as our prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you think it's a bit early to be jumping to conclusions?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Are you saying there's another way to open the door other than with the master key? Oh, I get it. Perhaps you had a spare made for someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll have you know, I have never made a spare, so what are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Nothing. Guess I should've known better than to suggest that someone like you would.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">On top of which, she knows our good detective, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there anyone in this district who hasn't at least heard of Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Good point. He's practically a celebrity among us prosecutors.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really!? I never knew I was so talked about, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">We're holding our collective breath, you know. For when you screw up so badly that you're literally chased off the force.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Wait, WHAT!? IS THAT TRUE, MR. EDGEWORTH!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... O-Of course not. T-That's hogwash!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phew... Don't scare me like that! I almost had a heart attack there...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Making it all that more probable that she was the one who faked the dying message.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By "dying message", you mean the bloody letters that spell out "Gumshoe"...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I figured that whoever wrote his name must have wanted to frame him. And just the act of choosing his name is proof enough that the two knew each other well.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! What are you waiting for! Hurry up and present some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would love to... But first, we should listen a bit more, and digest what he is saying. <thought>And Press him for more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you wish to continue insisting that Ms. Byrde was set on stealing something?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Why not? It's the truth, after all. It was also by your logic that we came to the whole thievery conclusion anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That may be, but you must also be aware of the fact that the safe is a secret safe. The existence of which is only privy to prosecutors...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I find it a little hard to believe that a hidden safe was a part of her cunning plan.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">B-But...! But she could've found it by accident while she was turning everything else upside-down!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I highly doubt that. I'd say the culprit knew exactly what they were looking for. After all, only the bookshelf and the safe were targeted.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Nnnnghaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! Even I didn't know about that safe, pal! And that means there's no way Maggey could've known about it either!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Th-Then are you proposing... ...that the killer is a prosecutor...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting conclusion. That's definitely looking more and more probable.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong, Prosecutor? Do you have a different suspect in mind now?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I... I... Curses! Why!? What made you--!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's with the angry face all of a sudden...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's... It's all my fault...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's Jim... He knew... about the existence of the secret safes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! What did you just say...!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">We were partners! Like inseparable conjoined twins! That's why I told him. I filled him in on the secret safes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then that means...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yeah, I know. I had only just told him, too... Obviously, it was wrong of me to tell him... I still can't quite believe it, but the thief who broke into your room was probably Jim...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now he's claiming that the victim was the thief...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And... you were simply trying to stop him, weren't you? Ms. Maggey Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I mean, you ARE a security guard, right? That's your job. But, killing is going a bit too far, even in your risky profession.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What the--!? You're still accusing Maggey of the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yes and no. I mean, she had stumbled upon Jim, who had probably drawn his gun... I get it! It was self defense, wasn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">N-No! I... I couldn't... I could never do something like that, not even as a security guard, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Plus, even if he was the thief, he wouldn't have a key to this office!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Which is precisely why he had to steal it, wouldn't you say? It was Jim who stole the master key.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Pretty impossible for a supposedly "stolen" key to be here with us, unless... ...well, unless you retrieved it from Jim after you killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman, are you honestly accusing your own partner of being a thief?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I don't want to admit it, but it's the only way for everything else to make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Has he no honor!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Now then, I think we're done here. The investigation waits for no man. Would you people be so kind as to see yourselves out?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't kick us out! This is Mr. Edgeworth's office!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, but I'm the one who's been assigned to this case. You are all suspects to varying degrees, and therefore, ineligible to run this show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Listen, pal! How many times do I have to say this!? Maggey CAN'T be the culprit!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Calm yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We have no choice but to accommodate his request... for now.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ha ha! Thank you, Mr. Edgeworth. At least ONE of you understands. Now, then, if you could remove yourselves from my crime scene, I'd be most grateful.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Mark my words, Mr. Portsman. We will meet again.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">If that's a formal request from the legendary prosecutor himself, then I suppose so. Now don't disappoint me, you hear!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What is with that prosecutor!? I can't believe how rude he was! It was... unbelievable!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please maintain your professionalism, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm gonna find some real solid evidence proving Maggey's innocence! You'll see, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But we've been kicked out of the crime scene, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">T-True... So then, what now!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Looks like my life's fallen into yet another gigantic ditch.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do not despair, Ms. Byrde. We can overcome this as well. There are many other places and things we should be looking into anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh!? Really, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For example, this hallway. The lynchpin of his argument against Ms. Byrde is related to the master key. In that case, this hallway is the perfect place to look for more information... ...regarding the mystery surrounding my door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering if I may speak with you for a bit concerning this case.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I've always been a big fan of the courtroom, but this... ...this is like a dream! A dream where I'm being cross-examined by THE Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't let this chance pass me by. I must remember to ask her about the master key. I should jog her memory by showing my notes to her through the Present Button.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you ever met the victim before?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I've seen him a couple of times before when I had to go to Mr. Portsman's office. Mr. Faith was always playing basketball with Mr. Portsman, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That sounds like fun! Just once, I'd have loved to play with them.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It sounds like fun, but the only person ever taking a shot was Mr. Portsman... All Mr. Faith ever did was pass him the ball, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...On second thought, I don't think I'd have fit in all that well with them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Maggey Byrde, correct? I take it that you are an acquaintance of the detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was under my supervision back when she was still on the force, sir. One day, she got caught up in a murder, and things started going downhill, so she quit.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But I owe a lot to Detective Gumshoe for introducing me to my current employer! Or so I thought until a few hours ago... Right before I was about to clock out for the night...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You got caught up in this whirlwind of a case, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Don't worry. My whole life has been nothing but a whirlwind of bad luck and failures.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Since I was 6 months old, when I fell from the 9th floor of my apartment building... ...I've been hit by all sorts of vehicles, gotten sick from all sorts of foods... ...failed at almost every test I've taken, experienced almost every kind of disaster... And now, I even managed to be named a criminal, just when I've become a security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's... a lot to go through in one lifetime...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I know! And just when I thought I had finally found my happiness... ...I wind up getting you and Detective Gumshoe involved in my bad luck.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't need to worry about me, Ms. Byrde. Nor do you need to worry about yourself. I will solve this case and prove your innocence. All I ask in return is for your cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, sir, Mr. Edgeworth! You can count on me! I'll do all I can to help!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did you mean by you "used the master key"?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh, I had to use it to open the door for this prosecutor who had forgotten his key. I mean, it's my job as a security guard, right? .........Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's right! I just remembered! The prosecutor who forgot his key... It was Mr. Portsman, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? Please tell me more, Ms. Byrde. Quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">It was around 12 AM. Mr. Portsman had forgotten his office key, so he came down to security, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's when you loaned the master key to him?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">No way! It's against regulations to loan the master key out to anyone! I walked with Mr. Portsman to his office and opened the door for him personally, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And then? What happened after that!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, he called for me to come close up his office as he was leaving to go home. That was around 1:30 AM, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, in summary, for the sake of one forgetful prosecutor... ...you used the master key twice <thought>Used the master key – This key was used to unlock and lock Portsman's office at 12 AM and 1:30 AM.</thought> tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Talk about suspicious!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I doubt you can say that you've never left your keys at home, Detective... <thought>I think this calls for a thorough examination of Mr. Portsman's door.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's a Prosecutor's Badge, isn't it? It proves that you're really a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting... Despite all appearances, she seems to know more than Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">With that badge, even I could be a professional prosecutor... Sir, may I please try that on? Just for a little bit!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think that would be a very good idea, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I-I guess not...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>On second thought, they're actually on the same level...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So when did you discover that the master key was missing?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">By the time I realized it, I think it was around 1 AM, sir. And I noticed it was back at around 2:30 AM. It was just sitting there on the ledge where the security room's reception window is. But I'm sure that between those two times it was not just gone, but stolen <thought>Master key was stolen – This key went missing from approximately 1 AM until 2:30 AM.</thought>, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why is such an important key stored in such an insecure place?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah, it's not like that, sir. We always keep the key further inside the room, away from the window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Always, you say? Except for this time, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I admit that was a bit careless, but I had my reasons! I left it out because I was sorta using it at the time. It was after I had used it that I left it sitting out on the ledge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She used the master key?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I've had to open Mr. Portsman's office up for him a number of times before. I've also had the chance to see the inside of his office on a number of occasions, too. He's got shelves upon shelves of sports memorabilia, trophies, and awards in it... ...to the point where it's almost beyond gaudy, sir. ...But maybe I just feel that way because I'm jealous since I don't have even a single one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't say that, Maggey! I... I'll make a special "Guard of the Month" award, just for you!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">...Thanks for trying, but I've already got a mountain of consolation prizes, sir. They're proof of just how unbelievably unlucky my life has been. Plus, getting an award from you just isn't the same as getting a real award, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N...Nnnnnnnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm just a lowly security guard, so... ...I'm not sure what I should do with that other than to guard it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* It's like talking to another Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Prosecutor">It looks like you're in quite the pinch, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To be sure, a murder within the walls of the prosecutor's office is no trifling matter. We must find, apprehend, and punish the killer accordingly post-haste.</line>
<line speaker="Prosecutor">Sounds like a messy case you've got on your hands. If you ever feel lost, or need some advice, my door is always open!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How gracious. I will keep your offer in mind. <thought>...Who is this guy again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is everything alright?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, sir! If you must know, I weighed myself this morning, and I'm finally at 154 pounds!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Congratulations, but I was asking about this hallway and this room.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Oh! Everything's OK, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A word of advice. Stay focused, or you may start to lose even more weight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...? It's...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! isn't this that missing 0-series file, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No doubt about it. The bloody letters mark it clear as day. ...There seem to be a few pages missing. Our thief took only what was necessary, and left the rest behind.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what are these 0 files about, sir? I guess they've got something worth stealing in them, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not particularly. It's just a collection of court case files. However... ...the cases within these files are not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They belonged to the high prosecutor that used to occupy my current office. I have my reasons, but let's just say I was charged with keeping them as they were.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then that means the thief must've also wanted the file for a specific reason, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would seem so. Only the pages related to that case from 10 years ago are missing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder why anyone would care about such an old case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the stolen file... But what's it doing under here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and why would you steal something and then leave it behind?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like our thief took only what was needed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what are these 0 files anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Didn't I just explain that a few minutes ago?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess they've got something worth stealing in them, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not particularly. It's just a collection of court case files. However... ...the cases within these files are not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They belonged to the high prosecutor that used to occupy my current office. I have my reasons, but let's just say I was charged with keeping them as they were.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then that means the thief must've also wanted the file for a specific reason, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would seem so. Only the pages related to that case from 10 years ago are missing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder why anyone would care about such an old case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A well-crafted, high-quality sofa for visitors. The stitching is excellent.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Talk about a luxury waiting area. These babies are also great for napping, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would sleep even out here, Detective? In a hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whenever I do, I always wind up dreaming about giving testimony up on the stand. But it always ends the same way: me getting trounced by a lawyer! Isn't that awful!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe I should give it a try sometime... To envision myself winning, naturally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I bet the thief's... not under here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess there isn't enough space for anyone to hide under here anyway. I mean, if someone could contort themselves to fit, I'd be REALLY impressed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Sounds to me like somebody has already tried at least once before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A minimalist, yet classy door made of top-quality wood. It's sturdily made, making it near impossible to break in by force.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's almost... majestic, sir. I wish I could be as stately as this door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Only Gumshoe would praise a door as something greater than himself...</thought> Being a detective has its own rewards, and a certain virtuous value... I think. If you live up to your full potential... that's a poignant trait that anyone can admire.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see! So you're saying, sir, that me being me is the best thing I can do for everyone?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Right.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That long pause wasn't exactly reassuring, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">1202. These four numbers on a number plate alone proclaim this to be my office.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoops! ...Hey! These number plates slide right out, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They have to be able to take the plate off when a room becomes vacant, you know. Although... the idea that it can be so easily removed is kind of...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't see any signs of forced entry.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And according to the guard, no signs that the lock was picked, either, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Meaning that the door really was opened with a key. Hmm... Did you happen to ask if any prints were lifted from the doorknob?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Apparently, the doorknob's clean as a whistle. Wiped, they think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Whoever this thief is, they did a good job of not leaving any clues behind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is a basketball doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's Mr. Portsman's prized possession, sir. I heard he also plays soccer, dodge ball [sic], and even tennis.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And not a single one of those sports is suitable to be played in a hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This office...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... 1203... 1203... Hey Maggey, whose room is this again?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">...It's Mr. Portsman's, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So he's my new neighbor, I see... I suppose he moved in while I was away overseas?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A minimalist, yet classy door made of top-quality wood.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's kinda majestic, too! Fits in really well with the ambiance of the prosecutor's offices! Even Mr. Portsman seems dignified, just because he works behind one of these.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nonsense. A man doesn't become more or less dignified because of where he works.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, he still seems more dignified than Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Payne...? I suppose custodial work can also be dignified.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Room 1203. I take it that this is Mr. Portsman's office?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, you can't mistake it because of that basketball hoop, sir. Oh, that reminds me. Mr. Portsman had actually wanted room 1202 really badly. But since you were already occupying it, Mr. Edgeworth, we put him next door, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So why was Mr. Portsman so particular about getting room 1202?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'm not sure, but I bet it's because of something like his birthday is December 2nd...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup! That's gotta be it! I can't think of another reason why!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can think of at least three... Bah. Why am I even wasting time thinking about this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The door is locked tight.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Heh heh, I bet the ol' credit card trick wouldn't work here, huh Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the office of a high prosecutor, Detective. These doors would be pretty ineffective if the average cat burglar could get through them.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aha! So I guess only a GREAT cat burglar could get in! That must be who our culprit is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Might I advise you to return that conclusion to whatever pawn shop you bought it from?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's Mr. Portsman's personal basketball hoop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't believe he put something like this in the hallway of a Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, you know, it's actually pretty useful, sir! I haven't gotten lost trying to get to your office since it's been here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How long have I had the same office, and yet you STILL managed to get lost!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This location contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm? I don't see anything wrong at all, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe! You should think a little harder, sir! ...Although I don't really get it myself, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I see... In that case, I'll point out what's wrong once more for the two of you. <thought>I sense that if I look a little harder, I'll find the contradiction slumbering here. I should probably also flip through my Organizer one more time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's a contradiction here between reality and the evidence. If what Ms. Byrde has said is true, then why is this door locked tight?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? You know, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Byrde, are you sure you didn't re-lock this door?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I am certain of it, sir. And I don't think Mr. Portsman noticed it himself that I hadn't...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Which means... what, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It either means that he actually DOES have the key to his office... ...or that the door Ms. Byrde opened wasn't this one at all, but a completely different one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She opened a different door? But how can you prove that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's an easy way to find out. All we need to do is... ...we need to examine these:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we examine the fingerprints on the master key...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, if that's what you want to examine, sir, that was the very first thing we did. I can tell you that we didn't find any prints other than Maggey's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's so brilliant, Mr. Edgeworth! So what can we deduce from that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, well...</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">I'll tell you what I deduced! I think this means that the culprit wiped their prints off!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Y-Yes, that's exactly it. I'm glad you were able to come to the same conclusion. However, the more important matter is... </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prints on the number plate, they will tell us all that we need to know.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Everything? Really? ...Like what, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Like... Well, for example... And such as... Well, we know for sure that Detective Gumshoe's dinner will only consist of instant noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Woooooow!!! That was amazing, sir! How did you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Was that supposed to be a joke to cheer me up, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, that's it. Now then, we should get back to doing what we need to do and that is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prints on the doorknob will tell us everything!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you! Yeah, you, pal! Do us a favor and see what you can lift from this, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So!? What did you find out!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no need for such belligerent nostril flaring, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! I have found only Mr. Portsman's and Mr. Faith's prints on this doorknob.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So only two people's prints were found on this, huh? That's pretty decisive...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? I'm lost, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thinking logically, a certain other person's prints should be on this knob as well. <thought>Now then, whose prints should also be on this doorknob?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">............</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, we already found Mr. Portsman's and Mr. Faith's prints, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Urngk! I-Is that so... W-Well, there should be one other person who left their mark on this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And why would my prints be on this knob, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Are you saying that Mr. Gumshoe has broken into Mr. Portsman's office before!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!? I've never even been inside that office! What are you saying, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, well... ...I was just testing your naïveté. I'll answer you straight from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wish you had done that from the very beginning, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you find it odd that the prints of the person who unlocked this door are absent?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the door that Ms. Byrde opened could not have been this one, but a different one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What have we here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is this basketball property of Mr. Portsman?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yes, sir! He's always ready for a match!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Basketball, soccer, dodge ball [sic], tennis... It doesn't matter what sport it is, he's game. Although, I think it'd be a little hard to play tennis with this ball. Ho ho.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That isn't the point you should be focusing on, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You're right, sir! Now I know what I should be focusing on! Bad Mr. Portsman! Someone should teach him to clean his toys up after he's done playing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I think we've reached the end of this conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What's this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you looking at, sir? Oh, hey! How about a game?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's OK, Detective... I just found the position of this hoop to be a little off.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're right, sir! I guess it shifted when someone made a seriously sweet slam dunk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The positioning of the hoop is definitely unnatural... I'd better take note of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What's this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you looking at, sir? Oh, hey! How about a game?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's OK, Detective... I just found the position of this hoop to be a little off.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're right, sir! I guess it shifted when someone made a seriously sweet slam dunk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The positioning of the hoop is definitely unnatural... I'd better take note of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like a scrap of paper. I'll get it, sir! Let's see... Oh, there's something written on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It looks like a note from the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and it's for Mr. Portsman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like a scrap of paper. I'll get it, sir! Let's see... Oh, there's something written on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It looks like a note from the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and it's for Mr. Portsman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've already finished examining this area, but it never hurts to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is a basketball hoop doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, didn't this used to be just outside next to the building a long time ago?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So when and why was it moved indoors...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't remember exactly, but I saw one of the officers drag it up here recently.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Drag it!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard that it wouldn't fit in the elevator, so the poor guy had to bring it himself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...All the way up to the 12th floor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Byrde... I'm afraid there's a flaw in your story.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">What!? No way, pal! I mean, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said that you locked up Mr. Portsman's office at around 1:30 AM, correct? However, the master key had already been stolen at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Woooow... Nothing gets by you, Mr. Edgeworth! You saw that contradiction like a pro! I had totally forgot all about that! But thanks to you, I remember it now! You're right! It was around that very time that I realized the master key was missing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I'm a security guard, sir! I couldn't just admit to losing the master key, could I? So I... I pretended to lock up his room... sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You "pretended"?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah, I used my house key and made it look like I was locking up, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So in actuality, you never did re-lock the door, then.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Well, I thought that maybe I could go lock it after I found the key... Come to think of it, I guess the door still hasn't been locked properly...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. You look rather intrigued by something. Care to share?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aw, it's nothing... but I noticed that Mr. Portsman calls his partner "Jim". And the detective in that Sunday night drama, "All My Cops", is named Jim, too! I bet one of them is a big fan of that show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You seem to know a little something about it yourself. I take it you watch it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course! The tight bond of friendship between prosecutor and detective is great, sir! But it's nothing compared to the super strong friendship we have, ho ho ho.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Friendship", Detective? I think you're mistaking it with "pity".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-How can you say that, sir!? And after all we've been through, too... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About Ms. Byrde...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way she's the killer! Please don't tell me you buy into that accusation, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rest assured I think she's innocent. However, I need to ask her a few things regarding her security guard position.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, if you're only asking, that's OK. Just stand next to her and then touch the Talk Button. Then you two can talk about whatever topic you pick. When you want to ask her about evidence, all you have to do is Present it. After you choose what to show her, touch "Present" again, and off you two go! I recommend showing different people different things. You'd be surprised by what they say!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you for the explanation, though I don't recall asking for one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, just so you know, sir, you can show ME evidence in the same way, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do believe it's time to get down to business and ask some questions of Ms. Byrde.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ignored again... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering about the investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I've been waiting for this! Let a real, seasoned pro teach you how it's done!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A real seasoned pro? Of instant noodle cuisine, perhaps.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know that you can always check out the really important spots in more detail, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And if the area is too big, you can always use the Arrow Buttons at the bottom, right? Oh, but don't worry, sir. The Arrows only show up when you need to use them to see more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I knew that as well.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">AND! When you think there's a contradiction or something unusual, try Deduction! First, you line up your cursor with the suspicious-looking area. Then touch "Deduce" and choose your poison, I mean, evidence. When you've settled on a piece, you've gotta Present it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm pretty sure I already knew that as well, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, if you can remember all that, then welcome to the world of pros! I dub you, "Ace Investigator"! Class dismissed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And all I wanted was an update about the investigation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I love basketball! I play all the time when I'm off duty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You should see me dribbling, faking, and weaving like a pro with my trusty coat on, sir! They call me the "Green Supernova"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He wears that tattered rag of a jacket even on his days off?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Poking around in this hallway has actually paid off quite handsomely.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh...? H-How so, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In a variety of different ways... I think it's time we had a little chat... ...with the real culprit of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Y-You know who the real killer is!? Wow, Mr. Edgeworth!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As long as my logic is sound, then yes... The mastermind behind this murder is none other than Mr. Portsman.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Whaaaaaaaaaat!? Mr. Portsman!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I knew it! That's exactly what my logic senses were telling me, too! I suspected it was him from the instant he accused Maggey of being the killer, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That is anything but logical.</thought> Lady and gentleman. Prepare yourselves. Come what may, it's time to knock on Truth's Door.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Mr. Portsman! I've finished processing the bloody letters, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Alright! Let me take a gander at it! Pass it here! OK, looking good! You there! Take good care of this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gwwwwoooooooooooooooaaar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, if it isn't Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">End of the line for you, Portsman. We've got you now!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Call off your dog, Mr. Edgeworth. Is this some kind of joke?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's no joke. We know, Mr. Jacques Portsman, that you are the guilty party in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...! You must be pretty upset, getting chased out of your own room. I'd be mad, too. So I guess you can stay... If you promise to stay out of our way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You intend to hide your crime under the guise of a prosecutor doing his job? Hmph, I can see right through the unsightly, paper-thin mask you wear upon your cowl.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ha ha. Who'd have ever thought it would come to this? Actually, come to think of it, your mentor was Manfred von Karma, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">The legendary prosecutor who never lost a single case for 40 long years. But there was always this... incessant chatter about forged evidence with that guy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Really teaches me that I've got to stay on the lookout for false accusations, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you done trying to play mind games with me, because they won't work. The only thing you should be using that mouth of yours for now is explaining yourself. Although that, too, will only dig your hole deeper. Either way, your game is up.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, aren't we full of ourselves? Even though you have yet to prove anything.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I have no idea what sort of hair-brained idea you have in mind, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but we are not finished, yet.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Boy you're stubborn. I suppose you're basing your accusations on something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll show you what I'm basing my accusation on... with evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I have no idea what sort of hair-brained idea you have in mind, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My accusation is a hair-brained idea, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You tell me. I'd say it is. After all...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...there's a mountain of evidence that points away from me being the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? And what, pray tell, kind of evidence are we talking about here?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Jim was my partner, so you can't say I had a motive for killing him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And...? That's it? That's not even an anthill, let alone a mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">But it's more than enough, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Might I recommend that you review what the word "evidence" means.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It doesn't change the fact that the evidence doesn't point to me as the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Besides, how, may I ask, do you propose I unlocked your door and got in here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, I believe I have already shown how earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Your speculations mean nothing, as I still insist that I could not gain access to your room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do now? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim to have had no way to open my door, however, is that really the honest truth?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ha ha! Alright, I'll humor you. Go ahead, shoot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well, then. I propose that you used this to open my door!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............? And how do you propose I used this object to open your door?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You... That is...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's OK. I know when someone's just grasping at straws.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Gnnnrk! <thought>What was it that Mr. Portsman used to gain entry into my office? I'd better take another look in my Organizer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I need to gather a bit more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">What's wrong? Don't tell me all you wanted to do was find fault with my flawless logic?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Look, I feel bad doing this to you, but I've got work to do, so we're done here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Oh? And why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because there is a flaw in your reasoning.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Are you calling me a liar?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So? Where's your proof? The saying, "Evidence is everything" isn't limited to just the courtroom, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You need not remind me. I'll show you all the evidence you want in time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you were able to open my office door. With the master key, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wait, wait, wait. Hold on for a sec. I never laid a finger on that key, as you already know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. You were able to open my door without lifting a single finger. Well, maybe you did, but only to direct.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. You used your finger to direct this person to open my door with the key!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You asked this person to open the door for you!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...Let me ask this in return! How and why would I have the master key in my possession? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Aaargh! That was careless! Stay calm and think about it one more time. The answer is nearby, I just know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So, what were you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You asked this person to open the door for you!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...Let me ask this in return! How and why would that person have the master key? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Aaargh! That was careless! Stay calm and think about it one more time. The answer is nearby, I just know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So, what were you saying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You had asked Ms. Byrde to open your own office door for you, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yeah, I kind of forgot my key at home. Happens a bit too often for my taste, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the room you had Ms. Byrde open at that time was not your own, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You have quite the imagination. But why don't we ask the girl herself whose door she opened, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Um... I'm certain that it was Mr. Portsman's door, sir. I checked the number plate to make sure I was opening the right door, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">See, Ms. Byrde backs up my story.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yet, what if you had mislead her, to fool her into thinking what you wanted?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hah! And how do you suppose I did that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By switching the number plates on our doors, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's right! They do slide out pretty easily!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Furthermore, you then used one other thing to give a very strong impression... ...that the door she was opening was yours and not, in fact, mine. <thought>What was it that Mr. Portsman used to make Ms. Byrde think that it was his room?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............? What's wrong, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Even I wouldn't get tricked by something like that, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I suppose not...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Was Maggey really mislead, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe so, and Mr. Portsman used this to give her the wrong impression!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">What!? The basketball hoop, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's quite the peculiar fixture in any hallway, let alone a hallway in this building. Which is why it left an unusually strong impression on you. It's an object perfectly suited to sit just outside the office of a peculiar prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Gwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">That's very true, sir! Because there was a basketball hoop sitting there... ...I thought the door I was opening had to be Mr. Portsman's!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are signs that the hoop has been moved. To sit it in front of my office, to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I...I see. So that's how you throw suspicion on people. Thanks for the tip. But I think your conjecture is a little off the race track.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Now you're just spouting nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he intends to claim his innocence to the end, does he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I'm as pure and innocent as my jacket. And Ms. Byrde is as dirty and guilty as the jacket she wears.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">My jacket's not dirty, I'll have you know! I just washed it yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please calm down, for I intend to show who is the one truly covered in slime here.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Now you're just spouting nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nonsense, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yes. Because I'm telling the truth here.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I had the girl open my office door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Using the master key, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Sure. You have a problem with that? That IS what the master key is for, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps we should place it in an elaborate labyrinth of some sort for people like you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">After that, I was in my room the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what were you doing in your office?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I was doing my usual training regiment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Training regiment? Were you going through your law books from start to finish?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Mainly batting practice and some weights. Oh, and I jog when I get the chance.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, you must be the buffest prosecutor we have!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...With the weakest legal muscles, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I was doing my usual workout so...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You don't have a single reason to suspect me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think I've given you quite a few reasons, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">B-But none of those would stand up on their own!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then what about all the evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">It's all circumstantial! No judge would convict on such flimsy evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He seems to be trembling a little... One more little push... All I have to do is find the flaw in his testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That, was a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wh-What are you talking about!? How was that a lie!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a note that the victim left for you, Mr. Portsman.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">A note?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was left under your door. Or did you not notice? And right here, it says, "but you're out."</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were not in your room when the victim came to call on you. So then, where were you and what were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shall I explain it in full detail for you? You were busy snooping around in my room, the very room you had Ms. Byrde open for you!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Th-That's just nonsense! You have no evidence that I made the girl open your door for me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, but I do. I have very decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">N-No way!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I think you need to take a good look at this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You know... Nope, I've got nothing. Getting sleepy, are we? I guess it is getting kind of late.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argh! I'll have you know I'm wide awake! And I'll prove it to you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had your door dusted for prints.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">My door? Hah, what for? Come on, I bet you didn't find anything. You sure are good at wasting time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're right. I didn't find anything, and definitely not Ms. Byrde's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Her prints? What do they have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's put it this way. If she really was the one who opened your door... ...then her prints should naturally be on the doorknob she touched!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Aaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Further, all of the prints on my office door's knob have been wiped clean off. I can only assume it's because Ms. Byrde's fingerprints were on it. Don't you think it's time you gave up your charade? We know you stole into my office with the intent of stealing something from me. And Detective Faith found you out. Possibly because he heard sounds coming from a room whose occupant was on leave. Mr. Portsman, you killed Mr. Faith to silence him. And I had the misfortune to return when I did; you had to threaten me as you escaped.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I said when you had the gun to my back... ...no one gets away with committing murder in my office.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">.........Heh heh. Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Haaaaa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And just what's so funny, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, that look of stiff seriousness on the face of this office's finest prosecutor... ...as he makes a huge mistake in accusing me is simply too much to bear. There's just nothing else like it in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Mr. Edgeworth just explained it all, and he even backed it up! You're the murderer! Stop trying to be slippery and just admit to the crime already!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And as I said earlier, it's all so circumstantial, so full of conjecture. You say you checked my doorknob for prints? Well, I can readily confess that I had wiped that knob down well.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I'm a little obsessive-compulsive, you see. I didn't want to touch a doorknob that you had touched. Which is why I wiped the knob down as soon as I could after you opened the door. After that, it makes perfect sense that only Jim's and my own prints would be on there.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You! You made that up just now, didn't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Furthermore, as for the note Jim left for me, do you know exactly when that was? For all we know, he could've left it there before I arrived at the office. Like, early evening, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying you failed to notice a note in your doorway?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hey, even geniuses fail at times. I was probably too preoccupied by work-related matters, although that's no excuse.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Now that's just a flat-out lie! There's no way you didn't notice a note that size!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, but you can't prove that, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Say something, Mr. Edgeworth! Back me up here, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... Portsman makes a good point. I can't prove that he didn't simply overlook it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Besides, I have an airtight alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Airtight, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I only realized that I had one just now as we were talking. I guess it would've been better for all of us if I had told you sooner!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">If memory serves, you came back to this office at around 2 AM, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think it's that perfect!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Like I said, I don't care. Ask around all you like! You'll see for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir, yes, sir! I'll go check out his alibi, sir! Be right back!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth, sir! I think we're in trouble! It's just like Mr. Portsman said! The guys down in Criminal Affairs said they saw him at around 2 AM!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You see?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>All of the evidence points to him being the culprit. So there must be a contradictory point in his alibi somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">If memory serves, you came back to this office at around 2 AM, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are correct; it was around 2 AM...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Are you sure? It's really important to me that you're spot on with the time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I remember checking my watch then, and make no mistake, it was 2.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ooh! Giving testimony like a pro! OK, so you came back to your office at 2...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And it was then that you had that unfortunate confrontation at gunpoint with the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is as you say, however...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yes, however, you are the only one who claims to have bumped into the culprit. So tell me, did you see the person's face? Was it me who you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It was pitch black, so I couldn't actually see.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Oh, come now. I'm sure you saw something! Try a little harder why don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm beginning to feel like I'M the one being interrogated here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Oh well, it doesn't matter if you remember or not. It only matters that you ran into the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">But at exactly that time, I was down in Criminal Affairs!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you paid the Criminal Affairs Department a visit...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yup! Right after I left the Prosecutors' Building, I headed straight for the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ask around. I'm sure the other detectives will corroborate my story. It's the perfect alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, well, we did go and ask around to confirm your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And it was just as I said, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Yes, sir. A number of detectives said that they saw you at around that time.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">See! I have the perfect alibi! That's the ace I had up my sleeve.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Portsman's alibi may seem perfect at first glance... ...but I know there's a hole in it somewhere. All I need to do is "Press" him a little and see what comes of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">What's wrong? Why the sudden sullen look on your face?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Can't you say anything back, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Heh, I think we've reached the end of the line and it's time to get off this crazy train. You there!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Please escort the young lady out. But remember, be gentle.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Maggey!!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Detective Gumshoe!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there... nothing I can do? There must be a way to turn this situation around! If I only had a clue... Did I miss something that can help me cast doubt on his alibi (Mr Portsman's alibi – The intruder I met could not have been Portsman. Then who could it have been?</thought>? I need to calmly think this through one more time, and with Logic!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Evidence points to the shelves being disturbed once before and once after the murder. But who is to say that the person who did it the second time is the same as the first? </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were two bullets left at the scene of the crime. One that robbed Mr. Faith of his life... ...and one that nearly robbed me of my jacket. However, the murder weapon only shows signs of being fired once. Meaning that it is entirely possible... ...that a second gun was used in my office tonight. But, seeing as how the killer had to steal Mr. Faith's gun... ...I doubt the killer had another gun up their sleeve. Therefore... ...the second gun could've been the property of an entirely different person.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which could mean... ...that there was another person <thought>Another visitor – Maybe the victim and his killer weren't the only visitors to my office tonight.</thought> who paid a visit to my office tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If, indeed, there were two culprits... ...then that resolves the contradiction behind our murder weapon. Despite the fact that there are two bullets here in this room... ...the murder weapon only shows signs of being fired once. Leaving the possibility that the other bullet was fired from the other visitor's gun. Furthermore...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Supposing that there was yet another visitor tonight... ...that would also resolve the issue of why my shelves were upended twice. We know that the shelves were disturbed once before and once after the murder... ...so it shouldn't be much of a stretch to think that it was the work of two different people. Once by the person who stole the victim's gun and then killed him with it... ...and once again after the murder by our second culprit... ...who was the owner of the second gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we suppose that the second culprit's gun was the one that was pointed at my back...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman. It seems that I need to amend my assumptions regarding this case.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Great! So you've finally come to your senses.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir! What are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This has been a big misunderstanding on my part from the start. I had assumed that the person I ran into was the killer, but that may not be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person I ran into was just your average thief.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A thief...? But, sir doesn't that cause some sort of contradiction in the facts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not at all. It simply means that the killer was someone else. And it means that in actuality, two culprits stole into my office tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean TWO!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It explains both why my shelves were disturbed twice and how there were two guns. Mr. Portsman tricked Ms. Byrde and gained entry into my office.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Now you're just leading the argument. You still don't have any actual proof, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could please go along with my hypothetical scenario for now, Mr. Portsman. In the end, if you really are innocent, you should have nothing to worry about.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Grr...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, returning to my scenario, Mr. Portsman was out to steal something from me... ...which is why he checked my secret safe and ransacked my shelves. This is the first time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So then... this would be when the files were put back in the wrong order, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. And then, just when he was about to look somewhere else... ...who should walk in but his own partner, Mr. Faith.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why did Mr. Faith come into your room, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He probably had business with Mr. Portsman, which is why he was in the area. But that's when he noticed sounds coming from my office would be my guess.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oh! Because you were supposed to be away, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And he must've thought it was odd, so he came into this office to check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. And as a detective, that was the right thing to do.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">But when he came in, he found his own partner standing there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because it was Mr. Portsman, Mr. Faith probably let his guard down. But Mr. Portsman was not so merciful as to let him leave alive. He waited for a chance and stole Mr. Faith's gun from him, and then...! He killed him. He silenced Mr. Faith for catching him in the act of stealing.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was the moment in which the first shot was fired, the one that landed in my files. Following that, Mr. Portsman wiped the gun down and left it behind as he made his exit. He could afford to do that because he had also left the fake dying message behind.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're such a complicated troublemaker, you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, if things were as simple as that, then all would be solved. However... ...there was yet another visitor to my room, and this is where it gets complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">There was another...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Visitor, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and this other person's objective was also to steal something from me. Now then, even after Mr. Portsman left, the door to my office remained unlocked. However, this new visitor had no way of knowing that, and so... ...they stole the master key from the security guard's room... ...and then entered my room and searched through my shelves. This was the second time they were disturbed, and it seems the thief found their prize.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The stolen 0 file, right, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. Only, just as the thief was about to leave with the file, I appeared. The thief then threatened me with their own gun, and made their escape. The second bullet was fired during that brief encounter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So the shelves getting messed up twice and the two bullets... It was all because two different people were doing those things at two different times!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. So now do you see, Mr. Portsman? The person I met was just a thief, and was not, in fact, Mr. Faith's killer! Your alibi for the time frame in which I ran into the other person is now irrelevant... ...because we now know that the murder took place during the first culprit's visit!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's so funny, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Absolutely splendid! Your scenario explains everything!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course it does! It's Mr. Edgeworth, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">But you know, it still doesn't change the fact that it's all circumstantial.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Supposing if, and that's a big "if", your theory is right... ...it would indeed render my alibi, which has withstood scrutiny, mind you, irrelevant. But there is still one defining point of your argument for which you have no evidence. Your supposition that I was the "first visitor".</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Grrrrrrr! Mr. Edgeworth! You can't let him get away with that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........But he has a point. I have absolutely no proof at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Don't say that, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I don't believe this! Don't worry Maggey, I'll do something if I must!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You know something? I find your attitude to be somewhat peculiar, Mr. Edgeworth. If the person you met really was just a plain ol' thief... ...then why is that person not your main suspect? That is, if your theory is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That thief you ran into should be your real suspect, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you think we should be out there looking for the thief?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Of course! Now isn't the time to be wasting time on dead-end discussions!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think it's at all "dead-ended". I find your alibi to be fascinating. Let's continue where we left off, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know he's lying. I know he was here, at the scene of the crime. I just have to find a way to prove it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">That thief you ran into should be your real suspect, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, no, I wouldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wh-Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's elementary. The dying message, of course. Mr. Faith's killer very clearly left those letters on the spines of those files... And it was after they were on there that the thief stole one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean the 0 files, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's how we also know the letters themselves were a set-up, and not from Mr. Faith. If the thief was the killer, do you think they would try to undermine themselves?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Aaaah! Err, maybe the killer just didn't think of that either? Yes, that must be it! Maybe, just maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">We should be out there looking for that thief right now. They might still be nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Once escaped, I highly doubt a thief would linger nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Well, you never know. Maybe they didn't get what they were really after.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? You talk like you know quite a bit about this thief.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, it's nothing like that! I have no idea about anything. After all...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I hate to repeat myself, but as I've already said, I was training in my room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But according to Mr. Faith's note...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Hold on, I thought we already cleared that up. Didn't we say that Jim left that note for me in the early evening? If you have proof that he left it at a different time, say, just before he was murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't have any, no.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You see! So I insist again that I was in my office the entire time...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And when Jim came to deliver some evidence to me, I was down at Criminal Affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't you go there with Ji... Mr. Faith?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Ah, that's because he said he was tired and was going to take a quick nap. You know those sofas in the hallway? He likes to sleep on those. It's one of his habits.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what of the evidence he brought?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">They were related to yesterday's case. Just two items: a gun and a pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Interesting. This piece of testimony seems too crucial to let slip through the cracks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">He brought me two items, a gun and a pendant, that are related to yesterday's case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A gun and a pendant...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Yes, this gun, which was the murder weapon... ...and this pendant, which belonged to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why were you taking them to Criminal Affairs?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">There was something in a past case file I wanted to compare these two to. But all this has nothing to do with this case right now. Anyway, I believe you'll find the long paper trail I left to be to your satisfaction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, this is all matching up with what Detective Gumshoe found out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So I can't be expected to know what happened around here after I left.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't expect you to know, can I?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Nope. But I guess you can expect me to take a guess based on logical deductions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Then let's see you deduce.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Jim waited for me to leave, and then stole the master key. For the purpose of sneaking into your room, of course. And that's when Ms. Byrde caught him red-handed... and the murder occurred. It's all exactly as I had laid out earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know he's lying. I know he was here, at the scene of the crime. I just have to find a way to prove it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Only two pieces? I believe the proper phrase here is, "you fail."</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">E-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You fail as a prosecutor, Mr. Portsman, as you intend to keep evidence hidden from me.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">What are you talking about? I-I haven't hidden anything from you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, here's a piece I think you should read. Carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Ah! It says that Mr. Faith was bringing three pieces!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and this is the victim's real dying message to you, Mr. Portsman.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">He...! I can't believe...! To get tripped up by simple arithmetic...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where is the missing piece of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...I... It's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You have it, don't you? Only the guilty would make such a face. Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't have to say it, sir! I'll pat the guy down from head to toe!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Wh--! Don't come any closer! I'm warning you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is all part of the investigation, PAL, so don't even think about stopping me!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Noooooooooooooooo!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! What's this!? He had this on him, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Despite what you said, it would appear that you do have something to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why would he hide something like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. There's only one reason why anyone would hide evidence of this caliber. Because it would unequivocally point to that person himself as the real killer.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">.........Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's examine this video tape in a little more detail! For the section of the tape that will drive the last nail into his coffin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The KG-8 Incident...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's a police case number, sir! Does that mean this video is evidence from that case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interesting... However, what's recorded on this isn't what's important right now. Let's give the casing a thorough once over.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! That's blood, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I believe this is what the "good prosecutor" was trying to hide from us! This blood is still fresh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean, this might be Detective Faith's blood!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">...N-N-N-N-No! No! You've got it all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, no amount of denial can save you. We have but to run a blood test to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You told us that you had received evidence from the victim earlier. Now you will tell us when and how did the victim's blood find its way onto this video.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah! It's totally suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was it at the moment of his death!? Did Detective Faith have this video tape on his personage when you killed him!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You know very well there's no way to prove that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not even if we were to examine this tape for fingerprints?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Gnaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I had to take a guess... ...I'd say that the only ones on here would belong to the murderous you, and Mr. Faith!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">No! Impossible! I--! I'm--! Iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiieeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Portsman has been placed under arrest for the murder of Detective Buddy Faith, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And the results we got back from the lab techs on the tape turned out to be real solid, sir! The bloodwork came back, and it was definitely Mr. Faith's blood on there. And as a bonus, they were also able to lift a few of Mr. Faith's fingerprints as well!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Thank you so very much, Mr. Edgeworth! I still can't believe I got to see your cool deduction skills outside the courtroom! I'm impressed beyond words, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was nothing. I'm just sorry you got caught up in a murder in my office. Please accept my apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Aww, it was nothing. Really. Compared to what I've been through, I mean! I consider myself lucky that it was only a burglary and a murder this time, sir! If it had been a hold-up, or a hostage situation, I'd have thrown my hands up in the air. I think I'm finally rising up from a "Goddess of Misfortune" to just an "Unlucky Person"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something tells me we should have hired a different person for security detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know something, sir? That Mr. Portsman really was one corrupt prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why would you say he was "corrupt"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I heard that there were a number of suspicious things related to his court cases. There's even rumors about how some of the evidence he uses is forged, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Forged evidence, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And they say he even decided not to prosecute a few cases for some really vague reasons.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Oooh! That guy was a complete disgrace to the entire profession!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We never did get around to asking what his reason was for breaking into my office.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... Whenever we got near that topic, he just clammed up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Although, we can be pretty certain that it was to steal something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is just between you and me, sir, but... ...there's a rumor that some sort of huge organization is involved behind the scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Well, well...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With Mr. Portsman not willing to divulge anything, it certainly lends credence to that rumor. ...It would seem that we haven't heard the last of this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Then Mr. Portsman isn't the bad guy!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I didn't say that. But rather, that there are still many more mysteries for us to solve. For example, we still haven't figured out the significance to this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, sir... I don't think there's any mystery left to that piece...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You... might be right there...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I think you've solved the case already, Mr. Edgeworth. The only thing left that we still don't know about is maybe this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the 0-series file. The significance of which we have yet to fully comprehend.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person who stole this file... the other villain of the night...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Yeah, I wonder who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what happened to the stolen pages? <thought>I wonder... Who in the world was it that held me up at gunpoint?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I came across this while I was processing your office earlier, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This card--!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What is it, sir? Is that a bird or something on there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not just any bird... It is the mark of the raven. A three-legged raven. Even you should know what this is, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! It's about that thing, isn't it? That Great Thief everyone's talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it is the mark of the Great Thief "Yatagarasu"! Under the mark of a legendary bird, the Yatagarasu is noble to the end, a modern Robin Hood. Labeled "mysterious" and "phantom-like", the Yatagarasu appears and vanishes at will. Though we don't know much about this thief's ultimate goal, we do know the targets. The Yatagarasu likes to find and make public, evidence of corrupt dealings of all sorts. The theft is always performed in silence and always with perfection. Once a target is chosen, no dramatic calling card or announcement is sent forth. Instead, the chosen corporation is infiltrated without even the target noticing. Some days later, the evidence that was found is sent out to the mass media... ...along with this single card. Although, it has been a while since the Yatagarasu's last appearance...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth! Look, something's written on the back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Let me see!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's the location of where the thief put the stolen files!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the person who stole the contents of the file was the Yatagarasu...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Yatagarasu". "Organization". Quite a few key words are popping up in this mystery. The murder in my office... The return of the Great Thief "Yatagarasu"... Looking back, I can't say I didn't see these events coming... ...for they were heralded by the incidents that began to occur two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing of interest here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Tsk... Where has the time gone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! You must be really worn out from your trip. Are you jet-lagged? You really should go home and take it easy, sir! Remember, a man's gotta have his health!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand... However, I can't allow this case to go unsolved.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nope! You shouldn't push it, sir! Leave it to me! I'll get to the bottom of it! I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few days passed, and as I suspected, the case went unsolved. Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Looks like even the mighty "Genius Prosecutor" is no match for me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I have already figured out who the real culprit behind this caper is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Sorry, but I'm going to have to ask you to get out of my crime scene, Mr. Edgeworth. ...No offense or anything, but you're cramping my game.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I must object to your line of logic!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">And which part do you have an objection to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's... Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Stay cool, Mr. Edgeworth! You're no good when you're all flustered.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">The detective's right, for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>H-How did it come to this!? Calm down, Miles. Listen carefully and think everything through a bit more rationally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would behoove you to take a good look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I see it, but I fail to see how it has anything to do with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-Is that so...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">You're not at the top of your game today, are you, Mr. Genius Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't allow him to set the pace here. I must remain calm. Only by doing so can I find the fatal flaw in his reasoning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Portsman. There is a large flaw in your logic...</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Really? I think it holds up rather well, actually. What do you think is wrong with it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! Um, nothing. Let's move on.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This isn't like you at all, sir! Concentrate!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That was careless of me. I can't afford to do that or the truth will slowly slip away. Remain calm, Miles! It's the only way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Unfortunately, your faulty logic was only able to carry you so far. And now I'm afraid I have to place Detective Gumshoe under arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Please do something! Get me out of this!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh! Is this the best I can do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">So, how about it? By now, even you must see that the girl is clearly the culprit. You hear that, Jim! I finally got the one that did you in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-Hold on there!</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Save your breath. There's no one left to listen to your inane ramblings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You! What are you doing here!? ...Sir.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I've come to announce that the investigation is over. And that the girl is under arrest. Game, set, and match.</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Mr. Edgeworth! Please, help me, sir!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nnrgh! Is there nothing I can do!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">I know you'd love to pin this on me, but swing and a miss, Edgeworth. Swing and a miss.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">E-Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Portsman">Look, I have an alibi. If you have evidence to the contrary, I'd sure like to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must be a way for me to squash Portsman's alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Portsman">In the meantime, I'm taking the girl with no alibi into custody, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
</xml>