<xml>
<title>Turnabout Beginnings</title>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ugh... I'm so nervous. I feel like I'm going to die. I never should've accepted this case...</thought> Eeeeeeek! ...Ah! G-G-Good morning! <thought>Don't be so jumpy, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I-I din't do nuttin'! I swear! I din't kill nobody!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Terry Fawles... ...My first client. Sentenced to death 5 years ago, and now... a prison escapee.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Just relax, Mia! Make small talk and try to relax him!</thought> ...Err, umm... So why did you escape anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Ah. Ah. UGGA!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eeeeek! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...Ugh. I din't do nuttin'! I din't kill nobody! I never... I never lie! I din't escape from nowhere!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Err... But, Mr. Fawles... The police just recaptured you two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Ugh. Sorry. I told a little lie.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">But anyway, I din't do it! I never killed nobody!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, sorry for asking but... You're on death row, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Uh. Uh... UGGA!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eeeeeek! I'm really, really sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">They sentenced me to die 5 years ago! But I was tricked I tell you! That woman! She lied in her testimony! ...That's why I got the death penalty! I swear it! I din't kill her! I could never do that!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Two days ago, he escaped from the police wagon when it crashed... Then about 8 hours later... A policewoman was murdered before the police could recapture him. The police believe that Terry Fawles did it.</thought> Umm... After you escaped, did you meet a policewoman?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Yeah... I did. ...She's the reason I escaped.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So that much is true... He did meet with the victim.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">But I din't kill her! She was alive when I left! She was alive...! It-It's true!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I can trust him... right? I mean, I should...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ha...! You're not going to figure out the truth by just staring at the guy...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-You're... Why are you here?</line>
<line speaker="???">I came to see how our little kitten was doing all alone in the big, scary lion's den. ...I thought maybe you'd like someone to play with.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Err, where is Mr. Grossberg?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha...! That old man is probably still in bed. I bet he's clutching an empty bottle and mumbling in his sleep. Aren't I good enough? After all, it's me... Diego Armando!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I didn't say... So, Diego Armando, the finest attorney at Grossberg Law Offices, is here for me...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">No, no, no... You've got it all wrong! Today, YOU'RE the finest! After all, it took an amazing amount of guts to take this case! Imagine... An escaped death row convict for a first client!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yeah, err... Th-Thanks. <thought>I sure wish I could get out of it though!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Relax. I just heard some good news. The prosecutor for today is fresh out of his diapers as well.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">However... Unlike a certain somebody who I won't mention... ...he's earned the reputation as a "genius" since beginning his law career.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>G-Genius...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Well, it's about time to head in, Kitten. Sharpen those claws of yours. It's go time!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>A solitary confinement cell for the condemned must be the world's loneliest place. ...And that's what my client ran away from. Every other lawyer gave up on him... But not me. When I saw those overflowing eyes and heard that simple, child-like voice... I just had the feeling that he was telling the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Terry Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="???">The prosecution has been ready for a while, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I understand the lawyers for both sides are newcomers...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Y-Yes, Your Honor. I'm Mia Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Miles Edgeworth... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you're the new prosecutor everyone is talking about, eh? They say you joined the prosecutor's office at quite an early age.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At 20... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">I guess our little kitten hasn't earned herself much of a reputation yet, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Come on, Mia! You can't lose! Not to someone younger than you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Young people running a trial. I'm not too sure how I feel about that. ...Now then, the defendant in this case is currently a felon on death row. Two days ago, he escaped from a police wagon. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">But the defendant is not on trial for escaping prison. On the day that the defendant escaped, a policewoman was murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So we're here to determine if Mr. Fawles was responsible for her death...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">You got it, Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, Mr. Edgeworth. Let's hear your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor. It was five years ago. The defendant, Terry Fawles, was sentenced to death in this very court. His crimes were kidnapping, extortion... and murder. The girl he threw off the bridge was only 14 years old.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A truly horrible crime. I remember it well. There was no decisive evidence, so the trial was long and protracted.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. But in the end, what finally decided the case was... ...a certain witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A witness's testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The testimony of Detective Valerie Hawthorne; the person who confronted this criminal. She arrested Mr. Fawles at the scene and later testified against him. She said she witnessed Mr. Fawles throw his young victim into the river. For those who are not aware, Eagle River is well-known for its powerful current. Most bodies that fall in are never recovered...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So Ms. Hawthorne's testimony was the one that put him away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That policewoman you just mentioned... That wouldn't be...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. The victim. The same woman that was killed 2 days ago... Police Sergeant... Valerie Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aha...! I see... The man who was sentenced to death based on her testimony escaped two days ago... ...with only one thing on his mind. To take revenge against the woman who convicted him. ... Hmm... Aha! The truth is becoming clear to me now!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes... It's quite obvious that the defendant is guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Wait a minute! That's not right! At least hear the case before you decide on the outcome, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Grrrngh... Watch yourself, Ms. Fey! I'm not sure I care for your word choice, or your tone of voice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Young people these days simply don't know how to respect their elders.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Why you...! You're even younger than me, you hypocrite!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Edgeworth, please call your first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I call the detective who was in charge of the initial investigation of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness... State your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gumshoe. Dick Gumshoe. I'm the homicide detective in charge of the case, sir! I finally got promoted to the detective division half a year ago!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't believe anyone asked you about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, ma'am! You got any idea how much work it takes... ......</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You... Y-You're really gorgeous...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, seriously... My heart... It's aching for you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. Pull yourself together and try to be professional. Otherwise... I'll write you up on contempt so quick that something other than your heart will ache!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Urk... O-OK, I-I got it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now, Detective. Tell us about the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Right away! The victim was Sergeant Valerie Hawthorne, a veteran on the police force. She was stabbed in the back with a knife and died from excessive blood loss.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That much is already stated in the autopsy report. The court would like to hear more details about the incident itself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! I gotcha! OK! Let's take a look at this aerial map of the area here! This is a sketch of Dusky Bridge, an old suspension bridge. And the river that runs under there is Eagle River. The victim and the defendant met there... On top of the bridge. After stabbing her in the back, the killer carried the victim back to his car. He was recaptured at a police checkpoint as he was trying to make his getaway, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was the victim's blood found on the bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim, Sergeant Valerie Hawthorne, was wearing a thick coat, sir. Unfortunately, no traces of blood were found on the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Edgeworth. I warn you that I absolutely despise conjecture. If there was no blood on the bridge, then you have no proof that they even met there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. If you would listen to the testimony we have prepared, I'm sure you'll be convinced. The two of them most certainly did meet on the bridge that day...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, Mr. Edgeworth... I'm not sure I like you wagging your finger at me as though I were some hoser! Detective, proceed with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Here we go, Mia! Hang on...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">OK now... Listen carefully, Kitten. One little mistake and this guy will drink you for morning tea! Trust me and get ready.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">On the day of the incident, an unknown person phoned the sergeant and asked to meet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, you certainly have established the importance of the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, would the defense please hurry up and proceed with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor! C-C-Cross-examination... Coming right up!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hey, hey! Settle down there, Kitten! If you keep trembling like that, you're gonna make me spill my coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I-I'm not t-trembling! It-It-It's just cold in here!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">The courtroom can be a cold battlefield alright. Especially... for a beginner.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I don't need you to worry about me...! I mean... I mean, the defendant, the witness... everyone's a beginner in here!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! You got me there. But maybe you should keep your claws out, and show them what you've got... Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It's OK, Mia. Stay calm... Just remember those court procedure videos you stayed up all last night watching!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">On the day of the incident, an unknown person phoned the sergeant and asked to meet.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This "unknown person"... You have no idea who it might be, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, but I'm afraid I do!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The one who called Sergeant Hawthorne was the defendant, Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Whaaat! The defendant...! The defendant called her!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sergeant Hawthorne was a very thorough person, sir! She left a note about her phone call with Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A note...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, a top-secret memo that she left on her desk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... According to this note, it seems the one who called her to the bridge was indeed... ...the defendant, Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Nngh! <thought>Whose bright idea was it to keep that note from me!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Looks like the judge is even more sure of his verdict now. Listen up! Never ask a question if you don't already know the answer!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It's that detective's fault! He's the one that said, "unknown person"...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey now! Don't make that face at me! I just said it that way 'cause the prosecutor told me to!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Was that... a trap...? ...With that cute face, I didn't expect him to be so sneaky.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sergeant Hawthorne went to Dusky Bridge at the designated time and met with Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">A bridge up in the mountains? But why meet there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Because it is a very important place to the defendant, that's why.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you remember, 5 years ago, the defendant kidnapped a young girl. He was chased onto a bridge... And it was there that he killed his hostage. And the place where all of this occurred is, of course, Dusky Bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The very place where Sergeant Hawthorne arrested and handcuffed Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Returning to the scene of the crime... How nostalgic.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And that's where she was brutally murdered, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Was the body of the victim discovered right away?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. We were really on the ball. We found the criminal within one hour of the murder. It was great! We even got to say, "Don't move! We've got you surrounded!"</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...Wait a second. Isn't there something weird about that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">The location was a suspension bridge, up in the mountains. So how did they find out about the crime so quickly...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sergeant Hawthorne must have mentioned the phone call to someone else, right?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! If that's what had happened, then she wouldn't have been killed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She never mentioned the phone call from Mr. Fawles. But... She left a note on her desk about it. If only I had noticed it earlier... Maybe she'd still be alive.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I wonder why she didn't mention the phone call to anyone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The criminal stuffed her body into his car trunk and tried to make a getaway.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles had a car, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that bridge is way up in the mountains, ma'am. The defendant and the victim both went up there by car. I mean, how else, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What! You mean the defendant drove his own car?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, no, of course not. ...It was stolen. He stole it from a young couple that had been waiting at a red light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Car thieves... I'm not sure how I feel about car thieves.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Is this guy sure about how he feels about ANYTHING?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is a photo of the stolen car's trunk. ...Naturally, that's the body of Valerie Hawthorne in there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whoa! That... That doesn't look too comfortable...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The victim... She was stabbed in the back, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! ...For some reason, men always seem to get stabbed in the back...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>We're talking about a woman here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can't tell from this photo, but... ...the knife was stuck in her back nice and firm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The condition of the body when it was discovered is very important information. Detective, was there anything strange or noteworthy in the trunk of the car?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here's a photo of the trunk. But I don't see anything strange, do you? Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What did the defendant have to say about this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What he always says, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I din't do it! I din't do nuttin'!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That's all he says.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Nuttin'"? I wouldn't say he did "nuttin'". At the very least, we know he stole a car!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's just what he always says, Your Honor. And then he always says...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Uh. Sorry. I told a little lie.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, in any case, it seems he was caught and arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Fawles was arrested at a police checkpoint we set up at the base of the mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That certainly is some impressive police work.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, no, actually it was way too close for comfort. We set up that checkpoint just after 5:00 PM... We figured that Mr. Fawles might just try to run.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...What do you mean it was too close for comfort?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The two of them arranged to meet at 4:30 PM. And it takes approximately 30 minutes to go from the bridge to the checkpoint.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hmm... That WAS kinda close. Any later and Mr. Fawles could have slipped right by.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen up, Kitten. There's a big trap waiting for you in that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A t-trap?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Walk into it carelessly, and it'll leave more than just a flesh wound. Fun, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No, it's NOT!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Well, if you want to have any chance at all, you'd better get some more information. And if you're going to get caught in a trap, it's best to get caught early. You can always look for contradictions afterwards. </line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The ever-famous "contradictions". I sure hope I can find some of those...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Witness! ............</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Wh-What is it...? Do you have something to say, Ms. Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'm sorry! I-I totally forgot what I was going to say... This is... This is the first time I've ever had to actually address someone like that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Grrgh... You should have practiced before coming to court! Honestly, Ms. Fey... I'm not sure I like this!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hmph...! Say there, little Kitten, want a piece of my coffee candy?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Candy?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Well, you're still too young to be drinking real coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Grrr... Come on, Mia! Shake it off! You're a lawyer!</thought> Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This photo... You said that there was nothing peculiar about it. ...Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah, that's what I said!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well then, I suggest you take another look at the note written by the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The n-n-note...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It very clearly says, "Wear white scarf for identification."... The caller must have forgotten what the victim looked like. Thus, this special request.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaah... I, umm...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I have one very simple question for you, Detective. Where is the white scarf? I can't seem to find it in this photo...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Well, to be honest, we didn't find it in the trunk, ma'am...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And you stopped there!? You should have looked for it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaaarrrggg...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The caller told her to wear it to identify herself, so I'd expect she did just that! Well, Mr. Edgeworth!? What do you have to say about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* I see the defense is a little... lacking.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The scarf you are searching so desperately for... ...Is it this one, perchance?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Where did you find that, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On Dusky Bridge. I was there first, and decided to conduct my own investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why...? Why didn't you tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I made a decision to keep all pieces of evidence in my personal satchel. It's the safest place I know.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hmph! That hot-shot sure has a flair for the dramatic...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not exactly "white", as the caller requested... But as you can see, it's close enough, for what it was intended for.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... It looks like it spent some time in the mud.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not surprising... It was drizzling on the mountain that day.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Prosecutor Edgeworth... He was intentionally hiding that scarf the whole time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will accept the scarf into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if the attorney for the defense is finished embarrassing herself... ...I'd like to move on with the testimony. That IS alright with you, isn't it, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Boy would I like to wrap this scarf around his smarmy little neck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good. Now, if we're done with this mud-covered scarf business... ...the prosecution moves to establish conclusively, and with hard evidence that... ...Ms. Hawthorne and Mr. Fawles did indeed meet on that bridge that day. Further, we will show exactly what occurred there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That sounds quite promising. I can't wait to hear all about it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Argh... Everything is moving at his whim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Don't forget, Kitten. There's a reason why everyone considers this kid a genius.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>A genius, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, there's an eyewitness who was there when the incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Looking at this photo... ...you really get the sense that this bridge is very high up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is about a 40 feet drop from the bridge to the Eagle River down below.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth, who took this photo anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's just say that it was a well-intentioned third party.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aha! A potential witness! So why isn't this person in the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... They said they absolutely did not want to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The person in question is very delicate, Your Honor. Besides, as long as we have this photo, we see no reason to compel her to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm not sure how I feel about that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, as you can see, Terry Fawles had both the motive and the opportunity. I think it's quite clear at this point what happened on that bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hmm. Aha! The truth is becoming clear to me now!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it's quite obvious. He's clearly guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">N-Not again! That's not fair! I haven't even done my cross-examination yet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What do you mean, "Hmm"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, there's an eyewitness who was there when the incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Who is this eyewitness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's a college student!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A female college student...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! Meaning she's "female" AND a "college student", ma'am! She doesn't do well in front of other people, so I came to testify for her.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Maybe so! But as the attorney for the defense, I have the right to cross-examine her...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the time being, we're not relying on the witness's statements... That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The prosecution has other, more decisive evidence. Our case doesn't rest on the vague testimony of a female college student.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A female college student, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It means she's "female" AND a "college student", sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you absolutely must hear her testimony, you'll have to give us a good reason why.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Grrr...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please tell us about the more decisive evidence in question.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This photo was accidentally taken by the witness. It shows her wearing the scarf, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The victim is wearing a scarf in that photo alright.</thought> So, about the witness who took this photo... What was this person doing all the way in the mountains?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She was taking photos of wild flowers apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are many unusual types of flora on that mountain, Ms. Fey. People in the area say it's because of the spirits that live there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-S-Spirits! Now that you mention it, th-this photo... This cloudy fog-like thing... Is-Is it a ghost!? I-I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, Your Honor, no... I don't think it's a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was drizzling that day; unfortunately, it's a little hard to see what's going on.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Drizzling, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. There was a light rain coming down. The whole place was dreary... ...But not as dreary as the mood that's in this court room right now. Ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Looks like a cold front just moved in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case... The point is that the area was quite damp. There was even some fog.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I even slipped and fell while I was on the bridge. It was really something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, the criminal shoved the victim down from behind and stabbed her in the back!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Is that part of the witness's testimony as well?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course it is. He pushed the victim hard in the back and she fell down right on her stomach!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... ...I remember that happening once myself. It was really broodle.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... <thought>Are you talking about seeing someone get pushed, or were you the one getting pushed? Or does it mean that you pushed someone down like that once...? With his mind-boggling tales and the way he said, "brutal", I wonder if he's Canadian...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Save your nasty look for the right person.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">...Take a look. Poor baby... The Court Record seems to have wet itself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hey! Watch where you spill your coffee! <thought>The Court Record, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That must have been when the scarf fell off.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So in other words, there was a struggle between the criminal and the victim, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what the witness said. Well. It looks like she didn't remember about the scarf. But from what she said, it sounded like a pretty violent fight, ma'am.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The area was wet from rain. The bridge was probably wet, too. Which would explain why the scarf was all covered in mud, but... There's something about this testimony that's still bothering me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Heh, talk about a surprise. I had no idea there was a photo.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">S-So what do I do...&#160;?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">You really still believe him? Mr. Crybaby, I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course I do!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hmph...! So the little kitten believes in fairy tales, huh... In that case, the answer is obvious. If what you believe is the truth... ...then that means that somewhere, hidden in that testimony, is a contradiction. One huge contradiction waiting to be discovered. ...That's your chance.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So at the time of the crime, there was a light drizzle coming down, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and fog, too. Just a generally soggy atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, I have evidence that doesn't go with the soggy atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But this is a photo of the victim's body that was found in the car trunk.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Considering the conditions at the scene of the crime, something isn't right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well by all means... Please enlighten us as to what isn't right! What is it about this photo of the trunk that doesn't fit with the conditions that day?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally, the answer is... right around HERE! ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems to me that Ms. Fey could use a trunk herself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One that she could hide all her bitter memories from this trial in, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho ho ho... You truly are a genius... A genius of sarcasm and word-play.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oops! It looks like I really put my foot in my mouth that time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Just relax. Lick your wounds clean and then go after him again, Kitten. No matter how bitter the memory... It can never be as bitter as dark black coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Alright, Mia! You have got to think harder this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let me ask you one more time...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally the answer is... right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim's... coat? As far as I can see, there is nothing strange about it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's exactly what's strange! Remember the testimony! What were the conditions on the bridge that day? It was drizzling and foggy. Dusky Bridge was all wet. If the victim really had fallen down on her stomach on top of the bridge... ...then the front of her coat should have been covered in mud!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That... That's exactly right! The other day I fell on a muddy street and my gorgeous playoff beard was befouled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I do admit that the crime scene was quite wet that day. However! That doesn't mean that the top of the bridge itself was muddy! If Your Honor had fallen in the shower instead of on a muddy street... ...his glorious hockey beard, pride of the Legal League, would be wet, but not muddy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fortunately, I have yet to test that. Still, your point is well-taken.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you prove that the surface of the bridge was muddy that day?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The surface of the bridge, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! A real man wouldn't stand for a taunt like this!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Neither would a real woman!</thought> Of course I can!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Here is the evidence that proves the surface of the bridge was muddy!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The evidence is...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Wait a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What is it? Your timing is terrible...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">If you present that evidence, it would be like... Like jumping off a 100-story building into a bubbling pool of magma. ...After tying a 10-ton boulder around your neck.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What is THAT supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">To put it simply... It would be suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Why didn't he just put it simply in the first place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is your little chat finished? Can we move on now?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes... I-I've changed my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Life is short, Ms. Fey. Hurry it up already!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, Your Honor! The defense is now prepared to show our evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The evidence is... this scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It should be obvious... If the scarf fell onto the bridge and got this muddy... It means that the bridge was obviously covered in mud!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urrrnngh...! No... I can't be outwitted by this novice bimbo...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hey! Same to you, buddy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey's assertion makes perfect sense to me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do admit that there appears to be a contradiction between... ...the condition of the victim's coat and her scarf. However! The real question is... why is there a contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For every contradiction, there exists an explanation. Let's look at what the explanation in this case may be, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A-Alright...! <thought>It's not like he's really giving me a choice here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">You're doing pretty good. ...For a little kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">No matter what he says, a contradiction always comes down to a lie. It's either the victim discovered in the trunk... ...the witness's photo showing the defendant and the victim... ...or the witness's testimony that stated she saw the moment of the murder. Just relax and think it over. It's pretty simple, isn't it? The false evidence... It's one of those three.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph! What you said just now! I'm not sure I like that!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Th-That wasn't me, Your Honor! It was the coffee aficionado over here that said it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is not in the habit of accepting false evidence, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Blame it on him, Your Honor. He's the one trying to slip false evidence into the court.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">But we won't let him! We'll expose his evidence as the flimsy scam it really is!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes! The false evidence in this case is the...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">About the photo that the prosecution claims was taken by a witness... It certainly seems to show a man in a prison uniform and a woman in a coat. However! We can't tell any more than that from the photo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying the people in the photo may not be the victim and the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Well, that's certainly a possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So perhaps it was another prisoner and policewoman? I admit, people have their quirks. Perhaps they were part of a role-playing group?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Well, I suppose that's also p-possible... I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">You messed up again... Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">There should be something else that's even more suspicious. Now think the whole thing over again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">From this point on, Ms. Fey, I will penalize you for making unsubstantiated accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ugggh... Don't do it, Mia! Don't cry until you get home!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If the victim really did try to repel her killer and if she did fall down on the bridge... ...then you would expect her coat to be dirty. Therefore! The body that was found in the trunk of the car... It was NOT the body of Valerie Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you have to say to that, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* Objection.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Not only a whisper, but he mixed in a sigh, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Valerie Hawthorne was more than a simple meter maid; she was a sergeant. There's absolutely no chance that a mistake about her identity could be made.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Uuurgh... <thought>I guess he's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">From this point on, Ms. Fey, I will penalize you for making unsubstantiated accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ugggh... Don't do it, Mia! Don't cry until you get home!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It is a no-brainer. Obviously it's the witness that's suspicious! During his earlier testimony, the detective pointed out a crucial fact. "The criminal shoved the victim down from behind and stabbed her in the back." Now, is that testimony exactly what the witness claims to have seen?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. ...That's what the witness told us.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That testimony... is filled with holes. After all, the victim's coat isn't dirty at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! It's not just true. It's the truth. If there was a truly decisive witness in this case... ...I'm certain that boy wonder over there would have called them in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Your Honor! The defense requests to cross-examine the eyewitness! The testimony presented so far is not only vague, but contradictory as well!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth? It appears that we'll need to hear from your mystery witness after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... *sigh* You should brace yourself. ...For the brutal truth.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, the prosecution has no intention of hiding the witness from the court. We are prepared to present our witness at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... Please bring forth your witness at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What Mr. Edgeworth said... kind of worries me... What does he mean by "the brutal truth"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, let's proceed with the testimony. Mr. Edgeworth. Please go right ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, Your Honor. The prosecution summons... ...the woman who saw the events that day with her very own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is it, Mia! The battle begins here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Witness. What is your name and occupation? ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Everyone is so silent that I can hear their hearts going pitter-patter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ohh... When I look at you... How can I put it...? You look as scrumptous [sic] as a double-double and a dozen doughnut holes... I feel like I want to hurry up and hand down a verdict just to have a bite...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hey, hey! Not so fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...*sigh* As I said before... This witness is very sensitive and delicate. I would ask the court to please exercise care when addressing her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, indeed... Thank you, Mr. Edgeworth. You are a true gentleman. Ms. Fey! You could learn a lot from this man!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...If he's such a gentleman, he sure doesn't act like one to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Umm... Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Eh? Yes, my dear?</line>
<line speaker="???">This is my first time, so I'm sure I'll make a lot of mistakes. Anyway... I just wanted to say I'm sorry for all the trouble I might cause...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... Not at all! It's no trouble at all!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now then... May we please have your name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">My name is, umm... ...Melissa Foster. I'm a college student... A-A freshman in the literature department.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were on the scene when the unfortunate event occurred, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...And you were the one who took this photo? Is that accurate?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Waaaaaah! H-How can you be so mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now see here! What are you doing shoving that in her face like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh? B-But it's just a photograph! It's not like it's something dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next time I'll be forced to penalize you!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Uh oh... I don't like the turn this has taken...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...? <thought>Is she... staring at me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Umm... And you would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh? I-I'm the defense lawyer. ...My name is Mia Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">... ...I see. So you are...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, young lady. Could you please give us your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes, Your Honor... I-I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I was using my camera to take some pictures of wild flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... By the way, where were you standing when the incident occurred...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the map would be of help here.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Umm... I was standing right over... here. I was standing in a beautiful field, surrounded by tall cliffs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you took the photo from that location, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I brought the camera I was using at the time, just like Mr. Edgeworth asked me to.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. What a cute camera... Just like its owner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Alright then, Ms. Fey. Time for your cross-examination. But I warn you, make the witness cry again, and you'll feel the wrath of my gavel.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I was using my camera to take some pictures of wild flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Did you say... "wild flowers"?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes, the mountain is famous for its beautiful spring wild flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm... But it's only February.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, I... I couldn't wait for Spring to come.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho... I know just how you feel! It's just like when I first started growing this glorious beard of mine... I just couldn't wait, so I wore a dyed blonde Santa beard until mine grew in properly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Would you mind if we got back to the facts of the case, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Then, I noticed there were two people standing up on the suspension bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Was there anything strange about the two of them?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I'm a bad girl. ...I know I am. It looked like they were having a really serious conversation up there... ...So I decided to watch them. Like some kind of Peeping Tom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, not at all! Everyone is like that! I love watching other people fight, too. In fact, I can't get enough of it! ...Actually, that's why I took this job in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Too much info, Your Honor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...In any case, it's perfectly natural for you to have kept watching them. Especially dressed as they were...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, anyway... I was watching them very closely.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Suddenly, they just started fighting!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Do you have any idea what they were fighting about?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Eh? No... I have no idea. Why do you ask that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, I just thought that maybe you overheard what they said...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I would never... I would never eavesdrop... I've got more class than that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right, Ms. Fey! Don't drag the witness down to your level!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Grrrr...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">That's when I hurried and took the photo that shows the crucial moment.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why did you take a photo?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, the two of them were really going at it... Ever since I was a little girl, I always wanted to be a news reporter... I guess that part of me just kind of took over...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Smells like a lie to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I understand completely! Even now, I can't completely abandon my boyhood dreams... I still use my grandson to test my comedy routines on!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So he wanted to be a comedian, huh. ...Not that it has any bearing on this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">All I could do was to use my camera. So I took the photo of the crucial moment and gave it to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Witness. When you said you took a photo of the crucial moment,  is this what you meant?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Err...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">All I can see in this photo are two people facing each other. You testified that you saw the two of them starting to fight. Normally that's the kind of thing we would refer to as a crucial moment! Why haven't you presented a photo like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...W-Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The photo we presented was the only one there was.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But if you really wanted to capture the crucial moment... ...then what happened next? You must have taken a photo of it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... Hmmmmm... Doh! Err... Umm... My apologies, young lady... But Ms. Fey's assertion is not without a certain amount of merit...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>He can certainly downplay a situation, can't he...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...I-I'm sorry... ...I'm a very bad girl. I umm... I used it all up... The film, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You ran out of film!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Err, this photo was the last one.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, that is the truth. ...I personally examined all of the photographs she took that day. All the other photos are of the witness herself, playing among the wild flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The witness herself? Then who took the photos?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well... You see... My camera has a timer feature built into it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, you took photos of yourself!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I remember taking some photos of myself once, too!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Please! No details...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It seems that Ms. Fey's assertion was not so decisive after all.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Wait! Just a minute!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if she had no film left, she couldn't very well take more pictures, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Foster, perhaps then you could tell us about a different sort of photo. Photos of the incident that you "took" with your very own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Mr. Edgeworth... You're quite the poet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then! Let's get back to the cross-examination. ...Let's hear your thoughts on the fight that you witnessed!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes... Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Boy, this guy is really a sucker for sweet talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! It looks like the other kitten in the room is the one that's getting all the attention.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yeah, it's sickening.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">And right after that, I called the police.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You called the police?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes. Because it looked to me like the murderer was going to try to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...We were already moving before the call even came in. Thanks to the victim's note, we had already started our operation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That was certainly tough luck for the criminal, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">The victim turned around and tried to run away, but...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The victim... Why do you think she tried to run away?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">With her police training, she certainly knew better than to turn her back on a criminal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was a large, powerful man with a knife. If it had been a quaggy woman like you, I'm sure she would have acted differently.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>"Quaggy"!? Why you...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If it had been me, I probably would have jumped into the river!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>There's still something wrong with this testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">She only got about 10 yards before she was stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So you're saying Sergeant Hawthorne wasn't able to get away from him...?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, it's a narrow bridge and it was swaying back and forth... If you ask me, both of them were in danger of falling off. I only wish I could have done something to help her...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... That seems to make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I wonder about that... Something seems kind of off...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! You have a good sixth sense. When you feel that something's off, that's when you need to figure out why...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>If Terry Fawles isn't the criminal... Then there must be something strange in that girl's testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Be careful, Kitten. That girl has the judge wrapped right around her little finger. You're going to have a tough time poking holes in that testimony of hers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>You're going to have to come up with something really good, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Witness! Your testimony is a joke!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Huh... Wh-What...? B-But I... I just...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! I thought I warned you not to make the witness cry!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">One short testimony and two bad contradictions... There's no possible excuse!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say there were... two contradictions!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's simple. Just take a look at the diagram of the area. According to her testimony, the two of them were in the middle of the bridge. But if they were, and the victim had turned around and tried to run... Well, then...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-She would've hit a dead-end...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You said 10 yards, but she couldn't have ran even 5! Because Dusky Bridge is collapsed on that side!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Waaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What does all this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's very simple, Your Honor. This charming, little witness told a charming, little lie. That's all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Nnnn...ggg...urk...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This beautiful, young lady has been l-lying to the court...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just a moment, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>M-Mr. Edgeworth...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... Allow me to personally apologize for the confusion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's one major mistake in this diagram.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What did you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you referring to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's all because this diagram was made after the incident occurred. It's a very old bridge... We couldn't find any official blueprints of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So you're saying...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm saying that even though this bridge is currently in disrepair... ...there's no evidence that can prove that the bridge was broken during the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Th-That's ridiculous...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can't actually tell the condition of the bridge from this photo... I apologize to the court for not being more clear when I presented the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Hmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! That guy is good.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">He planned it from the beginning. He's a genius alright... That diagram of the bridge was his insurance policy.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What!? That coward!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Fey... It seems you've once again made a reckless accusation.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I-I'm so sorry! I should have been more careful myself...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no, no, no! It wasn't YOUR fault at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then... Shall we go on with the trial? I'd like to establish, once and for all, what it was that the witness actually saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Alright, young lady... May I ask you to please proceed with your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">But I... It's so hard to go on...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We're all on your side, Ms. Foster!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no need to worry. Just tell us what you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">After he stabbed her in the back, he quickly picked her up in his arms.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Witnessing such violence must have been difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes, sir... I-I'm still shaken up...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">If he accepts this testimony as it is, we're finished.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">D-Don't say that...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Oh well... Maybe I'll stop off at my favorite caf on the way home. They make a really great mocha latt...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This trial isn't over yet!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! That's what I like to hear...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Ms. Fey. Your cross-examination, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The contradiction is staring you right in the face, Mia! Go on the attack!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">After he stabbed her in the back, he quickly picked her up in his arms.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Are you saying that the victim didn't fall down on the bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Err... Umm... Actually, maybe she did fall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course she didn't fall down on the bridge. If she had fallen down, this photo wouldn't make any sense. If that was the case, her coat would've been all muddy.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">If you don't mind, I was asking the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* No need to be so rude.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, young lady?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">... Of course she didn't fall down. The man in the prison uniform grabbed her before she could.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! We're one step too slow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And then, what did the defendant do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Then he carried her over to the car.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You personally witnessed that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Did anything strange happen when he did that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, I don't know if you'd call it strange or not... ...but that's when the victim's scarf fell off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You mean this scarf!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her words match what we found at the scene. I don't see any problem...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I suppose that was the only way he could make sure the body stayed hidden.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You mean the defendant carried the body all by himself?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Considering the size of the defendant, I don't think it would be difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, but... Let's remember they were on a narrow bridge that was ready to collapse! Is it even possible for him to have carried a dead body on a bridge like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, the fact of the matter is that he DID! That kind of talk is just silly!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Wow... Why did he get so emotional all of a sudden?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, if you think there's some other possibility, please share it with the rest of us.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">A killer not wanting his victim to be found... I can understand that. However! The idea of moving the body for that purpose is clearly odd. There was a much easier way to make sure the body wasn't found!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well? What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Take another look at the map of the area and you'll see how. There's a river right below the bridge. Earlier Mr. Edgeworth pointed out something interesting about the river.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For those who are not aware, Eagle River is well-known for its powerful current. Most bodies that fall in are never recovered...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In the kidnapping case 5 years ago, the victim's body was carried away and never found.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If 10 murders were to occur at that same spot above the Eagle River... ...you can bet your boots that every other killer would have tossed the body in the water!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! I'm not sure if I care for the way you put that, Ms. Fey! But I must admit it does seem odd not to have thrown the body into the river!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ooooh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* How sad. Perhaps Ms. Fey would do well to try taking a dip in the river herself. After all, you claim to be such an expert in the ways of nature...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My point is that no matter how odd you may find the killer's method of body-disposal... ...the fact is that this is what the killer did. None of your arguments have anything to do with what the witness saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Quite true... Ms. Fey, it seems that your assertion is without merit after all.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But what the witness claims to have seen is totally ridiculous...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surely you can't deny that the body was found in the trunk of the car.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's certainly consistent with what the witness has told us.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, witness, go on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I-I'll try...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All you have to do is tell us only what you saw. Otherwise the mean lady might yell at you again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Who is he talking about!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Alright! I-I'll do my best!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">The killer broke into the trunk of the stolen car and hid the body in there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What did the man do then?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well... Naturally, he got in the car and was about to flee. That's... That's when I came to my senses. I said to myself, "You have to call the police!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And so that's when you called the police?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You're sure that you saw all that with your own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes. I'm 100% certain.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">He couldn't just leave the body on top of the bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why do you say that? It's already a broken-down bridge hidden away in the mountains. Doing anything more to hide the corpse would be going overboard, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes, but that mountain is famous among hikers. A surprising number of people go up there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But it's February, right? And it was raining that day, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">There is also a small temple and a channeling dojo there. You know those monks... They just love cold, isolated places...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think the witness is trying to say that the corpse could have been found at any time... Besides, the witness is merely reporting what she witnessed with her own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Oh, I'm sorry... I'm only supposed to talk about what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">And you're absolutely certain that it was my client who was carrying the body?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">... Well, he was wearing a prisoner's uniform, but... as for his face...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you're saying you didn't get a clear look at his face?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, they were far away and it was raining as well. I-I thought I was only supposed to say exactly what I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Excellent! You're a remarkably honest young woman!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Something about this testimony is bothering me, but what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hey, Kitten... Have you ever put salt in your coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No... Why would I!?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">It may actually go better with coffee than sugar, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen. My point is if you're not sure, you might as well add a ton of salt to it. It might... bring out the rust in something. Like a piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>He's right, Mia... Go present something. You've got nothing to lose!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">By the way, I wouldn't put salt in my coffee. The two don't go well, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Ms. Foster... It looks like you've done it this time.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...? D-Done what?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Made a crucial mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A c-crucial mistake? Like what, Ms. Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"The killer broke into the trunk of the stolen car and hid the body in there." You're saying you saw that, right? With your very own eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's simple, Ms. Foster. Take a look at the diagram. The place you claim to have taken the photo from that day is here. Do you see what I mean? Even if you tried to see the car... ...this outcropping of rock is directly in the way.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right, Ms. Foster.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">From where you were standing, you could not have possibly seen the killer's car.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Aaaaah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admit that the diagram shows a large outcropping of rock. However... It isn't so tall that it would stop her from seeing the car!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Th-That's right! It-It's not high at all... I-I was able to see his car just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm so sorry... But that just doesn't wash.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I believe it was the witness who presented this as evidence to the court, yes? This is the location that the photo was taken from. Your own photo tells the whole story! You can clearly see the left side of the bridge... But the outcropping that is being referred to is really more like a cliff.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your view should have been completely cut off by this cliff! But still you claim to have been able to see the killer's car!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">... Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or-Order! Order in the court! What is the meaning of all this ballyhoo...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... Don't jump to any hasty conclusions. The fact that the escapee fled in a stolen car was reported on the news. After witnessing a murder, I'm sure you can appreciate that the witness was very upset. She must have heard about the stolen car and convinced herself that she saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But she was repeatedly warned before starting her testimony! She was told to testify only about what she saw with her own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Err... Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I think... I think I must have remembered things wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hey! Wait a minute! You can't just say that...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Fey, no one on the face of the planet is perfect.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm... Yes, indeed... Quite true! You know what they say... "To err is human, to forgive, divine." I'm inclined to give the benefit of the doubt to our witness here.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What...!? Th-That's not fair...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Save the tears for later, Kitten!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Don't look back until the trial is over. Now is the time to go forward.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">B-But...! But that wasn't fair!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">OK, Kitten, you need to relax. Then you need to remember... The other kitten's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">The killer broke into the trunk of the stolen car and hid the body in there.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">So tell us... How did you know that? How did you know that he broke into the trunk?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Aha...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Until you can explain how you knew that... ...you're going to have a lot of very suspicious people on this side of the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, I'm certain that he broke into the trunk. Because... Because there were marks left on the trunk lid. I'm certain they were scratch marks from when he broke into it...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What...!? L-Let me see that photo! It's true... These certainly look like scratch marks around the keyhole! HMMMM...! It's obvious that this trunk has been broken open. Well, Ms. Fey? Are you satisfied...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The judge is on her side! I can't make any mistakes here! What she just said... Is there a contradiction in there somewhere...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Something about it still doesn't feel right, but...</thought> I, err... OK, I guess I'm satisfied... Sort of.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope this has cleared up any doubts...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, I believe it has.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hey Kitten, this is no time to play around!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Overlooking such a huge contradiction... What am I going do with you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Contradiction...!? So that wasn't my imagination after all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let's move on to the next...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">J-Just a minute!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it now, Ms. Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I've got a big problem with what this witness said!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'd appreciate it if you didn't change your mind every 5 seconds!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ugh... Hang in there, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Melissa Foster. It looks like you've finally betrayed yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You said you were in a field taking photos of wild flowers. But even so, you knew about the scratches... The question is when! When did you get a chance to see those scratches!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Finally...! I've finally got her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! I'm getting pretty tired of waiting over here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then perhaps it would be faster if Ms. Fey explained herself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! There's only one possible explanation! The reason the witness had seen the scratches was...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Because she just happened to be passing by the area where the car was parked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Frankly, Your Honor, after hearing a pathetic response like that... I have to question whether or not such a pathetic lawyer should even exist...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you hear that Ms. Fey? I believe Mr. Edgeworth just called you a canucklehead.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Yeesh, isn't that overdoing things a little bit...? Come on, Mia! One more time! You can do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Because the stolen car actually belonged to her. That is why she knew about the scratches!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Frankly, Your Honor, after hearing a pathetic response like that... I have to question whether or not such a pathetic lawyer should even exist...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you hear that Ms. Fey? I believe Mr. Edgeworth just called you a canucklehead.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Yeesh, isn't that overdoing things a little bit...? Come on, Mia! One more time! You can do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's only one way that the witness had the chance to see those scratches.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes? What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally... When she opened the trunk... and stuffed the corpse in herself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The person who really hid the body in the trunk of that car was... Melissa Foster! It was you that did it, wasn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Th-That's ridiculous! I could never...! It was the man in the prison garb! He-He's the one that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't think so, Ms. Foster. If Mr. Fawles had been the one that put the corpse in the trunk... ...he would have simply used the car key. There was no need to break it open.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">B-But...! He stole the car...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">He stole it from a young couple that had been waiting at a red light. Which means that the key would have still been in the ignition.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Oh...! I-I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thank you for telling us about the scratches, Ms. Foster. Without that, we never would have uncovered the truth. It couldn't have been Mr. Fawles that put the body in the trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Nooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">P-Preposterous! To even suggest that the witness put the body in there! If that were true... then how do you explain the photo that she took? The corpse could only have been put in the trunk when the incident occurred. And we already know that at the time, she was taking photographs!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Now is your chance, Mia! Finish this thing!</thought> On the contrary, I'm not so certain about that anymore, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's no need to think too deeply about it. What I'm saying is the shutter for this may not have been pushed by Ms. Foster herself!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To be quite honest, Ms. Fey... I wish you would have thought a little more deeply on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hey Kitten... Don't start getting all sloppy on me now. The fact is, she wasn't there, but the photo got taken. So how did it happen? This is a fastball right over home plate.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That's what I thought, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, take a moment and think it over again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't think you can make a mistake about it. Take a look at her camera. It has a timer built into it! Even a mini-tripod!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmm...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Almost as if the camera was brought just to take this picture!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you trying to say then, Ms. Fey!? That when the crime occurred, Ms. Foster wasn't in the field as she claimed!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, if she really did use the camera's auto-timer... ...then the answer is yes, she was somewhere else.</thought> Exactly. She was NOT in the field.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Would the defense please explain further.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen... This is a crucial point. "Where was Ms. Foster when the incident occurred...?" In answering that question, we'll also make clear Ms. Foster's true identity.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, please answer this question. Where was Melissa Foster when the incident on the bridge occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally the witness was right... here! ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... In the spot where the defendant's car was?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! She had to put the body in the trunk before the defendant returned!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't mind if I ask one teenie-weenie question, do you, Ms. Fey...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Uh oh. He's got that condescending tone in his voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If she put the body in the trunk at that time, as you suggest... ...that must mean that Valerie Hawthorne was already dead at that point, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please take a look at the top of Dusky Bridge. It certainly looks to me like the victim is still alive... Am I mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Err...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If Valerie Hawthorne was already dead, then... who is this? The mountain is famous for spirits, so maybe you think it was the ghost of the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Well, it COULD have been a spirit... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! Don't waste the court's time with this kind of foolishness!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A-Anyway! I still maintain that the witness was in a different place at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you certain?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, I am certain! More or less.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, come now, Ms. Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally, the witness was standing right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... Well, what do you think, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* Before pointing out where the witness was standing, Ms. Fey should do something herself. She should figure out where SHE stands, if you catch my drift!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh don't worry, the drift was certainly caught...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, failure is an excellent opportunity for growth. Now try better next time.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ah, yes... Thank you...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally, the witness was right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's... But that's where the victim, Ms. Hawthorne was standing! Order! Order! Order! Ms. Fey! What on earth...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor, if I may... After parting with the "victim" on the bridge, the defendant fled by car. But this would mean that there was no time to put the victim in the trunk. In other words, if someone put the body in the trunk... ...it could only have been before the defendant met the "victim"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How asinine! Of course Mr. Fawles met with the victim! The only person with the opportunity to have put the victim in the trunk... ...is the same man that killed her, Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You still don't understand, do you, Mr. Edgeworth? By the time the witness's photo was taken, the victim was already dead... The person in the photo was NOT Valerie Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? I've never heard anything more ridiculous in my entire life! Then who exactly is the "victim" in this photo!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's obvious, isn't it? It's your own witness.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Whaaaat...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's the only possible explanation. The woman that Mr. Fawles met on the bridge that day was not Valerie Hawthorne! It was you! Melissa Foster!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">M-M-Me...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Let's remember that it was raining and foggy on the mountain that day. Mr. Fawles himself believed that the woman in front of him was Valerie Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the defendant knew Valerie Hawthorne very well! After all, she was the woman whose testimony helped get him convicted!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But since then, my client has spent five hard years in a federal penitentiary! He couldn't remember exactly what she looked like anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are just making this up as you go along! Where's your proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've got it all right here! This piece of evidence will blow this case wide open...!</thought> At the time of the incident, Mr. Fawles had forgotten what Valerie Hawthorne looked like!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Wait a minute, Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">First of all, relax. Second of all, think the whole thing over again!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>H-He's right, Mia! You need to calm down and think it over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles had forgotten the victim's face. That's why he needed some piece of identification. Namely, this muddy scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It was Mr. Fawles who requested that she wear this scarf to identify herself. That's already been proven by the note the victim left!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In other words, as long as you were wearing a scarf like he asked... ...anyone could have pretended to be Valerie Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well? What do you have to say to that, Melissa Foster!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Nnng...Gggh...Unnn...! N-N-N-N-N-Nnnnoooooooo!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Err... Ahh... Where's Ms. Foster...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She's collecting herself in the Lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It's obvious that Melissa Foster did it. She hid the body in the trunk and disguised herself as the victim... She set up the camera to snap a fake photo of them together...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">The only question is... why did she do it...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, isn't that obvious? She's the true criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we'll have to wait for Ms. Foster to compose herself before we start again. Until then, this court is in recess. The defense and the prosecution are instructed to wait in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! This court is in recess!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles, I...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">UGGAAAA!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eeeeeek! I'm sorry! I-I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I wanna say thanks. You're real good! You really hooked me up!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thanks! We're almost there! Once I prove that she committed the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">...Yeah, but there's one more big obstacle we've got to get past.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ob-Obstacle...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Yeah. Motive. Why would Melissa Foster kill that policewoman anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Motive, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Anyway... We're still badly in need of information.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Information... Right...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">What we need the most is info about this Melissa Foster herself. All we know is that she's a student studying literature. And one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Well, the incident that happened 5 years ago, of course. The kidnapping-murder case that Zebra Boy is on death row for...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I din't do nuttin'! I din't kill nobody! I never lie!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles! In that case... Tell us more about it. ...About what happened 5 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... OK. I trust you. That day. 5 years ago. I dream of it. Every day. This picture. It reminds me everything. Bridge looks same. Just like then... 5 years ago... Like it could fall apart... Fall apart any minute...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So it's been broken like that for at least 5 years...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Sorry buddy, but you sound like the one that could fall apart at any minute.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">It true. I did... ...I did kidnap her. ...Five years ago. I kidnapped. My girlfriend. Dahlia Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Your g-girlfriend? Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hey, hold on there! Did you say, "Hawthorne"!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The victim's last name...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia Hawthorne... Valerie's little sister.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-Wh-Whaaat!? Are you serious!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The detective back then was Valerie Hawthorne!</thought> At first I thought shooting someone for a kidnapping was crossing the line, but... If it was to protect her little sister, I can understand why she did it...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Wrong! No protect sister! Valerie betray me! Betray us!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What do you mean she betrayed you!?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Everything. All lies. All make-believe. Kidnapping, too...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A make-believe kidnapping?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia. My girlfriend. My love. My Teen Angel.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ugh. Did he actually say, "My Teen Angel"? He's seen one too many soap operas.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I do anything she says. Anything Dahlia says...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>"Anything Dahlia says"...?</thought> H-Hold on a minute! What you're saying is that the kidnapping 5 years ago was planned by...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yeah. Me and Dahlia... ...And Valerie, too.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Valerie was in on it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia's family rich. Jewelry business. We get one jewel... That's what we thought... Me and Dahlia wrote kidnap note. We send to her dad. Asked for 2 million dollar diamond. Tell him make exchange on Dusky Bridge. ...We tell him Valerie make transfer 'cause she new detective.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Having a police detective in your pocket is a useful thing alright. In the end, you were planning on splitting the 2 million three ways, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yeah, but! That woman! That woman! Valerie! She do it for real! She shoot at me for real! Me and Dahlia!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I was shot in arm. Dahlia... She jump in river.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Jump...? You don't mean she jumped on purpose, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I couldn't do it! I could never push her...! Anyway, I blacked out... Wake up with police all over.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">...And that's when they decided to give you the death sentence.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I couldn't believe it. That woman. She betrayed me.</line>
<line speaker="Valerie">That man... Terry Fawles... He killed her! He threw her off the bridge! He threw my beloved sister into the roaring river 40 feet below!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...These 5 years... All I wonder is... Why! ...Why! ...Why! ...Why! Why did she lie!? That's all I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">So that's why you called her. You wanted to hear the truth from Valerie herself.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yes... but I forget what she look like. So I tell her to wear scarf. I don't want to hurt her! ...Just ask why! Why! Why did you lie...? Why did you betray me...? I just want to hear answer come from her mouth. That's all!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So that's why... That's why you made a crazy escape like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Just one thing, Zebra Boy... My senses are tingling all over. Tell me, Mr. Fawles... Where is it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Huh? Where's what?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Come on now, Kitten... The ransom. The 2 million dollar diamond. Remember that now? Did you give it back to Pops? Did the police take it?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh? You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">No really. I dunno. It's gone. With Dahlia.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...With Dahlia?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That day. On the bridge... Dahlia put it. In backpack... Now gone. With Dahlia. Gone... Forever... Into Eagle River...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It disappeared with Dahlia, huh...? Wait a minute...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">...You can come back in now! We're about ready to go!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles! Just one more question! When you said, "with Dahlia", do you mean the diamond is still missing...? Along with the body of Dahlia Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Never found her... My sweet Dahlia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>They never found her...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Swallowed by river... Gone... Dahlia... My Teen Angel...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Your "Teen Angel"...? How old was she anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Just 14...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">F-F-Fourteen!? <thought>I guess you were robbing cradles before diamonds...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">She plans a fake kidnapping and disappears into the river with a rock worth 2 mil... Man oh man... Angels these days.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Fawles takes the fall... And gets a one-way ticket to Death Row... Is Dahlia Hawthorne an angel or is she really a...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">...It's time, Kitten. It looks like we have a few more aces up our sleeve now.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...You bet!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">The training wheels come off now, Mia! You've got to strike while the iron is hot! That's one of my rules. Remember it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's continue with the trial of Mr. Terry Fawles. ...Witness. Are you feeling better?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes, Your Honor... I-I'll try my best.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You're a brave young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Not this again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can understand a defense lawyer wanting to get her client off the hook... However! To try to pin the crime on an innocent student is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My witness is not the person on trial here. She's an innocent bystander who witnessed a violent crime. ...That's all. What possible reason would a girl like this have for murdering a policewoman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's certainly hard to imagine this woman as a murderer...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Her motive, huh... I figured that's what I had to establish next...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Fey? Do you have any evidence of a motive?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Err, yes! Of course! ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Hah...! You're still acting as tame as a kitten... Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Armando...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen... A lawyer is someone who smiles no matter how bad it gets.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Smiling on the outside while your guts are twisted in knots is the mark of a pro.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Maybe so, but I wish you would quit grinning at me like that.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Umm... Excuse me... May I speak, Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course! Mr. Judge is ready anytime you like!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I'd like... I'd like to say something. Some people here are suspicious of me, right? Th-That's why... I... I at least wanted you, Mr. Judge, to know that it's not true...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm! I see! You're such an honest and upstanding young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">It looks like this witness is a real professional.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Look at that 100-watt smile. ...Just when things are darkest for her... CLICK. She lights right up!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then! Let's hear what the witness has to say!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I was out of the country until the year before last.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Out of the country, eh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. Furthermore, she has no possible motive for committing murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">You're up to bat, Kitten. Sharpen those claws and put on your best smile.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-You bet! <thought>Somehow, I have to tie her to this case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I was out of the country until the year before last.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, what country were you living in then?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">We were all living abroad, but after my parents were killed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was a brutal civil war. She had to try to make her way back home alone...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I lost everything... I didn't even have any personal identification...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What kind of sob story is this...? ...What do I do? Should I press her for details?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>There's nothing I can do about her claim to have lost all her identification. All I can do is wait to find some other evidence about her real identity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, Ms. Foster. Please proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Witness. Answer my question. I'll even repeat it for you. What country were you in?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, this line of questioning is childish. What country she was in and how many languages she may speak are irrelevant here. What we're here to evaluate is whether this witness has any connection to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I've lived abroad ever since I was a little girl... That's why I could never have known Mr. Fawles or Detective Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I think we've established that point.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, indeed. Well then. Shall we add what you've just stated to the official testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes, please. ...Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Naturally, I didn't know either the victim or the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You didn't know either person? Are you certain of that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes. I'm afraid I'm rather shy around people.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Oh well, that can't be helped.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Why is he just agreeing with everything that comes out of her mouth...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The first time you saw either of them was when they were on the bridge, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes... It really was a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Until I entered college, I had never even been to Eagle Mountain before...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So what made you decide to go to Eagle Mountain anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I just love being outdoors... Picnics, hiking... You know, that sort of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...You don't look like much of a hiker to me. But you do look like a digger of sorts.</thought> But Eagle Mountain is a two-hour drive from here and no trains run through there. There are plenty of mountains that are closer and easier to get to.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, I went there once with the college Hiking Club. I fell in love with its stark, desolate beauty and its cold, yet romantic, gloominess...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Didn't know you were such a goth...</thought> By the way, what's the name of your college...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution objects to any questions that involve the witness's private life.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All that matters is that she is a material witness to a crime. The witness doesn't need to respond to questions that are clearly malicious in intent.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Thank you! She's really gone too far...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm! Ms. Fey! You're treading on thin ice here!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I hardly said anything! Talk about sensitive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">And I certainly don't have any reason for wanting to hurt a police officer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Perhaps, but your behavior that day was very suspicious! Not only have you contradicted yourself here in court, but you know things you shouldn't. For example, the scratches on the trunk of the car.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well th-that's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately Ms. Fey, your last statement proves nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh really!? And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness came to the police station once to identify the suspect. It's entirely possible that, at that time, an officer showed her this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That seems like a rather serious mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! That's the oldest trick in the prosecutor's book.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Th-That's not fair...!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">That wicked inmate... I'll never be able to forget that horrible day...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Holding a grudge and killing the officer who testified against you 5 years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">A grudge...?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, the policewoman's testimony was crucial, wasn't it? ...Crucial in getting the defendant sentenced to death.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and that's precisely why he harbored such deep anger against her. So much anger that he forgot his own guilt...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">My client has always maintained that he's innocent of those charges!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">He seems rather forgetful. ...Your client, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Not only did he forget about what he did, but he forgot the poor policewoman as well.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Your client... He forgot what the detective looked like, right? It's too bad for her that he didn't forget about her testimony as well.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, she's right about that. Mr. Fawles is kind of forgetful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Any more damage to my client's image could be a disaster... The judge already has a bad enough opinion of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just can't trust someone with a bad memory. What did you eat for dinner one week ago today? ...At the very least, a person should remember that much. As for me, it was payday, so I had a nice moose steak with some poutine on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...And how does this relate to anything!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether it's eating steak or committing murder, a person shouldn't deny their actions. I'm in complete agreement, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You said, "he forgot what the detective looked like." What did you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well he couldn't tell who she was without some kind of identification, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quite right... That's why the victim was wearing a scarf as identification.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Why, if I had been wearing a white scarf that day... ...then he probably would have tried to kill me...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's true. He's clearly a bitter man!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is bad. Mr. Fawles's reputation just keeps getting worse and worse. Sometimes it's best not to poke too deep... What should I do with that last statement?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! What the witness said just now was tremendously important! I'd like it added to the official testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has no objection... After all, the defendant is a killer and a mentally unbalanced one at that... That testimony only helps to further prove that point...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">N-No, that's not why I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough. ...Witness, if you would?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">My pleasure, Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Any more damage to my client's image could be a disaster... The judge already has a bad enough opinion of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just can't trust someone with a bad memory. What did you eat for dinner one week ago today? ...At the very least, a person should remember that much. As for me, it was payday, so I had a nice moose steak with some poutine on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...And how does this relate to anything!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether it's eating steak or committing murder, a person shouldn't deny their actions. I'm in complete agreement, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I guess I'm lucky I wasn't wearing a white scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What do you mean by lucky?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well... It's February now. Everyone is wearing scarves. If I had accidentally worn a white scarf like he said...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then you yourself might have been killed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... That would've been a terrible loss for this world!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! It looks like you pressed too hard this time, Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Armando...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Keep looking around you and you're going to lose sight of the finish line. Justice is blind, but she's not deaf. Sometimes you have to know when not to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Witness... I want you to look at this photo you took. It's hard to see in the photo, but look at the scarf the victim wore as identification.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you are talking about this scarf right here, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Y-Yes! That's it! The scarf the policewoman was wearing...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've got her now, just don't mess up...</thought> ...But that's strange. In your testimony, you stated the following... "I guess I'm lucky I wasn't wearing a white scarf."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-White?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...This is the scarf you identified as belonging to the victim. But it certainly doesn't look white to me!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Oh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it was foggy that day... And it was raining as well! It's not surprising that she mistook it for white!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sorry, but not this time. The witness just confirmed that this was the victim's scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but... What's the significance...? It's true that the scarf doesn't look white, but...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's only one explanation for this mix-up! The reason why the witness thought the scarf was white is...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Here's the definitive piece of evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That...? That's your definitive piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! ...If my thinking is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then. We have one mystery solved! The answer is simple. Ms. Fey's thinking is wrong. ...That's all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Please, Kitten. You've got to do something... You're killing me over here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, I've got a definitive penalty to reward you for your definitive piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, that wasn't what I was expecting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... Do you have evidence or not? Perhaps you can tell us about why the witness thought the scarf was white, eh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...Witness. Have you ever seen this note?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">N-Note...? I, err... No, never...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's top-secret evidence. There's no reason that you would have.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmm, I wonder about that...</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Wh-What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This note shows Mr. Fawles's instructions to the victim regarding their meeting. It says... "Wear white scarf for identification."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">White... Scarf...? AAAAAAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Witness! You KNEW what this note said! There's no other possible reason for you to mistake the scarf's color!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...It's true. Mr. Fawles did give instructions to Valerie Hawthorne about their meeting. The note that she left said: "Wear white scarf for identification."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, what about it...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Isn't it obvious!? Doesn't it strike you as odd!? That note was a secret piece of evidence! How is it that the witness knows about it!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Hmm... It is odd, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth!? Did you show top-secret evidence to the witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Your Honor... I certainly never gave anyone permission to do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In that case, the only way the witness could know about the note would b--</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">J-Just a moment! Of course... Of course I didn't know about the note! It's just... I saw it when it happened. ...With my own eyes. When the victim went to see the killer... She used her own scarf to signal him. That's why... That's why I assumed that the signal was a white scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... I suppose that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Come on, Mia! You can't let her weasel out of it that easily!</thought> ...Witness! Sorry, but your explanation isn't going to work here.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">B-But why!? It-It's true! That's what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Impossible. There's no way you could have seen the victim use a white scarf to signal him!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Here's the definitive piece of evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That...? That's your definitive piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! ...If my thinking is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then. We have one mystery solved! The answer is simple. Ms. Fey's thinking is wrong. ...That's all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Please, Kitten. You've got to do something... You're killing me over here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, I've got a definitive penalty to reward you for your definitive piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, that wasn't what I was expecting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well? ...Do you finally believe me?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Come on, Mia! You're running out of time...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You've said several times in your testimony that the victim was wearing a scarf... ...A white scarf, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes... Is something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's what I'd like to know. ...Ms. Foster. Have a look at this. It's the victim's scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sure people would disagree about what to call this color. ...However! It certainly is not white! You KNEW what the note said!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She knew... the contents of the note...? N-NOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It says, "Wear white scarf for identification." That's the reason why you said it was white!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Or kidnapping a poor girl... I just think the defendant is a terrible, horrible monster!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You knew about that incident? But weren't you out of the country until the year before last?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Well, I saw a report about the escaped convict on the news. They had an in-depth report about his whole history.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you were still living abroad 5 years ago, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I can't let her get away with these lies...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen to me. She's neck-deep in this whole thing... Somehow, you're just going to have to get her to show the court her true self.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ugh... Unn... Urgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Ms. Foster!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">NOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Mr. Edgeworth! I'm waiting for an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm quite sure this note wasn't leaked to the public!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And yet...! This witness knew exactly what the note said! At the time of the murder, the number of people that knew were quite... limited. Terry Fawles is one. The person who wrote the note, Valerie Hawthorne, is another. And finally... One more person.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you say... "One more person"?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">That's right... A person that no one would have suspected... Have you figured it out, Kitten?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yup! The third person that knew the contents of the note was...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armando">...Hang on there, Kitten.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What is it, Mr. Armando?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Here. I made some special caf con leche for you... I put in plenty of sugar. Drink it up before it gets cold. Don't be shy.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm... Why are you doing this?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Your brain needs stimulation. Drink some of this and then think it over again. Listen. Keep messing up like that and you're going to get the judge mad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! Don't just stand there casually drinking coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oops... I think it's too late...</thought> B-But Your Honor...! Th-There is one more person! There is a person besides Mr. Fawles and the victim that knew what the note said.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that person is... Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dahlia Hawthorne...? I've never heard that name before.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Look at the victim's note. This is what it says... "Talk to Dahlia. Tell her this time..." There is her name, right there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this... So who is this person!? This... Dahlia Hawthorne...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh*... Ms. Fey must be desperate if she's trying to bring the dead back to life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The d-dead...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Dahlia Hawthorne was the victim's deceased younger sister. She was killed in a crime 5 years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Killed in a crime...? Y-You don't mean...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. She was kidnapped... And killed. By Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You said she was "killed"... But was she really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you implying...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course, people thought she had died 5 years ago... ...when she fell off of Dusky Bridge and was lost in the Eagle River. However! Her corpse was never found!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She was declared legally dead 5 years ago! As far as the law is concerned, Dahlia Hawthorne is officially dead.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But the fact remains that her body was never recovered! Dahlia Hawthorne was 14 years old, 5 years ago. If she were still alive, she would be 19 now. ...Melissa Foster. I believe that's the same age you are!</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even you couldn't...! Ms. Fey...! You're not saying...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But I am. That's precisely what I'm saying. This "witness" before us is the girl that was kidnapped and killed 5 years ago! This girl is in fact Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHA...! WHAAAAAAT!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Nice work... That was like tossing a grenade into a 3-alarm fire! But unless you can tie all the loose ends together... ...you're nothing but a hit-and-run arsonist.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I... I understand. <thought>If I can expose her true nature, I can turn this whole case on its head! Now is my chance to make Mr. Edgeworth squirm...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Hmm... Hmmm... Witness! Just who are you anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">I... I... I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I didn't think it'd come to this. That's enough... You don't have to say anymore, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Melissa">... Yes. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What! Mr. Edgeworth! Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. I have an admission to make. I honestly never thought the defense would pursue the matter this far...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't...! You don't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. The prosecutor's office isn't filled with fools, you know. Naturally, we conduct full background checks on all of our witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What did he say...?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! It looks like the kid knew. He knew her true identity from the get-go.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No way...! But then why...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">If you hadn't revealed her secret, he wasn't going to say anything about it. All he wanted was her testimony, so he made a little trade.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me introduce you to... ...the victim's younger sister, Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... But... I thought she died 5 years ago...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We thought so as well... But... Well, as you can see...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why!? Why did she hide her identity for 5 years!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That has nothing to do with the current case. She was merely an accidental witness to a crime...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Accidental...? I don't believe that for a minute! For the last 5 years, she's been playing the role of victim! And now we find her acting suspiciously at another murder scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Really, Ms. Fey! Your strategy is clearly obvious. You're trying to pin your client's crime on an innocent witness in order to win... ...At any cost.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">H-How dare you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, let us take a moment to think. Five years ago, this girl was kidnapped and nearly killed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But even worse than that... 5 years later... ...Dahlia Hawthorne lost something much more precious. Her big sister. Ms. Fey must be insane to even suggest that she murdered her.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm inclined to agree with the prosecutor's logic. Ms. Fey! Do you have any evidence to back up your assertion!? What possible reason would this witness have for killing her beloved sister!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Well you see... <thought>I thought I was winning, but somehow he's turned it around on me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! I think you need a little push in the right direction, Kitten...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ah! That wasn't me! It was this guy... This crazy coffee addict...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we've heard enough empty threats from you, old man.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! What makes you think they're empty, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because your protg looks like she's sweating bullets!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ah...! <thought>I AM sweating bullets!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">...You think you're in a tough spot, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course! Aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">...No. You've just arrived at the moment of truth, that's all. Whether you win or lose... That's up to you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Up to me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh*... The rashness of youth. How charming.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This coming from someone younger than me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's not waste any more time. ...Ms. Fey. What motive would this witness have for murdering her own sister, Valerie Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What is this? Is this the defense's idea of a joke?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If so, I certainly don't get the punch line... Well? Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, that was... The rashness of youth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The rashness of youth!? And what is your point in furthering such a stereotype!?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">That witness stayed hidden for 5 years, Kitten. There must be a good reason for that. And somehow it must involve Valerie Hawthorne...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>OK, one more time, Mia! You gotta read the Court Record more carefully this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...The story starts after Terry Fawles escaped. He called Valerie and told her he wanted to meet. This is the note she left... It says, "Talk to Dahlia. Tell her this time, the whole truth must come out." ...Valerie Hawthorne gave Dahlia a warning. She told her she was going to reveal to the world the whole truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The whole truth...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There was a dangerously important secret between Valerie and Dahlia. That's the reason Dahlia felt she had to kill Valerie... To keep her mouth shut permanently!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A terrific story, Ms. Fey! If you like fiction, that is. Enlighten the court, Ms. Fey. What was this secret that was so important? Where's your evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Dahlia and Valerie Hawthorne, and Terry Fawles... There's only one important secret that connects them all...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, yes... I know this secret. ...Your Honor! The defense would like to request further testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Regarding the kidnapping 5 years ago. We believe it will explain a lot of things. Such as the nature of the important secret between the Hawthorne sisters!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Ugh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. I'll grant your request for further testimony. I know it will be painful for you, but can enlighten us once more, my little maple leaf?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes, I-I'll try. Mr. Judge...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Putting on the old charm one more time, Dahlia? But this will be the last time you hide behind your womanly wiles!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Five years ago, I was kidnapped by Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The kidnapping left her emotionally scarred. With her sister's help, she left the Hawthorne family and started all over again. And we're to believe after all that, she murdered her sister? Preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Mr. Edgeworth. ...Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you've heard, the witness is still traumatized from the kidnapping. ...I'll ask you again to be extremely gentle in your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>...Mr. Edgeworth got the jump on me again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! If we're not allowed to fight, then let's twist some arms. ...Listen up. We've still got that info... That ace up our sleeve.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...What info?</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Come on, Kitten. Don't say you've forgotten already. The fact that the kidnapping 5 years ago was staged!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That's right, it was a fake kidnapping! Terry Fawles told us that in the lobby.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I do anything she says. Anything Dahlia says...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What you're saying is that the kidnapping 5 years ago was planned by...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yeah. Me and Dahlia... ...And Valerie, too.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Yes! That's it! The fake kidnapping is your best shot, Mia! That's her secret!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Five years ago, I was kidnapped by Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Did you and Mr. Fawles have a relationship?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...Y-Yes. As a tutor...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were tutoring him? Mr. Fawles?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">N-No, of course not! Don't be ridiculous! Mr. Fawles came to the house to tutor ME!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That makes sense... 5 years ago, she was only 14.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He probably came up with the kidnapping plan during that time. The Hawthornes are in the jewelry trade and are quite wealthy, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Quite the clever fellow, that Mr. Fawles.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Did I hear him right!? Did he just call Mr. Fawles a clever fellow?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The ransom price was a raw diamond. My sister, Valerie, brought it to the bridge...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I heard the diamond is valued in the neighboorhood [sic] of 2 million dollars.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">2 million dollars!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">It was still uncut, so it was about the size of a pint of milk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">HMMMMM!!! A 2 million dollar pint of milk... I don't know what to think about that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant demanded that her sister, Valerie, make the exchange. Not as a detective, of course, but as an individual.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">By the way, I want to ask you, Mr. Edgeworth. Why do you think he wanted to make the exchange up there on that mountain? If he ever got surrounded, it would be hard to escape...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's one thing a kidnapper wants to prevent, and that's police involvement. In a place like that, it would be easy to tell if he was being followed. With only one entrance to the mountain, he was ensuring his safety.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">What a wickedly clever man that Mr. Fawles is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Yeah, right. It was all YOUR plan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Anyway, Valerie brought the diamond to the mountain and...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">After she made the exchange, she shot Mr. Fawles in the arm!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That was a dangerous thing to do considering you were being held hostage.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes, but...  Actually, that saved my life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">You see, Mr. Fawles was holding a knife in his right hand... Somehow, I just KNEW he was going to use it. I knew he was going to use that knife to kill me!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's why my sister shot him! It was to save me!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's when Mr. Fawles tried to kill me by shoving me off the bridge from behind!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'd like to hear more about what happened right at that moment!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well, when Mr. Fawles was shot in the right arm, he let go of me... I-I was dazed. I turned to try and run away, but Mr. Fawles turned to grab me as well... As I ran past, he and I locked eyes for a second, and he gave me a large, bloodthirsty grin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Bloodthirsty grin... Oooh...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">And in the next instant...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I advise the court to remember that the river is 18 feet deep and incredibly swift...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I-I was a strong swimmer, but I was knocked out... When I came to, I had been carried away by the river to a strange place. I'll never forget that day. The crumbling bridge, nowhere to run... Then just one little shove from behind. That was it. Before my sister could catch me... ...I fell into the river.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I survived, but I was afraid I might be kidnapped again for my family's money...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that's why you hid your identity?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes... I only told my sister.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Valerie Hawthorne, eh.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes, she's the only one who knew about me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Meanwhile, legally, this witness has been deceased for 5 years.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I... I didn't ever want something like that to happen to me again.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">So I decided to change my identity and start a new life...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that new identity was "Melissa Foster", right?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes, my sister helped me get the official paperwork taken care of.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That makes sense... Without an insider's help, doing all of the paperwork would've been impossible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">She was the only person left in the world I could count on. And you... You think I k-k-killed her... There's no way I could!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">It's the moment of truth for this witness, too. Once the truth about this staged kidnapping comes out... Everyone in the court will know how much of a Jezebel she really is!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've just got to prove that kidnapping was a hoax!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You say that Mr. Fawles pushed you into the Eagle River... However, that's hard to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">B-But it's true! I felt a push on my back... I'm certain of it! It was Mr. Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry... I guess I wasn't clear enough. I shouldn't have said, "that's hard to believe." I should've said, "That's impossible."</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I-Impossible...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I ask that the court recall the condition of Dusky Bridge, now and 5 years ago. That bridge hasn't changed one bit in these last 5 years. If someone had pushed you from behind as you have claimed... ...instead of being carried away by the river... ...you would have been smashed by the bedrock below! A most certain death.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Do you understand now, Dahlia Hawthorne? The very notion that my client pushed you from behind is impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, this event occurred 5 years ago! Why, for all we know, the water level in the river may have been higher back then.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But it's 40 feet from the bridge to the river! A small change in the water level wouldn't have made a difference!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ugggh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You're right! If the events occurred just as the witness has testified... ...then the defendant couldn't have pushed the witness into the river. Young lady! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Uuuh! I... I... I, err... You see, I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just a moment, Your Honor! It's true that the witness testified that the defendant pushed her into the river... However! She never stated that she fell from the back end of the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What... What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After being shot in the arm, it's plausible that Mr. Fawles panicked! Therefore, he could have unwittingly pushed her off the side of the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's true, she would have fallen into the river! Well, Miss Hawthorne!? Is Mr. Edgeworth's explanation correct...?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... Now that you mention it... I do remember now. When I fell off the bridge... ...my skirt got caught on one of the bridge's side wires!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Ms. Fey's assault has finally reached its conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Not now, Mia...! This is no time to retreat!</thought> Unfortunately for you... this is just the start of Ms. Fey's assault!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I believe your reasoning went something like this, Mr. Edgeworth. "After being shot in the arm, it's plausible that Mr. Fawles panicked! Therefore, he could have unwittingly pushed her off the side of the bridge!" However! Once again, I'm forced to say, "That's impossible!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">R-Ridiculous! What's so impossible about it!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Because your flawed logic contradicts the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This evidence shows the fatal error you've made!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... It's a fatal error, alright. Unfortunately... The error is yours, not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Uh-oh, here it comes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey. At this point in the trial, I can't just let that pass!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ouchie. <thought>Come on, Mia! Take your time and think it over again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! All of the answers are right here in this photo! Take a look at the wires supporting both sides of the bridge! They extend up to about five feet off the ground... It would be impossible to push someone off from there!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">NNNNOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But let's remember the size and strength of the defendant! Wires like this wouldn't be a problem for him! He could have easily picked up a 14 year old girl and thrown her over!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So young, and already so forgetful, Mr. Edgeworth. Mr. Fawles had been shot in the right arm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And more importantly... ...Valerie Hawthorne had her gun trained on him... at point-blank range!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ugh...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So! Mr. Fawles throwing the witness off the bridge? That is clearly impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">GWAAAAAAAHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Wh-What is the meaning of this!? </line>
<line speaker="Mia">Dahlia Hawthorne! You jumped into the Eagle River intentionally!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...!? What is this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed! What do you mean by such a ridiculous remark!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes! It's ridiculous! My sister was there to help me! She had her gun and handcuffs. She could have saved me... Jumping into a raging river like that... That would have been suicide!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Perhaps... But still, that's exactly what you did! You were probably confident that you could handle the swift current. But even more so... ...the witness had a much more compelling reason for jumping into the river!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Then what was it!? What was so important that she'd want to jump into the river!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The witness is still alive. This fact alone explains everything! This is why she risked her life by jumping into the rapids of the Eagle River!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That isn't even worth a reply. Ms. Fey. I hold you personally responsible... ...for confusing the court and causing great emotional pain to the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have no choice but to impose a penalty on you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is an easy one, Mia! What was it she was after...? Even Edgeworth must have realized it...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Five years ago... ...something else disappeared along with Dahlia that day. The item that Valerie brought up the mountain with her... The 2 million dollar diamond!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">AAAAAHHH!! N... No... It-It can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes. Dahlia had it all planned from the beginning! The 2 million dollars... She was going to keep it all for herself! She forced Mr. Fawles to help her fake the kidnapping...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">At the last minute, she betrayed him and threw herself into the river... ...with the ransom tucked away safely in her backpack...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why that's... that's simply ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Your Honor! Five years ago, the witness was only 14 years old! Do you really think a 14 year old is capable of such a demonic plan!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This woman IS a demon. And there was one more person who helped make a demon out of her. Her sister... Valerie Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You mean the victim was involved in the kidnapping plot as well!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But she was a detective then! You're saying she participated in her sister's kidnapping!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Precisely! I'm sure that it weighed heavily on her conscience for the past 5 years. This is the sole reason behind the victim's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">On the day of the murder... ...after receiving the phone call from Mr. Fawles, Valerie called her sister, Dahlia. And then she told her what she was planning to do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Planning to do"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She was going to tell the whole truth... As she wrote in her note!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">THAT is what sealed Valerie Hawthorne's fate... THAT is when you hatched your demonic plan to kill two birds with one stone. A plan that would ensure neither of your accomplices to the kidnapping would talk. And THAT is why... ...you killed your sister, Valerie Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who is that!? Laughing at a time like this!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Forgive me. It's just hilarious...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness? Is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">You amuse me, woman! MS. MIA FEY...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">You can certainly weave an exciting tale... Naturally... you have the evidence to back it up, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ev-Evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Evidence that I planned the kidnapping, of course... That at 14, I plotted it with Mr. Fawles and my sister.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">And one more thing. What happened to the 2 million dollar diamond? If you can't provide evidence to at least show that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm... Well, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I... I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">What a joke. YOU, MS. FEY... Are you stupid or something?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Nnrgh...! <thought>How can I prove a fake kidnapping that happened 5 years ago!? I don't even have decisive proof of Valerie Hawthorne's murder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well it seems... that we've come to the end. To be honest, the witness's behavior does raise certain suspicions... However, I am forced to reject the assertions made by the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Of course you are.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Is this it...? Is it really over...? That girl has made a fool of me and there's nothing I can do about it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Without evidence the trial is over? Who decided that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Come on now, Kitten. Haven't you figured out that you can make your own rules? For example, even if there's no evidence, there's still testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>T-Testimony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">On the day in question, Dahlia Hawthorne murdered her sister, Valerie Hawthorne. She hid her body in the trunk of Mr. Fawles's stolen car and then went to meet with him... ...disguised as her sister, Valerie Hawthorne. That's what you think, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">In that case, there's only one answer, right? There is only one person left who can testify about Valerie Hawthorne's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Since there's no proof, there's only one thing left to do! Who is the one person who can testify to that demon woman's crimes...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Armando">Listen up. This is your last chance. Think it over carefully one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Relax, Mia! This is easy...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! The defense wishes to call a new witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A new witness?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! We would like to hear the testimony of Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's only one person that can shed any further light on the situation... Only one person that knows what Dahlia's role in the kidnapping was... Only one person that can say whether the person in the photo is Valerie Hawthorne... ...or whether it was in fact her younger sister Dahlia, disguised as her. There's only one person who can solve this riddle once and for all... And that person is... Terry Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth? What is your take on this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Why not? The prosecution has no objection.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff! Bring the defendant to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is my last chance, Mr. Fawles... My last chance to establish Dahlia's guilt... You're all I have left!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defendant, you've heard everything that's been said up to this point, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Uhh... Umm... I don't believe it! No way! Dahlia died! Five years ago! Valerie betrayed me!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles... I don't know what she said to you 5 years ago, but one thing is clear. Dahlia is very much alive. And you were used. For 2 million dollars.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That's... Not... True...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Fawles. There's only one question I want the answer to. Two days ago on Dusky Bridge... who did you meet? Was it Valerie Hawthorne? Or was it Dahlia Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia... Dahlia... Did you... betray me? ... Five years ago she promised... She promised... Never, ever betray each other...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Terry...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia! It-It's true! You are alive...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">You don't trust me anymore? That makes me sad.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Tell the truth! The real truth! I... I believed in you!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... I shouldn't NEED to say it. You should already know...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">But... There is one thing that I WILL say. My life is in your hands right now, Terry.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dah...lia...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will allow Mr. Fawles to testify once and once only. Well then, Mr. Fawles. Yours will be the final testimony in this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">GAAAAAAAHHH!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeeek! I'm sorry! I apologize!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Uwah! Uwah! UWAAAAH!! W-Water! P-Please! Water!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Can't talk... Need water...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Ha...! Oh well, I guess it'll have to be my coffee instead. At least it'll match the way he's probably feeling right now... Darker and bitterer than Hell itself.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">UWAAAAAH...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That day... 4 PM... I stopped the car. I was in front of bridge...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles! You're covering for her! Do you think she would do the same for you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's enough, Ms. Fey! His last statement was a fitting way to end the final testimony of the trial...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, Ms. Fey... Please proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Is this how you want it to end, Mr. Fawles? Another guilty verdict to go along with your death sentence!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">There's only one person who can stop it... You, Kitten. ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That day... 4 PM... I stopped the car. I was in front of bridge...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">According to the note, the meeting was supposed to take place at 4:30. You certainly arrived early, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">It was raining... Already dark, too...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You waited on the bridge for 30 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles...?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Eagle Mountain... That spot... Strong, strong memories...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... <thought>Why did he just clam up? Could it be... he's hiding something here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">She wasn't there... So, I waited on bridge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were quite early, so you waited on the bridge, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yeah... I like waiting. I'm used to it.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">I'm sure he is. Zebra Boy waited 5 years to ask a single question... To find out why a woman betrayed him. To him, 30 minutes must've been like a blink of the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I watched my car from bridge. I never put no body in that car!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were watching the car?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That bridge. Other side is broken. Nobody can come from there. So... I was watching car.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh*... What else were you expecting him to do...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I suppose that's the obvious thing to do, but... ...something's bothering me. I'm getting that feeling... A contradiction?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I wonder what's on the other side of the broken bridge anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No one lives there. There's a small shrine up on the mountain, but that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Anyway...! Nobody came... No car, nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Finally, one woman came. She stood front of me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles. Think carefully now. Are you certain that it was Valerie Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Uh. Uh. Uh... I never lie! It-It's the truth! It was... Valerie! I remembered her face!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wait a minute. If you had remembered her face... ...then why did you make her wear a scarf as identification?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Uh. Sorry. I told a little lie.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">......</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">But! The woman I met... She was different from woman standing here now! She was different! It was Valerie!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">We talked... Then she left.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What did you talk to her about anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Valerie told the truth. About the kidnapping 5 years ago. She said, "Someone needed to take the blame for it... That was all I could think to do." She said that. That's why she lied... Got me the death penalty...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And were you satisfied with that answer, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Dahlia died... It was my fault. But I don't really remember... Maybe I did... Maybe I did push her in...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">It don't matter no more... Either way... My Dahlia... My sweet Teen Angel... Dead.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>But you just saw that she isn't dead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">After Valerie talk to me on bridge... Nothing left to live for...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Fawles">That was... That was Valerie. Not my Dahlia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">How can you be so sure!? It was raining at the time, and sunset that day was at 5 o'clock. It would have already been pretty dark on that mountain at 4:30!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please Mr. Fawles! This is your last chance! You've already taken the fall once for something you didn't do!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... That woman... It wasn't Dahlia.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stop right there! What more needs to be said!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmmmm.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Even if it means the death penalty. Even if it means taking the blame for murder... You'll still do whatever is necessary to protect her... Won't you, Mr. Fawles?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armando">I know it's obvious, but... he's clearly lying. He's been cursed... by Dahlia Hawthorne. He'll probably go to his grave still believing in her.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Even if you can show he's lying, the poor guy will still be cursed... You'll still have to point out the contradiction anyway. That's the curse of being a defense lawyer, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So when you got to the bridge, no one had arrived, huh? So you waited on the bridge... You're sure of that?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... Yeah. I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You're sure, huh...? Well then I'm sure too, Mr. Fawles... I'm sure that you're lying.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Huh! Uhh... Wah... Wah! Wah! WAAAH!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? I would love to hear your rationale on this, Ms. Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You want to know who arrived at the bridge first? Just look at this photo. It's perfectly clear. Obviously the person that came first would be the one at the end of the bridge, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But that's the victim at the end of the bridge!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Precisely my point. In other words, Mr. Fawles... You must have arrived at the bridge after she did.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Nng... Urkkk... Ahhh... Ggggaah... Blah...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Umm, Mr. Fawles. Please don't get so worked up. We just want the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">... I got there around 4 o'clock. It's true.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I... I had somewhere to go. A special place...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you go to this special place before you went to the bridge?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Yeah... It's an old temple about 15 minutes from the bridge. Five years ago, me and Dahlia... We promised each other... We swore we wouldn't betray each other... She brought a memento... To represent... our love.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A memento...?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Five years ago, I hid it under base of tree there. It's a special memory for me. This is it... This is what I went to get.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This little bottle on a necklace is your memento? It's quite charming... but it looks empty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! You heard what my client said. He arrived at the scene at 4 o'clock. But he then left his car unattended and walked away! He was gone for approximately 30 minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">With that much time... ...Dahlia Hawthorne could have easily hidden the body in the trunk of his car!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-NOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... There certainly was enough time for it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've still got a chance!</thought> Mr. Fawles! There's no mistaking it!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">............ Urp!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh? Mr. Fawles...!?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Th-That's enough... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Witness?</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I-I promised her... 5 years ago... If it ever happens... ...that we can't trust each other no more... Then... ...we're supposed to... drink... bottle... Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No! Stop the trial! Your Honor! We need a recess!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">I... I was stupid... Couldn't... keep... promise... So I did it... I... drank... this...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No! We are so close! Just a little more... I was going to prove your innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">No... Don't want that... Don't... trust... self... Maybe kill again... Kill sweet Dahlia... again...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Fawles!</line>
<line speaker="Fawles">Mr. Ar... Armando... Th-Thanks... For the... coffee...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">MR. FAAAAAAAAWLES!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And so my first trial ended... Suddenly, and tragically. It ended with no winners... Only losers. I ended up with a wound that cut so deep into my soul, I thought it'd never heal. I'm sure it was the same for the young prosecutor as well. But one person... The true criminal, Dahlia Hawthorne... She left the courtroom with a secret smile on her demonically sweet face.</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Unforgivable... That witch...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando...</line>
<line speaker="Armando">We were so close to the truth. It was right there in front of us. You were just a little too soft, Kitten...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's my fault! It's all my fault that Mr. Fawles killed himself!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Don't cry, Kitten. You're going to make my coffee all salty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I knew it...! I kn-knew I wasn't cut out for this...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">............... Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Armando">Don't you get it? You can't cry yet. The only time a lawyer can cry is when it's all over.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Armando...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! What do you think of the witness's statement!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't think anything of it. How about you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... I guess I don't think anything of it either...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then we don't have a problem. But we do have a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>If there wasn't a problem, couldn't he just let it slide...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, but... I think the only thing out of place here is that pointer finger of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... That could very well be...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Here, take this penalty and try thinking things through again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What's the problem!? Pointer fingers are made for pointing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This evidence establishes that the defendant is lying, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't ask me to confirm your facts!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">S-Sorry... This is my first time handling a case...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, let's make it a memorable occasion... with a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>And here I thought he would go easy on me because I'm new...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Terry Fawles...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>