<xml>
<title>Turnabout Sisters</title>

<line speaker="April">Well hello! I didn't expect anyone to visit me in such a dank place as this... It's really quite... moving. Not! You stinking lawyer! I hope you die! Have you come to laugh? Yes, laugh at the fallen Miss May!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, not really, there's something I wanted to ask.</line>
<line speaker="April">Unfortunately, there is nothing I want to BE asked. Haven't you done enough questioning, you...! Spiky-head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here we go again...</thought> Please, you're scaring the security guard.</line>
<line speaker="April">... So? What is it you wish to ask of me, then? Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For starters, how did you get to be so totally whacked!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He hasn't moved an inch. A real pro, this guy. Or maybe he just doesn't get to see a lot of women like Miss May in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the man who stayed with you in your hotel room...</line>
<line speaker="April">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me about him? Where is he? C'mon...</line>
<line speaker="April">No way, Jose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe if I had something to get her to talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you place a wiretap on Mia's phone?</line>
<line speaker="April">Aww, when you say it like that it sounds so... cold. So criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... tapping people's phones is a crime, Miss May.</line>
<line speaker="April">Oh, and I suppose you learned that in Lawyer School, hmm? Creep!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This woman is impossible to talk to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say... Why are you so... angry? I mean, you don't look like a bad person...</line>
<line speaker="April">Ooh, that does it! Bottom-feeding, scum-sucking lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-bottom...? <thought>I can't tell, does she have a thing against lawyers... or just against me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Hey, guess what. Actually, I, um, really hate your guts. So get lost. Because, well, I'm not cooperating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks, I noticed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like forensics is taking the day off today. Detective Gumshoe's nowhere in sight. The police really gave this place a working over. I doubt there are any valuable clues left. Suppose it can't hurt to take a look around, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You couldn't cram more legal books in here, even if you wanted to. All the cases that the chief worked on are filed here. Hmm. Are some of the files missing...? Nah, I'm imagining things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. Looks like Grossberg is out today... again. Maybe he's avoiding me for some reason?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? Old photos? There are two lying here. Something's been written in pencil on the backs. "DL-6 Incident - Exhibit A," "DL-6 Incident - Exhibit B"... Let's take a look at these...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sure I've seen this person somewhere... Perhaps I'll borrow this photo. I'm sure no one will miss just one little photo. And it might be a valuable clue... I'll take it for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would Grossberg have a picture of this man...? This might be a valuable clue... I'll take it for now. I'm just borrowing it. I'll return it later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't need it now, whatever it is. If I ever run out of clues, I'll know where to find these. <thought>Although I can't be sure the photos will still be here then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A photo lies on the desk. Maybe I should switch it with the one I took?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'll swap them...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, on second thought, I'd better not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second... Wasn't there a giant painting hanging on that wall...? Yeah... yeah, it was a painting of...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wasn't it? It wasn't a very memorable painting, anyhow.</line>
<line speaker="April">YOU AGAIN!? Can't you take a hint and stay gone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, the only reason I'm back here is because YOU won't talk to me!</line>
<line speaker="April">Oh, so it's MY fault now? You don't just have spiky hair, you also have a spiky heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That does it. When this case is done I'm shaving my head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the man who stayed with you in your hotel room... Can you tell me about him? Where is he?</line>
<line speaker="April">I'm not telling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, he's being accused of murder! I don't think you want to be protecting him.</line>
<line speaker="April">Hmm. Would you have sold out the late Ms. Fey to the cops?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No.</line>
<line speaker="April">See?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Damn! Hmm... maybe if I had something to get her to talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any thoughts about this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="April">... Who's that? Your mother?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... *sigh* Looks like I've just been wasting my time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="April">Look, I've said several times, I'm not telling you...&#160;! Where did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah hah! A reaction!</thought> This is him, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="April">What? Who? When? Why...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It IS him. This is the man who stayed in your hotel room the night of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="April">No! No, that's not right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice try, Miss Cooperative.</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">D-do you have proof that was him? Hmm? Y-yeah! Proof! Show me proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm so close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, welcome, sir! Quite the performance today, if I dare say so myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um, thanks. Sorry for putting you on the spot like that.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">No, no, not at all, sir! Your efforts today can only help the Gatewater's "rep," as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? "Rep"?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Yes! Our reputation will swell as the hotel where the murderer used a wiretap! We can charge a premium for the room, of course. It will be great for business, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa, whoa! Miss May hasn't been charged with murder.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">I, too, will become famous! "The Bellboy who brought the murderer ice coffee"...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I feel like we're both stuck in the same bad dream...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">So! You are our honored guest. Please let me know if there is anything I can bring you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A vase, as expected. I'm not good with flower names, except maybe tulips and sunflowers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? There's still a screwdriver stuck in that drawer!</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, please leave that as it is, sir. That's the "Drawer of Terror, Hiding Place of the Murderer's Wiretap." It's set to become one of the most popular attractions here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy's serious! I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bottle and two glasses rest on the table. Why hasn't he cleaned these up by now?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, I beg your pardon, sir, but if you could please refrain from touching those... It's part of the decor. I call it: "The last drink... before murder!" We'll be famous! The talk of the hotel industry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice weather again today. I can see the Fey &amp; Co. Law Offices, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, yes. We plan to install a telescope in that window, of course. Just $5.00 will earn you three minutes of a "view to a kill"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">J-just kidding, sir. Oh hoh hoh hoh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By that look in his eyes I'd say he was more than serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Miss May...</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Oh, her? Sir, not to boast but I knew the moment I saw her... "She'd do it!" I said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do WHAT!? I'm starting to think the most suspicious person here is this guy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you about the man who was with Miss May...?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, yes... He struck me as a real "Lady Killer," if you'll pardon the expression. I knew it from the moment I saw him, sir. He and I are of the same ilk. We both carry the scent of... danger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There we are in total agreement, Mr. Psycho Bellboy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">If you had a photo of that man, I'm quite sure I could identify him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A photo. Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about this hotel?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Absolutely! And on that subject, I have an excellent idea, sir! Currently, this hotel is known as the "Gatewater." I propose that we add a subtitle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A subtitle!?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">The Gatewater Hotel -- Murder Manor --Well? What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... sounds great! <thought>Whatever floats your tea set...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Well, it's a fine photo, sir. However, the person Miss May was accompanied by was, well, a man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... yeah. Right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">... That's him, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I'm the lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Oh, I know that! I just wanted to say "Detective" once. You know how it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No. No I don't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Without a doubt, that is the man who checked in with Miss April May. How about I write an affidavit swearing that that's him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An affidavit? <thought>This guy is way too excited about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well thanks, but I don't think that will be necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Oh? Oh, I see. Well later then, if you need it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, sure. Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Yes! I've always wanted to write an affidavit, sir. From hence forth I will be known as the "bellboy who swore the affidavit"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just hurry up and write it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not even Miss May can play dumb to this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to press the matter, but are you sure this is him?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">I, too, am sorry to press the matter, but that is him, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for this.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">No no no, not at all, sir! I hope you'll use it to take that Miss May down hard, sir! Hard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I sense an unhealthy level of excitement behind that unchanging smile? His tea set is rattling!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">I'm sorry... All I could think about during the trial was the hotel... I wasn't paying much attention to the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* He's out again? Huh? No more photos on the desk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="April">You're wasting your time! Miss May's lips are sealed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you have a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="April">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bellboy's affidavit! He told us everything he saw. He told us about the man you checked in with. He told us who he was.</line>
<line speaker="April">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm getting somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, okay... she's vulnerable now. I should be gentle.</thought> Miss May... It would be easy for me to hand this affidavit to the police.</line>
<line speaker="April">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If they get involved, wouldn't your boss be even more... er... inconvenienced? All I want to do is have a little chat with him. You won't tell me?</line>
<line speaker="April">... Is that all you have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="April">Id it's so easy for you to "get the police involved," then why don't you? Somehow I think you're not up to it, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Show them a little kindness and they jump all over you! That had the opposite effect to what I hoped...</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Aww. *smirk* Poor little lawyer... And you were so close!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't working... I think I've worn out this piece of paper's usefulness.</thought> Dammit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The man in this photo is the one I want! Why did April May not want to talk about it... she must know him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it, all or nothing! Time to do a little bluff.</thought> No use playing dumb! <thought>If, indeed, that's an act.</thought> If you don't talk, I'm taking this photo to the press!</line>
<line speaker="April">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even though he should be a witness to murder, this man is in hiding. I'm sure the press would have a field day with his reputation!</line>
<line speaker="April">...! Ooooh! Fine! I'll talk! You... you win, Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes! Man, that felt good! It's great to be alive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Why are you pumping your fists in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*cough* Now, tell me about the man you were with.</line>
<line speaker="April">That man... He's my boss. Redd White, the president of the information gathering conglomerate, Bluecorp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Redd... White?</thought> "Information gathering?"</line>
<line speaker="April">Well... I suppose you could call them a detective agency.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... So this is the man that was with you the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="April">... I'm... I'm scared to talk. I don't want to end up like her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...!</thought> It's okay, I'll just ask Mr. White himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me where Bluecorp is located?</line>
<line speaker="April">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Redd White, at last! Finally, a lead on this guy! If April May couldn't have done it, that leaves him! Time to take action!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. The bellboy seems to be out. Huh? The sound of water coming from the shower...</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">"La-dee-da! Money-Makin'... Money-Makin'... I got the Money-Makin' bluuuues..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone seems to enjoy washing the showers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The screwdriver is still stuck in the drawer. I'd better not touch it. No telling what the bellboy would do to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bottle and two glasses rest on the table. I'd better not touch them. No telling what the bellboy would do to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright, this is getting ridiculous. Where the heck is that loafer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">*Ah-HHHHEM!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, that old familiar clearing of the throat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah hah! You again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, hello, Mr. Grossberg.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Well, well. You were quite the thing, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">The trial! The trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He was there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Reminded me of myself when I was a youth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess something got passed down through Mia... maybe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It brings back memories, it does! "Ah... the days of my youth... like the scent of fresh lemon..." you see. ... I apologize.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I... It was all a bit too much for me, my boy. Seeing you today, I... well, I... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I appreciate the reminiscing, but I'd much rather you gave me some information!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you came to see the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, yes I did. Something was bothering me all last night, you see. I couldn't get a wink of sleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, you see, it's just... Mia's sister, that poor girl. My boy, I owe you my thanks, truly. I don't know what I would have done if things had gone poorly for the girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you were that worried about it, why didn't you offer to defend her!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I asked before, but, why did you refuse her request for defense? I think I have a right to know.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">A right, Mr. Wright? No, no, I'm sorry. It's just, I need more time to think about it, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>He does seem troubled about something... Maybe I can find something that will inspire him to talk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The other day I'm sure there was a big, pretentious-looking painting on that wall...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">"Pretentious-looking"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... you know the one I mean. Anyway, where did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, yes, well... I... got rid of it. Got quite tired of the thing, really. I, er, sold it, you see. Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sold it!? I'm not sure I buy that...</thought> Wasn't that painting rather important to you, sir? Did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I don't see how it's any of your business! Please, speak no more of that accursed painting. I didn't... I... *mumble* *mumble*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Ah, my apologies. I need to think about things. Alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He barely even glanced in my direction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, I was wondering about this photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...! Where did you get that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I borrowed it.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, give it back at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg. Tell me about the man in this photo. He may have been in that hotel room with April May on the night of the murder. Do you know something about him... anything?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...! Hmm. Ahem! Very well. I'll tell you what I know. However... You didn't hear it from me, if you follow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That man is Mr. Redd White. He's the President of Bluecorp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Redd White... Hmm.</thought> Bluecorp... they're something like a detective agency, right?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">They're information pros. They sell information, you see. Sensitive information. Despite his name, Mr. White has the blackest reputation of any man in this country. Should you run across him, watch what you say. You wouldn't want him digging up any dirt on you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... selling information. Sounds like blackmail.</thought> Can you tell me where Bluecorp is located?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Redd White, at last! Finally, a lead on this guy! Even if April May couldn't have done it, he could have! Time to take action!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Now, I must ask you to leave. I need to think about things. Alone.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Where did you get that!? Give it back at once!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry to have taken it without your knowledge. But... I have to know. Who is this man? He was most likely in April May's room the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">! What's that you say!? A-are you QUITE sure? My boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What has him so flustered I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I... I beg your pardon, but I must ask you to leave. I need to be alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...! He's fallen silent as a stone. A rather large stone. I guess I should return that photo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I beg your pardon, but I am not at liberty to speak on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>What's with the surreal décor...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Welcome! Please furnish me with the title of your personage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What the...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Your name! What's your name? I was just inquirably asking the title that you go by.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Wright. Phoenix Wright. <thought>"Inquirably"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Mr. Wright, is it? Right, I see... Splendiferous. Perhaps I have intimidated you with my giantesque vocabulary...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this guy's problem!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">I'm Redd White, CEO of Bluecorp. You know, Corporate Expansion Official? My business dealings bring me into contact with the elite of the elite. So I'm afraid I am not used to conversing with the wordily-challenged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a fruitcake!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Hmmm, let me guess... You are an attorney fresh out of law school, are you not? That's the only explanation for why you would come to meet me like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does he mean by that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">No matter. So, what business does a "mighty" lawyer have with a man such as myself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yipes! This guy's arrogance meter is off the scale!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing this is supposed to be a desk? My my... This is quite the... thing.</line>
<line speaker="White">It is modeled on my body, see? Well? Does its sleek roundature not... inspire you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Haven't I seen this somewhere...? Is this a replica?</line>
<line speaker="White">Ridiculosity! I have no interest in anything but originals. That right there is a bona fide original! Worth five million, for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A statue of a man holding up the world. The "Bluecorp" sign certainly stands out enough... The model for the man is, of course, Mr. White.</line>
<line speaker="White">Truly a work of art! But, probably to beautacious for you to appreciate, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think it's a little too "beautacious" for just about anyone to appreciate.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An impressive line-up of trophies. "Judges Special Runner-up" "Best Participation" "Judges Cooperation Award" "Special Good Try Prize" Hmm. The words "Judges" and "Special" kind of stand out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the top floor of a 20-story building. The view is quite... presidential.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miss May is an employee of Bluecorp, is she not?</line>
<line speaker="White">Correct. She was my secretariat. What a shock it was to hear what she has done!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"What she has done"... You mean the wiretap?</line>
<line speaker="White">Indeed! She is paid to answer phones. Tapping them is NOT in her job description. She does gather information for us as part of her duties. But, I assure you, we do not condone illegal methods! It is ineffable that she would do this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like he's trying to turn Miss May into a scapegoat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night of the murder were you in April May's hotel room?</line>
<line speaker="White">Who can say? I seldom pay attention to mundane details such as time and place. My motto is: "Don't worry, be happy!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, Mr. White... The hotel bellboy has stated on the record that he does remember you very clearly.</line>
<line speaker="White">... No matter! The bellboy can say what he pleases. I still won't talk to you. If you want me to speak, put me on the witness stand! Although I doubt you'd be capable of doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. He raises a good question, actually... Why didn't prosecution call him as a witness? He should have "seen" the same thing as April May!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Oh hoh hoh. The police... the courts... To me they are mere toys. Playthings for my amusement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of company is Bluecorp, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="White">Ah, excellent question! We buy and sell various kinds of information. We are a company of the future! You might say, we ARE the future!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sell... information?</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">In just 10 years, I've built this business up into the grand office you see now. Ah, in case you were wondering, Bluecorp was named after the color "blue"! I, Redd White of Bluecorp, as founder and CEO, named it so! And why, you ask? Because I like the color blue of course! Fantabulistic, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... there's something that's been bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="White">Yes? What might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That big painting on the wall over there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a very striking piece of art.</line>
<line speaker="White">Magnificentatious, isn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. ... <thought>Why am I making small talk...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I've actually seen that painting before.</line>
<line speaker="White">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just yesterday, actually.</line>
<line speaker="White">Your point being...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My point is simple. Er, rather, my question is simple: Why is that painting hanging on your wall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, when did you get that painting?</line>
<line speaker="White">... Hmm... no idea! I forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've seen that painting before. Yesterday, in fact. Why do I find that painting here today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this wiretap...</line>
<line speaker="White">Ah, the one that Miss May used, right? Bad girl. Bad, bad girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She testified that she placed the wiretap at your request.</line>
<line speaker="White">How pathetic. I guess she's trying to pass the buck. Bad, bad girl. Sorry I can't help you. I know nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going to need hard evidence to get anything out of this guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this picture...</line>
<line speaker="White">Gorgeous! That's a picture of me! Ah, I see it was taken in the prime of my youth. About 10 years ago, at a guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The hotel bellboy says he saw this man on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="White">... On closer inspection, he does look a lot like me, but I'm afraid this is someone else. Nope. That's definitely not me. He's far too young.</line>
<line speaker="White">I am terribly sorry. But that really doesn't seem to concern me at all.</line>
<line speaker="White">... Mr. Wrong, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wright.</line>
<line speaker="White">It appears you do not fully grasp your position here. I ask again. Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... huh? A lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="White">No, my feeble friend. A "mere" lawyer. Worth nothing. Zilch. Zippo. Nada! Just like that sorry excuse for an attorney, Grodyburger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what!?</thought> Ungh! Oof...! Unh... uhhh... <thought>He... he punched me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Well, Mr. Lawyer. What will you do, eh? Charge me with assault? Charge away, I welcome it! For it is YOU who will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="White">Heed my exposition! The police, the courts, they all do my bidding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So you say... But I wonder... Is that kind of control really possible?</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">I don't expect you to understand. It is a world beyond your compensation. ... You came here from Grodyburger's, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg's... yes.</line>
<line speaker="White">Then you must ask him: Why is it that this painting of his hangs here? Perhaps then he will tell you? Perhaps he will explain how a man can live life purely for personal profit! ... Go now! Skedaddle! There is nothing more to discuss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm guessing this is supposed to be a desk? My my... This is quite the... thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This painting was, until yesterday, hanging in Mr. Grossberg's office. Why does White have it now? It's not hard to imagine a few possibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A statue of a man holding up the world. The "Bluecorp" sign certainly stands out enough... The model for the man is, of course, Mr. White.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An impressive line-up of trophies. "Judges Special Runner-up" "Best Participation" "Judges Cooperation Award" "Special Good Try Prize" Hmm. The words "Judges" and "Special" kind of stand out. He probably strong-armed them into giving him something.</line>
<line speaker="White">Would you be kind enough to cease your inane chattering and vacate the premises? Let me put it in language you are sure to understand: Shut up and get out! I have nothing more to say.</line>
<line speaker="White">Would you be kind enough to cease your inane chattering and vacate the premises? Let me put it in language you are sure to understand: Shut up and get out! I have nothing more to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently, Miss May is in questioning. I doubt they'll let me talk to her today.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? I don't think he's noticed me standing here. Maybe I should... clear my throat?</thought> Aaa-HHHEM!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Jumping Jehosephats! Oh! You!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong? You looked so pensive... like an old man at the end of his days.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm? I'm not senile yet! I was just thinking about this whole mess...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something's really bothering him, that much is clear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you came to see the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, yes I did. Something was bothering me all last night, you see, couldn't get a wink of sleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, you see, it's just... Mia's sister, that poor girl. My boy, I owe you my thanks, truly. I don't know what I would have done if things had gone poorly for the girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I asked before, but, why did you refuse her request for defense? I think I have a right to know.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">A right, Mr. Wright? No, no, I'm sorry. It's just, I need more time to think about it, my boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>He does seem troubled about something... I'm starting to have a feeling I know what it is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, I paid Bluecorp a visit.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh? Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg... I have to admit, something has been bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh? What is it? Well, out with it, my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You see, it's just...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg, sir... There was a giant painting hanging right there the other day, was there not? The one you said you had "no intention of parting with"? Well, I saw it. Today. It was in the CEO's office at Bluecorp. Redd White's office.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... So... you noticed. I suppose I should have guessed you would. It is a large painting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg, I know you and Mr. White are connected somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">C-connected, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! And I know what it is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're his client, aren't you? He's giving you information!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What's that now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been protecting him all along. You protect him because you need his services!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You gave him that painting in exchange for some valuable information, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Utterly ridiculous. Me, his client? I would never willingly deal with that man. Never!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Did I get it wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. White has something on you doesn't he? Blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that painting is fairly gaudy proof.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Very well. This may be the chance I've been waiting for. Maybe it's time to get this off my chest, so I can finally rest easy again. After all, you were Mia's understudy. Perhaps it was fate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's he talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not something I can claim to understand... But you and Mr. White are lovers, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">W-w-what! My boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sent that painting to him! As a sign! A sign of undying love!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">M-m-my boy, please! You're letting your fancies run away with you! Where do you get these bizarre ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I don't understand how you could...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That's because I'm not, we're not... Don't be ridiculous! ... Enough. I'll swallow my pride and tell you all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it! They are lovers!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">N-no! We are NOT lovers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That photo of Mr. White... Why would you have his photo, Mr. Grossberg?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Umm... yes, well. It's been a long time since then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A long time ago? I'm sorry... but I think not. I think you still have ties to Mr. White even today.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">R-really! Whatever gave you that idea! W-what connection could I possibly have to an individual such as he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's pretty straightforward, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You go drinking together! You're friends, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Now you're being foolish, my boy. Why in the world would I ever drink with the likes of him!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Whoops... maybe that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. White has something on you doesn't he? Blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...! I don't... I don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg, sir... There was a giant painting hanging right there the other day, was there not? The one you said you had "no intention of parting with"? Well, I saw it. Today. It was in the CEO's office at Bluecorp. Redd White's office.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... So... you noticed. I suppose I should have guessed you would. It is a large painting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg... tell me what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Redd White is supplying you with information, obviously!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What's that now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been protecting him all along. You protect him because you need his services!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Now you're being foolish, my boy. What possible use could I have for the services of the likes of him!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Whoops... maybe that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought it was strange. Here was Maya, your own apprentice's little sister, in desperate need... Accused of killing her own sister no less, and you wouldn't take the case! I finally realized why. You and Redd White are connected. He's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll bet you and White go way back! He's your boss now, and was before, I bet!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">My what? Boss? Are you serious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! You both have that sort of "we're in the same club together" feel to you.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Please, stop. You have a very peculiar sense of humor, Mr. Wright. Very well, I'll talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What does he mean... "sense of humor"? I was serious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. White has something on you doesn't he? Blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...! I don't... I don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg, sir... There was a giant painting hanging right there the other day, was there not? The one you said you had "no intention of parting with"? Well, I saw it. Today. It was in the CEO's office at Bluecorp. Redd White's office.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... So... you noticed. I suppose I should have guessed you would. It is a large painting...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg... tell me what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not something I can claim to understand... But you and Mr. White are lovers, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">W-w-what! My boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg. The other day, there was a giant painting hanging on that wall. I saw that painting again, today. It was in the CEO's office of Bluecorp. It was a present, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, my boy, you have a splendid imagination!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I don't understand how you could...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That's because I'm not, we're not... Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess I was wrong. But it just seemed so right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Sorry, my boy. I don't think I can help you with that.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Redd White is a man who makes his living through intimidation. Bluecorp is a company that excels in finding people's weaknesses, I'm afraid. I've been paying them for 15 years now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>15 years...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">All because of the "DL-6 Incident," as you may have guessed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The name on the back of those photographs!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">As you suspected, I could not stand in defense of Maya because of this. White would have destroyed me if I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's the connection!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It is hard for me to tell you this, my boy. But arresting Redd White will be nigh on impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Impossible? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He has information on everyone. It gives him an iron grip! He owns judges, attorneys, prosecutors, police... and politicians.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">They are bound, unable to do harm to themselves, and therefore, to him. Don't look at me like that. What you see is nothing more than the weight of many years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is the "DL-6 Incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">"DL-6" is nothing more than the sorting code the police gave the case. It was 15 years ago now... I received a request from a medium. A spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A medium...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Her name was Misty Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Indeed. She was Mia's mother. She had been investigating a murder at the bequest of the police. And... she failed. As a result, the police called her a fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is what Maya was talking about the other day!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I did all I could for her, and in the end, cleared her of wrongdoing. That murder case, however remains unsolved to this day. That case, is the DL-6 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why were you blackmailed over this, Mr. Grossberg?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">The DL-6 Incident was top-secret at the time. It made sense. The police didn't want people to know they were using a medium! They couldn't let people know. But one person found out. I... I told him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You told White?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He offered me riches... It is an embarrassment to me now. Because I talked, the police were mocked far and wide. In secret, they began looking for the one who sold them out. Of course White heard about it, and he came to me. Only this time, the offer was blackmail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... White controls the law of this country as he sees fit. Yet if you would still challenge him... Have a close look at Mia's office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's office...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">She followed his every move for years. She may have recorded something of what she found.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's funny, looking at this room, it seems... so normal. Hard to imagine a murder took place here. Mr. Grossberg said there would be clues... Maybe I should have another look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All the cases the chief ever worked on are filed here. They're in alphabetical order. Let's take a look... Which file should I look at...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see if there's "A" record in this file that catches my "I." "A"... "B"... "F"! "Misty Fey." That's Mia and Maya's mother. Hmmm... Should I take a look?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"'I have tarnished the Fey name.' Leaving only these words, my mother vanished. I was determined to find the ones who had made my mother blame herself in this way. Using the E.S.P. that runs in my family, I held an audience with the dead. Finally, the names of two men surfaced. One was Marvin Grossberg, a lawyer who sold my mother's information for riches. The other was the man who sold that information to the press. This parasite, who makes his fortune on threats and coercion... His name is..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. The record stops there. ... So Mia knew Grossberg...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it has much to do with the current case. I'd be interested to know what it contains... but I'll leave it alone for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... "J" through "S"... Nothing much in here. Maybe I'll just skim some of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah... this is taking too long. Later. *yawn* I've never been good at reading these things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"T"... "U"... I know, "W"! "White"! ...&#160;! The entire "W" section is missing! Was it taken...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* Well, no harm in flipping through a bit, I guess... The biggest part's here at the end in "S"... "Suicide"? Eww... She has a collection of suicide reports. There's politicians... policemen... ... ...! There's writing on most of these in pencil. "White"...? This is Mia's handwriting. Wait, I get it! Mia thought he was involved in these "suicides"! White drove them all to... ... I can use these newspaper clippings. Hmm... let's find the most disturbing one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Shall I check Mia's files once more?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which file to check?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... not much in the "J-S" section. I'm not sure reading suicide accounts will be very good for my mood... I think that's enough reading for today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see much point in checking files that are missing all the key parts. *yawn* I give up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this in Mia's files...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So she was investigating Redd White, as I expected. Well, if you wanted to challenge him, you could present this in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not a bad idea...</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Well, aren't you persistent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but there's something I have to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="White">Mr. Lawyer, I really hate having to repeat myself... But it seems the message has not yet penetrated your thick skull... Stop bothering me! If you try my patience further, I fear a nasty accident may occur. Do I make myself clear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Transparent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think we're past needing to talk about April May. I've got to put this guy on the spot, and quick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Hmm? What's the matter? You seem... distressed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy is a pro at pulling the wool over people's eyes. I've got to put him on the spot, and quick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Stop that! Your hot gaze is giving me goosebumps!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no point asking someone this crooked a straight question! I need some evidence I can use as ammo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">What's wrong? Is something stuck to my face? Why yes! There's my eyes, and my nose, and my mouth... But of course I jest. You need not restrain your mirth, my friend! It is okay to indulge in my cosmopolitan sense of humor. I will not think less of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the only clue that Mia left me... I'd better make this one count!</thought> Mr. White... see this? It's an article describing the suicide of a politician.</line>
<line speaker="White">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was embezzling secret government funds. Then, one day, word got leaked to the press. The very next day he took his own life.</line>
<line speaker="White">And this concerns me how...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this article in Mia's office.</line>
<line speaker="White">Miss Mia...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She had a file filled with articles like this. Every one of them was labeled with a single word... "White."</line>
<line speaker="White">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. White, I know what you did to this politician.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You bribed him!</line>
<line speaker="White">B-bribed!? ... What exactly has led you to say this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... gee, that's a good question. I guess I got ahead of myself there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">Hmph. You certainly have an active imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dammit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were spying on him, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="White">"Spying"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You snooped on him, and found out about the embezzlement. Then, when you revealed it, he was driven to suicide!</line>
<line speaker="White">Mr. Lawyer. I know nothing of this. And, even in the highly unlikely event that I did do such a thing... All I would have done is provide "information." That is not a crime in this country.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gah! This guy's as cool as a cucumber...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="White">I have no intention of parleying with you about this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were blackmailing him!</line>
<line speaker="White">Blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not just him, either. You were threatening and coercing hundreds of others! You were involved in all of the suicide cases that Mia investigated! This company is built on blackmail! I'm right, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="White">What a bizarre accusation. Mr. Wrong... What is it that you should be doing now? Investigating me? No no no. I think not! You should be searching for the one who killed Miss Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[Secretary's Office, hello?]</line>
<line speaker="White">Mr. Wrong will be leaving now.</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[Yes, sir. I'll send someone right away.]</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second, Mr. White...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are absolutely right. I should be looking for the killer now. And actually, I've done better. I've found him. He's sitting right in front of me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're wrong, Mr. White.</line>
<line speaker="White">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I should be doing now is going after you!</line>
<line speaker="White">Just what are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia was on to you. She was keeping tabs. For this reason you had April May tapping her phone. Then, Mia was murdered, and all the documents about you mysteriously disappeared. So, the culprit would be...?</line>
<line speaker="White">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even a child could work it out, Mr. White. You did it!</line>
<line speaker="White">...</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[Secretary's office.]</line>
<line speaker="White">We won't be needing an escort for Mr. Wrong. Instead, please connect me to the public prosecutor's office.</line>
<line speaker="White">Hello. Chief Prosecutor? I've changed my mind. I want to testify tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[What's this about?]</line>
<line speaker="White">The Mia Fey case. I witnessed the murder, you see. And, thus, as a very important witness, I would like to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[What? Why now? I thought you said you didn't want to go to court?]</line>
<line speaker="White">Quietude...! I told you I changed my mind, didn't I? Oh, and one other thing. Send the police over here right away. The man is standing right in front of me. He looks dazed but could be violent!</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[What? What man?]</line>
<line speaker="White">Are you even listening? The executioner! The hatchet-man! The liquidator... The killer, man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">[Mr. White... this isn't another one of those...]</line>
<line speaker="White">Chief Prosecutor. I do not believe you are in a position to freely offer your opinions to me, correct? I'm telling you to send the police, now!</line>
<line speaker="Interphone">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="White">... Did I not tell you, Mr. Wrong? You are a mere lawyer! As was Miss Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How dare you!</line>
<line speaker="White">I'll point the finger at you, and you will be tried as Miss Mia's killer! The case is as good as settled. No lawyer of any worth will defend you. I have friends in the local lawyer's association, you see. You'll be given a lawyer so stupendously inept that they make even you look competent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I feel faint.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Gumshoe, reporting, sir! Aaa! Butz! Hairy Butz!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wright, actually. Phoenix Wright. And my friend's name is "Larry"...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, right! Sorry, pal. Butz was that murderer, right?</line>
<line speaker="White">Detective Gumshoe. I present to you, the man who killed Miss Mia Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="White">Take this despicable human being into custody. ... Farewell, Mr. Wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe it's only been a day since the first trial. My trial begins tomorrow. White's going to set a trap for me. And the prosecution will be in on it, of course. Edgeworth, included. An attorney was assigned to me by the state, yesterday. I refused. I had an idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Wright! Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Maya! Great, they let you out of detention.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just now, yes. It's all thanks to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah. Now I'm afraid we've switched places.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? You mean, you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I explained what had happened to Maya. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't believe it! How many people does that man need to destroy before he's satisfied!? My mother... My sister... And now you! This has gone too far! Mr. Wright, please tell me, is there anything I can do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, you can be my defense lawyer tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Leave it to me! I am Mia's sister, after all! Lawyership runs in our blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wasn't it E.S.P. that ran in your blood...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'd better run to the bookstore and pick up a copy of "Law for Rookies."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you could cheer for me in court.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Cheer for you? You mean... like a cheerleader?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Um, yeah, like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'd better go get a uniform and some pom-poms...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Okay, listen up. I want you to help me break out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean... a jail break?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Tonight's our only chance!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I'd better go get a hacksaw while the stores are still open. Oh, oh! And a rope ladder, and a getaway car! Can you drive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... W-wait. Wait wait wait.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What what what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm kidding! It was a joke!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No really, I was kidding. But thanks. It's good to know you're on my side. <thought>And there really isn't anything you can do for me anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... but I can't just sit here and do nothing! I've got to give that man a piece of my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just a piece...?</thought> Okay. Then, come to the court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-okay! I'll be there! I'll show them a thing or two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the beginning of a new century, yet with crime it's the same old story. In fact, it's gotten worse. Lengthy court proceedings are no longer realistic. Beginning a few years ago, a limit of three days was put on initial court trials. Almost all finish in a day. Most with a guilty verdict. I never thought I would end up in the defendant's chair myself. Tomorrow the true culprit will appear as a witness. This is it! It's me or him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>