
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Academy</title>
<line speaker="Athena">...Sorry, Boss. I couldn't do it. You know, that little bit of advice you gave me? "The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles"? I don't know exactly what you meant... ...but there was no way I could force a smile in that courtroom today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just glad you remembered that. But now how about relaxing a little--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Relax?! Not gonna happen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie... she asked me to defend her because she believes in me. But I... I... felt completely helpless. If it weren't for their confessions, I'd...!</line>
<line speaker="Means">But if this trial proceeds in the same manner and ends in the same way as the mock trial... ...would you not lose everything you've worked so hard to gain?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'll just have to make sure that doesn't happen, then, won't I!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>No, I can't lose it all! Not now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You okay, Athena? You're turning kind of pale.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I can't just stand around here! I'm going to finish the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can't it wait? I just took a batch of freshly baked cookies out of my magic panties!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, but I'd better get going! Save me one for when I get back. Apollo, you wait here! I need to see Junie at the Detention Center first right away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! I'm going with you! Sorry, Mr. Wright, but I'd better go too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No problem. You two be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's so much I need to ask Junie. What happened in court today... Where we go from here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, now! Fancy meeting you here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Prof. Means. What brings you here?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I asked him to come. He arrived just a little before you. I wanted to ask him something. But first, Athena... I want to apologize for my sudden confession after you worked so hard to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She was calling me "Thena" until just now...</thought> No, I should be the one apologizing. The whole thing spiraled out of my control.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Athena, I--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry! I'll really bring it tomorrow! I'll find something to prove your innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">About that............ Athena... I've been thinking of asking Prof. Means to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I myself only just heard of this a moment ago.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh... So, she thinks Prof. Means would be... No! I can't let this happen! Not with the way he wants to do things!</thought> J-Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I know, Athena, but will you please hear me out?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Athena, do you actually think Hugh or Robin could've committed this crime?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The body was moved right before the mock trial. Besides Junie, they're the only ones... ...who could move freely around the campus at that time...</thought> I'm sorry, Junie, but at this point, I can't rule them out.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was afraid you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Juniper is seeking a lawyer who can clear all three of their names. Only I am capable of such a feat.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But how can you possibly prove that all three of them are innocent?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I am a result-oriented person. Come tomorrow, I won't fail to have the perfect piece of evidence ready. For the end really does justify the means, especially for me, Prof. Aristotle Means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh... I really don't like the sound of that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I'm sorry, but... Just as you believe I'm innocent, I believe that my friends are innocent, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right. If that's how you really feel, we'll respect your decision.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we want to continue our investigation. Could we ask you some more questions?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Sure, I don't mind. Prof. Means, would you like to stay and join our conversation?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes, of course. I am your lawyer, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's that smile again. Why does it always creep me out?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">About your confession, Junie. It's not true, is it? </line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. I wasn't thinking straight. All I knew was I had to help my friend.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean, because of that school rule? The one that says you can't graduate if you are convicted of a crime?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No! I didn't do it because of some rule! I did it because she's my friend *cough* *cough, cough*... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Why is there discord in her voice again? ...Could it really be that the friendship between the three of them is on the rocks? There's more here than meets the eye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">When did you three first become friends?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well... Even though we were in different courses, we really bonded from the first day of school. We vowed to work together to bring an end to the dark age of the law. That was when our proof of friendship came about.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's that proof of friendship again. I just wish this were as simple as that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. We even have proof of our friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeaaaaaah!!! As long as our friendship lasts! You can bet we'll be carrying them around!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But the situation kind of changed recently. When the school's policy shifted to training legal professionals who produce results--</line>
<line speaker="Means">Allow me to explain. In the lawyer course I teach, producing results means winning trials. Prof. Courte, on the other hand, taught that finding the truth was the only valid result. Unfortunately, that clash of ideas created a rift among our students.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">At some point, we stopped talking about it. While that meant fewer arguments... ...it also meant we couldn't be as frank and open with each other as we used to be.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I think I understand now. By putting their friendship on a pedestal, they actually did more harm than good. It seems the relationship between the three of them isn't as simple as I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Juniper, thank you for talking to us about this difficult subject.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, thanks, Junie. Now, if you could tell us about the day of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, you told us yesterday that you went home a little after 6:00 PM. Was that a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...I'm sorry I didn't tell you this before, but... ...what actually happened was I left the art room a little after 6:00 PM and... ...headed over to my dressing room, where I worked on my stage costume until 7:00.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's it? You didn't go anywhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No, nowhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If that really were it, then there would be no reason to lie in the first place. She's gotta be hiding something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Junie, do you remember this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, but something's wrong here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wrong? What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I took this picture at around 6:00, which was before I'd left the art room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the clock here says it's just after 7:00.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">By 7:00, I'd already been working in my dressing room for some time. So, there's definitely something wrong with the time in this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm, I guess we'd better go check the art room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, just one last question about the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">On the day before the mock trial -- the evening of the murder -- you ran into Hugh.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............Yes, I did.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">At around 7:15, I went to the main building before going home. That's when I saw Juniper. We didn't say much as we passed by each other. She seemed her usual self. That's it. Anything else you'd like to ask?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She suddenly went silent. She always was terrible at hiding things. Was she trying to keep their meeting a secret by lying about going home at 6:00?</thought> All right, I won't press the matter any further.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That was just a prop. To think it would become an actual murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The killer is trying to make this case look exactly like your script. That's why this awl was used like that.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But... But why would anyone do that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, that's the million-dollar question. I wonder if Junie has her suspicions but is afraid to share them with me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, can you tell us anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I don't really know what to say. Um...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She went silent. Seems like she doesn't want to talk about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is there anything else you noticed on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Well, I don't know if this will help, but... That evening, I went back to my dressing room to get something I'd forgotten there. It was well after the last bell rang... I'd say, maybe around 8:30.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Around 8:30, huh? That's over an hour after when the crime supposedly took place.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's when I noticed that both stage statues were finished. They were quite large, and they were each covered with a white sheet, but I could tell. It made me happy to think that after all that hard work, they were finally finished.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right... The statues that Robin made. So they were covered in white sheets...?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...*cough*... *cough* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Junie! Are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough* Sorry. I'm a little tired, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, I think this meeting is over. Prof. Means?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I will use any means possible to get the result I want in Juniper's case. But it will require considerable preparation, so I must be off.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...A proposal?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, this isn't another one of your crazy--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By sundown today...!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I, Athena Cykes, along with Apollo Justice...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait a second. Don't drag my name into--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We're going to discover the truth behind this murder mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">......What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we're going to bring you solid evidence showing just what that truth is!</line>
<line speaker="Means">I see... So, it has come to this, has it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we succeed in doing that... ...I want you to promise that you'll accept it, Junie, no matter how hard it is to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then, you shouldn't need anyone else to defend you except me. Have we got a deal? ...I trust that's okay with you too, Prof. Means?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I have no objections, as long as Juniper is satisfied with this arrangement.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............Okay. But only if it's the real truth. I'm sorry to put you through this, Thena. But thank you. I've been thinking only of myself this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, it's way too early to thank me. But you can thank me all you want once I get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Means">...Very well, I will see you back here at sundown.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry for all the trouble, professor. It's just, she's new to the agency, so...</line>
<line speaker="Means">Don't be silly. I find it all rather thrilling. Now, let us meet here again later!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">If you'll excuse me, I'd better go.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, see you later!</line>
<line speaker="Means">But if this trial proceeds in the same manner and ends in the same way as the mock trial... ...would you not lose everything you've worked so hard to gain?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Argh! This is no time to be thinking about that! I've got an investigation to do. I WILL find the truth by sundown, no matter what!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only the three mock trial participants could've moved the body before it started. That's why the killer must be Robin, Hugh, or Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right, and that means at least one of them is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">To make matters worse, I have a feeling each one of them is hiding some sort of secret.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>We'll have to bring it all to light. I'm not looking forward to it, but it has to be done!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Today's trial focused on the day of the crime and the actions of those involved.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, like when the voice was recorded, and who went to the art room and when. If we analyze the info we have, we should be able to ID the killer! There's no lead in these legs! I've been training for a day like this! Okay, on my mark! Ready, set--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No running for me. I'm done trying to keep up with you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the main argument tomorrow will be over how the body was moved. Detective Fulbright said Prosecutor Blackquill already has a plan. I bet it involves some bit of info that will damage Juniper's case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Poor Junie. She gets discouraged much easier than I do, too. I'll just have to reassure her the best I can!) No problem. All we have to do is find some irrefutable evidence before the day is done!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Come on, lazybones!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha, ha. Very funny, Mr. I-Dangle-Around-Someone's-Neck-All-Day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">More damaging evidence. Juniper's case seems to have no lack of that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We still have time to turn this whole case upside down! But it'll require some legwork!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right. Let's give it our best shot.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the spirit! We'll start with wind sprints! Two hundred yards, ten times! Ready to go?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, wait! Wouldn't our time be better spent investigating the case?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hungry, Athena? You haven't had lunch yet, right? Well... It's a virtual snack bar in my magic panties! Cookies, chips, Snackoos! You name it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's not the most appetizing place to keep snacks...</thought> You know, I'm not that hungry anymore. I'll just have some juice from the fridge.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Great! I've been waiting to have you try drinking from my magic panties.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. That's even worse.</thought> M-Maybe next time. I'm really busy with the investigation and all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you are? Well, when you get back, I'll have all sorts of things ready for you in my magic panties.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Just the very thought is making me shudder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I saw your debut fight, Athena You looked like an old pro out there!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wasn't nearly that good, but thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aww, c'mon! You'd put a pitbull to shame! You sunk your teeth in and never let go!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You exploited your opponents' faults, and you split hairs like there was no tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was amazing! I can't tell you the last time I was on the edge of my seat for a whole fight!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Trial = Boxing Match = Trial?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I heard the school festival was canceled. Maybe I could invite you to one of my school events instead to make up?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, that's a great idea! Let's talk about it once we settle this case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Okay. And we could put on a mock-trial-slash-magic show!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh... how would that work?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">At the trial's climax, the victim's wound suddenly heals and she comes back to life! Then a huge shower of confetti rains down on the audience as they give a standing ovation!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, they'd be on their feet, all right, but definitely not to cheer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it my imagination or did something just move?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Afternoon, you two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin. What are you doing here? Don't you think sneaking onto campus like this... is just slightly suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'll have you know I'm continuing my investigation, in the strictest of confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't want to be caught napping again at tomorrow's trial. And that means a thorough investigation today. Think you can lend us a hand?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm not one to refuse a damsel in distress. But you needn't have asked, Fräulein. I'd intended to help from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're the best, Prosecutor Gavin! <thought>Okay, time for a thorough investigation. I bet we missed lots of stuff yesteday!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Gavin, you were scheduled to perform at the school festival, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. But I hadn't seen this stage until yesterday. That backdrop with the starry sky and big crescent moon isn't half bad. We also had some tricks up our sleeve to make the concert really rock. Pyrotechnics, a fog machine, big banners... Things like that. It would've looked like this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, the plans from yesterday. What's that design on the banner there in the back? I know the scales are the school emblem... ...but what's with the number six? It looks like it's in serious pain or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Athena, ixnay on the ixsey.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's the Gavinners's logo, Fräulein. Oh, and nice Pig Latin, Herr Forehead. Really smooth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! I, uh... I meant, it looks like the number six rocking seriously hard.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nein, Fräulein, it's a G for Gavinners, not a six. But whatever floats your pretty boat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So where is the banner? I don't see it anywhere onstage.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was an important part of the show, but the school managed to misplace it somehow. It's a pity. We had it specially made from heavyweight high-grade cloth. A missing banner and two broken statues -- there are mysteries aplenty to be solved, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Come to think of it, one of the broken statues was of Prosecutor Gavin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As you can see here in the stage plans... ...right here, we have the statue of me... ...and right here, Herr Wright's statue. But little does that matter now, as we both lie in pieces thanks to you, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did I ever do to you?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually, this statue broke into rather large pieces. Why don't we try to put it back together? Maybe we'll learn something new.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hmm... Picking up the pieces of a shattered rock star? Achtung! That's one über-cool idea! There might even be a song in there somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yay! Let's do this! Schnell!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this an investigation or am I interrupting a German Language Club social event?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm flattered, Fräulein, but the answer is nein.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean, "nein"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You want to record my godlike voice on your little tape recorder there, ja? Well, sorry. I may have retired from the music biz, but I will not sell myself cheap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It's a piece of evidence, you-- Oh, never mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sixty-seventh?! Wow, this school festival goes way back. Oh, look. The text on this sign isn't written, it's embroidered! And there's a warning in even smaller embroidery... "Embroidered sign lovingly crafted by the Handicrafts Club. KEEP DRY!" <thought>But the sign is outside. What happens if it rains?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I dunno... This is fine for a rock concert, but... The nighttime sky as backdrop for a courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Personally, I think it's breathtaking. I mean, speaking the truth under a starry sky? Don't you think it's romantic, Fräulein? And the waning crescent moon represents the maximum three-day trial cycle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Three-day trial outdoors? No thanks. If it starts raining my hair'll be ruined!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's even a prosecutor's bench here on this stage.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, the memories, Fräulein. As a former rock star, and a prosecutor... ...the prosecutor's bench has taught me much about human emotions, passion, and fight.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can picture it now -- you with your silvery singing voice and Apollo sweating bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, how about picturing me winning once in a while?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The winner of the mock trial was to take the training seminar right here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean, Hugh or Robin?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... Besides Junie, they're the only ones who could move freely around the campus... ...before the mock trial. That means one of them must be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's not really enough to go on, is it? We need to talk with Juniper one more time and persuade her to give us a name.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. And that means we have to find irrefutable evidence before the day ends! <thought>There's no time to lose! But we can't rush it, either! Efficiency is the key!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, they built a witness stand, too, even though it's just a temporary stage. <thought>Oh, but I think they're still working on it. Let's see what this notice says.</thought> "Caution: Pedestal features a high-speed rotation mode. Activate with care." <thought>You mean this thing spins...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a bit too far away to get a good look. Maybe we should try a different angle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I like the view. The judge can look down on everything from up here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, not bad for a temporary stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Is that so, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh, your judge act from the mock mock trial? I don't know why, but it kind of creeps me out. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wrong answer again, Mr. Justice. A penalty for our mock lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arrrgh! ...That is NOT funny!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The body's gone. All that's left is a white outline. I never knew Prof. Courte personally... ...but seeing her reduced to a white outline leaves me cold inside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But in a way, she still lives on in the messages she left behind. Like the strange way her body was posed and the signs of her wrists being bound.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right. Let's use her final messages to catch her killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no, Prosecutor Gavin! You're a complete wreck, literally! Why in the world would someone do something like this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know, but whoever did it must've felt an amazing sense of release.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Can I take that as a confession, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! No! I feel bad for Robin. She worked so hard on these. Let's pick up the pieces for her!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You got it! Let's check every corner of this stage then, ja!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look what I made! Not bad, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You're like a recording artist who samples other people's work and calls it their own.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, you know what they say. Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery! In any case, we have a statue smasher in addition to a killer to catch now!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nein, I suspect they might be one in [sic] the same.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The other statue Robin made... It's been smashed to bits. If there were some larger pieces, we might be able to put this one back together, too.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, but all I see are itty bitty ones.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what Mr. Wright would think... ...if he knew we put Prosecutor Gavin's statue back together, but left his like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We could always come back to it after the case is solved. I'll help you fix it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This statue doesn't look anything like you or Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The goddess bearing scales and a sword... She's a symbol of fairness and strength.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But she and her symbols were shattered along with the statues of you and Mr. Wright. This is a direct challenge to the rule of law! Well, if they want a fight, they've got one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, take it down a notch, tiger. Let's save the fighting for when we find our culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look! There's your rival over there, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who, Prosecutor Gavin? We've battled it out a few times before, but I wouldn't call him--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, not him. I'm meant [sic] that speaker over there! It can output massive blasts of sound that rival your Chords of Steel!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have better things to do than compete with a speaker, so just forget it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait... You don't think this weird box here is--</line>
<line speaker="???">Sss, sss, sss... Hands off!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I knew it. I'd know that voice anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's just ignore it. I mean, it made its wishes loud and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So, this is the future cardboard box technology has afforded us, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a copy of the school paper with that story about the alleged love triangle. I wonder if people waste their time reading this stuff...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-What was that?! I thought I heard something just now...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You're just hearing things! It was nothing more than your ears playing tricks on you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Found one! A piece of Prosecutor Gavin's shattered pride!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Are you saying my pride is as fragile as plaster of Paris?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like there are other large pieces scattered about.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's find what we can!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Found another piece of the statue!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But there should still be some more. Let's leave no stone unturned.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This looks like another piece of the statue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Apollo! This makes five piece in all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we have all we're going to find.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's get back to where Prosecutor Gavin was shattered!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I think you might want to reword that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't see any other big pieces lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. Let's see if we can put this statue back together.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, Apollo you come over here and Prosecutor Gavin, if you could hold this...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it! Not bad, if I do say so myself!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, but don't you think it's strange? We put the statue back together, but look. What's with all these leftover white pieces?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm... These two look like they go together. And these pieces, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Athena? What do you think you're doing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't stop me now. The artist inside me wants to get out and have a good time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... what is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah... It's the goddess of law holding a pair of scales in one hand and a sword in the other. That's quite the feat you pulled off there, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whew! I love that feeling you get after you work really hard on something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no, no! I knew WHO it was! I meant to ask what's it doing here!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not sure. There's no statue like this in the stage plans.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Still, I could swear I've seen this statue somewhere before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The more we learn, the deeper the rabbit hole goes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">At least we're moving in the right direction. Let's keep searching the stage for clues.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've been wondering about something this whole time. You know that pole at the edge of the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean this? It has a wire that goes off and connects to something somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This pole supports the wire over the stage. Just seeing it makes me want to climb it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with your constant desire to run and climb things?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's wrong with being competitive? You need to man up a little, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I'm not climbing that thing, that's for sure. I'd like to keep my spine intact.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Care to see where that wire goes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An impressive building fit for an impressive school.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, and these beautiful walls are like a big blank canvas. See? My shoeprints leave really distinct marks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, cut that out before you get us in trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This wire is for hanging banners over the stage. One of the policemen who was here earlier was checking how it worked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so that's why the banner looks like it's out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The banners are hung and removed from the art room over there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the art room over there? As in the scene of the crime?!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Bingo, Fräulein. It's still crawling with cops, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey...! Anyone in the art room?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, it's you people! Ha ha ha! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, it's Detective Fulbright! ...In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is that some kind of a greeting between you two?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright! Can you lower that banner from there?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course! Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">How's that?! *huff* *puff* Whew!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Detective! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Always glad to help! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, is that some kind of greeting between you two or not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, looks like the banner's down now. Let's go take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the art room -- the scene of the crime -- over there. Let's get Detective Fulbright's attention!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait. We probably shouldn't bother him unless we really need something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww... I really wanted to do that whole "In justice we trust!" thing again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It’s a little hard to see from this angle. Let’s look at it head-on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at this banner. I don't think it would flap very well in the wind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">An unflappable banner? Hey, I like that! It goes perfect with unflappable lawyers and unflappable rockers! It's like it was made for this very stage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at this. The bottom part is all knotted up. Lemme try and unravel it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geez, did you really have to? You don't come across an unflappable banner every day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, there are some things that have to yield to forces beyond themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What a cruel world we live in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, a scrap of paper was caught up inside. ...It's blowing away!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I got it! ............Yes! Great catch, huh?! Looks like some kind of note. What does it say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"October Hugh 120." What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A test score maybe? Pretty impressive when you consider that 100 is a perfect score!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't see how even Hugh can get beyond perfect...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fräulein, shall we inspect the banner again, now that it has been unraveled?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is the emblem that's on Junie's school uniform.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right. ...Wait a sec! It's hard to see against the red material, but look. There's a dark red stain here, just under the emblem.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This banner was on a wire connected to the art room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, and the art room is where the murder occurred. Are you thinking what I'm thinking?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This stain might be from the victim's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's really not much of interest here. At least, that's what my intuition tells me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... We've pretty much finished searching around here, but... just one more look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whew! That was a whole lot of poking around in such a short time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does that mean you're satisfied?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually, there was one more thing I wanted to check out. See that metal fence back there? There's just that one segment, so it seems out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It looks like they were in the process of removing them after the stage was set up. But they were never able to finish on account of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We should take a look if you think it could be important.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... This track looks man-made.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right. And it looks like it starts from behind the backdrop.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe a big muddy pro wrestler was hiding back there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Well, that was totally random, but we'll never know until we take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like something was being dragged through here, and this is where it started.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but whatever it was, it's long gone.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Must've been pretty heavy. Perhaps it was used in setting up the school festival.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, then I guess it wasn't a pro wrestler. Still, this could be something important.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's about it for the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. I think we'd better search the art room next.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I think I'll hang around here for a while. But make sure to tell me once you find it, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Find what?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What else? The Gavinners banner that disappeared from the stage. You never know -- it just might be connected to the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Really? Or does he just want his banner back?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Sss, sss, sss. Don't tell me... So, in short, that's...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? Hey...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That box... It just took off running.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I have a pretty good idea who that is, as I suspect you do, too. Come on! We can't afford to have any weird articles written about us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The maintenance area's over in that direction. After that box!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Myriam, you're liable to get tossed in the garbage truck if you hang around here.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I'm just an empty box. And that's what you do with them -- you throw them away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, did you change boxes? I like the new look.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">What does it matter anymore?! I was a complete failure in court today! My work, my pride, my dream -- everything I've worked so hard for... Gone!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, Ms. Scuttlebutt, but... ...doesn't believing you had a scoop when you really didn't make you a failure as a reporter?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">A f-failure as a r-reporter?! Kahk-kahk-kahk. Kaaahk kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk! Ack! ...Ah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come to think of it, calling her a failure as a reporter might've been a bit extreme.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss, sss! Scold me! Despise me! Pack me away where I'll never see the light of day! I've been cast aside to waste away into a big pile of mushy paper mache!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I kind of feel responsible for this, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now's our chance to prod her for information while she's vulnerable! I bet that's what you were just thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What kind of a person do you think I am? <thought>He read me like a book...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was you on the stage earlier, wasn't it? Why'd you run off like that?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">......... Take a look... at this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why are you showing me a burnt up old rag?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, it's really hard to see, but I think that's the Gavinners's logo there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, is this the banner that disappeared? It's all burned up.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">D-Don't look at me. I just happened to find it in the incinerator.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Incinerator? Did Blackquill actually make good on his threat to burn her box?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We should probably try to find out whether someone tried to destroy this on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, this banner is sounding less and less unrelated to our case, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Myriam? I owe you an apology. I shouldn't have said you were a failure as a reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss... Too late. I already decided journalism isn't for me. The last step is to erase all of the photos on my PC! I'm really going to do it! Here goes! Five percent... Ten percent... Sss, sss, sss! Four years of my life down the drain!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Shouldn't we stop her, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Myriam, you should keep publishing your paper. I didn't mean what I said, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">You didn't mean it? ...Oh, no, my photos! Stop! Cancel! Abort!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Did you stop it in time?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Deletion progress... Ninety-nine percent complete... There are only two pictures left. Sss, sss, sss. Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you going to do now, Athena?! You owe it to her to make this right!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I know...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Don't worry, Myriam. Your photos may be gone... ...but the memory of your photographic genius will live on forever in all of our hearts!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ooh... Athena. That was cringe-worthy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Myriam, check this out! You took some amazing photos of the three of them. I'm sure they really appreciated it.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Obviously. I'm the ace member of the Newspaper Club. The only member, in fact!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know this won't make up for the photos you lost, but here are your newspapers back.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">There's no rest for the wicked! I plan on pursuing those three for as long as I live.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Myriam, why are you so obsessed with Juniper, Hugh, and Robin?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">O-Obsessed?! I'm not obsessed with them! It's just, they were so close, ever since their freshman year, so uh... well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, are you thinking what I'm thinking?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, I think that's the only explanation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">W-W-Wait a second! You're not thinking what I think you're thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk! ...kahk-kahk!!! Kaaahk kahk-kahk-kahk!!! How could you possibly know thaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's one abused laptop.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">...Kahk-kahk-kahk. My laptop won't turn on. Never thought my life would end so soon. A mere seventeen years...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Now I really feel bad.</thought> Oh, I know! Myriam, we have a laptop at the office. We'd be happy to lend it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Huh? Y-You have a laptop I could use?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure, but on one condition. I want you to ask Junie, Hugh, and Robin if you can hang out with them.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">What?! Like I could ever do that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, but that's the deal if you want to borrow our laptop.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You scare me sometimes, Athena. You're like good cop, bad cop all rolled into one.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk. Fine! I'll do it! If that's all you want!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yay! I'll be by later to bring you the laptop!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">W-Wait! It's not like I owe you anything, but here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Thanks. Oh, it's a set of pictures.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like they're setting up the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Yeah, I took them when they were putting the stage's backdrop into place.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, you sure have an eye for photography! <thought>...From what I can make out, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">There are the last two photos that didn't get deleted. They're all yours.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss, sss! Well, see you around, Scary Lawyer Lady!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was really impressive, Athena. What's next?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... I'd like to talk to Hugh or Robin if possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's walk around and see if we can find them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pretty impressive the way you fixed that so quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wouldn't really say I fixed it. I just looked at the pieces to see how they fit together.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Too bad we can't put Mr. Wright's statue back together, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I totally forgot! But we're running out of time, so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin and Lady Justice are back up, but Mr. Wright still lies there shattered. But that was totally your call. I promise not to say anything to Mr. Wright, as long as you don't make me run anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah...! You wouldn't...! Would you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Once we take care of this case, I'd better come back and fix Mr. Wright's statue, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just wanted to say thanks for helping with our investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No danke necessary, Fraulein. I was doing this partly for myself, too. I also have access to police data and gear, what with my many fans on the force.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I assume you always get official authorization, right, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You are such a stick-in-the-mud, Herr Forehead. Let's just say, I have my ways. So relax. Unlike Prof. Means, I believe there is no proper end without justifiable means. And that always includes a bright smile and some wicked air guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For a second there, I thought we were going to get philosophical... for once.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks like something was dragged through the dirt here. The track seems to start from behind the backdrop.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder what could've made that. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wouldn't rule out a pro wrestler scraping by here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. Now you're getting oddly specific about your oddly random ideas.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why are you carrying a sooty mess of fabric around?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, about that. This is kinda hard to say, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the banner you've been looking for. It was found in the incinerator.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What?! This ash and cinder?! That's all that's left?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Somehow, I don't think was a random act of vandalism.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, it no doubt bears some relation to the case at hand. In short, this is a challenge directed at me and Gavinners fans everywhere. Mark my words, Fraulein. I WILL find the perpetrator behind the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great, thanks! <thought>Does he mean whoever burned the flag... ...or the professor's killer? I'll just cross my fingers that they're one and the same.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You must be so disappointed, Athena. You can't master magic in a day. It takes practice, practice, practice.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... I don't quite follow.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm talking about that jumbled mess of a statue. Look at all the cracks in that thing! I mean, you totally botched your restore-the-broken-statue trick, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Trick? I wasn't trying to--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When you botch a trick, don't admit defeat by resorting to glue or things like that. Just smash it to bits and start all over again! Here, give it to me! I'll show you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-N-No, don't! <thought>I don't have time to put it together again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, here it is -- the art room where the grisly crime occurred. Let's start looking--</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Stop right there! This is an active crime scene! No unauthorized personnel allowed!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Can't you make an exception? You won't even notice we're--</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Freeze! I don't think so! No exceptions! Now, move along! Nothing to see here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. He doesn't seem very accommodating this time. Let's try again later.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! That's Hugh over there! Hugh, we wanted a word with you, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">If it was Mr. Wright, then sure, but you two? Meh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I knew it. There's a hint of discord in Hugh's voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're not getting off that easy. After all, you're a possible suspect, plus you actually confessed in court.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Whatever. So, what do you want from me? But make it brief. I don't have a lot of time, and I assume you don't either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">About your confession today... You weren't serious about that, were you?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Let's just say I had no choice thanks to a certain lawyer who failed to get the job done.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you're really prepared to take the blame for this?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Not gonna happen. The voice on the tape is female, so that rules me out. Let's put it this way: you don't actually believe that ridiculous play on words, do you? Well, my confession is just like that -- a means to an end. Or as we say around here... ...the end justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. But I actually DO believe the voice is shouting, "Hugh O'Conner!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Juniper's confession was quite advantageous to the real killer. But if Robin or I were actually the killer, we wouldn't have confessed. It's that simple. Even you should be capable of such reasoning, or have I overestimated you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You'll make a great lawyer someday. I mean, you seem to enjoy getting under people's skin.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... Could Hugh and Robin's confessions really prove their innocence instead of their guilt? This is going to take some serious thinking on my part.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sure looked like Prosecutor Blackquill was twisting your arm to testify earlier today. Is there some sort of secret he's using against you?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...I've no intention of saying anything more. Now, if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hold! I am not through with you yet.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. It seems the rogue prosecutor has it out for me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Leave, and we just might discuss you-know-what.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Ack! N-No, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>One little statement and Mr. Cool loses it? What's that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I changed my mind. ...I'll stay and testify.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You really are a rank amateur. Even if that were true, you think I'd open up to you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So, he's not denying it. That secret might be causing the discord in his voice. Then again, we have the same problem with Junie and Robin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You're just wasting your time and mine. Next question.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">About that meeting with Prof. Courte on the 23rd... Why did she want to see you?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I've no intention of telling you. You'll have to force it out of me any way you can.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... Prof. Means strikes again. <thought>Then again, Hugh IS in the lawyer course.</thought> But didn't Prof. Courte used to say that the only good result is the truth? So, why don't you drop this whole charade and just tell me the truth!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...The truth. How can you be so sure it will help you solve this case? The truth isn't necessarily your friend, nor Juniper's for that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, you're wrong! I don't care what anyone says. I'm going to defend Junie the right way -- using the truth! <thought>That's the only way to honor Junie's wishes and Prof. Courte's memory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I see. Very well, Ms. Cykes. I'll testify tomorrow about that truth you're so interested in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hugh...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">But... Heh heh heh. Don't look to me if something happens to Juniper because of it. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What a terrible thing to say. I thought you guys were friends?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Yes, we were. Until just recently, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Were?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I already told Juniper, so I might as well tell you. I don't really care about her anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Just as I have my secrets, she has a side you've never seen. Juniper's not all sunshine and rainbows like you think she is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What are you saying?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">This conversation is over. I said I don't have a lot of time and I meant it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it just me or is this your name here?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, that's my name, but how should I know what it's doing there? But being that the whole campus looks up to me... ...I'm not surprised to find my name mentioned here and there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>And I'm not surprised he said that, being the narcissist he is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">He doesn't care about her anymore? Why would he say that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That didn't go so well. I guess we'll just have to pin our hopes on his testimony tomorrow. Athena, what do you say we head over to the art room. Might be a nice change of pace. Hopefully, the police have completed their investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right. We don't really have much time left, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Why, if it isn't my little lawyer friends again!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks again for lowering that school banner for us earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Don't mention it. Helping those in need is what my brand of justice is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... So, this art room was where the murder actually occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. You can't see it with the naked eye, but there's blood on the floor! That area roped off in the middle of the room marks the spot. The police investigation is done, so if you want to look around, knock yourselves out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Find anything new, Detective Fulbright?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Good question! Unfortunately, the answer is nothing much yet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He sure is confident for having found nothing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But if we're talking outside of the art room, there has been a major breakthrough!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, dear! Unless I find out what that is, I don't know what I shall do.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No need for the theatrics. I was told I could fill you in on this one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, you saw right through me, Detective! I'm impressed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looking to get arrested for murder via unwarranted flattery, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what's the major breakthrough you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You want to know?! You really want to know?! You really, really--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, just tell us, already!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aww, you're no fun. ...Anywho, we got the results of the voiceprint analysis back!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Voiceprint? You mean for this tape recorder?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Exactly. The voice belongs to the suspect Ms. Woods, beyond a shadow of a doubt! See right here?! They analyzed the voice on the tape inside and out!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">And you thought the voice on the tape was saying, "Hugh O'Conner!" Ha ha ha ha ha! Thanks for the good laugh, Ms. Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! <thought>He's the last person I want laughing at me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So now there's evidence of Juniper shouting, "You're a goner!" around the time of death. If we were to take this as truth, how are we supposed to make sense of it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I don't know... I can't think of any reason why Junie would shout that in the first place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? That was totally random. Well, two can play at that game! In justice we trust! How do you like them apples?! Pretty spiffy, huh? I polish the leather case to a rich luster daily. And once a week, I apply an anti-rust protectant to my badge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is all that really necessary?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course, it is! A detective's badge is his first line of defense! I'm sure you treat your badge with tender loving care, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, I always see your badge gathering dust on your desk. And you usually scramble to find it right before leaving the office.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nngh...... <thought>Hmph. No comment!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The mock trial is the key to this case. That much I'm sure!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but even if the case and the script are similar, that doesn't mean Juniper's guilty. I already proved that in court this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, right. This could be a problem. What to do, what to do!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, we better get back to our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hey! Don't walk away like that! Even champions of justice need help sometimes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Seriously? He wants me to help him convict our client?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's gonna give the prosecution a decisive advantage! Prepare to get owned tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think so. We have new evidence that will blow your case out of the water!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, yeah? Well, Prosecutor Blackquill has a witness ready to deliver brand-new testimony! Plus, he has a new tie and a pair of even flimsier shackles just ready to break! Tomorrow's trial will be ours! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, tomorrow I'll be using a new shampoo and I'm changing breakfast cereals, too! What about you, Apollo?! What'll be new with you tomorrow?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we should approach the case with a fresh, new attitude. It's what's on the inside that's important. We'll be fine as long as we stand strong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Wow, Apollo! That was actually really inspiring!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I see! So, that's your symbol of justice! Well, here's mine! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'd be happy if I never saw one of those again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, this area with the rope around it...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's where we detected a large bloodstain. In short, the victim was stabbed here or somewhere close by.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The fact that there's no visible blood means it was wiped up with something, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Right. But we were able to detect trace amounts of blood. Merely wiping it up does not remove all evidence of wrongdoing! And that--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In a nutshell, is JUSTICE... right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I'd appreciate it if you'd let me have the cool lines...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is the clock that created that major problem for Junie. Let's take a closer look!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Don't waste your time! I've checked it, and it's a hundred percent accurate!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You sure? How'd you check it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course I'm sure! I compared it to my own watch! See?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... Detective Fulbright, didn't you notice that your watch had stopped?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It has? Ah... Ah! This is unacceptable!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We obviously can't rely on him. Let's take a look for ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see... Wait a second! It's ahead by one whole hour. Well, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ah... Argggh! B-B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This clock must've also been an hour ahead when this photo was taken! If so, that would fit perfectly with Junie's testimony. Prosecutor Blackquill won't like this. I almost feel sorry for the detective... Almost.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can at least pretend to feel sorry by wiping that big grin off your face...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">W-W-Wait just one minute! The clock is an hour ahead right now, sure! But what proof do you have that it was running ahead on the day of the crime?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... That's a good question. Wait. I think I just might have something...</thought> Detective Fulbright, you would agree that there is a moon outside this window, right?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sure, it looks like a nice drawing of a crescent moon.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But if you look at that window in the back with the winch attached to it... ...you'll see that the only view to be had is the opposite side of the school building.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oof! Then... Then what's this moon doing here?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Gavin, you were scheduled to perform at the school festival, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. But I hadn't seen this stage until yesterday. That backdrop with the starry sky and big crescent moon isn't half bad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Isn't this the same as the one painted on the stage backdrop?</thought> The proof's right here, Detective. This shows it was 6:00 PM when the photo was taken!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fulbright:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. Guess I blew that one. What now?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What's this?! Is that the voice of someone in need?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, because of you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know what this moon really is. And if you look at this photo, you'll know too. This shows where that moon in the photo came from and the truth of Junie's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Wh-Wha-What?! Where?! Where does it show that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you look right here, it will all become crystal clear!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fulbright:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, right here. See where I'm pointing?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Very funny. Now hurry up and show me what you're really talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... <thought>Guess that wasn't it. Let's think about it step by step. What was that moon in the photo really made of?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">They were still prepping the stage, so its backdrop wasn't in place yet. This photo shows them in the process of moving the backdrop into position.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can see that. That's the big board hanging here. The size matches, too.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But there's no picture. That's a crucial detail.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It is, but I believe what we're seeing in this photo is the back of the board.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The back of the...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. And at around 6:00 PM when this was taken... ...a photo of that same board was being taken from the front.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What do you mean the front? The front is against the wall!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's where you're wrong. What about the window? Remember how we said the moon shouldn't even exist in this photo? Take a good look.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Are you suggesting the moon is the one on the backdrop?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly! In short, this photo was taken while the backdrop was being moved! And as you can see here, it was around 6:00 when the backdrop was being set in place. So, the art room clock was running fast at least as far back as the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">How-ow-ow... How can I ever face Prosecutor Blackquill now?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yes! I just blew a hole in a piece of the prosecution's evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The photo taken with the school camera was from 6:00 PM or thereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">sob* How am I ever going to explain this to Prosecutor Blackquill?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Honesty is the best policy! Look him right in the eye and say you're sorry for screwing up!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, you're right! Only in sincerity is there justice! Plus, I'd like to avoid getting chewed out all over again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Knowing Blackquill, Detective Fulbright's going to get chewed out no matter what.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, it's gone. Remember that strange statue in the school camera photo?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right. Wonder where it is? <thought>Robin's a member of the Fine Arts Club. Maybe she can shed some light on this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's a paint palette here. No surprise there, considering this is the art room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like someone mixed yellow and red to make orange.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I prefer yellow. You, on the other hand, are way too red.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think this is saying that the two of us have to work together to solve this case. Ooh! What if this is Prof. Courte sending us a message from beyond the grave?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about the blob right next to it -- the one with red and green?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe she's implying that you need more delicious greens in your diet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you saying Prof. Courte is watching over our dietary habits from the Pearly Gates?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look! That's you on this mobile, Apollo! A red demon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A red demon? Looks more like a snake curled around a brush to me.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No, no, see the antennas and the yellow spots on its back! Anyone can see it's a ladybug!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I guess we'll have to agree to disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Fine, we can investigate this further at a later date. Agreed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's do that. You okay with that, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I really regret bringing this up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">A picture of a girl wearing a floral hat... Oh, it has the artist's name right here. "C. Courte." Wow, Prof. Courte must've painted this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So is this what they consider art? I really don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I swear I've seen this girl before. There's an air of fragility about her. And those pity-inducing eyes... Who is this again? Her name's on the tip of my tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can see the other half of the building over there, and the quad and the stage down below.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. This must be the window Detective Fulbright stuck his head out of earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, yeah, thanks for the help, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">A true champion of justice always comes running to those in need!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great, then how about telling us Prosecutor Blackquill's strategy for tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">All right, let me think...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Well?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">.........Hm? Oh! Hey, I'm not falling for that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So close I could almost taste it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Some wire and a winch... So this is how they reeled the banners in and out. There's a nice view of the stage from here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin is still standing in front of that broken statue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, it really wasn't you, Apollo? Don't worry, you can tell me. I won't tell anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh... I'll never clear my name unless we catch the real culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, a piece of pottery. Looks like it's already been fired. I bet Robin made it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I bet it won't last long, not with the way she deals with her own work, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, it seems like such a waste. I mean, this one already has some color on it. It looks just like bloodstains the way the glaze was dribbled on to it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just like... b-bloodstains?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust! That DOES look like bloodstains. We'd better examine it at once!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get it. The victim was stabbed in the middle of the room where the big bloodstain is... ...and then brought over here, at which point, some of her blood dripped onto these pieces. That means the body very well could've been dropped from this window.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In the mock trial script, the body was dropped onto a mat. Then, a ball cart was used to move it over to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The maintenance area is below this room, and the storehouse there has a mat and ball cart.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, even the moving of the body was carried out just like in the script. The killer sure had a thing for Junie's script.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, what did you expect?! That's why we suspected the defendant in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, you're wrong! And I'm going to prove it in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't that a mock trial script? Actually, there's a whole bunch of them here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see... Looks like everyone from the judge course submitted one.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The victim Constance Courte was the Fine Art Club's advisor. So, she probably spent a lot of time up here in addition to her other duties. This isn't where I'd keep a bunch of scripts, but I'd wager that's how they wound up here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Poor stressed-out, overworked Prof. Courte! I know exactly how that feels!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You must, because your desk always looks like a tornado hit it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, you're one to talk, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me? What about Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe we should rename the firm "Wright Stuff-All-Over-the-Place Agency."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Three busts sitting on a shelf... A judge, a defendant and either a lawyer or prosecutor. The bearded one must be the judge, and the bummed out-looking one, the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, there's another one that's fallen onto the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder which one fell -- the lawyer or the prosecutor. Think, Apollo, think! This could tell us how tomorrow's trial will go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll... just wait for tomorrow's horoscopes, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A picture of a girl wearing a floral hat... Oh, it has the artist's name right here. "R. Newman." Wow, Robin must've painted this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this Juniper? The clothes are different, but...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, look. There's a piece of paper stuck to the back. Let's see what it says... "Completely lacks Prof. Courte's artistry. Must keep practicing. --Robin" Huh... I think this is plenty good myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder what it would've looked like if Prof. Courte had painted Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet it would've been really artistic looking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It kinda looks like there's a Prosecutor's Badge at the top of this statue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But it's not if you look real close. Another strange, difficult-to-understand work of art...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, look, it has a title. "Guilty, Guilty, Guilty." Heh, real creative...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Art... Either it's too abstract to understand or as subtle as a sledgehammer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A mock trial script on the floor, and nearby, an envelope marked "Use."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if Myriam's script was ever really inside that envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see here... "by Myriam Scuttlebutt." And the title is... "Rouge et Noir: Crimson Blood and Dark Judgment"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wouldn't take part in that mock trial if she begged me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It says there are special rules allowing the payment of bribes while court is adjourned. Oh, and you can bring in up to three dollars worth of fabricated evidence. It also says... "Welcome to the darkest mock trial ever, where the end justifies the means!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecution claims this is the script that was supposed to have been used.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But the scripts were selected by Prof. Courte. Considering how much she valued the truth... ...I seriously doubt she's pick a script entitled "Crimson Blood and Dark Judgment."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you have that title memorized already?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think we've examined pretty much everything we can. By the way, did Prosecutor Blackquill happen to tell you anything about tomorrow's trial?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust! It's no use trying to pry more information out of me! Having just learned that the clock had been one hour fast... ...means we're back to square one concerning the suspect's actions that day.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I wonder what the main argument will be about now.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">How the body was moved would be my guess, but Prosecutor Blackquill's got his own plans.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? Does he now...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Detective Fulbright--</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Try as you might, I won't say another word about the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I wasn't going to ask about that. I was just wondering if you'd seen Robin.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, you mean Ms. Robin Newman? She was just here a moment ago! And she mumbled something about watching videos in the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Video? What video?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, Detective. ...Athena, I think we should stop by the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There she is! Robin! Hey, Robin!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh, Athena, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you watching there?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Heh heh... Oh, it just so happens to be a video of the mock trial. I had to use a bit of coercion to get it, but the end justifies the means, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There it is again. Prof. Means sure has a lot of influence around here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Care to look into the true connection between the murder and the mock trial with me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sounds great, but do you mind if we ask you some questions first?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh heh. Sure, I'll tell you anything you W-A-N-T.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">About your confession today... Why'd you do it?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Because! Juniper hasn't done anything wrong! I had to stop the trial by any means possible!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right... The end justifies the means. So, you're a follower of Prof. Means, too?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Prof. Means is a wonderful teacher, as was Prof. Courte. I like them B-O-T-H!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She brushed that one off like a pro.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But with that style of justice, you run the risk of breaking the law.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Well... I'm prepared to quit school because of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I-I... I wanna be an artist! That's what I really want, maaaaaan! But noooooo! My parents forced me to study to become a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But if the trial went south, you'd have to drop out and give up on being a prosecutor... That's what you're really after, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Mm-hm. *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Talk about someone who literally changes at the bat of an eyelash...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess she's been dealing with her own problems, too. That totally makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, I suppose so, but that doesn't make what she did right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you tell us about what you were doing on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Finishing a statue. I was on the stage until the last bell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. You made the statues of Mr. Wright and Prosecutor Gavin, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh, uh, yes... yes I did. Both of them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is just a formality, but can you prove you were making the statues at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">C-C-CAN I PROVE IT?! YOU THINK I'M THE KILLER NOW?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No... That's not what I meant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Both Hugh and Robin were still at school after 7:00 PM. But neither of them can prove exactly what they were doing. Could one of them really have murdered Prof. Courte?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Have there been any problems now that everyone here knows you're a girl?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Heh heh, no worries there! I discussed the matter with Prof. Courte some time ago. I told her I wanted to let everyone know I was really a girl. And just today I found out that she spoke with the school administration on my behalf.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, they must really like you...</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I know, right? But now I can finally be myself here at school! I don't have to hide the fact that I love girly clothes! That's why, Athena, I simply must have this and... this by any means possible!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? B-But this is evidence we need for the trial. ...Sorry, but no can do!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Aww, don't be a party pooper, Athena. Come on, please? Pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, darn it...</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Anyway, thank you again, Athena! Thank you for revealing who I really am! I wanted everyone to know before the snitch found out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The snitch? <thought>Sounds like a new lead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">There's a rumor going around that one of the students here is a snitch. I hear they're watching everything we do, our activities, our relationships, our interests... ...and reporting it all to one of the professors.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But why would anyone do that?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Officially, I heard it's to seek out misconduct among the student body... ...but rumor has it grades were being bought and sold through this surveillance network.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's bribery. The situation at Themis Legal Academy is worse than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>While all of this is important stuff, I still want to ask about that thing in the art room. I'll have to present some evidence to show her what I'm talking about, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Prof. Courte's artistic sense... That's a tough one. I'd say it's avant-garde and very eclectic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>In other words, it's weird and all over the place. Come to think of it, that strange-looking painting in the art room... ...was one of Prof. Courte's works, wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">The statue in that photo was originally a statue of Lady Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Lady Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Prof. Courte had planned on placing it on the judge's bench in the Lecture Hall... Heh heh. But the day before the mock trial, it broke while she was polishing it. She said she'd take it back to the art room and try to fix it somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... this... is the statue in its proper state?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">You bet! Just look at that wild silhouette! Wow! It's so C-U-T-E!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I... don't get it... Do you have to be an artist to appreciate stuff like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena... The Lady Justice that you put back together on that stage...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right. I didn't realize before because it was in pieces, but before it was smashed... ...maybe it didn't look like Lady Justice, but more like it does in the photo! But what in the world was it doing on the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh, that's Juniper's stage costume! It's so C-U-T-E! Why don't you try it on, Athena?! C'mon, just try it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm, it's really pretty to look at. But it's really not my style with all the frills and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">What?! No, that's not true! I mean, there's a Cinderella inside every girl! You'd look great in anything! Just put it on and I'll brush on some yellow glaze. It's your favorite color, right?! Then it's in the kiln you go! How would you like that? Rare, medium, well done?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So when she said Cinderella, she literally meant burn me to cinders?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh! Lady Justice! That's sooo C-U-T-E!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think this is cute?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeah, totally! The balance of the scales! The keenness of the sword! The cracks running all the way up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That last one's only because I put it back together.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh, I totally know what you mean! It's that feeling you get when something is so cute you want to smash it to bits! R-I-G-H-T? RAAAAAAAAAAAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sorry, but that sounds more like a case of the crazy than a fondness for the cute.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Aww, maaaaaan... That's my blood, sweat and tears in a pile of rubble right there!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why not make the statues again? I'm sure the two of them would be delighted.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeah! I could totally do that! And this time... ...I'm gonna make them even more realistic by making full body molds of the models!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Full body molds? Um... are you sure that's safe? How about plain old measurements?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh, Athena. Measurements are for wimps! Full on YOLO is what art's all about! I'm gonna drop both of 'em in a big pool of plaster! YEAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know I should stop you, but some part of me really wants to see how this plays out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Robin, I just remembered something I wanted to ask you. This photo shows a piece of art on the table. Do you know what it is?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">WH-WH-WHOOOOOOOOOA! Look at that unique artistic sense! That has to be one of Prof. Courte's creations, maaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Courte's... artistic sense?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yay! A present from Athena! Ooh, this is so exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... sorry, but it's not a present. I wanted to know whether you knew anything about it.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">*sob* ...That's not nice, Athena. Why are you so cranky today?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I wasn't until a moment ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think that about covers it.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Okay, then how about watching the mock trial video with me? What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure, sounds good to me. Er, so, how do you wanna watch it?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh heh. All classroom desks at this school have their own built-in computer, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, this place is definitely a lot cushier than I thought!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I know you guys are in a hurry, so I'll just fast-forward to the important parts. Let's start with the professor's pre-trial speech.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, that sounds like Prof. Means.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is the camera like this the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeah, it's in a fixed position in front of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How come teachers' speeches always make me so sleepy?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh he. Let's just skip to the end of his speech.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! What's the deal here? Why's Junie so large in this shot?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks to me like she cut right in front of the camera.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh heh heh. Juniper was also in charge of the audio.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even though she was already playing a part in the mock trial itself?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">She had to do it to keep the script details secret. She was all over the place that day. When she wasn't in the trial, she was in the audio control room dealing with the music.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, so this is what the Lecture Hall looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like there's a judge's bench back by the screen, and a witness stand up front. What about those balconies with the professors' names on them?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Those are the faculty seats. Prof. Means and Prof. Courte were in charge of scoring the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Okay, let's fast forward this a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ah, that was me! Could you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You read that line in the mock mock trial, Apollo, but you made it sound kind of weird.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Cut me some slack. It was my first time reading that script.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I think Juniper's going to speak next.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, what an emotional performance. She'd put a real actress to shame.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait. Could you go back and play that scene again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You really think that's necessary?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Stop! Did you hear that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you're on to something! Let's play that last part again!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I don't follow. What are you guys so excited about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think this piece of evidence should explain it. <thought>Time to show Robin a piece of evidence that links the line we just heard to the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right... What was the connection again?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">C'mon, Athena! I know you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I do? Really?! <thought>That voice shouting, "You're a goner!" has come up over and over again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sure you remember this. It contains a female voice shouting a violent threat. I'll play it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The voices and performance do sound similar, but... I can't believe this is happening!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just a possibility, but if the voice on this tape is really a recording... ...one made from the mock trial video, then that means this evidence was fabricated.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They didn't get to do a voiceprint analysis in time for court today. That's why the gender of the voice became so important. And if the real killer had foreseen that gender would become key in today's trial...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...He would've tried to deflect attention away from himself by making the suspect female. So basically, the only one with something to gain from doing this is our sole male suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Wait a second! NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAY!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prof. Means's credo is "The end justifies the means." So it makes perfect sense that a student who took those words to heart... ...would fabricate evidence. We need to get that tape analyzed as soon as possible!</line>
<line speaker="???">......Allow me to assist you with that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Gavin! At least make some kind of noise so we know you're there!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's go big or go home with rock star entrances, Fräulein. Timing is everything. Let me make a copy of that tape right now, and I'll get you the results as soon as I can. I trust that would be all right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Very much so! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Athena? It's almost sundown. Isn't it about time we head over to the Detention Center?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think Junie will agree that this is something that could prove her innocence. But... <thought>Will her heart really be open to accepting it? She had to have known this was what I'd find!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">...And that about covers the main gist of our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Means">I see. Very interesting. You've been quite the busy beaver today.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thank you for all your hard work, Athena. Well, my time's about up. And it will be getting dark soon, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">You must be tired after being on your feet all day. You should go home and--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, wait! You have to listen to me!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I don't... I don't want to hear any more. I know what you're going to say, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, you promised.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We're going to discover the truth behind this murder mystery! And we're going to bring you solid evidence showing just what that truth is! If we succeed in doing that... ...I want you to promise that you'll accept it, Junie, no matter how hard it is to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............Okay. But only if it's the real truth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So please. Please just listen to what I have to say. Once you've heard me out, I'll let you decide what to do.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The voice in this recording has been proven to be yours, Junie. And in the mock trial video, we can hear you reading your line from the script. We're having both of them analyzed now, but from what I can tell, the voices are the same. And the only one who'd benefit from faking the voice recording would be Hugh.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">......... But that doesn't make any sense. I mean, Hugh confessed in order to protect me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This may sound strange, but his confession is a ploy to make himself look less suspicious. In other words, he was just pretending to protect you. Besides, his confession came after you and Robin had already confessed. If he hadn't confessed right then as well, wouldn't that have seemed a little suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Say what you will, Athena, but none of use would hurt a fly, let alone kill someone. Hugh is a gifted student. He gets outstanding grades and never causes trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait. Athena. My bracelet reacted just now...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It did? <thought>But why?!</thought> ......... Junie, can you look me in the eye and repeat what you just said?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, um... none of us would hurt a fly, let alone kill someone. Hugh is a gifted student. He gets outstanding grades and never causes trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now I'm sure of it. She's lying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No. That's the one thing I'm not. The Student Council President isn't so easily shaken.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nice try! But I just spotted a telltale habit of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Huh? I don't know what you're--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! It's you and your loud voice that's unnerving her.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No, I already told you, I'm not nervous! I'm not Student Council President for nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, in any case, it looks like I got that one wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Juniper, you start coughing when you're under stress. You can't hide it from me no matter how hard you try. When you said, "and never causes trouble," a cough escaped and made your scarf flutter. As for why you were stressed, it's because you were lying.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, you're trying to hide Hugh's connection to this case, aren't you? And I believe that also ties into a secret about yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">A-A secret? About me? I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I already told Juniper. so I might as well tell you. I don't really care about her anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Juniper's not all sunshine and rainbows like you think she is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He ended their friendship after he found out about Junie's secret, which means... Hugh must've felt betrayed by Junie, making her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're the killer! ...Just kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I had you going there for a moment, didn't I? Thought it might lighten the mood a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, it's probably not a good idea for lawyers to punk their clients.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah... right... <thought>Well, that didn't go as planned...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're an accomplice to the crime. You weren't at first, but you got involved to help cover for Hugh.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Athena... I knew it was a mistake to ask you to be my lawyer. Maybe it's not too late to ask Prof. Means--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No, wait! That was just a little slip up. <thought>I better not hurt her feelings again. Time for some serious thinking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You were Prof. Courte's snitch, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">There's a rumor going around that one of the students here is a snitch. I hear they're watching everything we do, our activities, our relationships, our interests... ...and reporting it all to one of the professors.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And while fulfilling that role, you learned something about Hugh you'd rather forget.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I-I don't know what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, please. Stop hiding things from me. I hate having to force things out of you like this.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Looks like we're going to have to do this the hard way. Time to review the evidence and see if I can't prove my hypothesis. I must have something that proves Junie's the snitch, and Hugh's connection to the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Woods:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Juniper's one cool customer, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Wait! I don't think that was the right piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Whatever you show me won't change the fact that I've already told you all I know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right here in Prof. Courte's Planner, it says, "Routine Report." I believe this is meant to mean when the snitch would report in to Prof. Courte. I also believe Prof. Courte planned to meet Hugh in private based on the snitch's info. And from their meeting, Hugh must've put two and two together, and figured out your secret. So you see, it all makes sense only if you're the snitch, Junie.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*sniffle* ...Aaah...! Forgive me... Forgive me, Thena. I... I... *sob* I've been lying to you this whole time! The truth is, I... I suspected Hugh from the start!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did? <thought>Now this is surprising...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, that. It's my voice, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apparently, it's a recording of you reading your script during the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But earlier, when you said it was Prof. Courte's voice -- that was quite shocking. I never would've imagined it was the professor yelling at Hugh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh, that? That was just... you know...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That was such an inspired leap of logic. You really are something special, Thena.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, it takes a special kind of person to make a claim like that with a straight face.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It doesn't take my sensitive hearing to detect dripping sarcasm, genius.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, can you tell us anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I don't really know what to say. Um...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She went silent. Seems like she doesn't want to talk about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Juniper, I don't have that special kind of hearing that Athena does... ...but I don't need it to sense the pain you're feeling inside. And its intensity is directly proportional to how you feel about your friend. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*sob* Apollo...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please, Junie, tell me why you suspected Hugh. I have a feeling that will be the key to getting to the bottom of this whole case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What exactly was your role as class snitch?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Prof. Courte had told me how academy alumni had strayed from the path of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The dark age of the law, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">She didn't want any more of our students going astray like that. But few others at the academy shared her view.</line>
<line speaker="Means">I thought her ideas were beautiful, though sad and unrealistic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She asked you to be her eyes and ears, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I used to report once a month about any wrongdoings I'd seen or heard about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that report session in her planner, the one from October 22nd, was a part of that?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. That's when I reported Hugh to Prof. Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She snitched on her own friend?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I had accidently [sic] overheard Hugh talking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">He was talking to someone on the phone. I think it was one of his parents.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What were they talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Something about having paid money for good test scores. I only overheard him talking, so I never did find out who the money was going to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! <thought>That's bribery! Hugh was buying his way through school, and if that's the case... ...then that evidence that always seemed out of place might actually be about his secret!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I-I'm not sure I see what you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, um, never mind then! <thought>Besides, I know what this evidence is for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We found this while we were investigating the stage. It's got Hugh's name on it. I didn't know what the number meant at the time, but now that I'm hearing about bribes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...it must mean that a bribe of 120 grand was to be paid in October.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's more, take a look at this mark. The same mark is on the pages of Prof. Courte's planner.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">W-Wait... But would Prof. Courte have that kind of information in her planner? You don't really think the person who was taking the bribe money was--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just a possibility at this point, but it may indeed have been Prof. Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">B-B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Th-That is impossible! She'd be the last person I'd ever suspect of accepting bribes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like I said, it's just a possibility. <thought>But a rather good one. Maybe their private talk had to do with the possibility of the bribery being exposed. And what started out as a little argument soon got out of hand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not your fault, Junie. Anybody would've suspected Hugh if they knew what you knew.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No, I don't believe that alone would've driven him to murder. There's another reason why I suspected Hugh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>You've got to be kidding me. There's another reason?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I saw Hugh around 7:00 PM the day before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, so she's finally ready to talk about that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">When I... When I saw him... his... his....! *cough* *cough* Oh... Thena! *cough* *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Junie, are you all right? Just try to relax and tell me what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Junie">I, I never wanted to see what I did. But I'll have to live with it, won't I?! In that hallway... Hugh's hands... his hands were... dripping with blood!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">His hands were... dripping with blood...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What?! But why?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">What am I... going to do? Deep down, I know Hugh can't be the killer! But my mind keeps telling me he is, no matter how hard I try to convince myself he isn't! Oh, what am I going to do?! Hugh... Hugh... He's...! I... I can't take this anymore, Thena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So she hid the fact that she had seen Hugh and said she went home at six because... ...she wanted to avoid talking about what she saw...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie... It must've been terrible holding all of that in. But it's going to be okay. I'll get to the bottom of this. And that's my promise from one good friend to another. I'll be defending Juniper tomorrow. If that's okay with you, Prof. Means.</line>
<line speaker="Means">My main concern is whether you can defeat that prosecutor. ...But I won't try to stop you. I will be watching from the gallery. And shall look forward to seeing what sort of results your methods can produce. Good luck tomorrow. Now, if you would excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena... I'm sorry. I really mean it. I wish I had trusted you from the start. You have to uncover the truth tomorrow. I know you can do it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry. We already know that the prosecution's key piece of evidence is a fake. And thanks to you, we figured out the motive, too. Let's give this our best shot, Athena. Let tomorrow be the day Juniper walks free!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wouldn't have it any other way! <thought>We should be all ready now. What could possibly go wrong this time?! Still... There's this strange, uneasy feeling I can't shake... I'd better be imagining it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing of particular interest here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... We've pretty much finished searching around here, but... just one more look.</thought></line>
</xml>