<xml>
<title>Turnabout Serenade</title>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, hey, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, well, you know... ...Um, actually, nothing. I mean, something. ...Or maybe not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Out with it. The suspense is giving me an ulcer.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you know, the trial today? I was thinking... If you gave it a score, what score would you give it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Score? Um, gee... I guess I would... um, or maybe... well... ...Bah. I'm just as bad as you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See? It's so... so vague!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Clearly. Machi avoided a guilty verdict, which is something. Though I can't say I'm any less confused about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I asked Interpol about that number. I'm sure you'll find their answer intriguing. "IPXX314206"... The agent registered under that number... ...was Romein LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the victim, Mr. LeTouse... Who would have guessed he was actually an undercover Interpol agent!? ...What a mess. And we don't have any idea what he was investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, true, but we know who shot him now! Lamiroir told the whole court!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wait! That voice just now... ............ It was him. I am sure of it. That voice I heard, talking to Mr. LeTouse... when I heard the gunshots fired. It was him! It was Mr. Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's another mystery, Apollo! I love mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't. Speaking of mysteries, what's Mr. Wright up to? I wouldn't mind asking his opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now that you mention it, I haven't seen Daddy around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, is he some kind of stray that just wanders in and out at will?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wouldn't say that, but he has been going out a lot. Some "top secret mission", he said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Top secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Anyway, you can't just rely on him to save the day! And you've got me to help you. We'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine... right. Well, time's a-wasting, as they say. Let's investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are several books of magic mixed in with the legal books on the shelves. I dusted them recently. Nothing like the gleam of clean books!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Charley, the potted plant. Huh? His leaves are looking a little... brown.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good morning, Mr. Charley! Ack! M-Mr. Charley! Your leaves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you weren't giving him enough water?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, no, it must be stress. He's worried about the new recruit at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, don't blame it on me! You are watering him, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was Daddy's turn to water him this week... Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright has been away on his "top secret mission", no?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm sorry Mr. Charley, this is all my fault. I'll water you soon, promise!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, that ring kind of gets in the way. Our client the other day tripped on it and fell on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Sending my ring rolling out the door! You know how long it took me to find it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know how long it took to calm down the client? And in the end, they walked out without hiring us. Could you clean up a bit?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But don't you think the props give the office a festive, fun-filled mood?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure law offices have to be festive and fun-filled.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! This is the "Wright Anything Agency"! As CEO, I want an office that says we know how to have fun!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess it is her office... isn't it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A strange, split box leers at me from the wall. No matter how many times I see that there, it still strikes me as... odd.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I guess I've gotten used to it, after growing up with it always around the house.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What kind of a home did you grow up in!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'd hide in there when we played hide 'n' seek! You just get in, slide the sections around, and you're impossible to find!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I bet you would be...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A faded photograph showing one of Trucy's favorite magicians. She talks to it daily for good luck, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack! I almost forgot! Umm... I hope I become a famous Grand Magician! Oh, and I hope Apollo becomes an Ace Attorney! ...There! All done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I suppose if you're going to talk to inanimate objects, a photo isn't so bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How is your magic act coming along?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I've been working on my "cups &amp; balls" routine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that the one where the ball moves from under one cup to the other?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! The very same! Here, watch... First, I put one of the cups over the ball... then I snap my fingers! Ta da! The ball's under the other cup!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's not there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... ...Watch me pull something out of my magic panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nice try.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guess I know what I'll be doing tonight. Practicing! You can be my audience, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's one of those hats you pull things out of, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course! My hat's like a little universe! Bigger on the inside than on the outside!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... That reminds me of a sci-fi show I used to watch.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Incidentally, my pocket is a little universe, too! And my panties, and...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've seen some restaurants that set out real food to show what's on the menu.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I have, too! But I noticed something strange... One time, there was a sandwich without any lettuce! Like it had disappeared... by magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm sure someone just swiped the lettuce and ate it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, that sandwich... You didn't...! Apollo, you shouldn't eat sample food, no matter how hungry you are!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just how hard up do you think I am!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, how about some tea? Here you go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, thanks. That's nice. ...But this is not the time to be drinking tea!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right, we have to get investigating! Ack, that was a close call! We almost relaxed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir dropped a bomb in court today... "It was Daryan"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir said she's never forgotten a voice, right? That's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's that called again? Um... Elephant ears...? I bet that's what they're called...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Somehow I don't think that means what you think it means. ...And she has to be wrong, this time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wrong? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I mean, look... Those gunshots were right during the concert!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! I was burning up the dance floor at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Did you happen to look up on stage? Maybe... at Daryan, even?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You bet I did! He is one of the Gavinners's guitarists after all! He's so cool! ...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. All the Gavinners have a rock-solid alibi. He couldn't have shot Mr. LeTouse backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... Lamiroir heard him, didn't she? She heard Daryan backstage... Right...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Somebody's either wrong, or lying very badly here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An Interpol agent... hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was wondering, what is "Interpol" anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Interpol? They're the guys who catch international criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why can't they just call them "International Police" instead of making up some silly name?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... ...Anyway, you think he was investigating Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaa--!? Why would anyone do that? She's not a criminal! She couldn't be!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't be fooled by appearances is all I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But remember I'm a magician, Apollo! I can spot a palmed coin at fifty paces!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If only it were that easy. ...In any case, we know he was working on something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder if it was something that has something to do with something. That something being our case. The last something, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something like that. ...Frankly, the whole thing is making my head hurt. <thought>What was Mr. LeTouse up to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That again? You sure like your attorney's badge. Still, I'm afraid our clients are getting tired of it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well I'm not. So there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not sure about that, sorry. I was ripping up the dance floor at the time of the shooting, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Trucy? Was that another one of your tricks?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It wasn't me! I can't even make Mr. Hat laugh like that!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Wherever the mundane gives way to miracles, a word is whispered... Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! The other day...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's there!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We... didn't just imagine that, did we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was wearing a silk hat. ...Friend of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hardly!</line>
<line speaker="???">We meet again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, um, nice to meet you. Who... are you? <thought>And could you please stop smirking like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah. Ahhhhhhh! It's you!!! Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uncle Valant...? He's your uncle!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, silly! It's the Great Gramarye, Valant Gramarye! The Grand Magician!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes, it is I, the Great Valant Gramarye. As seen on television.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And could you please stop smirking like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">It's been a while, Miss Trucy. Seven years to be exact! My, how you've grown!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good to see you again, Uncle Valant! You... look exactly the same!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I hate to intrude, but... What is a Great Magician doing paying us a visit?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I believe it was you who wished to see me? So, be quick with your questions! And do not quail, quake, or quiver. I am quite tame. Though my stardom may sear the sight... I'm quite down to earth when need calls.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He does have a certain aura to him, it's true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's ask him about the case, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>His "aura" sure isn't lost on our magician-in-the-making. She's practically drooling with enthusiasm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">After all... ...Uncle Valant's one of Daddy's best friends! That's why I call him "uncle".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What? Daddy... you mean Mr. Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, I mean... My real Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Trucy's real father!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, Apollo... Don't tell me you don't know about Troupe Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Troupe Grammarie... huh? No. But it does sound kind of familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Oh, lost life! Lamentably listless lad! To not know of the greatest troupe of magicians on the planet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Valant Gramarye... The name began to surface in my mind. It was a name I'd heard on television as a child.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You bet you've heard the name! He made a cruise ship disappear, and blew up an amusement park... ...Oh, and he made all this gold disappear from a safe! And then escaped from a high security prison!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... ...You said he is a magician?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I open the locks to hearts chained... by mediocrity. This is the true miracle of Troupe Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do remember... seeing you on television... a long time ago. Weren't you with someone else...? Like, a duo?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A duo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, you had a partner. "Something Gramarye"...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes... Zak. Zak Gramarye. A masterful maker of magic, a capable crafter of shining showmanship!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">? Why's everyone so quiet?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daddy...? <thought>Huh!? Oh, no way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Once upon a time, the Troupe Gramarye included two Grand Magicians. Myself, Valant Gramarye, and my partner... Zak Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this Zak was...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He was my real Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy's father, a magician... I guess it makes sense.</thought> ...I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There wasn't much point in talking about it... Not now that he's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, it's OK. I'm not lonely. I've got my Daddy, after all! And you make me laugh, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Glad that I'm good for comic relief, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Not that I see Daddy around much these days.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">What's this? You would ask me for a miracle? Free of fee? Then thy wish be granted! Thy will be done! Thy evidence evicted into the ether!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! No evicting, please! <thought>...Are all magicians like this, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Reasons?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Two, in fact! The first being, of course... ...to see you, Miss Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You don't know how happy I am to see you again, Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I'm sure you are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not one for modesty, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">When I encountered you at the Coliseum... the first time in seven years... ...I could fain contain my emotions! I wept oceans! And to learn you now defend that poor pianist, that blinded boy! Twas a hot topic of talk amongst the staff, you know. And defend him you did!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh heh. Well, it wasn't all my doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I'm his defense attorney, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">My other reason for coming here today... was this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's... a video tape?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Quite so. A recording of the concert, no less. I've brought it for you, Trucy, on behalf of Troupe Gramarye. Will you watch it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow... It's almost as good as it was live. So... what's the word? Mysterious...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There are more mysterious things than her song going on... Way more mysterious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This Valant Gramarye has good reasons to be here today... But I wonder what his "reasons" were to be at that concert?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I was wondering... That stunt in the middle of the song there...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I didn't see a stunt...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about Lamiroir vanishing and reappearing!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that? I guess I'm so used to seeing that happen I didn't even notice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So young to be so jaded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">A simple slight-of-hand [sic], a petit prestidigitation. A modicum of magic from me... to you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So that's why you were at the concert!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. I was there to watch my trick take to the air...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're the one who knows how it was all done.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Of course. I am like a deity, with the stage as my domain! I suffer no mystery upon those floodlit boards not grasped tightly twixt my fingers. It is a potent, primeval power I possess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Well... Do you think you could... ...tell me how it was done!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's like, totally against the rules, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not during a murder investigation, it's not!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Mais non, for my illusions are mine alone, m'sieur. Also...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Also what?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Recall that the terrible occurrence happened later. Well after my illusion entranced the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Don't even ask. I won't answer.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad for you, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr. Whose side are you on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I, Valant Gramarye, now make my leave, Miss Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's no need to rush, Uncle Valant! You should stay a while!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I am afraid I cannot. I may not. I shall not. I have been asked to assist with an analysis and so I shall slink back to the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you'll be at the concert venue today?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Correct. If you would call on me, come to the Coliseum! See you later, crocodile.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With a whir of his cloak, and a wink of his eye... ...he turned and walked out through the door. Normally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, there you go, Apollo! Let's get cracking!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right. <thought>Valant Gramarye... I've got a few more things to ask him. Foremost among them, that bit of magic that made Lamiroir disappear... ...And how he knows Trucy, and her "real" father...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this photo is of your father, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someday, I'll be as good a magician as Zak Gramarye! You'll see! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No wonder she's so devoted to her art...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You should have seen him on stage, Apollo! He made things disappear right and left! Poof poof poof! Until he even made himself disappear! Cool, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, yeah... <thought>Is that how it really happened?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi may not be guilty, but he's still a suspect.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But they don't have any decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but only someone as small as him could have gotten out of that room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right... the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And... he lied.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lied?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi Tobaye can see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! Machi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Speak of the devil.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He looks like he's doing OK!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I forget. Why did we come here? It's not like we can talk to him or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Words are overrated! Feelings are what matter, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's kinda hard to build a court case on feelings. But, since we're here, anyway. Might as well get what I want to say off my chest.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you need someone to complain to, I'll listen...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think she's actually worried for me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That security camera is looking at me. Why do I feel this sudden urge to make a silly face?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A security guard. He stands here, watching this room. His eyes when he looks at Machi are gentle. Maybe he has a kid the same age.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, what did you think of the trial today?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Whew. I'm glad he doesn't understand English after all. If he did, he would have been scared out of his mind by that trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, all's well that ends well. You have to be more goal oriented. If he's not guilty, we win.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, if he's innocent, we win. Machi might not understand English, but I bet he gets that better than you do.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm glad Lamiroir testified! What a great person. She even got Machi off the hook by naming another suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daryan of the Gavinners... The detective. I wonder if Machi knows what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I mean, if he could follow how the trial went at all. If no one told him there's a new suspect, how would he know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Machi... You can see, right?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">........................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Machi can see, and Lamiroir can't... The whole world's gone topsy-turvy!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">........................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sorry, Apollo. I don't think we're going to get any information out of Machi. ...Which makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Yeah, I guess it does...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think he said... "I am sorry I cannot speak your language. You are very beautiful, fair maiden."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This is why I never trust a translator.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Imagining what, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's just, I couldn't help but feel that... I dunno. Machi... ...He doesn't understand what we're saying, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How could he? He's a young Borginian! He doesn't speak English.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but my bracelet is reacting to him.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Maybe it's malfunctioning? Or it's scared, because you keep making those "I'm so mad" faces.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was I that bad? <thought>Machi lied about not being able to see... But what if that's not all he lied about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you're curious about it there's only one thing to do. You should ask him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think it'll take something big to get to him... Some kind of undeniable evidence.</thought> ...We'll be back, Machi.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">........................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo! What a great day! It's perfect weather for sleuthing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The weather matters for an investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't some days just feel like "magic" days or "defense" days?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, sure. Let's get started, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right on! Show us your stuff, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your voice training! This is the perfect place for it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I did enough at home, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aw, there's no need to be shy! Keep that up and you'll never make it on the big stage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm happy in the courtroom, thank you. I am a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then you're in luck, because it's lawyer weather today! Don't you just want to face the blue sky and shout, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, the weather has nothing to do with lawyers. Let's get going already!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! A blimp!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those balloons next to it have ad banners on them.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... "Big Sale, All Shirts 50% Off."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. It's an ad for the department store next door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that... creature there?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooh! That's the police mascot, the Blue Badger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh? It's life size!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Haven't you seen them around town? Patrolling the streets? Yes, now even law and order has a mascot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'd run from that thing even if I wasn't a criminal. Why does its head wobble like that when it walks? It's freaky.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't think you're showing true Blue Badger spirit, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sunshine Coliseum sure is living up to its name today.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's huge! And Mr. Gavin got to play on that enormous stage... I'm so jealous! Someday, I'll fight my first battle on this stage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Battle?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, yeah, it's a coliseum, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, they don't do gladiatorial contests at these places any more, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I had no idea! I wonder why they stopped.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sometimes I worry about her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, a massive sign for the "Guilty as Charged" Tour. A giant Prosecutor Gavin stares out over the arena.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Maybe I can take it to the office when they're done with it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, where would you put it? You couldn't even get that thing through the front door.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then I'll put it outside! I bet it'd be good for business!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just as long as no one comes expecting us to prosecute.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, if anyone comes looking for a concert, leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is this part of some twisted plan of hers to make her singing debut, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, Mr. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir! I'm sorry about today... I...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There is nothing you need to apologize for. You were merely defending Machi.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... Are you OK? Alone, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Humans are blessed with five senses. Even robbed of one, we get by. ...Though it does make being a witness rather difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Speaking of "seeing", you knew who we were before we spotted you just now. And we weren't even talking.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I heard your footsteps several times the day before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh... You must have great ears!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ears that heard the crime taking place... Or so she claimed yesterday. ...But how?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would be the Blue Badger, the police mascot. There's a guy outside in a giant Blue Badger costume, lumbering about... He stands out even more than those Gavinners posters.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's all the same! He's the band mascot, too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't picture Prosecutor Gavin going for that kind of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Neither can I. I'll bet there's a story there just waiting to be told!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's been lying there since the day before yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's small. Maybe no one's noticed it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I kinda want to pick it up. It'd make a cool souvenir, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It does stick out in my mind for some reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the Gavinners's dressing room. They're all out on the investigation. Being backstage isn't half as glamorous without a band here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Lamiroir's dressing room... and the scene of the crime. It's kind of lightly guarded for being a crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not complaining! Makes it easier for us to go in! And Ema gave us her OK, right? We can wander in and do as we like!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How is Ema doing, anyway...? I hope she's not getting cavities from eating all those chocolate Snackoos...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a stack of Lamiroir's postcards. There it is... The "landscape painter in sound"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must be hard to pretend you can see when you can't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet the way she sings so effortlessly... you'd think she had life easy. Some people are just impressive like that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know it! It just makes me think about how much further I have to go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I hope we can solve this quickly and not add to her troubles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The speaker here is the same as the one in Lamiroir's room. I wonder if this one was blaring as loud as hers.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't see a volume control anywhere in the room... My guess is they give all the rooms equal treatment!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You mean equal punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They found Machi Tobaye's fingerprints on that air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with the long face?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a little lackluster, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lackluster...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I mean, using the air vent is so obvious! No audience is going to pay good money to see a trick like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Things must look different through a magician's eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It'd be much cooler if the killer got out through that tiny window!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't go there. You'll get your head stuck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right after the shooting took place... ...Lamiroir tried to come into the dressing room, and dropped her brooch.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think that fits with the other stuff we know. Do you think the timing of when she dropped it is important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Something about it bugs me, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at the way those bullets tore through this thick wall. That revolver really was something else.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder if someone as little as me could even fire it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dislocating your shoulder would kind of put a crimp on your stage career.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy always has stiff shoulders, maybe that could loosen him up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't even mention it. I'm afraid he might go out and actually try it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Nah, he doesn't have the guts to pull the trigger, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! It's fruit! Fruit, Apollo! Fruit!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I heard you the first time. It sure is a lot of fruit. I doubt anyone would miss a bit of watermelon...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know, I'll make it vanish! Into my stomach!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Better not. They might make you pay for it. And if you have the money for that, you should probably repaint the office first.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Watermelons are that expensive!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*shrug* These could've been imported from some exotic locale, for all we know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The shooter must have used that to climb up to the vent.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All this tragedy, because someone left a stepladder here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I don't think Mr. LeTouse was shot because of the ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You think it was Machi?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess... That air vent is pretty small, after all. <thought>Does that prove he was at the scene...? Did he escape in the time between the gunshots and us opening the door?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a poster for another show. "This Summer: A Legal Eagles Production of 'Case Closed'."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I looked into that performance group. Turns out they're all law enforcement-related, too. Apparently, their serious portrayal of law and order is a big draw!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That sounds so boring, it's probably pretty interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're a complicated man, Mr. Apollo Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A Gavinners poster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How many of those did they put up, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prosecutor Gavin looked so cool on stage! You should learn to play the guitar, too, Apollo! You can accompany my magic act!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...We'd certainly be a novelty act, if nothing else. <thought>I'll think about it if I ever lose my attorney's badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A speaker for monitoring the stage. It was blaring at the time of the shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a pretty old model for such a nice place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess they don't care about sound quality back here. As long as you can hear it... <thought>Not that a loss of fidelity could possibly make that music worse...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good speakers must cost a lot. You have any idea how much a nice one that size would cost, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Probably a good ten years of your allowance, give or take.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaat!? But that's almost 600 dollars!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Five dollars a month...? Poor Trucy... Wait till she finds out you need to buy two speakers for a stereo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's one of the biggest, most expensive-looking TVs I've ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad you'll never own one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Never"'s kind of harsh, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. How about "for all eternity" then?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Same difference.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, look. A part of the carpet has been torn up here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That was the part we did the luminol testing on in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Luminol... right.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what I couldn't stop thinking? Who's going to pay for this carpet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As long as it's not us... Maybe... the shooter?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess it's true what they say. Crime doesn't pay!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would hope that carpet replacement costs weren't the only thing holding you back.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's one heavy-duty bouquet there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have trouble thinking of flowers as being "heavy-duty".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But they call lots of things heavy-duty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not flowers, they don't.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What about a "heavy" scent?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you mean "heady".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What if the flowers were plastic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They still wouldn't be heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK, what if they were made out of metal?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, like a magnolia made out of steel?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Exactly! Though I hope all my fans don't start throwing metal flowers at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's one of those permanent dryers you see in hair salons.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is that what they're really called? "Permanent dryers"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do I look like a beautician? I just know they dry your hair and give you a permanent...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It just doesn't sound very glamorous, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK, how about a "permachine"!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Or you could go more simple, like "permer"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This isn't a bad game, thinking up official names for things. Not that it makes the name actually official or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A stack of presents for Lamiroir. Stars always get the biggest presents. You know, you could give me a present, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Here, have a piece of candy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Gee! Thanks!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She must not get a lot of presents... Poor girl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder weapon. So it belonged to Mr. LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That thing makes normal revolvers look like water guns!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. LeTouse was a big man. <thought>But how about the person who shot him? Wouldn't they have to be about his size?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This was the window where Lamiroir "saw" the crime from... I wish it was that simple.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Kind of hard to see a crime when you can't see. But she did hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but the window was closed...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe she heard it some other way?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all the electronics. They must be sound-related.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Doesn't seeing a bunch of machines like this make you want to just fiddle with 'em? Can I, Apollo? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no fiddling! You'll break something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you're going to make an omelet, you gotta break some eggs! That's what Daddy always says.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These eggs look kind of expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the ladder we used to climb up the stage tower. ...Not a moment I'm likely to forget any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Me neither... I'll never be able to climb another tower again without thinking about it, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'll never be able to climb a tower again, period.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still can't believe we found Machi and Mr. LeTouse up there...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. I used to not like high places. Now I hate them.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's not like it would have been nicer if we found a dead body closer to the ground. ...Though that reminds me. Daddy's bad with heights, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, no kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He took me on a Ferris wheel ride a while ago, you know! Halfway through, his face got all green and he mumbled "objection" over and over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Poor guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That song... Isn't that the one Lamiroir was singing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, you're right. "The Guitar's Serenade"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, I'd love to do a show on a stage like this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd come to see that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The house is full, and as one, the audience sighs with wonderment! There I am, singing my ballad, rose petals swirling through the air...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not bad... wait. Aren't you a magician!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Oh. That's right. I was a magician, wasn't I.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Some dedication...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha! If it isn't Miss Trucy! And indeed it is!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What exactly are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I take real responsibility in tasks undertaken. I am inspecting my equipment of illusion to make sure naught is amiss, Miss.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Lamiroir Teleportation Illusion! Ooh!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Should anything go wrong, it would reflect poorly upon me and my troupe. As I went about my exacting examination, I happened to notice that piano. ...And I remembered that fair lady's melancholy melody.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey Apollo, maybe Uncle Valant can shed some light on this whole thing for us!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's one big piano! I've never actually played one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh. You should get Mr. Wright to teach you sometime.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No good, he can't play either.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I kind of feel bad for the guy now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe now's my big chance! Stand back, this could be the debut of a prodigy! ...Eww.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you make that noise just now?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... Let me try it again. You know, I think something's stuck in the piano! Time to take a look under the hood... ...Huh. Look! This was stuck between the strings. It looks like some kind of switch.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Someone must have thrown this into the piano...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you think that thing was doing in there?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Throwing things inside pianos can't be good for them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not to mention you wouldn't be able to play whatever notes go with the strings it was on. <thought>But the piano was fine during the concert... That must mean it was thrown in here after Machi played.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So maybe someone threw it in here after the second set...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was wondering about the show the night of the murder. Lamiroir's vanishing act was your illusion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed. The purple prosecutor petitioned my performance. At the climax of the song, he said, make her disappear. ...Like a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like a dream...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet, what can I work with on a stage meant for musical endeavors? There are none of the conveniences of a stage built for sorcerous acts. It was a challenging task, and so I accepted.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She disappeared from the top of the tower... ...But in order to move, you would have had to use some sort of secret tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">People come to me because I am a professional among professionals. My illusions are custom-made for a time and a place. ...Now, because of the murder, all the eyes of the nation are on this concert. Not a bad thing, as far as the fortunes of Troupe Gramarye are concerned.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... you were here checking up on your trick to make sure it went well.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">And went well it did. Now, speaking of pianos... ...That piano over there troubles me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It troubles you...? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Why? Why do you ask, why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think it's probably quicker if I just go check it out myself, thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I know what you are thinking in that head of yours. "Gramarye, yes," you say. "I recall seeing him on television." Something of that sort?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, actually, yes, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! He just read your mind, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Or everyone tells him that and he made a good guess.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">It was twenty years ago... A young magician, a genius of his time, came down among us... His name... was Magnifi Gramarye! It was he who began the great Troupe Gramarye! At his prime, not a day passed that he did not play upon the screens of every TV there was.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I do have a vague memory of someone like that on TV...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet, several years ago, that time came to an end. My troupe pulled a vanishing act, yes. Cries for magic no longer heard, the TV screen a barren waste, stripped of illusion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-That's not true! I still went to all your shows! Like that one in the parking lot down at the supermarket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>When you start playing supermarket parking lots, you know you're in trouble.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...We hone our skill at these small venues, always awaiting our time. ...Yes, one day we will rise, up from obscurity, onto fame's shining stage once more! I do this not only for the magic that is Gramarye, but for my partner...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your partner...? You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. Zak Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy's father...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Before he disappeared seven years ago... ...there was no name higher than Gramarye in show business circles. None. I will see us returned to glory! I, Valant Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Our founder Magnifi Gramarye was truly a genius, a worker of miracles.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll never forget the one I saw when I was little! How he made that whole jumbo jet go... um, what happened to the jet again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Apparently someone doesn't remember it as well as they thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Of all the would-be magicians who came to his door, only Zak and I had the talent. In no time at all, Valant and Zak were the shining stars in the Gramarye crown.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Cool, huh? And Zak Gramarye was my daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Now that Magnifi and Zak are gone, I have but one wish. Let it be I, Valant Gramarye who brings the Gramarye miracle back to the big stage!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm rooting for you!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Miss Trucy, you cannot grow up quick enough! I need your skill by my side!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">One skill, coming up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How do we manage to get off the topic of the case so quickly all the time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah... The proof positive of your profession, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Might I... have a look? Oh! What's this? It is gone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! What'd you do with my attorney's badge!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha. Don't be alarmed. Miss Trucy! Take a look into your topit, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eek! It's your badge, Apollo! What's it doing in there? That was amazing! Wasn't it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He called that pouch at her waist a "topit"...? Is that some kind of magician speak?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Pardon me? I have no money, if that's what you want.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! No, no, I was just... Um, never mind. <thought>The way he looked at the revolver... What was that? It was almost as if he had seen one before... and maybe wasn't too happy about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was wondering about the stunt in the video, right in the middle of the song.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I didn't see a stunt... Oh, that? I guess I'm so used to seeing that happen I didn't even notice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So young to be so jaded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">A simple slight-of-hand [sic], a petit prestidigitation. A modicum of magic from me... to you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So that's why you were at the concert!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. I was there to watch my trick take to the air...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So! Can you tell me how you did it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa! You can't just ask that sort of thing, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's against the rules to ask a magician how they did it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not when you're doing a murder investigation it's not!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Well, you might have a point, there. Will you tell us, Uncle Valant?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">It is against all that is sacred to inquire as to how a trick is performed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK, so you tell me how he did it, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, you're a magician! Aren't you part of the same secret club?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Words cannot express my shock and chagrin... All I can see before me is this stage, and me, upon it. ...Nothing smaller, nothing less radiant catches my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">True. You're getting on in years. Not much time left to make your mark, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">............ This is not how I was seeing it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he doesn't care about what I have to show him, I get the point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This switch, sitting here, tempting me to push it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't. You might blow up the whole coliseum.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, please... To think that every strange switch triggers a bomb... That kind of old-fashioned crime drama thinking doesn't cut it in our busy times!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alright, Trucy P.I., please enlighten me. What do you think this switch does?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Maybe it turns on the electric razor in Prosecutor Gavin's dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...A switch as big as razor to turn on a razor? OK...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was quite a statement you made today in court. ...About hearing Daryan Crescend's voice at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I did not know his name... ...but I never forget a voice.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">La-Lamiroir! Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That voice just now... ............ It was him. I am sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...No way...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...As I said in court: I was on my way backstage from the stage. That is when I heard his voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm guessing Daryan and Mr. LeTouse were talking about something?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...The next moment, I heard those gunshots.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you call security?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">To be honest, though the noise was quite frightening... ...I never imagined the gunshots might be real. And, I was in quite a hurry myself. I left the scene at once.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... it really was Daryan's voice that she heard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... <thought>At least, she certainly thinks it was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I met Machi before my debut as Lamiroir... I was singing in a restaurant in Borginia.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And he was playing the piano?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes. He was very kind to me when he learned I could not see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that when you started playing "opposites"? With Machi pretending he couldn't see...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, no, it wasn't then. That began after our major debut. ...After I became known as the "landscape painter in sound".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must have been tough for Machi... ...Pretending he couldn't see, and all the while acting as your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">We held hands always. He would write with his finger on my palm to signal to me thing I should know. He is a smart, gentle boy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I see what she's getting at... ..."Machi would never harm a soul"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About Mr. LeTouse...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah yes. He was an Interpol agent, I hear?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you had no idea?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Of course not. No one did.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess that's what it means to be undercover.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But someone was after him... They had to know who he really was.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Why did he pose as my manager? I do not understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have no idea?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I can only assume that he was investigating me... But why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Perhaps it is not so, but I cannot deny the possibility. Because of my condition... As my present is veiled in darkness, so, too, is my past clouded from my memory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Clouded... right.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The darkness that I fear is not the darkness that I see whenever I open my eyes. The real darkness... lies in my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In your heart?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I have no memory of the time before I became Lamiroir. I awoke from darkness, into darkness, you might say. I was singing in a restaurant those days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What was it that she said about not being able to remember the light...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I do not know my past. Perhaps I committed some terrible crime in my past. Everything before becoming Lamiroir is lost to me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But I don't think you...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I can think of no other explanation. Why else would an agent of Interpol approach me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think your past might be related to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No way! That seems really unlikely to me. I mean, you're such a sweet person, Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I thank you. Machi, too, tells me this often when I fear who I might have been.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We took a look at your performance again. It was even better the second time!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That reminds me... That was an incredible illusion you pulled off!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Illusion...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When you teleported from one stage to the other? Remember?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, yes. Apparently, they hired a professional magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Valant Gramarye...</thought> I was wondering, do you think you could tell us how it was done?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I'm afraid I cannot. Mr. Gramarye made me swear to never tell a soul.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was afraid of that...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hard to be a magician if you can't keep a secret, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think you could tell me about this?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I'm sorry, but my information about the outside world is somewhat limited. I only know what I have heard, or felt.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe that explains why she didn't react when I showed her stuff the other day. She was still pretending she could see then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That's correct. You need them to communicate across such a large stage. Everyone on the staff had one, of course... ...And all of the band members, too, I should think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Prosecutor Gavin and his lackeys had them on, too, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">They're quite helpful, though limited. They only work within thirty feet or so. After all, they're only for use on stage. And a stronger signal would interfere with the sound system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, that makes sense. <thought>You'd think someone would notice if they dropped their only communications lifeline. ...So why was this one lying here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, I am reminded that I wished to speak to you about something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">When I was walking this hallway before... I stumbled upon a small device of some kind. It was lying on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Device...? Maybe you mean this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's been lying there since the day before yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Might I... touch it? ...... I thought as much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? What did you think?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">This is one of our headsets. Everyone on staff wears one during a concert.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder whose this is?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">We use it for communication. It would be quite inconvenient should it go missing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll hold on to it for you then. We'll give it to Prosecutor Gavin when we see him.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, that's best. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, can I put it on?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Attached"? I'm not some kind of robot, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Everyone on staff was wearing one of these headsets... This might warrant some further inquiry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I ask you about this headset, Lamiroir? You said that all concert staff were wearing one?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That's correct. You need them to communicate across such a large stage. Everyone on the staff had one, of course... ...And all of the band members, too, I should think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Prosecutor Gavin and his lackeys had them on, too, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">They're quite helpful, though limited. They only work within thirty feet or so. After all, they're only for use on stage. And a stronger signal would interfere with the sound system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, that makes sense. <thought>You'd think someone would notice if they dropped their only communications lifeline. ...So why was this one lying here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">10-4 that, little buddy, this is Trucy reporting in, over. ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why the sudden silence?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No one answered.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't be silly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What good is a receiver that doesn't receive? That's like Ema not performing forensic investigations!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You make her sound like she's some kind of forensic investigation machine! Which is just silly. Unless... she's a super hi-tech android that runs on Snackoos! Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh oh... There's only one person I know who can munch with such... venom.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hello, Ema. You're looking as grumpy as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, am I supposed to be happy? You give me the second degree in court, and Prosecutor Gavin makes me look like a fool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're talking about the blood stain Mr. LeTouse left?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My department chief had a field day with that one. "Even a blind person could see the shooter wasn't blind!" Funny guy, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But that blood stain helped uncover the biggest mystery of all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now we know that Mr. LeTouse was really with Interpol.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We wouldn't have found that out without you!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I suppose. Maybe that's why the chief gave me these after he was finished chewing me out. Said it was my reward.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Are chocolate Snackoos popular down at the precinct or something?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I was hoping we could check out the crime scene again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Be my guest. You're not going to find any clues in here. ...Though I did find something strange.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something strange?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the air vent with Machi Tobaye's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with the frown?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Can't a girl frown anymore? Is that a crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! No, of course not, I just meant...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Machi Tobaye's fingerprints are on that air vent. Why would his fingerprints be there if he wasn't the shooter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's not a question I want to have to answer in court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! Wipe that frown off your face. One stick in the mud per crime scene, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess girls can frown, but defense attorneys can't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, the carpet's been torn up here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the part we did the lunimol testing on in court!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Loony mall"? What's "Loony mall"!? It's "Luminol"! Get it right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...! Ema's kind of scary when it comes to science.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Best learn the word and not incite her wrath again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I met my embarrassment quota for the year, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, that's a good thing, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um, how?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I mean, think about it. Now you don't have to be embarrassed about anything else all year!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...If only it worked that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It just bugs me to think that little kid outsmarted me. And it makes him even more suspicious now that we know he can see! He could have seen the air duct, and he could have shot that revolver.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But that's not how it sounded in Lamiroir's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean her saying she heard Detective Daryan's voice at the scene? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why can't we have a normal, straightforward killing once in a while in this country!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll pretend I didn't hear that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Was that true what you said in court today? You know, about the case... About how everything was happening according to those song lyrics?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..."The Guitar's Serenade", you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I found the link, you know! First, Prosecutor Gavin's heart-shaped key ring was stolen. Then Lamiroir flew through the air. Then Prosecutor Gavin's guitar caught on fire. And in the end, a bullet took Mr. LeTouse's life... And he went up into the sky with a guitar... Well, thirty feet up, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It is kind of hard to chalk it up to coincidence, hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know! And I found it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You think the same person did all of this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't ask me. I didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Neither did I! I couldn't fit through that air vent anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What... You all think I did it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sometimes I worry about that girl.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...So what did you find?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's so little I must have passed over it yesterday. I found it under the sofa.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Part of some device, I think. I haven't a clue what. The bit sticking out from the end looked familiar, so I had it examined. Turns out it's an antenna.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, like on a beetle?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Like on a cell phone. This device must use an electronic signal of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">An electronic signal, you say? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...What are you trying to do, burn me alive!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C'mon, it was just a few sparks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Says you! You weren't the one holding it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's enough sparks flying around here just with you two talking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway... Now we know this is a remote for an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let me see that for a second. ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, this is definitely a little transmitter. The signal's weak, probably only reaches thirty feet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A transmitter, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally, if you look at a cross-section diagram of the stage area... ...Let's see, thirty feet from Lamiroir's dressing room... That covers the backstage completely. It also looks like it would cover the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It kind of seems unlikely anyone would use this on stage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, you're a bit like Mr. Wright. He always carried his badge around, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I think he did it so he'd never forget who he was, or his duty as a defender. Something like that. Pretty noble, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess there really isn't a need for me to carry this around. Though it seems to have made a decent impression...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why did they have to commit their crime according to the song? Seems like it'd be more trouble than it's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they were trying to throw off the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's certainly possible. But risky, don't you think? Just carrying someone as big as Mr. LeTouse would be tough enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She may be a snacking fiend, but sometimes, she actually makes some sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's an Interpol-issue revolver, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which means it belonged to Mr. LeTouse. He must have had it to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sounds that way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, if it was Machi... Are we saying Machi stole it from Mr. LeTouse...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now that's really hard to imagine him doing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think you could take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm. A small device... Looks like a transmitter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A transmitter?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You press this switch here and it sends out a signal. No idea what it's for, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think you could take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm. A small device... Looks like a transmitter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A transmitter?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You press this switch here and it sends out a signal. No idea what it's for, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A signal... You mean an electronic signal?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Say, Ema... You know that "strange object" you said you found?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let me try pressing this switch...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... Yeeeeeeeeeeoooooooooouch!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I-I-It's on fire! Ema's device is on fire!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's the big idea!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, now we know what this is: an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This part here must work like a lighter!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It nearly lit me up, that's for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, don't look at me like that. I didn't do it on purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I suppose. At least, we're getting somewhere with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo! Let's ask Ema more about this switch!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now that she has some first-hand experience.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What! You aren't trying to burn me up again, are you? Who sent you to get me? Who?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not out to get you, promise.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Promise!? No promise is good enough with you still carrying that weapon around! Try burning me again with that trigger of yours... ...and I'll throw 100 bags worth of Snackoos at you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've never seen someone munch so furiously. Better stay clear for a while.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think you could take a look at this, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her rate of chewing is increasing... Better back off before it's too late!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're off to look for more clues elsewhere, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I feel better just knowing what this thing is now. I'll have to look into igniters a bit more later.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd like to know a bit more about igniters myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This switch triggers an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad, I was hoping it was for a bomb that would blow up the whole coliseum. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're scaring me. If Ema hears you talking like that she'll arrest you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And then she'll do all sorts of scientific tests! Like splitting your hairdo into three separate spikes. While she stands by, laughing and laughing in her high-pitched voice. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... I said she'd arrest you, not me. And she's not some kind of mad scientist.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Did you just hear someone laughing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All these little parts... It's pretty complex. I'm guessing this is where the fire comes out. Other than that...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good thing machines run even if we don't know how many work! ...That's what Daddy always says.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not really a saying you want to go around repeating, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What? Come to laugh at the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daryan...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">That old bag opens her pie hole, and wham-bam my life goes down the chute. Thanks! They won't let me work while I'm a suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daryan isn't in the best of moods, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not many people are these days, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It is a crime scene. Not exactly the happiest place to hang out.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Then Gavin had to go rub salt in the wound... My alibi's rock solid. Rock solid!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, about your alibi...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You have to ask? The shooting happened right in the middle of the third set!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... that's right. <thought>The music was blaring when we heard those gunshots... ...And found Mr. LeTouse dead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I've got ten thousand witnesses who saw me, too. Right there on that stage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your guitar playing was something else!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Thanks, little lady. ...See? This whole thing's a sham. I can't believe they aren't letting me work!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's no need to yell at me... <thought>It's Lamiroir's fault... She was the one who said she heard his voice at the moment of the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Man, I never even talked to that old windbag! How could she possibly identify me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They won't let you work?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He won't let me work! Gavin! Says I gotta lie low till the suspicion is cleared. What suspicion!? He can be such a stick in the mud.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin? A stick in the mud?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He may look all flashy and showy, but he's straight as an arrow, man. ...'Cept when he's depressed. You hear him whining the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, you mean the thing with the mixing board?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And then there was that performance just now. What was that all about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This part is off.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is that? Hmm... 2nd Guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was you Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He's just a perfectionist, is all. Not a bad guy, really.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I think the Gavinners are the best! I have all your albums.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The band's fine, too. Gavin can write a good tune, I'll give him that.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">"The Guitar's Serenade", eh? Classic tearjerker, that one.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You don't think he based it on a real experience, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Probably not. He writes by feeling, more than memory.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! You mean the songs just kind of "come to him"?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, something like that. I guess you could call him a genius. Of course he changes the song and lyrics on a whim. Drives me up the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He makes his court cases on a whim sometimes, too.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He changed the lyrics to a song just before a recording the other day, even. Wants to put in this line about a university student obsessed with girls. Whatever!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm? Why does that sound strangely familiar?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Of course it always turns out good in the end. That's his talent, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Look, if you want to talk about the case, talk to someone else, 'kay? Don't want Gavin having another one of his hissy fits.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, him? He's down at the prosecutor's office, most likely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecutor's office... <thought>I've never been there, have I.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The data on the victim should have come in from Interpol. ...Normally, I'd be down there dealing with it. Normally.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Let's go check it out! I've always wanted to see the prosecutor's office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Maybe that's not such a bad idea.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right on!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Say "hi" for me, OK? Oh, and "screw you". And tell him I want into that crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, we'll be going now.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hey, wait.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What do you really think happened? Really? You don't think I did it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Great. Way to instill a guy with some confidence. Just remember, I was ripping it up on stage when it happened, OK? Ripping!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Don't get led astray by some siren song, eh? Get this one wrong, and you'll be eating humble pie for a year. I'll bake it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's... not talk to him anymore. Alright?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Detective Daryan Crescend... He's one stone I'd leave unturned if I had a choice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This place is deserted.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder where Lamiroir went off to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure she's OK on her own. She seems resourceful.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess... But I can't help worry about her a little.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... this is it. The Gavinners's head office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not the band's office. It's the prosecutor's office.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, so that's why I am asking, what is this creepy thing... object... whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Looks like Prosecutor Gavin is on the phone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh well, guess we'll have to come back. Or we can hide behind that bookshelf real quiet-like...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's eavesdropping.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why? We'd just be waiting. Quietly. So he didn't notice. What if we heard something scandalous about the band!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She'd make a good reporter... for a gossip mag.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What? A "replica"...? So why was he after it in the first place? Yeah, LeTouse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>LeTouse...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Look, don't talk to me about those Borginians, OK? Just get me that report, chop chop. ...And stop leaving mysterious objects in my office, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's times like this when I start to miss Daryan... ...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erm, hiya!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee! Just thought we'd drop in. Hope you're not mad...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...How could I be? There's not enough "tee hee" in the world, in any case. Have a seat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Prosecutor Gavin, the philanthropist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Watch and learn, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, who have you come to see?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Klavier, lead vocalist for the Gavinners? Or Prosecutor Gavin, scourge of the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you think he means, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think he's giving us a choice. We can either ask him about the concert... or the case. <thought>Which way to go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was an impressive bit of pyrotechnics that did this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the guitar from the concert, isn't it...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I thought it was one of the staff playing a gag on me. I never guessed that wasn't the end of it... I had a specialist analyze the guitar, incidentally.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? Did you find anything out?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He didn't have a lot of time, so it's still unclear... But the results he came up with were... intriguing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Intriguing? <thought>How does that guitar tie into everything that went on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sounds like something we should ask about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's that on the plate there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that... gum?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Gum...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he was chewing it when the phone rang. So he put it on the plate for later consumption.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You'd think a rock star could afford a fresh stick.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't jump to any conclusions, now. That's no chewing gum. Take a closer look... ...Although I really shouldn't be offering, should I.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is that...? It looks like a lump of plastic...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, that phone call...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, so that's why I am asking, what is this creepy thing... object... whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Looks like Prosecutor Gavin is on the phone.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What? A "replica"...? So why was he after it in the first place? Yeah, LeTouse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin, does this have something to do with Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Wait a second! You were listening to my phone call, weren't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Who? Us? I-I tried to stop him, really! But he forced me to!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you were the one digging for a scandal, Ms. Reporter!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Too [sic] tell the truth, I'm not even sure what it is. But apparently, it's a model of something undercover agent Mr. LeTouse was after.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This... lump?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you mind telling us what you do know about it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all the guitars! Why so many?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You can never have too many guitars. They are like... my lovers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I didn't just hear him say that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They're backup guitars, Apollo. Don't you know anything? Rock 'n' rollers always smash their guitars at the end of a show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No wonder it's so hard to make it as a musician.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what, you should try rocking a little, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And breaking his guitars while he watches? That might be a little too rocking.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha. Of course, I would never do such a thing. Did I not say, they are like my lovers? Do I seem like the kind of man who would do such a thing to ones he loves?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, no! Not at all! I mean, you're Mr. Gavin, upstanding prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What happened to Prosecutor Gavin, god of rock?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, look at that stereo!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">To me, a life without music is inconceivable. I never turn down the volume, even when I'm working on a case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's such a huge speaker! It must be really loud!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This room is completely soundproof, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? At my place I can hear when the neighbors turn their VCR on to record something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you can get Mr. Wright to talk to them, work something out?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And lately, we've been getting complaints about Apollo's voice training.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Maybe I'll go have a word with Mr. Wright, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This display shows all the evidence for the case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, Apollo! He's got three televisions!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hey, don't look at those too closely. I'm still sorting out the details.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Each monitor shows evidence for a different case. He does them all at once!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wish I had three TVs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What would you possibly do with three television sets?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I may look laid back and relaxed, but in reality, I'm quite busy, you know! I'm living life at turbo speed! Doing magic, going to school, investigating cases... But... But if I had three big TVs...! I could watch a magic video, do my homework, and catch a crime drama all at once!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The first two seem useful, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo? You look confused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was just wondering where the "work chair" in this office was.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You're looking at my favorite chair right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's a massage chair, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That is an ergonomic, adjustable office--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I love the ones with the vibrating rollers on your back! Those feel great!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Did I say something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No. I merely realized the futility of an explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The view is exhilarating, ja? I sit here, gazing down upon the city, writing my songs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Try working on cases.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is the same thing. I write lyrics the same way I corroborate evidence. It is a harmony between the logical mind, and the primal spirit within!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is it so hard to admit that you like staring out your window and daydreaming?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, that reminds me, did you see the paper today?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes! I always read the TV section.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good girl. How about you, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I read the funnies.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Then you will not have seen this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Concert of Tragedy -- The Prosecutor's Deadly Song!"</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, is that a new show? I haven't heard about that one.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's not a show. It's an article. News, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, does this have anything to do with the case...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Since getting back from the trial, my phone has been ringing off the hook! "How does it feel to take a man's life with a song?" "Have you ever hummed a man all the way to death row?" "Do you think you could sing for me over the phone?" ...It is endless. Endless! Thanks to the case you made today, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that was all Apollo's idea!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey!</thought> Hmm? Is that a newspaper over there, too?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah yes. The Borginian Daily Bugle. Go ahead, take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, thanks, but I can't read Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, that's right. Suffice it to say this is big news over there as well. Though they didn't go so far as to mention the lyrics to my song.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Probably no one in Borginia could believe it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It's probably seen as "just a theory" at this point. Their journalists didn't see the need to mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That makes sense. I hardly know what to think of it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir's testimony will probably be in the evening edition, I'd imagine. Which is why I've had Daryan step down from the investigation for now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, we ran into him moping in front of the coliseum.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir was my invited guest, so it is a rather delicate situation... ...You understand how much I want to solve this case. Quickly, if possible.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I really love that song. It has such a great atmosphere to it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You co-wrote it with Lamiroir, if I remember correctly?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. It was last year... I had gone to tour Borginia's legal system, as a matter of fact.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And that's when you heard Lamiroir's voice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was at a small jazz club. ...I wept that night. I knew I had to meet her, to talk with her. So I used my influence, which is not inconsiderable, to arrange a meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, prosecutors really have a lot of clout.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think he's sort of a special case, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Thankfully, she liked the work I did, and we wrote a song right there, backstage. Machi on piano, that dulcet voice... And myself on a guitar that I borrowed from Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And music history was made! Probably not an experience your average lawyer would ever have. Like Apollo, say.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is a memory I hold dear. And the song we wrote that night... was this. And that very guitar is right over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean... this charred lump?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't call it a lump! That's a piece of history! And it's only browned, not really "charred".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No matter. I shall never sing that song again. I wouldn't have used that guitar again either, even if I could have.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What happened during that song, anyway? Why did his guitar suddenly catch on fire?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think you could show it to us? Your charred... I mean slightly burnt guitar?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure he doesn't mind. What more could happen to it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It was a beautiful instrument. It was played lovingly for many years. A guitar befitting a woman like Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How did it end up here?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She gave it to me. I mentioned how much I enjoyed playing it that night, and she made a present of it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So this guitar is from Borginia?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That it is. We couldn't carry it on the plane. Changes in air pressure and humidity ruin the wood. So, we vacuum packed it in Lamiroir's studio. I used a special shipping service available to me for transporting evidence. They brought it right up to my office for me. ...Pristine and untouched.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See, prosecutors do have a lot of clout.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I still think he's a special case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Such a valuable guitar... It's too bad it got burned.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was it that you were saying earlier? ...Something about intriguing results from an examination of the guitar?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, you know how guitars have a round hole in the front? It is called the "sound hole".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, so that's what it's called.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, they found something attached to the wood just inside the hole. ...A broken device of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A broken... device?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. This, in fact. The examiner is busy with evidence for the case now, however. So he'll be checking this out once he's finished with everything else.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Odd. That device looks strangely familiar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This was found in Mr. LeTouse's bag. It's apparently a replica of something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A replica... <thought>It's a small lump, about an inch and a half long.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We analyzed it... but there's not much to say, other than it's a lump of plastic. Perhaps it was to be used in the identification of whatever it is a replica of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean... whatever Mr. LeTouse was after?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That seems to be the most logical explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well? Well? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't ask me, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? If you don't want to tell us, you could just say so.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I've put in a request to Interpol via my contacts in Borginia... But, apparently there is a block on information somewhere along the chain.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Something Interpol doesn't want to tell Borginia... Something about this little piece of plastic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. LeTouse went through all that trouble to become Lamiroir's manager... ...just to come to this country to find out more about... this lump? And he died for it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I've sent someone to the coliseum to fetch Lamiroir. Perhaps she knows something about it, being a Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The Guitar's Serenade... Might I ask, did you enjoy it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a lovely song! I got all teary-eyed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah yes, the "cursed song that turned a concert into a tragedy", wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I was singing it for you, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa! Th-That's so special!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It was Lamiroir singing, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I am glad you were moved. It is that kind of song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>......Ack! I've run out of snide comments!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That looks like one of our tour-issue headsets. Why are you wearing it, Frulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I thought it'd be cool! I could pretend I was concert security and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, we found it at the venue and thought you might want it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, no, please, you keep it. It goes well with your cape, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee! You think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She does look like she belongs on a stage, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin, about this remote... <thought>Wait!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Excuse me, did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This remote control might be valuable ammunition for the trial tomorrow! It's too early to show my hand now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You would think someone with such a loud voice would speak more clearly, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It has to be one of these...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That "device" that was found in your guitar...! ...Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...! Why, that looks like the same thing! What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Another one!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was at the crime scene... In Lamiroir's dressing room. Detective Skye found it, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...At the scene of the crime? What could that mean, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My apologies, but there's no way I'm going to talk details about the case with you. If you want to get my attention, bring me something... dramatic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not here to get your attention, Gavin... ...I'm here to get your information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's lightly scorched, and then there's this...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's burned clean through!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep, It's pretty much a useless piece of junk.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...It's kind of like you after a trial, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Which part? The burned clean through, or the useless piece of junk?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Sample", huh? Think they out a big enough label on it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe it's to keep people from eating it by mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, they might think it was an otherwise tasty, white lump of plastic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe it's the manufacturer? "Sample Toys: When you can't afford the real thing!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like a company Mr. Wright would like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Thanks for dropping by, ...Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why, you gave me so much information! That igniter, for instance...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. That.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I've never met an attorney so forthcoming with the prosecution. It's a big help. ...Or perhaps you're just a tad nave, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I guess I could have hid it, but somehow, showing it felt like the right thing.</thought> I could say the same... to you, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for the information. About the, er, strange lump of plastic. The one that Mr. LeTouse was investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I've been thinking, Herr Forehead. We encounter many incidents in our lives, all of us. Not all of them simple.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Especially not the ones where people are killing to song lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That is why I try to at least remain simple inside. And I keep a simple goal: to discover the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's why I like to keep relations civil, ja? ...That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I can live with that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Frulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can I ask you why you sing in a band?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah. Because I want women to turn and look when I walk down the street.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's pretty simple, too.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now if you'll excuse me, I've got work to do. Another time, perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The charred remains of what was once a fine guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin got it as a present from Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And he had it shipped back from Borginia in a vacuum-sealed case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Kinda sad how it ended up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Not to mention there was an igniter placed just inside the sound hole. I wish I knew why...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why the sudden silence, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I'm sorry. It's nothing, really. I was just wondering, wouldn't it be cool if that replica just happened to vanish?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ah, the young magician at work again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Though a simple disappearance would kind of lack punch. What if it hatched into a dove? Or a person, dressed like a dove...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There she goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These guitars are vintage models. Probably pretty expensive, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They've even got little locks on them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Weren't you good at picking locks?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! You don't want me to...? ...Well, I do kinda like that cherry red one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm kidding! I'm kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh. That's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sorry, my little thief in the making. Maybe next time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's an insanely big speaker for a room this small. Oh, look... All the CDs are Gavinners CDs.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He left his TV on. Think we should turn it off for him?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nah, wouldn't want to make him angry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK, if you say so. It's kind of a waste of electricity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You just want to play with his TV. I know you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee! How'd you know? It's just, I've never seen a TV this big before!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hate to break it to you, but it's actually a monitor. It doesn't play TV shows.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!? You mean no soap operas!? No Saturday morning cartoons!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Nope. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I... I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There, there, you'll get over it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a cool chair! I'm going to sit in it now while no one's looking! Wow! So this is what it feels like to be a star!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Who would have thought a chair could bring so much joy into someone's life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can imagine sitting here, strumming my guitar... "Oh, it's you, Herr Forehead. Sorry... I'm busy. Woooo."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, that was a remarkably good imitation.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee! Maybe I'll make that part of my Wonder Bar repertoire!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What floor are we on again? The view is incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! The people look like little rice grains! Hey! That one with the blonde hair! Do you think that's Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... He's a little too small to see.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But look at the one next to him with the big black poof of hair pointing straight ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh yeah, that's Daryan alright.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Looks like Machi is in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, the police must have a Borginian interpreter. That's no fair. I wish we could talk to him.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess we'll just have to come back later if we want to see him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That security camera is looking at me. Does that thing just sit there recording 24 hours a day? It must use one of those ultra-long-play tapes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A security guard. He stands here, watching this room. I think the guard is trying to set a record for the longest time without blinking.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Oh, it's you. You came at a good time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hello there, Ema. What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Either of you know where Lamiroir is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... well, I saw her in the backstage hallway a while ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah? That's strange...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can't find her anywhere. I was supposed to bring her to the prosecutor's office...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir's missing!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's hard to imagine her wandering off somewhere on her own. ...Being that she's blind and all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. We'll help you look for her.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Great! Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? The stage is pitch dark!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The power breaker must be off for this section... Great.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll go get someone! Yipes, it was really dark out there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dark... That's all Lamiroir has, when you think about it. <thought>What would it be like to live in a world of darkness?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Hey, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Doesn't something about the stage seem different to you? Like, something's changed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Changed?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't put my finger on it, but it's bugging me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now it's bugging me, too! What's she talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, that case... Wasn't that open before?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh. I guess someone closed it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait... Look! Where the case closes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something's sticking out! That... doesn't look like an instrument. You don't think it's...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's open it, Apollo! Eeeeeeeek! Lamiroir! Lamiroooooooir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema! We have to get Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir was taken directly to the hospital. Ema ran around, barking orders, making phone calls. Trucy just clung to my arm and cried... And me, I was still in shock. Two bodies in two days is two too many.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ema! How's Lamiroir? Is she OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, you. We all owe you a big "thanks", that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... she's OK?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. She came to a short while ago. You found her before it was too late.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-That's good to hear...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Someone attacked her. ...She was struck on the forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By who!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But they hit her on the forehead, right? That's right in front of her! How could she not see... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. Would you like to see her now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She wants to thank you for saving her life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, Mr. Attorney. You were the one who found me? Thank you from the bottom of my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm just glad you're OK. Tell me, what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The door down the hall reads "X-ray Room". I never did like X-rays... I don't think I'd enjoy looking at someone's insides. Spotting nervous tics is intense enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must be a recovering patient. He keeps staring at us. What's so unusual about an attorney and a magician?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A nurse watches, hawk-like, from the reception desk. She glares at me whenever I talk. Maybe my voice carries?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Some visitors are here in the waiting room, watching TV.</line>
<line speaker="TV">"...murder during a concert at Sunshine Coliseum..."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, looks like we're on the news.</line>
<line speaker="TV">"...with his current hit song, "Guilty Love", is in the courtroom as prosecutor... ...singing the defendant all the way to death row..."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Prosecutor Gavin this, Prosecutor Gavin that! Where's my fifteen minutes!?</line>
<line speaker="TV">"...The Guitar's Serenade... On sale now!"</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was after I spoke with you in front of the dressing room. I sensed someone approaching. I thought it might be someone come to see me, but they said nothing. When I went to return to my dressing room...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You were hit?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I knew, that very moment, I knew! The assailant... was trying to kill me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was lucky for me the first blow did not knock me out. I turned and ran for the stage. Someone was chasing me, I could hear footsteps... Yet I reached the stage first.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I had overheard maintenance people talking. The power to the stage area was off, they said, for electrical work.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Darkness is my ally. There was a contrabass case near the stage. That is where I hid.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the assailant couldn't see you!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Once in the case... I'm afraid I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that sounds like a really close call.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you have any idea who it might have been?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Unfortunately, no. Whoever it was, they said not a word.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yet, when I consider that I was struck high on the forehead... I must conclude that whoever hit me was taller than I am.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good point... <thought>She's sharp!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And you're much taller than I am. You're about as tall as Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, that means it was likely an adult, and probably a man. <thought>...Could it be him!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But why would anyone attack you, Lamiroir!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The detective asked me this, too. And to her I gave the same answer I give you: I do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Well, they call it "Borginian"... It must only be found in Borginia. For certain, all in Borginia know of these.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a cocoon... so, do you get silk from it?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I do not know the details, I am sorry to say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I thought she said all in Borginia knew of these?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There is one fact I do know about the cocoon, though. Something all in Borginia know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The cocoons... They are not to be taken out of the country. If someone does, and is caught, they will be put to death.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">T-T-T-To death!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I do not know. Yet, if Interpol was involved... ...I'm sure there is a good reason.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But this is just a piece of plastic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was carrying a replica... but looking for the real deal. That's my best guess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, that's what he was up to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tracking down Borginian Cocoon smuggling...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Smuggling...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It seems I was "marked".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Marked"...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Life changed for me with the popularity of my songs. I began to travel around the world.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! So you could have brought those Borginian Cocoons with you...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...On my trips, yes. That was probably the suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And Mr. LeTouse was placed as an undercover agent to look into it.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Borginia is a small, sheltered country. Not many of our people venture into the world outside.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is that why they suspected you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... Mr. LeTouse wasn't a Borginian, was he. He was an Interpol agent, which means...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there must have been some reason other countries didn't want the cocoons out. Something scary enough to get Interpol involved.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Like what? How could such a tiny ball of thread cause such a commotion?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, Lamiroir, I wanted to ask you about this. Do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">This... this is what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. LeTouse was carrying it. It's a replica of the thing he was after.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He was "after"...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, in his secret identity! As an undercover agent!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...So that's what he was doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! You mean, you know what...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I know, of course. This must be... ...a Borginian Cocoon. ...Or rather a convincing replica thereof.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why haven't I heard of a Borginian Cocoon before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why would he be carrying this around? Was it some kind of souvenir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I'm sorry, I'm not quite recovered from the attack...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She looks like she's had a rough day... I'll just put this piece of evidence away for later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's one other person I need to talk to!</thought> Thank you for talking to us, Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was the least I could do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, I have another request.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">If it is within my power...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I need an interpreter. Someone who speaks Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you come with us, if you're well enough?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I see... Yes, yes of course. I shall accompany you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Where are we going?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C'mon, Trucy. We're about to get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The giant instrument case that Lamiroir was hiding in. Things like this wouldn't happen if people didn't make such big cases!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I'm not sure the case is to blame here, Apollo. We have to find whoever did this to her. No one hits a siren of the ballad on my watch and gets away with it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry. We'll find her assailant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... We came to talk to you about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi...</line>
<line speaker="Machi">!................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you interpret for us, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... I'd like to talk to you about when we first met. ...When we still thought you were blind.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now we know the truth. You can see, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was completely fooled, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... Isn't there another secret you're hiding from us?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">......!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wait, Mr. Attorney! What do you mean by "secret"?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do I mean by "secret"? Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">................[Borginese speaking]</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, Mr. Attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't need a translation to understand that. I'd know that "wrong evidence" look anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I'd imagine you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh, let's try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If I'm not mistaken... ...you know something about this, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">......!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, you got a reaction! A big one!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi, you didn't...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Trucy and I are trained to see people's uncertainty. Not that we would have needed any training to see that one.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. Attorney, please tell me what this is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir, please, interpret!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know you know something about this by your reaction. If you won't tell me, I might have to give it to the prosecution... ...and have them look into it!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">! .................... [Borginese speaking]!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He asks you to "wait, do not be so hasty."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">M-Machi...?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">.................... [Borginese speaking]....[Borginese speaking]?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"Do you know everything?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, everything. Well, sort of.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Have him tell us about it!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"Very well"...</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi, he is upset he could not speak with you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's hear him out before he gets grumpy, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is this cocoon, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"The cocoon, the silk, is a potent cure."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A cure...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It must cure some disease.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It's a cure for "Incuritis".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A cure for Incuritis?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, if it's a cure, why keep it in Borginia like that? Just think of all the lives they could save by sharing the medicine!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I do not understand the reasons myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK, well, at least we know what it is: a cure. And Mr. LeTouse was after cocoon smugglers. Wait, was Machi...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi, you weren't...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He couldn't be a smuggler! He's so little!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, you're only 15, and you're sort of a magician, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, that's true. I am sort of a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She said "sort of"! Oh, to have a copy of that security camera tape...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, Machi? Are you... a smuggler?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He... won't tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">First he plays blind, now he plays dumb...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder... Do you think he brought a cocoon here to sell it to someone? If Machi really did bring one into the country... ...was he planning on making a deal for its sale?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"I can't go home"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can't go home!?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....[Borginese speaking]....[Borginese speaking] ....[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"I can't go home to Borginia. I do not want to go home." The penalty for taking a cocoon from Borginia... is death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right! It's punishable by death!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]........</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"About the case..."? What about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He wants to tell us about Mr. LeTouse's death!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking], [Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="???">This meeting's over.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Daryan?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What do you mean? Visiting hours aren't over yet.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">There's a call for Machi from the Borginian Embassy. This meeting is over. ...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just give us five more minutes. We can call them back after that.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Sorry, no go. C'mon, piano-boy. We're leaving.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daryan! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...I never liked you. Either of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Darn it! We were so close! He was about to tell us! Hey, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He didn't want us to hear what Machi had to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...And there can be only one reason why.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why is everyone ignoring me!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, sorry! <thought>This is it... I know who I'm after now. It all happens tomorrow... in court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No clues here.</line>
</xml>