
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Academy</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">Were you able to sleep last night?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?! ...Oh, sleep! Sure, I slept! <thought>For a grand total of zero hours.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Guten Morgen, you two. You look like you're ready to put on a real show. But before you do, I have a good luck gift for you. The voiceprint analysis came back, and the results couldn't be more clear. The voice in the mock trial video and the tape recording are one and the same.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words, the recording's a fabrication.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The lab is continuing their study of the tape. So far, they've found signs of overdubbing. But it's going to take a bit longer to recover the audio that was erased.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! Wh-Who's there? Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you see who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No. I got a quick look, but they got away. I think it might've been Hugh. I bet he was eavesdropping.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder if he saw our hand.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, I'm sure he wasn't the only one just now. I bet Robin and Box Girl were listening in, too. I will make sure they don't make a run for it. That is my final gift to you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, all that's left now is to reach out to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Time for a mini Chords of Steel workout! I'm Apollo Justice and I'm fine!!! ...Your turn!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm Athena Cykes and I'm fine!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene for the trial of Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Cykes Brigade is totally psyched... er, I mean, the defense is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution is ready as well... er, I mean, isn't that right, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, moving right along. Yesterday's adjournment was unexpected, yet necessary. But I'll be running a tight ship here today, so no funny business from anybody, understood?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness, Robin Newman and Hugh O'Conner have recanted their confessions. But later, I shall grill them at leisure to find whether I can charge them with perjury.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this sure complicates matters. Still, one must not overlook the facts. Now, about the school camera photo that was submitted yesterday--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A pity, but that evidence is no longer relevant to this case. The art room clock runs fast. It cannot function as an accurate measure of time. As for the bungling detective who overlooked that, he is paying for his failure as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Poor Detective Fulbright. I hope he returns to work with all his body parts intact.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But if that's the case, then what will we--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The accused is the sole person who could have moved the body from art room to stage. And I mean to prove it here this day.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It's just like Detective Fulbright said. But what else does he have up his sleeve?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">My understanding of this heinous crime is thus. The murder took place near the center of the art room, as evidenced by the bloodstain. Blood was also found on some pottery next to the window over the maintenance area. Which is to say the body was carried over to that very window. From there, it was dropped down to the maintenance area below. And though there was nary a scratch to the body aside from the fatal wound... ...that, too, was per the script. A high jump mat was employed to cushion the fall. Then, a ball cart was used to haul the body over to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not very clever. I mean, it's the same exact body moving scheme as the script. Anyone could've moved the body that way.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why you--!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Moreover, the prosecution has a witness, which is most unfortunate for you. Witness! It's time for you to come forth!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">.........Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* Well, then, will the witness please state his name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hugh O'Conner. I'm a senior at Themis Legal Academy, and I'm studying to be a lawyer. Yesterday, I told that lawyer there that I would testify to the truth. So, I intend to cooperate fully in today's trial. Happy now, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nrgh... <thought>What's he up to now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court appreciates your cooperation, Mr. O'Conner. Now, your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The Lecture Hall was packed before the mock trial, but the rest of the campus was empty.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The real truth hurts so much, doesn't it, Ms. Cykes? Or maybe you thought I was going to bring up something else entirely against your client?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! <thought>Never a snappy comeback when I need one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's coming straight at us today, using any means possible.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">To protect the students who had to climb up high when setting up the stage... ...a mat was brought over to the stage from the storehouse.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our client is the Student Council President! What's wrong with her taking it upon herself to put the mat away after they'd used it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arrrgh! <thought>It sucks being the last to know everything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......I think I get it now. The drag marks we saw behind the stage were made by the mat.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If the only mat of that thickness was where the body is assumed to have been dropped... ...it would be hard to deny a possible link to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're off to a bad start again. You sure you're okay, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...It's game on, Hugh. Game on. I'm gonna turn your arrogant perfect-score grin into a teary-eyed frown of failure!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The Lecture Hall was packed before the mock trial, but the rest of the campus was empty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">What. I was just getting to the important part.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Eager to unsheathe your blade, Cykes-dono? Your heavy breath heaves to where I stand.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">So, the only issue is distance? You're not denying that you're a heavy breather?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! I'm just saying that scientific studies have proven that it's not--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hang in there, Athena. No matter how many insults they hurl, it won't affect the judge's opinion of you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What about my own self-esteem?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Let's get back to what happened before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's when I saw Juniper dragging a large mat from behind the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! <thought>If we win this one, I promise to donate another thick mat to the academy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Now, show me how to show you the truth. You'll have my full cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I was watching her from a vantage point between the stage and the maintenance area.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I was between the stage and maintenance area, and she was behind the backdrop.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm, he's sticking to his guns. The issue here is where Hugh was standing when he says he saw Junie. But nothing I say will mean anything without evidence. Time to dig a little deeper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Oh, and before you ask, I had my glasses on. Therefore, I'm positive it was Juniper. That is not an issue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">She was heading towards me, so I assume she was on her way to the maintenance area.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Hoy, Justice-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Our assertion is Juniper was simply putting the mat away. In that case, where would she be taking it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, umm... to the storehouse... over in the maintenance area...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Precisely. Therefore, there is naught wrong with witness's judgment in this matter. It is your wild charges that are the issue here. But I cannot help it if you keep seeing red.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's going to get a face full of Justice, Apollo-style, if he keeps that up.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh... Anyway, I saw her heading towards me...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">But I didn't have time to stand around and see what she did after that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know. Thank you for stating the obvious. <thought>I also know that you, Hugh O'Conner, were one of the participants.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Confidence sure goes all out when he tells the "truth."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't think he meant for any of that to be misleading, but it doesn't make it factual.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Careful now, Athena. A genius like Hugh could be leading you right into a trap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'd be surprised if he wasn't. But all I can do is charge forward with both eyes opened!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, you saw the back of the stage from the between the stage and the maintenance area? Well, let's take a look at this photo taken by Ms. Scuttlebutt, shall we? This photo shows the students setting up the stage the day before the mock trial. Do you see the big construction screen to the right of the stage in the background here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes. In fact, there were a bunch of those next to my house until a few days ago, too. It was so noisy behind there, but I couldn't take a peek. Oh, how it piqued my interest!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly, Your Honor. You cannot see past such screens. That is their purpose. Now, let's see... How exactly is that screen positioned again...? Ah hah! Since it was to the right of the stage, it should be right here. And from this vantage point... ...the witness claims to have seen our client behind the stage backdrop.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! But the screen would've been completely in the way!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Therefore, the witness couldn't have possibly seen our client from this point!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hrrrgh! ...Youch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! Mr. O'Conner! Have you been lying to this court?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The screen... Right... It must have slipped my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Are you telling me you, Mr. Genius, forgot something as literally big as that?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">There are two kinds of memory lapses: the normal kind you mouth-breathers have... ...and the genius-level lapses of memory that people like me have.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Why don't you just admit that it was a normal, everyday brain fart already?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the witness now please restate what he remembers minus the lapses of memory?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, that's easy. I was on the other side of the screen. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hrrrrrrgh! ...Youch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nice one, Athena! Keep it up!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The truth? What truth?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The fact that Golden Boy here was where he initially stated. That is to say, he was between the maintenance area and the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Athena, look at the photo again! Do you think...?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something on the other side of the screen... Something high enough to see the stage... No way! This crane right here? But I don't remember seeing a crane there on the day of the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me neither, but it's probably safe to assume it was moved before you found the body.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I recall making no such promise. It was you who came blubbering to me about keeping quiet in exchange for information.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's this about a promise? Is this about whatever Blackquill is using against him?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what's it got to go with going into the crane?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Golden Boy did not go up in that crane for fun. ...He was working part time as a crane operator within school grounds.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? Do you mean to tell me a high school student was operating a crane?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If this whole part time job thing is true, I doubt it would be limited to a single day. You were probably working at the same site the previous day, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this what you're thinking of, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yep. As the court can see, this photo captured the crane's operator. And if you look carefully, he bears a definite resemblance to Mr. O'Conner.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Are you serious?! This is ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How very interesting. Let's ascertain whether this is as ridiculous as the witness maintains.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The defense agrees with the prosecution. Let's bring the facts to light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's all very well and good, but just how do you propose to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The person in this photo has one really distinguishing feature. I'm not a hundred percent sure, but it's at least worth a try!</thought> We can clearly identify the person in this photo as the witness by examining...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should check for Mr. O'Conner's fingerprints on and around the crane!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Of course you'd find my fingerprints there. I was watching Juniper from there. ...And besides, what do fingerprints have to do with the person in the photo?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, what DO they have to do with that person?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court would like to remind Ms. Cykes that it is her job to answer such questions!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaah! <thought>If I could match a feature from the person in this picture to one of Hugh's features... I'd prove that the two are one and the same!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I have a question for the witness. What is your hobby?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. My hobby? If I had to say, it would be... ...scrapbooking tests on which I scored at least 100, which is all of them, actually. I use an iron to perfectly flatten each one before it goes in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just as I thought. Mr. O'Conner is obsessed with his own genius. It's no surprise, then, that he has one or two repugnant hobbies like that.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">None... None at all, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No it doesn't, but apparently, you have an interest in pain!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! <thought>I'd better think more carefully before people start to think the worst of me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The figure in this photo is wearing a very unique object around his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes. You can see it right there. But then, are you saying you mean to...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner's neck is almost entirely concealed by his tall collar... ...but that's exactly why I believe this warrants further examination!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No! Not a chance! That would be a blatant violation of my privacy!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You are a disgrace of a man. Now start unbuttoning that collar before I hack it off!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! What's the big deal? Now, let's see your neck!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">......... Guess I have no choice.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? ...Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, where did you buy that neckband, if I might ask?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I didn't buy it. It's handmade, and there's only one like it in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it sure looks like the neckband in the photo. Should we have the photo analyzed?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You are one irritating lady. ...Fine. I admit it. I work a part-time construction job. It has nothing to do with our school. Operating heavy equipment's no big deal for a guy who can parallel park one-handed. But I never expected one of my jobs would take me to my own school.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But when you factor in all of the required tests and apprenticeship period... ...wouldn't you have to be at least twenty to have a license for operating a crane?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Oh, um... about that... You see, I'm a genius, so, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">High school seniors are nineteen at most, thus, they fail to complete the requirements. But that does not apply to you, does it, Mr. O'Conner?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why doesn't it apply? He's a senior, so he's around that age, right?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, don't! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Actually, Golden Boy here is twenty-five. He took a seven-year break from school.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Wait. Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Take a gander at the official school enrollment documentation. 'Tis all right there.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Arrrrrrrrrgh! ...Youch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T-T-Twenty-five? You mean he's older than me?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A twenty-five-year-old high school student?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you have that backwards, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Even geniuses make mistakes. I just happened to make mine only seven years in a row.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Only Hugh could get away with using "only" like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough of this jibber-jabber. Suffice to say, the witness was up in the crane when he saw the accused dragging the mat. The accused readied all she needed to move the body immediately prior to doing so. That much is clear. I see no need to deliberate the matter any further.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Considering that the body was moved in the same manner as in the script... ...I find Prosecutor Blackquill's claim to be quite persuasive. Does the defense care to dissuade me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! As long as a mat was used to move the body, Junie's going to be under suspicion...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Athena. I just thought of something. What was Hugh doing in the crane right before the mock trial? He couldn't have been on the job at the time. I mean, he was waiting for the trial to start.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, why was he in the crane? Wait, you don't think...?! Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've got it! I've got an amazing idea that will turn the prosecution's claim on its head! <thought>A little conjecture has never stopped us before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, you were using the crane to...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The screen was in your way, so you wanted to move it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then why, pray tell, is it still in the exact same spot it always was?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's easy. The witness changed his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is close to changing its mind about the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo! Ugh. ...Another chance at that one, please!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, you were using the crane to commute to school!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. That would be a feat, considering we aren't even allowed to commute by bicycle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! W-Would they really do such a thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Probably not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, that's too bad. And too bad for you, too, as I must give you a penalty. No exceptions!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yiiikes! <thought>But commuting by crane sounds kinda fun!</thought> P-Please, let me give that another try!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The body was just like it was in the script, so it must've been moved like in the script, too. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those are pretty strong words, Athena. You sure about this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The witness is a licensed crane operator, so he could have used it to move the body!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wait, he's on my side this time? Or is this another trap?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Watch this! I can use a bow and arrow one handed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, that's a crazy level of dexterity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I can even drive a crane with one hand. That's easy. But operating the crane itself is so complex, it requires both hands. Now, I would have the court look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh... Please tell me that's a ketchup stain.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You wish. My hand was injured and required surgery. That's the reason I kept my hand in my pocket all this time.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I have already verified this with the hospital of treatment. Quite a nasty wound, they say.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-So, how did you hurt it?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I see no need to discuss that. It has no relevance to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Two hands are required to operate complex machinery such as a crane. Ergo, on the day of the mock trial, the witness was incapable of moving the body by crane!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Now I'm the fool?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I'd planned on moving the crane the night before the mock trial, but then I got injured. Wanting to keep my part-time job a secret, I had to do it just before the mock trial instead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Arrrgh! And here I thought this was the big break we've been waiting for!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now that the defense's sophistry is laid bare, I would have the court recall my claim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The body was dropped out of a third-floor window to a mat near the maintenance area. Then, a ball cart was used to move it to the stage. See? I've been paying attention!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well done, Your Baldness. Now consider this! The accused was sighted dragging that mat. Ergo, it was she who moved the body!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think you were on the right track, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, Juniper remains the prime suspect if we assume the body was moved as per her script. So, as the defense, you have to figure out how else the body could've been moved.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But... <thought>Oh, is he telling me to think of another way besides the crane?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes. If you have a counterargument, this court would love to hear it. And if--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you do not, it is time for the verdict. Isn't that correct, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that WOULD show that the mat had nothing to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There is a sword of great renown that cuts down sophistic lawyers. Its name is Evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, you don't scare me! <thought>Force a smile, Athena! You can do it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's wrong with your face, Athena? It's a weird mix of terror and creepy grin. Just focus on how the body could've been moved without it being dropped.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>How could anyone lower it without just dropping it? It's not like it could fly... ...Or maybe it could. After all, there IS a way to zip between the art room and the stage! Someone could've easily used that thing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm? ...Oh, yes, of course! Ms. Cykes, the court would like to see what you have for us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>All I have to do is show the tiniest shred of a possibility.</thought> The mat and ball cart weren't used to move the body! This is what was used!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? I would love to hear how that would be possible.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I'd love to hear that, too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, that would be your job, in case you've forgotten!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right! <thought>I know there's something that connects the art room and stage! I just have to show it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The key here is the thing that ties the art room and the stage together.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Might I propose an idea? It might do you well to tie your lips together, lest you further expose your ignorance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This isn't exactly the time for black comedy, Prosecutor Blackquill... Anyway! The court will recall the wire on which the school banner was hung. That wire was strung between the art room and the stage... ...which allowed students to run or reel in the school banner from the art room. The body could've easily been lowered down to the stage via this wire!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure that's exactly what he thought.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When we investigated the stage yesterday... ...the bottom part of the school banner had been tied into a pouch-like shape. And pouches are useful for carrying things. What do think [sic] this one could have carried?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, go on. Please explain!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The body was bundled into the pouch-like section of the banner and sent down the wire. The body would've been down on that stage in a flash! And there'd be no need for a mat!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I've heard the phrase "carrying the banner," but the banner doing the carrying?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you have an actual objection, then just come out and say it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I trust you recall the bloodstains left on the art room pottery. If the wire had been used to move the body... ...it would have to be via the window above the quad -- the one with the winch. However, the bloodstained pottery was next to the window above the maintenance area. Ergo, the wire and banner had naught at all to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, um, ha ha. The bloodstained pottery... I remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This doesn't look good. We'll be back to the mat theory if you don't do something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? I hope you have something better this time than a circus act.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If my wire theory is true, then that blood on the pottery must not have been...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">At first we thought it was red glaze, but it turned out to be blood. But what if we go back to the time when it was just red glaze by all accounts?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can't change fact to fiction, Ms. Cykes, let alone travel back in time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoops...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Ms. Cykes. Please share your thoughts on what this blood really is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's not the victim's blood. Did the police check to see from whom the blood on the pottery came from?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Shame on you, Cykes-dono. Have a little more respect for the constabulary. ...Fool Bright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like they didn't check it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, don't let it get you down, Prosecutor Blackquill! Everyone makes mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Spare me your cheek. We will know not either way till the tests are run.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>True, but in the meantime, I'm going to press my claim as far as I can!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness. I demand that the blood on the pottery be analyzed this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course. It shouldn't take long to get the results back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my. That was quick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're history if it turns out to be the victim's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Please, please let it be someone else's.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Nngh. It seems the blood was not from the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Furthermore, a comparison with other parties involved with this case reveals... ...that the blood belongs to one Hugh O'Conner.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Score!</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">.........</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough*... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Junie. Just try to relax.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">H-Hugh's hands... His hands were... dripping with blood...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, as we saw earlier, the witness's left hand had suffered a serious injury. He sustained the wound in a struggle with the victim, and his blood got on the pottery. <thought>Then, Junie saw his bloodstained hands as they passed each other in the first floor hall.</thought> It's the only explanation that covers everything!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">H-H-Heh. F-Fine, whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, how much dirt does he have on Hugh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The court will observe this odd-looking envelope. It was inside this that Myriam Scuttlebutt's script was found.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Scuttlebutt's...? But didn't the prosecution already claim that... ...this envelope is the one that contained her script?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Circumstances have changed. You see, Golden Boy had hidden this from us all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see here... My word! Talk about the world's most painful paper cut!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. You can clearly see that if this envelope is not opened correctly... ...a powerful spring-loaded blade will shoot forth, leaving a horrible gash upon the hand. The only one who had been told of the correct way to open it was Constance Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. You really want to see my script that bad? Well, you better watch out. Read it without my permission and you'll wish you hadn't!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yikes... Myriam wasn't kidding when she said that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The blood on the blade is the witness's. Our genius here tried to sneak a peek at the wrong script and paid for his foolishness!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ouuuuuuuch! <thought>This guy's the worst genius I've EVER seen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, Athena. The wound isn't that deep. We've still got the wire theory.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yeah... I've got it! Since the blood by the window overlooking the maintenance area isn't the victim's... ...there's no longer any basis for denying the body was moved using the wire and banner. Therefore, the defense once again asserts just that!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court would like to remind the witness that his role is not to point out--</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. And you... How can you adhere to such outdated beliefs. But whatever. It seems you've forgotten the two statues that were onstage directly below the wire. A body sent sliding down that wire would've crashed into them. Care to explain that away?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe he's right. The statues and the wire are extremely close together.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh... So the body would've collided with the statues? Hmm... What if they did collide? Wait, that's it!</thought> Speaking of those statues, we still don't know how they were broken. But if we assume the body crashed into them... ...that would also explain that loud sound we heard while we were in the waiting room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, now that you mention it... ...you and Mr. Wright went out to the stage after you heard that sound, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It was a little after the mock trial had started. Mr. Wright and I were practically bored to tears there in the waiting room, when-- Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Precisely. If that sound you heard did happen while the body was being moved... ...that would place it during the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oof. Which means the body wouldn't have been there before the mock trial started.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You see, right before the mock trial started... I saw the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He said he saw the body before the mock trial. If so... ...then my claim that the body was moved during the mock trial doesn't hold water! Stupid contradiction! It's going to get me and our case killed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The focus was on just three suspects because the body was moved before the mock trial. That has been the major premise thus far. Your assertion, therefore, contradicts the very foundation of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Good point.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Prosecutor Blackquill... is on our side! I bet he's figured out the truth behind this case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, great, as long as he's not up to something else.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If the statues really were broken when the body hit them... ...then Hugh's statement about seeing the body before the mock trial is a big fat lie!</thought> Okay, Mr. O'Conner! Let's get to the bottom of this contradiction about when you saw the body. Look me straight in the eyes and repeat your statement to me!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Argh! L-Like I said before, uh... before the mock trial, the body was, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I shall only say this once, Golden Boy. You had best tell the truth, and do it now. That is, if your head wish to enjoy the continued companionship of your body.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, out with it! Did you truly witness the body?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or were you just lying about it?! Well, which is it?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">............I...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You what?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I...!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I............ I never saw the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you sure about that? Lie to this court again and I'll charge you with perjury.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">There was no body on that stage! I've been lying about that this whole time! I'm... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yes! We've exposed Hugh's big lie for what it is! But why would he lie about this to begin with?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! The base premise that the body was moved before the mock trial has been overturned. I imagine that this has an impact on both the defense and the prosecution's case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, first I'd like to thank the prosecutor. This brings us one step closer to the truth. Now, at least we know the body was moved using the wire and school banner.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Indeed. That much I shall concede, Cykes-dono. The body was moved as you stated, and in the midst of the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So both sides are satisfied then?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. If the body was moved before the mock trial, we have our three suspects... ...but if the move took place in the midst of the mock trial, it is an entirely different story.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. All three suspects were in the mock trial. That gives them solid alibis.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this?! Who is this person in charge of the audio?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, no! How could I forget! It was...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! What's the deal here? Why's Junie so large in this shot?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh heh heh. Juniper was also in charge of the audio. When she wasn't in the trial, she was in the audio control room dealing with the music.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. The one who could enter the art room amidst the mock trial to move the body... ...was none other than the accused, Juniper Woods, for she was in charge of the audio!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eee... Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek! Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes! I see! That DOES make perfect sense!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>This can't be happening. Instead of exposing Hugh's crime, Junie's in even deeper. No matter how you slice it, we're cooked! And here I thought Prosecutor Blackquill was on our side, at least on this issue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Twisted Samurai strikes again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, twisted?! It's more like dirty rotten!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Your Baldness, it is time to put an end to this farce.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The prosecution has presented a quite convincing case. But the defense has one last chance to voice any remaining objections. Well, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! What are we going to do?! I've got nothing left! Nothing! Nada! Niente!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've been trying to think of something, but I'm drawing a big blank, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh... Poor Junie. Unless we figure out something, she'll be...</thought> O-Objection... Objection... Umm... well... I object to...!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-P-P-P...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Perfect...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Criiiiiime?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, this is some serious déjà vu. Didn't we just go through something like this yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, yes we did... This had better not be another one of his enraging traps...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The murder, the moving of the body, the cover up! It all sprung from my brilliant mind! Well, go ahead, arrest me! The real killer is right before you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order, Order, I say! M-M-Mr. O'Conner! You already confessed yesterday, then earlier today recanted your confession!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">As if you mouth-breathers could comprehend my genius! The end justifies the means! Now, bow down and kneel! Kneel before my great and maddening intellect.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There is no perfect crime, only a perfect alibi, for you were at the mock trial. And it is silly that I must remind you of this, but you were a participant the entire time. There shall be no mercy if you persist in hindering this trial with your silly little act!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hugh doesn't seem the least bit shaken by Blackquill's threat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Listen, Mr. Prosecutor. Calling that a perfect alibi is beyond contempt. Your Honor, I'd like to take this opportunity to offer further testimony. I will now demonstrate the very moment of genius that transcended even perfection!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You won't believe this, but I used a body double!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I have a question I was hoping the defense and prosecution might help answer. Is it just me or does the witness's testimony make no sense at all?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, it's not just you, Your Honor. All I got from listening to that was a headache.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, that was just plain weird, especially the whole thing about a body double.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I'm relieve it's not just me. ...And the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness, summon an ambulance this instance [sic]. The witness is stark, raving mad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, I think that would be for the best. Now, then, let's pretend that never happened and move on to my verdict--</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's not a matter of believing you. It's more along the lines of questioning your sanity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, the funny farm just called. They want their "genius" back.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Easy there, tiger. Think of it this way. We don't want a verdict to be passed just yet. So how about we give Widget a try?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, this is against my better judgment, but I'd like to conduct a short therapy session.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your better judgment? I'm a judge, and it's far beyond mine, yet I find it hard to say no. Prosecutor Blackquill, I trust you have no objections? ...Um, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The prosecutor said, "Rubbish! We will be out on a stroll!" then left with Detective Fulbright.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>How does he get away with stuff like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Then I'll interpret that as meaning he has no explicit objections. All right, Ms. Cykes, you may proceed with your therapy session.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've seen my share of crazy trials, but this one takes the cake!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You won't believe this, but I used a body double!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That wasn't the real me at the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That means I didn't almost lose! My body double did!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I slipped out stealthily while my double took care of the trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I had the run of the campus.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">In short, I'm the killer.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Juniper's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't get it. His confession is overflowing with happiness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he enjoys thinking how us mouth-breathers can't comprehend his genius.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But this goes way beyond normal happiness. He seems to take an insane level of delight in his confession!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, even a normal level of delight would be weird for a confession. Then again, he's not what I'd call normal.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hugh... Why are you confessing? Who is this really for? I feel like that's the key to his out-of-control emotion!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, yesterday you said that you didn't really care about Ms. Woods anymore.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I already told Juniper, so I might as well yell you. I don't really care about her anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Yeah, well, Juniper reported my secret to Prof. Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>His secret? ...Oh, the bribe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">She wanted nothing to do with me because I had disappointed her. That's why I don't care about her anymore. I was never trying to protect her. My confession was always about one thing and one thing only: the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">What are you...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can hear it clearly now, Mr. O'Conner -- the discord you've been trying to suppress. People don't normally feel like you do when you confessed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Hugh really was trying to protect Juniper?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, I'm sure of it. Hugh's feelings for her are the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But that means his confession is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Finally figured out the obvious, have we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, Prosecutor Blackquill, you're back.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The confession was naught but lies, save for the part about being in the mock trial. Can we all agree now that the killer is the one in charge of the audio, i.e. the accused?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gaaah! <thought>Why couldn't you have taken a longer stroll?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">N-No! You haven't unraveled the genius of my body double trick yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can't be serious. Do you really expect us to believe you had a body double?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Yes! Yes I do! But if you think I didn't, then prove it! Heh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Either we quit here and Juniper is found guilty, or we play along with Hugh's delusion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go with the least worse choice. But first, let me update his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You won't believe this, but I used a body double!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That wasn't the real me at the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That means I didn't almost lose! My body double did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I slipped out stealthily while my double took care of the trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I had the run of the campus.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">In short, I'm the killer.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Juniper's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A body double...? What a bunch of baloney.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know, but I can hear the noise. It means there's a contradictory emotion somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Contradictory emotion? Everything he says is one big contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right, and that's why I can hear his inner voice loud and clear! If we just think about Hugh and his competitive nature... ...we should be able to figure out the root cause of his discord!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... "I didn't almost lose," you say? Very odd... You exhibited happiness the entire time, except during this statement.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Argh! You don't know when to give up! ...Wait, now that I think about it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>No, don't! Stop making stuff up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">When I left the Lecture Hall... ...it was during Prof. Means's pre-trial speech. That's when I moved the body. I then slipped back in just before the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, you're saying you were there the moment your double was about to lose?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Yes, I was! Naturally, I wasn't happy when I saw that. In any case, I was at the far end of the Lecture Hall behind the screen. I figured no one would see me if I came and went through the doors there.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...Heh. I thought you could do better than that. The lawyer's bench is on the right side when facing the front of the hall. I used the door on the right side near the lawyer's bench. That means my movements were only visible to someone in the left balcony seat. But that seat was empty at the time, which is only natural. After all, it belonged to Prof. Courte, and as we all know, she was already dead by then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... <thought>That can't be right. An empty balcony seat on the left side contradicts this piece of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, really? And how would that preclude me from exiting?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, come on. Do I have to explain everything to you, Golden Boy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I'd at least like you to explain it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo! <thought>How could I make such a noob mistake?! Was the seat Hugh pointed out really supposed to be empty?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I've no idea where this contradiction is going. But I don't have any other moves at this point. Guess I'll just have to follow it and see where this takes me!</thought> You said the left balcony seat was empty. But was it really?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I saw it with my own eyes! It was definitely empty!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But what about this diagram? According to this, Prof. Means was supposed to be seated in the left balcony seat. But if you left the Lecture Hall during his pre-trial speech... ...he would've been standing there at his seat addressing the students and faculty!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Gah! No, this can't be right!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You do no one any favor by exposing the falsities of his confession.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I've told plenty of lies so far, but this part is true, I tell you! There was nobody in the left balcony seat. You gotta believe me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm, it doesn't seem like he's lying this time.</thought> Okay, Mr. O'Conner! Let's have you testify again, but this time, don't spare any details!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You got it! I'll repeat it as many times as you like! I mean, my ingenious escape act warrants repeating, considering I'm the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>All I really care about is whether that seat was empty or not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The second floor was deserted!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Why won't you believe me?! It's true, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I went out the back door without anyone noticing.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Then, all I had to do... was go through the empty audio control room!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">It leads into the hallway. So I was perfectly capable of moving the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoa, talk about a change in tone! It reads like a totally different testimony! It's like he realized something terrible the moment he opened his mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it's something he realized himself, this unease might also register in how he speaks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. I'll focus on places where he hesitates or stammers, then!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I detected powerful sadness and fear right after you said this part. It's as if you'd said something you shouldn't have.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">What's wrong with you?! You shouldn't reveal a person's inner feelings for all to see!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, it's you who is revealing your inner emotions by the way you speak. Plus, I have a good idea about why you're feeling sad.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Argh! You're a horrible person! Can't you just leave me be?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You said that you went through the "empty audio control room," but that's not true, is it? There was someone who returned from there once Prof. Means finished his speech. And that someone who was in the audio control room was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Wait a second. That's who you think was there when I passed through?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, positive! ...Or at least I wish I was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears to this court that the defense has a bad case of wishful thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>Darn it! There's only one person who went between the Lecture Hall and audio control room!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know you realized there was a problem with your statement as you were saying it. That's why you felt so uneasy. If the audio control room really was empty... ...that would mean Ms. Woods was roaming around the campus.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, if you really want to protect Ms. Woods, just tell the truth. If you believe in her, revealing the truth is the same as protecting her.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...Juniper's innocent. That's the truth. But in this dark age of the law, the truth can be easily twisted to serve anyone's needs. When the end justifies the means, your only choice is to fight back with lies!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hugh's heart won't hold out under this battle between truth and lies. Is there something I can do to make him recant his false testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh heh heh. I fear nothing now that I have lost everything! Go ahead, Prosecutor Blackquill. Cut me down if you wish!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I thought you'd never ask. With you gone, we may swiftly proceed to a verdict. Hrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrgh! ............Yah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aaaaaah! H-He broke out of his shackles agaaaaaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't want to be the poor accountant down at the Detention Center...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hugh O'Conner, in deference to your valor, I will limit your suffering with one clean blow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do not come between a samurai and his foe, Cykes-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek! <thought>I never learned about this in law school!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Careful, Prosecutor... Remember that shocking experience you had last time!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Very well, Golden Boy may live.. for now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Enough already, Mr. O'Conner. Ms. Woods would never want you to protect her this way. She values the friendship between the three of you more than anything!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, but I already knew.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And don't forget me! ...Though, in all fairness, it was pretty obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Woman">I thought he was genius at first, but...</line>
<line speaker="Man">The stuff he said was crazy.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Arrrrrgh! No need to rub it in! Just shut up and listen! It all started several days ago. I accidently [sic] learned that my parents have been paying good money for my grades.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's...! That's bribery!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So the bribery wasn't Hugh's idea?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">All of my perfect scores were the product of cold hard cash, not genius. Even worse, when I confronted my parents about it over the phone... ...Juniper overheard me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my... What a terrible misunderstanding.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I've been living a lie! I don't know what else there is to say! I'm no genius. I'm completely worthless... A perfect zero.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hugh...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Even so, I still wanted to make it up to Juniper for disappointing her like that. That's why I wanted to clear her name by pinning the blame on me! I mean, she probably hates me now, so it'd be a relief for her to see me locked away.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you were trying to help her, then why did you testify against her?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You were the ones who told me to tell the truth yesterday! So, I thought if I did, it would help her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He wasn't trying to provoke us?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like we seriously misunderstood him, in more ways than one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>At the detention center yesterday, Junie was in tears when she opened up to me. But the truth is, the friendship between the three of them is still rock solid! If there were something that could help me prove that to Hugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. We even have proof of our friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeaaaaaah!!! As long as our friendship lasts! You can bet we'll be carrying them around!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I know! What about that proof of friendship they mentioned?! Hmm... I wonder where or what it is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Maybe it's... No, that's definitely it! That band around his neck!</thought> Mr. O'Conner! That band around your neck! That's your proof of friendship, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proof of friendship? Is that anything like a proof of purchase barcode?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In court, evidence is everything. That's why the three friends created friendship bands. It's the evidence that proves their friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho. How very interesting... and chic!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If they have doubts about their friendship, they can look to the proof they have on hand. That's why Mr. O'Conner's hand always goes to his neck when he is pressured. It proves he still has feeling of friendship towards the other two.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">It doesn't matter if I wear it if those two...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I know! They must wear them in places that are difficult to see!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Really? And where might they be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How about around the belly button or on the soles of the feet? That would be hard to see.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">How could they wear their friendship bands there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right, you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Neither of them are wearing them now.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. For once I agree with you, Ms. Cykes. You're right. They're not wearing them. Why would they when our friendship is over?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait... No, that's not what I meant. S-Sorry, sorry! Let me try that one again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All we have to do is think back to their testimonies. Ready? Ms. Newman holds her arm when pressured. And Ms. Woods holds her wrist. I know Ms. Woods very well. She would never abandon her friendship with you over something like this. And taking the blame for her will only succeed in making her terribly sad!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Argh... Arrrgh... Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrgh! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Robin, those bands of friendship that you made just for the three of us. You may have forgotten about them, but not me!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hugh!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Hey Hugh!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">And to think... I should have known better than to doubt my best friends.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I... I didn't kill anyone. And I didn't have a body double.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Well, you could've fooled me! In fact, you did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hugh...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...So, Ms. Cykes, can I place my trust in you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm going to save Junie. So yes, you can place your trust in me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, am I to understand that the witness is recanting his confession?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">.........Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph, a most roundabout trial. I much prefer the turnabout variety myself. Now we are back to the fact that there was but one suspect who lacked an alibi. Which is, in the end, the truth you've been seeking this entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, we're back to square one? Now I'm exhausted and depressed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It probably doesn't matter at this point, but I might as well update the Mood Matrix. <thought>...Huh? Does this mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Further resistance is futile. The time for a verdict is nigh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What sort of devilry are you up to now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if our client wasn't the only one without an alibi? The trial would continue, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, yes, I suppose it would. But after such a thorough investigation, does such a person really exist?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, we've found someone. It may have seemed like a major roundabout... ...but Mr. O'Conner's testimony has cracked the case! <thought>There's no more noise. Hugh is telling the truth now. During the mock trial, the balcony seat opposite him really was empty! Which now means there is one person unaccounted for!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Besides Junie, the only other person without an alibi during the mock trial is...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Quite shocking, isn't it, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, shockingly out of the realm of possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yiiikes! <thought>This is no time to be making mistakes! Hugh's latest testimony is the truth. If I just base my decision on that...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The balcony seat was empty. That much IS true, isn't it, Mr. O'Conner?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's right. How many more times do I have to say it?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, basically, Prof. Means wasn't where he was supposed to be during the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Need I remind you, every last soul in the Lecture Hall heard him deliver his speech?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The speech was given from a hidden location. It explains why the witness didn't see anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fine. Let us entertain your notion. How would it affect this trial?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the defense is not interested in the trial, she can go practice law in the hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoops! <thought>Ugh. I need something that actually relates to the situation at hand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They ran out of time, so the speech was given later!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Stop right there. Everyone in that room heard the speech that preceded the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes... I don't only think I'll give you a penalty, I believe I actually will.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if the speech was pre-recorded? That's the only way the speech could've been delivered from an empty balcony seat!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Really? <thought>Wait a second!</thought> Mr. O'Conner! Did you just say that Prof. Means gave that phony recording to you?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Phony? The defense will refrain from hurling unsubstantiated allegations.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Well, I said he gave it to me, but what do you mean it's phony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, who could've seen this development...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The voice shouting, "You're a goner!" as recorded on this tape... ...was dubbed onto it using a line our client said in the mock trial video!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, this... this is an extremely crucial piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Prof. Means gave Hugh the phony tape. If that's really true, then Prof. Means has guilt written all over him!</thought> Your Honor! The defense moves to call Prof. Aristotle Means to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. The seat was never empty. 'Twas but an oversight by our dullard of a witness. An inmate who was formally [sic] a surgeon once told me something. He said it's often all too easy to overlooked [sic] critical symptoms!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough, both of you. ...Now, here's my opinion on the matter. While a surgeon overlooking critical symptoms is a problem... ...a witness's oversight, too, must not be overlooked. Thus, as to the matter of whether Prof. Means was or was not in his faculty seat... ...I believe we must ask the professor himself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I agree. Prof. Means should be here in the gallery today.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! Do as you please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will you please state your name and occupation for the record?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Certainly. I am Aristotle Means. I teach the lawyer course at Themis Legal Academy. And let me add that while... ...I welcome any opportunity to assist with the trial, I don't care for this undue suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Professor, we're just interested in the mock trial video right now. We just need to take another look at that speech you gave. Can we count on your cooperation in this?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Very well, if that's all you're interested in. Please proceed, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We need to find some sort of evidence that shows this speech was pre-recorded!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, I believe we're ready. Let's roll the video.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, no, I'd forgotten how long and boring his speech was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">Zzz...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Wake me up once this is over.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hey, no fair!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? ...Eeek! I'm awake, I'm awake! Isn't that right, Your Honor?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh?! What?! I-I'm awake, too! Wide, wide awake, see?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Means">That is about it. One of my better speeches if I do say so myself. I even saw some of our students with tears in their eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's obviously not familiar with the phrase "bored to tears."</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Listen, Cykes-dono. If you have subjected me to this epic study in tedium without purpose... ...Taka will feast on your tongue after I've cut it out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>But you were asleep the whole time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? Did you notice anything strange about that speech?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Could I please hear that last part again?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your face betrays...</line>
<line speaker="Means">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't tell me Your Honor has turned stone-faced, too! <thought>The professor said the pure white Lady Justice would be watching over them. Something isn't right. There must be a contradiction between the audio and video!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The professor said the pure white Lady Justice would be watching over them. But the Lady Justice in the video isn't even close to being white. It's as gold as gold can be!</line>
<line speaker="Means">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm not sure I can wrap my jaw around that to test its authenticity...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't say it was MADE of gold, Your Honor! Now, it's true that this statue is pure white... ...but it broke before the mock trial began. The one you see here is its replacement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, well, that's a shame on every count!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ironically, this golden statue sticks out like a sore thumb compared to the white one. Meaning the professor wouldn't have made a mistake in its color if he'd been present!</line>
<line speaker="Means">It seems that I have caused some confusion, but it was merely an oversight on my part.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, I was in a balcony seat. Furthermore, the statue had previously been white.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid this isn't sufficient evidence of the speech being pre-recorded.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We had our answer long ago. The accused was the only one to leave the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, wait! <thought>There's got to be something that can prove that the speech was pre-recorded!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to the mock trial video... ...the speech started here... ...and ended here. It was a little over ten minutes, but I doubt anyone wants to be tortured again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It was only a little over ten minutes? It felt like it went on forever.</thought> How'd you figure out how long it was?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Easy. There's a timestamp in the top right. All you have to do is... ...subtract the time the speech started from the time it ended.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The speech goes from 10:00-minute mark to 20:35. Wait a second... I could swear I've seen this same interval of time listed among the evidence... Maybe there's a way for me to use the speech time to show that it was prerecorded.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You're sure you're sure?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh, well, yes, I'm sure... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps this penalty will help you make your case with more conviction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaagh! <thought>Let's see... The speech took a total of ten minutes and thirty-five seconds. Hmm... 10:35... Where have I seen that number before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I would like the court to take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this is...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The voiceprint analysis that proves the voice on the tape recorder belongs to our client.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but didn't we just establish that the voice on the tape recorder was a fabrication?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did, but what I'd like to focus on is the noise that is also there.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Noise?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. The defense believes it resulted when the tape's previous recording was erased.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. And what do you hope to prove by that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The length of the noise is what's important. It's ten minutes and thirty-five seconds in all. And what did the timestamp read at the moment Prof. Means began his speech?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That would be exactly 10:00.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now, let's fast forward this long-winded exercise in boredom to the end. Okay, stop. The video timestamp now reads 20:35. Based on this, we know the time it took for the speech alone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right, subtract ten minutes and you get 10:35. Hm? Ten minutes and thirty-five seconds?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right, ten minutes and thirty-five seconds -- the same as the noise on the tape recording. I assume you all understand what this means. Prof. Means's pre-recorded speech had been where the noise is now!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You seem rather confident considering this is a mere happenstance match of numbers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The lab is continuing their study of the tape. So far, they've found signs of overdubbing. But it's going to take a bit longer to recover the audio that was erased.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The police are analyzing the noise as we speak. It won't be long until we know what was originally there. <thought>Now I'm sure of it. The professor was trying to create an alibi with the recording... ...by pinning the crime on Junie. Well, he's not gonna get away with it! Not on my watch!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">...Ms. Cykes. I believe you are well aware of my methodology. Even if Juniper were the perpetrator, I would vigorously defend her as per my word. And to that purpose, I offered to be her lawyer. Alas, look what's happened.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All I've stated are obvious deductions derived from evidence and testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Truth be told, I had no intention of testifying. I had been keeping quiet for Juniper's sake. But now that you cast this blame upon me, I have no choice but to reveal the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Uh-oh! This doesn't sound good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">I will now reveal the truth behind why I had to pre-record my speech before the mock trial. I, Prof. Means, always say what I mean and mean what I say by all means!</line>
<line speaker="Means">The defendant came to me with what she said was very important, and by necessity, secret.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! So, you're saying the defendant threatened you?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This has to be a lie... I mean, everything about it lines up too perfectly to be true.</line>
<line speaker="Means">On this most consequential of occasions, let me be completely frank with you. Juniper has truly taken to heart my teaching that states the end justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't believe you!</line>
<line speaker="Means">When she asked me to defend her, she said I must also prove her two friends innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her two friends? The witnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Correct. Hugh O'Conner and Robin Newman. I was to ensure all three walked free. All three were to achieve their dream. That was the result Juniper was seeking. And she was even willing to threaten me, her own professor, to that end.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. You, no doubt, had high praise for her ruthless tactics.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes, well, that is why I vowed to vigorously defend her despite her threatening me. There was a time when lawyers merely sought the truth if they wished for victory in court... ...but, alas, those days are over. Now, in the defense of justice, order,  and all that is good, the end justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I am so sick of hearing that phrase!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Though it truly grieves me so, I must tell you this. Forsake the truth if it's victory you seek. Steel yourself for this new courtroom reality.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That does it! He's gonna regret dragging those dismal, depressing ideas in here! Since he's already surrendered to the dark age of the law, it's up to me to fight it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Why so silent, Cykes-dono? Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This... This is a court of law. It's no place for longwinded talks about idealistic principles. That's why I'm going to let the evidence do the talking.</line>
<line speaker="Means">...Let's not get carried away, now, Ms. Cykes. It will not do to have you attempting to discredit my doctrine. Do not force me to rectify this situation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, go ahead and rectify it! ...Only if I lose and you win, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Means">The defendant came to me with what she said was very important, and by necessity, secret.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">You have a point there. If only Prof. Courte had been alive, I suspect Juniper would have gone to her instead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, our client came to talk to you after Prof. Courte was dead?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Let's go through this step by step, shall we? First, Juniper came to me that day.</line>
<line speaker="Means">She asked me to pre-record my speech and come to the audio room during the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">You have every reason to be surprised. I, too, was shocked when she told me that. Simply put, Juniper has a secret that she wished to protect that badly.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Is he kidding me?! That lie couldn't be further from the truth! The problem is, how am I going to expose it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">It was an earnest request from an outstanding student. How could I possibly have refused?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Juniper confessed to the murder and asked that I get her declared innocent in court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes. But it's now you to whom she has passed her demands on to. Ms. Cykes, you must realize that you, too, are being used by Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Your Honor, I ask that you, too, do not let her feigned weakness and innocence fool you. Juniper Woods is quite clever and extremely tough. And, perhaps most important of all, she is a fervent follower of my teachings.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, objection sustained.</line>
<line speaker="Means">...So be it. Nevertheless, the fact that she threatened me is immutable.</line>
<line speaker="Means">She also said I'd become an accomplice after losing my alibi due to the pre-recording.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes, well, perhaps I do have some serious reflection to do on this matter. I suppose it was just wishful thinking on my part. I wanted to believe that... ...Juniper hadn't actually committed murder and that she hadn't meant to threaten me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-Really?! Please do explain!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Long had I waited for a student who would embody my teachings.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Does the witness realize what he is saying?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Surely you must see the true meaning in my words. I am merely staying true to what I teach. And my methods are but a reflection of the times.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, wow, his way of thinking is really warped, but I haven't heard any inconsistencies yet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I wouldn't be so sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The more he tries to avoid logical inconsistencies in his testimony... ...the more likely we'll see inconsistencies between his actions and words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">It is a dark age in which live [sic]. And there is much I would like to say on the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Means">But when I said I would protect Juniper, I meant it because it's the humane thing to do.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">What a frightful look. I would ask that you not glare at me so. I've nothing but admiration for how Juniper was willing to go as far as to threaten me. That is why I am protecting her by any means possible. She has been a model student.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Liar! You're trying to pin the blame on her! How am I going to show that what he's saying isn't what he's really thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">You cannot possible [sic] overturn my claims, so isn't it about time you admitted defeat? After all, if my unassailable logic is not truth, then what is?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If he thinks I'm going to give in to his pack of lies, he's got another thing coming! I'm gonna find a hole in his story if it's the last thing I do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even though he's rotten to the core, he's a total pro. I mean, that all made perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but you can't believe a word he says! <thought>He's making this up as he goes along. He'll trip up on his own words yet! Time to see how consistently the professor's testimony matches up with his actual actions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So let me get this straight. You were trying to help Ms. Woods? Ha! That's nothing more than a bald-faced lie -- no offense, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Such defamation of my character and your hair follicles, Your Honor! It is an outrage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Ms. Cykes will clarify her statement, but leave my hair follicles out of it this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, of course, Your Honor. Now, please take a look at this. The witness gave this tape to Mr. O'Conner. Then he slyly whispered, "Take this to the police and tell them you found it."</line>
<line speaker="Means">There was no whispering, slyly or otherwise involved. I simply did that out of kindness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">...........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They say the road to hell is paved with good intentions, but not yours! You never had good intentions, only lies to protect yourself with while blaming another. You, professor, are the embodiment of the dark age of the law!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Um, Prof. Means? What's with your hair?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Quiet!!! No talking in class!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ow!</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">Homeroom</line>
<line speaker="Means">Eyes and ears up here, everyone! Homeroom is now in session! We will begin with roll call! ...Athena Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? ...Oh, uh, here?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Apollo Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm fine! Er, I mean, here!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Fool! The proper response is "here" without any extraneous information!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ouch! I mean... Here!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Next, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Here!</line>
<line speaker="Means">See, class? That's the proper way to answer! ...Simon Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Means">I said, Si-mon Black-quill! Are you here or not?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's always one, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, then, I'll just mark you absent. Now, get out of my class this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Get out? Very well, if that is your wish. Who am I to deny my homeroom teacher?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Is that such a good idea? Prosecutor Blackquill IS free of his shackles...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Uuuwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! It just so happens I was a member of my high school's Disciplinarian Committee! But is that really so shocking?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Constabulary lapdog to teacher's pet. What a malleable mutt you are, Fool Bright.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Very good, Bobby! You just earned a gold star and a promotion to Head Disciplinarian! All right, class is now in session!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh... Why do I have the sudden urge to go to the nurse's office with a stomachache?</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">Main point: Juniper is the killer. I am innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Pay attention! I am not the killer! Juniper is! This will be on the next test, so you had better be listening!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means [on blackboard]:</line>
<line speaker="Means">...Athena, you disappoint me so. To think you would label me a murderer! Now, pay attention! The murder occurred on the 23rd between 6:00 and 8:00 PM! But I was already at home by that time! So, how could I have been involved in this crime?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... No... No, I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Heh heh heh! So you admit it! Well, you just earned extra credit for your honesty! But you have also earned yourself lavatory cleaning duties until you graduate!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeuw! <thought>I do enough of that at the office!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Robin?!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I can't believe I fell for the professor's silver-tongued lies!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Why you--! How dare you talk about your teacher like that!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I'm not listening to you anymore, maaaaaan! No way, no how! Now, I have a confession to make! You know those two statues that were onstage?! I didn't make 'em all by myseeeeeelf!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The statues onstage? <thought>Do I want to know where this is headed?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">I was able to finish one of them, but the last bell rang before I had time for the other one. So, I asked Prof. Means to make it for me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, the professor was there on the stage after the last bell?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Right. And it would have been way past 7:00 PM before he could've finished.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prof. Means was still at school?! This is... Well, this is incredibly important testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The professor told me, "I'll take care of it." I thought my parents would let me be an artist if I said I'd made both statues myself. *sob* I'm sooo sooo sorry for not telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Robin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Not interested. But if you want a class in swordsmanship, I'm your man. Of course, only real blades will do.</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">No pets allowed in court!</line>
<line speaker="Means">No swords at school! All weapons will be confiscated! Gyaaaaaaaaaaaah! Nurse! Nurse!!! Where's a school nurse when you need one?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It would seem Cykes-dono seeks a showdown, Professor. In which case, you would do well to draw your staff, quick as lightning!</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">I said, no pets allowed!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Very well. Then I will just have to prove my innocence myself! The real lessons begin in second period. Prepare to be served, old-school style!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What does that...? Oh, never mind. Your testimony please.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, pay attention! Robin took over half a day to complete one statue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're saying the defendant saw the finished statues?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Precisely. She said so herself at the Detention Center yesterday. Her defense team was there and heard her say so, too. Don't try to deny it now!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That evening, I went back to my dressing room to get something I'd forgotten there. It was well after the last bell rang... I'd say, maybe around 8:30. That's when I noticed that both stage statues were finished. They were quite large, and they were each covered with a white sheet, but I could tell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, right. The professor was there when that matter came up.</thought> ...Before I address the professor's charges, I have a question for Robin. How hard would it be to complete a statue like that in one and a half hours?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">It would probably take me at least twice as L-O-N-G. So personally, I think it would be incredibly difficult to finish in that short a time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Gah! That didn't exactly help our case! But he won't get off that easy. He's bound to stumble over his own slippery means!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, pay attention! Robin took over half a day to complete one statue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Ah ha ha ha! What a wonderful question! She was having quite a tough time, you see. Prosecutor Gavin's statue alone took her from the morning hours into the evening!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, it is a rather large statue, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Don't be silly! It merely exposes the difference between student and teacher!</line>
<line speaker="Means">I, however, finished most of the other statue between 7:00 and 8:30 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Robin created the basic outline of Mr. Wright's statue before the last bell rang. I, in turn, completed the rest of it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. In academics, as well as art, learning the basics is incredibly important. In short, you skipped the most important of part of statue making, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Unlike Miss Fancy Pants here, who lacks all lawyerly fundamentals.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, quiet you...</line>
<line speaker="Means">Now do you understand? I did NOT leave that stage until I was done!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? Do you accept the witness's claim?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! No, I don't! I know there's more to this, and I won't stop until the truth comes out!</line>
<line speaker="Means">The more you struggle, the more you sink, like so much legal quicksand, so to speak. I used the world's ultimate technique to complete the statue by 8:30 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Means">The defendant Juniper saw the two statues with her own eyes at 8:30 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A pity for you, but we have already confirmed it with the accused. She is on record as having seen both statues.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, that's true. Just thought I'd give it a shot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Gah ha ha ha ha! I have the ultimate in courtroom techniques. It is absolutely airtight! I will bury you! This will be your final resting place, along with all who believed in you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Tsk... Is there no way to get to this guy?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">You better pay attention! Pay very close attention!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Completing a statue so quickly meant I could not leave the stage for a single second!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Well? Ready to concede that I never left the stage?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? Do you accept the witness's claim?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! No, I don't! I know there's more to this, and I won't stop until the truth comes out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd be careful, Athena. If you don't have anything... ...it's probably best to just grin and bear it for now until you find something to nail him with.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But...! Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Means">When will you cease this nonsense? I am quite busy today -- as I was the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Means">How could I have possibly had the time to go to the art room and commit murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Preposterous! I didn't even have ten minutes to spare. Not even five for a visit to the lavatory! Let me ask you, Your Honor. Do you find anything wrong with my claim?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So far, it appears that your statue making was quite a difficult chore. And I see nothing that could overturn your claim that you never left the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrrrrrr! <thought>But the art room is only a few steps away!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's the plan? All I can think of is pressing him like crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's all I can think of, too. We'll just have to seek out a hole to exploit!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Hm? I couldn't hear you. Say it louder this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... I concede that Prof. Means never left the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Gah hah hah hah hah hah! That's right! But what took you so long?! I was there at the stage the entire time! I couldn't possibly have committed that crime!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'm not gonna give up here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I have to side with the witness, Ms. Cykes. And unless you have any further objections, I'll have to put this issue to rest.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena... You've thought of something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Well, as I said, not yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so it's time for legal smoke and mirrors?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Not yet, Athena. It's not yet time to quit! It's at times like these, when it seems like there's no way out, that you have to... Yeah! I have to turn the case upside down! Instead of focusing on whether Prof. Means could've gone to the art room... I should focus on how he could commit murder without going there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">It seems our young lady has a real bona fide idea! I must use any means possible to distract her! See if she can think while I cast these stones! Aaagh! Who brought the bird to school?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Cykes-dono, if I hear one word of your usual jibber-jabber, I shall have your head! The murder occurred in the art room, yet the witness was on the stage. How do you propose to fill the vast gap between these two key facts?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If I accept the premise that the professor was on the stage the entire time... ...the only other answer is that we got something else wrong... Wait... That's it! Every last one of us made a huge mistake! We were totally wrong about the...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We got something seriously wrong. In short, we should've never suspected Prof. Means. He isn't the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If that's the case... ...then we're back to the defendant, as there are no other suspects!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if we got the murder weapon wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Really, now? And what do you intend to label the murder weapon, then?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh, uh... um...</line>
<line speaker="Means">Perhaps YOU bludgeoned the victim to death with your duller than dull thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'll give you a choice this time. Either change your thinking or suffer a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I know we got something wrong! So I guess I'll have the penalty...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If Prof. Means was on the stage the entire time... ...then he must be the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Continue, Cykes-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay. The murder was actually committed here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Care to explain how I got there and how I moved the body?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course. But we'll all have to think this over together!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...No, that task is for you and you alone, as is this penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaagh! S-So the location we're looking for didn't require the professor or the body to move...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... but is there really such a place?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The greatest riddle of this case has been how the body was moved from the art room. But if the murder occurred on the stage, that means the body was never moved at all.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means [on blackboard]:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Silly girl! When the body was found, there wasn't a drop of blood on the stage floor! Surely there would have been some blood if that's where the murder was committed!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There wasn't any blood on the stage? Really? But there WAS something at the stage at the time of the murder that's now bloodstained.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh heh. What's wrong? Cat got your tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'd say that about sums it up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's true, there were no bloodstains on the stage floor. But there WAS something on the stage that did have a bloodstain. And that would be this: this school banner. No blood would've gotten on the floor if this were under the victim when she was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! That's quite a compelling theory!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it noooooooow?! <thought>My theory makes perfect sense!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That was a pathetic attempt. You must put every inch of your body into your attacks. The autopsy states the cause of death was loss of blood. Yet only a trace amount was found upon that banner. Where did the rest go? Blood getting on there when the body was moved by wire makes more sense than not.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Gah ha ha ha! Very good, Simon! Tell me, what's your first choice for higher education? I'll write you the ultimate in recommendation letters! You're all but guaranteed to get in!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Y-You do?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If there was only a trace amount of blood on the school banner... ...then there must've been something else the killer used to soak up the blood. All I have to do is figure out what!</thought> This is what soaked up most of the victim's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where exactly do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right here. Can't you see it? It looks kind of like a smudge or something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see here... Wait a second! It doesn't just look like a smudge, it IS a smudge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! <thought>But a smudge is a smudge, right...? There must've been tons of blood, but there was only a little bit on the school banner. The only other thing that could've soaked up all that blood besides the school banner is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, it looks like there's some other piece of fabric on top of the school banner!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's the Gavinners banner that had been specially made for the school concert. Since it's on top of the school banner, the blood would have hit it first. It could have easily absorbed most of the blood, like a dishcloth... ...and only a small amount would've soaked through to the school banner below. So, it makes total sense for the school banner to only have a little blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Means">...Argh! Hrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, that banner absorbed the blood like a dishcloth! Yes, that would explain it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Gavinners banner was like a dishcloth...? Surely it was at least towel quality...</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Cykes-dono, you are learning to wield a blade quite well. But how will you respond when I come slashing at you like this? The remnant of a large bloodstain was detected in the art room. But why would there be blood there if the murder occurred on the stage as you claim?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't say. Care to explain how that would be possible?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor. Nothing is impossible, if you put your mind to it. Besides, all you need is...</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it was worth a try.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, it wasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeek! <thought>Ugh... I guess it really wasn't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">To think you'd stoop so low as to present mere garbage to this court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's only garbage because someone tried to destroy it by tossing it in the incinerator. That someone was most likely the killer seeking to get rid of crucial evidence. The killer used the wire to bring the blood-soaked Gavinners's banner to the art room. Then, the blood was wiped onto the floor to complete the ruse! It makes perfect sense!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Gah... Gwaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! This is quite a development! To think the body was never actually moved!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... I hadn't thought of that. If that loud crash wasn't the body hitting the statues... ...then what was it indeed? <thought>The knot in the school banner shows that something was carried along the wire in it. So if that's true, I know what I have to find! Something that was in the art room before the murder and on the stage after! The object that was sent down the wire to crash into the statues was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, I can't say I dislike it, but... How about you, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... My preferences aside, it gets a failing grade as an answer to the issue at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooooooo! <thought>Can I request a retake?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Aaaaagh! Th-That statue?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, I believe it was this statue that broke the other two, not Prof. Courte's body. The unique statue you see on the right, that's the pure white Lady Justice from earlier. Prof. Courte accidently [sic] broke it while she was polishing it the day before the mock trial. But she used her own unique artistic sense and technique to repair it as you see here. Nobody would have guessed that it was originally Lady Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Perhaps you are on to something. But why, pray tell, would anyone move that scrapheap relic in such a tedious manner?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Excellent question, Simon! Keep them coming!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know why. But the fact that you won't acknowledge it, shows how twisted you are. Lady Justice was moved during the mock trial. During that time, Prof. Means was fabricating an alibi with his pre-recorded speech. If we consider the facts, then Lady Justice was moved in order to...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Means was trying to hide the body! That's the only explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? But by moving Lady Justice, he actually led you straight to it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-There's always two sides to a story, and the truth is not always what it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes, this much, at least, is true. You've just earned yourself a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>Ugh. Think, Athena think. Why was Lady Justice moved? Try to remember everything that happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Means was trying to interrupt the mock trial. That must be the answer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then let me ask this. Why would the professor want to interrupt the mock trial?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I object, Your Honor! I object to how you always ask people questions like that! You should try thinking for yourself once in a while!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I just had a thought! It involves a penalty for a certain smart-alecky defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaagh! <thought>Ugh... The issue here is the moving of the Lady Justice statue. I need to focus on that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Means used his pre-recorded speech to fake an alibi during the mock trial. He wanted to make it look like he couldn't possibly have moved the body. Moving Lady Justice was his way of pointing us to the body and cementing his alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Gaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's quite a persuasive argument. For a while there. I thought you weren't taking the trial seriously. Well done!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fine, then. Say it already. I'm waiting...</line>
<line speaker="Means">The murder occurred the night before, but the body wasn't found until late the next day. Countless students passed the stage till they met in the Lecture Hall for the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">The body would absolutely be found.</line>
<line speaker="Means">So, answer me this -- why didn't anyone see the body that entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...That can be explained by, uh... Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If the victim was murdered on the stage and left there... ...the body would inevitably have been discovered. And, of course, there was nowhere to hide a body upon that stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is not good, Athena! Our claim is this close to being beaten to a pulp.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know... <thought>But we've come so far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Gah ha ha ha ha! Consider yourself schooled! I couldn't have possibly killed anyone! The killer is none other than Juniper Woods! It always has been and it always will be!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arrrgh... J-J-Just wait a minute...!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Poor Juniper. She must seriously regret having asked you to defend her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Means">And to add insult to injury, you nearly had Hugh convicted for murder. Surely, you haven't forgotten that little fiasco?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">Athena Cykes's attorney's badge is just for show!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Not only did you fail to defend your client, you also raised false charges against her friend. You have no right to call yourself a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Means">But if this trial proceeds in the same manner and ends in the same way as the mock trial... ...would you not lose everything you've worked so hard to gain?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'll just have to make sure that doesn't happen, then, won't I!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Don't tell me I've failed once again -- failed to save someone near and dear to me... I've worked so hard to become a lawyer, and even studied psychology. Has it all been for naught? Am I just doomed to relive that all over again?!</thought> Unnghh...! A... Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Athena! Wh-What's wrong?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Breathe in... Breathe out... Breathe in... <thought>Relax, Athena, breathe...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="???">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="???">Woods:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Junie...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I know you better than most people, Thena. And I know you'd never surrender to the dark age of the law like the professor did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you, Junie. But I feel like I can barely breathe. I don't know what to do.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Stop your bleating this instant. You look an utter fool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There is one who awaits you, is there not? And that is the reason you have studied so very hard. Are you prepared to give up on all you have worked for thus far?! It would not do to have you disappoint you-know-who!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I... I...!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But, Apollo, what am I supposed to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Listen, all you have to do is take a deep breath and look back over the entire case. If there's truth to be found -- and there always is -- you're sure to find it. Now, let me see you smile. Remember what Mr. Wright said? The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena Cykes is psyched and ready to rock. Prepare for your utter defeat!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Courte wasn't killed in the art room. She was killed right where her body was found. We know because there wasn't any time to move the body there from somewhere else. That means the body had to have been hidden somewhere onstage until it was found. Let's think along these lines and see where it takes us. First up... When did Prof. Means remove the body from its hiding place? Well, let's see. What was he doing right before the body was discovered? He was using the span of time his fake alibi created... ...to move the body to where it would be more easily spotted. Therefore, the only time Prof. Means could've removed the body from its hiding place is...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Before the mock trial? No, that can't be it. Hugh testified that he'd seen the body before the mock trial... ...but it turned out he was lying to protect Junie. The appearance of the body has to coincide with the time covered by the professor's alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">After the mock trial? No, that can't be right. We saw the body before the mock trial even ended. The when and why Prof. Means fabricated his alibi is key here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It was during the mock trial, specifically...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, Junie was in charge of the audio, so she would've left the Lecture Hall many times. There's no way to know which of those times to focus on. There's got to be some other way to pinpoint the timing of the professor's actions.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Means moved the body to an easily seen location during his long, pre-recorded speech. The professor also moved something to the stage that wasn't there before, specifically...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, we already have a body. Why would there be another one? After all, there was only one victim -- Prof. Courte. And she was already sprawled out on the stage. In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The gold Lady Justice! ...Wait, that one was in the Lecture Hall. It has nothing to do with the stage. I'd better rethink this. It was during his speech that the professor moved the body to where it could be found.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">During the mock trial, Prof. Means wrapped the white Lady Justice in the school banner... ...and sent it zipping down to the stage with a crash, killing two birds with one stone! He drew attention to the body and made it look like the murder occurred in the art room! But was there anywhere to hide a body on that stage? It doesn't seem likely... ...No, there had to be someplace! .........! Wait a second! How about something that should've been finished but was only mostly done? Something was used to cover the body up... ...but it didn't draw undue attention because it looked like it belonged there onstage. In that way, no one would suspect there was a body hidden inside! What was already on the stage and capable of concealing a body?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the body had been wrapped in the school banner... No, that wouldn't work. Someone would've easily noticed something like that. It had to be something where you couldn't tell there was a body inside.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Inside the Prosecutor Gavin statue...? No, that wouldn't work. Robin made the Gavin statue herself, from start to finish. And there wouldn't have been enough space to hide a body in there anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I know! The Mr. Wright statue was never actually finished! The body was wrapped under some cloth to hide what was really inside... ...cleverly disguising it as the boss's statue!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Newman gave up on the Wright statue, yet Prof. Means finished it in a single night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, what an impressive feat that was!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Come again? I'm afraid I don't follow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He hid the body by making it look like the statue of Mr. Wright. With the body wrapped under a piece of cloth, it looked just like a statue!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WH-WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I second that "Whaaaaaaaaaat?!"!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph! Now, this is getting interesting!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-oh... I think I know where this is going.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, Apollo! Time to turn me into a reasonable likeness of Mr. Wright! I'm going to pose like the statue, like so... And now I want you to wrap me up in a cloth so that I look like a statue!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I hate to ask the obvious, but where am I supposed to get this magical cloth?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that isn't the right color, Mr. Justice...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, given how sudden the request was, it's kinda the best I could do, Your Honor... All right, I think that about does it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, what do you think, everyone?! Do I look just like a statue of Mr. Wright or what?!</line>
<line speaker="Man">-- Looks like some random person to me.-- Weren't the statues a pair of busts?</line>
<line speaker="Woman">-- Phoenix Wright has that spiky hair on the back of his head.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Forget the hair. The statue's head is way bigger than your average person's anyway! <thought>You gotta hand it to me for trying, anyway. ...Wait, that's it! The hands!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... Her arms are raised over her head and there are dark bruises around her wrists.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. The professor was probably tied up with something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The marks on her wristed [sic] indicated she'd been tied up!</thought> Apollo, tie me up in a new pose! ...Wait, you're not into this kind of thing, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? No! Besides, it was your idea! ...Just tell me how to tie your hands, already!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Courte's wrists were tied together, and I can't help but think that's related! <thought>How should I arrange myself to match the shape I want, given her hands were tied?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tie both of my hands in an "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" pose!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You sure? What about the spiky hair on the back of the head?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I know! The boss is right there! Go pull some out and you can glue it on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I'm on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry, Athena. I... I couldn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, don't be such a wimp!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aww.. How unfortunate. And I was so looking forward to seeing where that was headed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's all Apollo's fault! <thought>Guess I'd better think of something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">How about trying my hands behind my back?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You sure? What about the spiky hair on the back of the head?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't have this massively long hair for nothing! Just use some superglue to bond it into place!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool! You shall ruin your hair. Lucky for you, no such glue residue was found on the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? ...Oh! When you're right, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whew... You had me all worried for nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing? Y-You mean...... <thought>Umm... If the body stayed in the same pose until it was discovered... ...then I really just need to think how it could look like the boss's hair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, tie both of my hands behind my head!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See! This makes it possible to fake the spikes on the back of Mr. Wright's head!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, but then what about the statue's arm? With both arms behind your head, you can't exactly complete the pose...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yeah, it would be awfully hard to make the objection pose like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I can't help thinking you've forgotten something, Athena. Something on the body that you don't have right now...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What did the victim's body have that I don't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means">Means:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ouch! <thought>Way to kick a girl when she's tied up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're certainly not the lawyerly ideal I'd like to present to my grandchild.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Double ouch! <thought>Now that's really piling it on! Oh, well, let's think that over again. How did the body look when we found it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right! There was an arrow sticking out of her side! Okay, Apollo, take that and plunge it into my side!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What are you crazy?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fine, then go get some duct tape! Rapido, schnell!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right, all right! I don't need to know other languages to know "bossy" when I hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The fatal arrow to the side! Spiky hair created from two hands! A masterpiece in the making! Now, cover me with that cloth! But remember to make the arrow stand out, okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">-- Mommy, the arm's too short!-- Shhh. Remember your indoor voice, dear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nobody's buying it! The arrow's nowhere near long enough!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But! <thought>What else could you use for the arm?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Still won't give up, eh? I must commend you, if only for your spirit and determination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course she's not giving up! After all she's put me through, she owes me an explanation -- and one that makes sense! Now, disappoint me again and the penalty will be doubly painful!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! I guess I'd better get it right this time! <thought>Think, Athena, think! Prof. Courte was murdered when she stopped by the stage to see Prof. Means. If it wasn't premeditated, he must've used something close at hand in his little ruse.</thought> ...Apollo. Show me those stage set up photos again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like that? Right now??? O-Okay, hold on!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Please, please, please... Please be in this photo! It just has to be!</thought> The arm on the Mr. Wright statue is really this right here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-This right here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright's not gonna like this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! ...Um, never mind. I retract my previous statement.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's all very well and good, but I won't retract your penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sacré bleu! <thought>Something longer than an arrow that pierced her body... It must be here somewhere.</thought> Arrrgh! What could it be?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it! I know what he used for the arm on the statue of Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Means">This is absurd! There is no such thing in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh heh. Don't play dumb with me, Professor. It's the staff you have right there!</line>
<line speaker="Means">S-Staff?! This is the spear of a great legal warrior!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whatever, just hurry up and lend it to me! The length is perfect! Mr. Wright couldn't possibly object to such an awesome arm! Okay, go for it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, I'll give your arm a hand! Cloth and binding coming right up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Woman">-- It's Phoenix Wright!-- Look, it's that famous lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Man">-- That's definitely him.-- I'd know that pose anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We did it! ...Didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Well?! Am I not the spitting image of the legendary Phoenix Wright?! The man who will bring us out of these dark ages and into an era of brilliant golden light!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Golden light? All I see before me......... is the pink specter of a man!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! That's just because Mr. Wright likes his statue! He's positively tickled pink! Get it, Apollo? He's tickled pink!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blah, that joke deserves a pink slip.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems the gallery is quite impressed with the defense's sharp thinking. And the witness?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Bah... The resemblance is nothing more than a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's examine the spear for prints! That'll settle this whole mess!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? And just what do you hope to prove? And whose prints are you hoping to find?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Mea--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, of course you'd find Prof. Means's prints! It is his spear, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, then, the vic--</line>
<line speaker="Means">The victim's prints would be there, too. I had her do repair work on it a number of times.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Your Honor. A penalty, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, at least your sense of justice is still intact.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It still hurts, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That spear might actually be a staff!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Bah! You know nothing, little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Spears are far more dashing than staves!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While this is all very interesting, it has little, if anything, to do with the issue at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We had assumed the victim's jagged wound came from the arrow being forcibly shoved in. But if the wound was from this spear instead... ...then we should be able to detect traces of the victim's blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Ack... Arrrrrgh... Your Honor, a b-brief recess, if you will! By any means possible. What if I get rid of my spear... Wait, what if I burn it...?!</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">What's wrong with a non-guilty verdict?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">If I do that I'll be found innocent... Yes, I'm innocent I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Means [on blackboard]">Bathroom detail</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill, what has become of our witness, Aristotle Means?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It is as Cykes-dono suspected. Blood was detected on his staff. He has admitted to this heinous crime. All of it. He shall join us in the clink tomorrow. His teaching skills can be put to good use there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great. He'll teach felons that the end justifies the means. So much for rehabilitation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can I ask what the professor's motive was?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. I could barely make out a word he said on account of his shattered teeth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>One of Blackquill's fellow inmates was once a surgeon. Why not a former dentist, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I eventually had him put pen to paper. It turns out, Prof. Means was the one taking bribes. The victim has suspected him after a report from the class snitch. That led her to question him at length the day of the killing -- right there on that stage. The result? The heinous crime that was brought before this court. The fool, like Newman, had come to know of the script's contents via the victim's note. It seems he came up with a plan to stab the victim with her own awl in order to... ...make the killing look like the one in the script and thus frame the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But that scrap of paper with Hugh's name had the same mark as Prof. Courte's planner--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, about that... Those planners are bestowed upon all students graduating at the top of their class.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! So, then...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. Once upon a time, Prof. Means was also awarded the same notebook. The handwriting is being analyzed now, but like as not, the scrap belonged to him. This too, was evidence of the bribery scheme that the victim had obtained. Know that Constance Courte was clean and that only Aristotle Means took the bribes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... To think a professor would murder a colleague, then try to pin it on a student. If this is the dark age of the law, then we can only hope that a brighter future awaits. And the first step is to hand down my verdict for a promising young lady. This court finds the defendant, Juniper Woods...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I wish you all the best on your road to becoming a courtroom judge. We will need young people like you... ...if we ever hope to restore the law to its former glory.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Y-Yes, Your Honor! I'll work as hard as I can. Maybe, one day, I'll be able to work with all of you to make a difference!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Proudly serve Prof. Courte's memory. Do not let her death be in vain.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's the last thing I expect to hear from him today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thank you, Thena! I really mean it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha ha ha ha! It was nothing, really! I can take the biggest tangled mess of a case and unravel it just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I dunno... You looked pretty wound up there at the end -- literally and figuratively!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You look pretty hungry for a knuckle sandwich, buster!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I... I wanted to thank you, too, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah ha ha. Don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">The way you were always there for Thena when she was in a bind... And at the Detention Center, when your smile gave me hope when there was none... It was like the warm rays of the sun shining down on peaceful woodlands. I think you're an absolutely amazing person!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, Juniper. That means a lot to me. But I still have lots of work to do! And I can't wait until we see you on the judge's bench!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Ha ha ha ha! I promise you I'll get there someday! That's why until that day, I'll... I'll--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guys, I've got some big news! I mean, this is huge! ...Oh, am I interrupting something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No no, it's okay... I think. So, what's the big news?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The school festival! It was supposed to have been canceled after what happened, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We just got a call. In memory of Prof. Constance Courte, who worked so hard to make it happen... ...the festival is being extended one extra day until tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! All right!</line>
<line speaker="Crowd">YEAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We've got a special treat for all of you. A love letter for Themis Legal Academy. Achtung, baby. It's time for The Guitar's Serenade.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, that what [sic] SO much fun! School festivals are amazing!!!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Tee hee hee. I think you and Robin are getting a little carried away.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Aaaaaah! Your singing voice, Juniper! It could melt my H-E-A-R-T!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...Mr. Wright. Thank you for that training seminar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. Just remember, the "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" pose is all about attitude. Oh, and congrats on your mock trial win. Although, Robin had you for a while there.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I did, didn't I! But I'm just glad we're back to how we used to be, thanks to Athena. And you know what? I think I'll stick with become a prosecutor after all. I'm going to make up for my mock trial loss by winning the real deals in court!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Mock trial loss? What loss? Wait. Did they reprise the trial and Hugh won?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Level-headed lawyer course genius and hot-blooded prosecutor course student... ...will go head to head in a mock trial battle for the she-devil's black heart!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So... does this mean it's really gonna happen?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">.........J-J-Juniper! There's something I've been wanting to say to you!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooooh! Is he going to do what I think he is?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">J-Juniper... Can we still be friends? You know, best friends like we've always been?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Best friends...? Hugh, weren't you going to profess your love for Juniper if you won the mock trial?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, I was going to confess... ...that I'm not a genius, and that I'm really twenty-five years old. But you already dragged it out of me during the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whoops!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Listen, Hugh. You, too, Robin, Myriam.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">M-Me, too?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Myriam's got this tactical espionage action stuff down to a science...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">...I've been thinking. It's up to us to put an end to the dark age of the law if we can. Let's all work together to usher in a new age where winning only results from the truth... ...and the end never justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Count me in!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I wouldn't have it any other way.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Best friends forever, huh... No matter what anyone says, nothing beats true friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You bet! And what about your BFF, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aren't you a bit old to be using that word? But yeah, he's the best friend a guy could have. Which reminds me, we're supposed to meet up and gossip about the new girl in the office.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! No talking about me behind my back! ...So, what kind of guy is he, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... If I had to describe him in one word...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And so, after some slight arm-twisting, Apollo promised to bring me to meet his friend. Unfortunately, that promise was never meant to be fulfilled. For not long after, their friendship was mercilessly severed by Fate... ...and the bonds between us began to fray and unravel as well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even now, those words continue to ring in my ears. The discord in our ever-cheerful Apollo's voice made him sound so cold... and distant. Why, Apollo? Why? Why would you leave us all behind?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? And how would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Just look at it! It's one huge contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. The defense is simply making another baseless assertion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>Crash and burn!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All that says to me is you're completely wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaahhh! <thought>I guess that won't fly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've been doing this for far too long to be fooled by such nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! <thought>And I really tried hard that time, too.</thought> Your Honor, can I at least get credit for trying?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I hereby award Ms. Cykes the court's "Wasted Effort" award.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Where's the love?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mind letting your slightly senior partner help out a little now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...If you insist. <thought>Actually, I could really use the help.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I find this statement suspicious. You should find the answer if you take a good look at the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Thanks, Apollo! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could get used this [sic] more humble version of you, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You okay, Athena? You can tell me if something's bothering you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No, I'm totally fine! <thought>Actually, I'm not anywhere near fine.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The thing with cross-examinations is the answer you need isn't always obvious. You have to dig deep to find clues hidden in the testimony. Really wrestle with it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so it's like grabbing a bull by the horns and wrestling it to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, try not to take it so literally. Just stick with pressing the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Thanks, Apollo! <thought>Okay, let's give it a try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, this is what you're happy about!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Happy? What are you talking about? I'm confessing to murder here. To call the grief I feel at the severity of my crime happiness is insanity beyond mine.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, uh... Guess I got that one wrong.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I pity you mouth-breathers. You should listen attentively to the genius of my confession!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, this emotion is inconsistent with your testimony! </line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You don't know what you're talking about. I take joy in my intellect, feel anger toward your superficiality... ...suffer sadness at the world's ephemerality, and wonder at the universe's mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. I should've brought my dictionary to court.</thought> Wait! Let me try that one again!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I also suffer sadness at the futility of your efforts, but if you must.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need prolong this trial any further. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Juniper Woods...</line>
</xml>