
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reclaimed</title>
<line speaker="Athena">*siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiigh*</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That was a big sigh, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you... lose the case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, we won. The defendant was found not guilty. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Then why are you so dejected?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy... were you being mean to her?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Picking on the new kid? Not cool, Mr. Wright. Not cool...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute! Talk about false accusations! We were able to prove the defendant's innocence... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">...But then Sasha got arrested instead. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So that's what happened. That's too bad... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what are you two going to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We're going to get to the bottom of this. I don't believe for a second that Sasha did what they're accusing her of. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I don't believe it, either! I won't give up! Boss, let's go see Sasha and tell her we want to represent her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right now, I imagine she's still being questioned by the police. Let's get started on the investigation first, and look for proof of her innocence. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sounds like a plan!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just leave the office to me and Polly, Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If there's anything I can do to help, just say the word!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. If you could organize the evidence and clean the office, that'd be great. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I meant, anything I could do as a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That takes care of that. Time to head to the scene of the crime!</thought>     </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? There's no water in this pool. Orlaaa! Where are youuu?</line>
<line speaker="Orla">...Fweet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can hear her at the bottom of the pool. Maybe there's some water down there. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla sounds so sad. Maybe she misses Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="???">Careful, there! You shouldn't get right up to the edge like that! </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You don't want to end up like the victim! Besides, the police are still conducting their investigation here. Don't go poking around!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright...! Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Is something wrong, Ms. Lawyer? You look angry. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I object to you arresting Ms. Buckler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective, I'd like to ask you some questions about the case, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Go right ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Buckler is one-hundred-percent innocent, so why did you arrest her?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I understand your desire to believe in her. But the fact remains that she's suspicious! Right now, there are investigators on the scene, so you can come in as you please... ...but ordinarily, a security card is required to enter this orca pool room. The victim and Sasha Buckler were the only ones who possessed this card. And yesterday, the day of the incident, there's proof the suspect's card was used.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> Somebody else could have used Ms. Buckler's card!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, my! I guess that would be one possible explanation...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! Didn't I sound just like a lawyer right there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. <thought>We'd kinda be in trouble if you didn't...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Except! The suspect confirmed she entered the room at the time the record states. She said she was here from 3:00 to 6:00 AM on July 20th. Apparently, she was giving the orca pool room a good cleaning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cleaning, in the middle of the night?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes, she said that a lot of the heavy-duty cleaning is done at night. The suspect also admits that she was fighting with the owner before his murder. What's more, nobody saw the victim again after he met with the suspect. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Objection...! Um, there must be something I can object to in there somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Save your objections for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So that's your symbol of justice, is it? Well, this is MINE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Wow. He can whip that badge out pretty fast...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We can top that! Take THIS! Twin attorney's badges!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aaagh! No fair! Two against one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No fair! Your police badge is bigger and flashier!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What?! You dare to call me... "unfair"?! Me, the very model of justice itself?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss! I'd say we won this round!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, in this battle there are no winners...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The poor victim... It's heart-wrenching! Crime cannot go unpunished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't want crime to go unpunished, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we'll do our utmost to defend our client.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm. Your form of justice or mine... Which is true justice? I guess we'll see how it plays out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, he doesn't have enough information right now to make up his mind. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for the translation, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Are you trying to bribe me?! What a heinous act! I'll bring justice down upon you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is food for the penguin. I wasn't trying to give it to you. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What kind of a person gives fish as a bribe?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, you'd be surprised. All kinds of people try to buy the police's favor... A politician once even sent me some raw meat as a bribe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Raw meat? So what did you do with it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">It goes without saying! I returned it to him, and then I arrested him! The meat was rotten by the time he got it back, though... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Must've been a pretty rotten day for the politician altogether...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! I have NOTHING to say about that! If you're lawyers of any mettle, you'll find the answers for yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, Detective Fulbright, do you think Ms. Buckler's questioning is over?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No, not yet. But I told the guy in charge to take it easy on her... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">...Oops! Forget I said anything. It doesn't concern you two anyway. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it does concern us. We intend to represent Ms. Buckler. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What? You do? In that case, I have a favor to ask. Could you get this medicine to her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Medicine...? Looks like a prescription from Hickfield Clinic... <thought>I've spent some time at that hospital, myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">We confiscated it from her home when we were doing a search. I can't get away here, so if you could make sure she gets it, that would be great. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Medicine, huh...? Does Ms. Buckler have some illness?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Um... I think that's the kind of question you'd better ask her. In justice we trust! Now I need to get back to the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can give it to her as soon as they let us talk to her. <thought>And we have to return her calendar to her as well. If we can't see Sasha or investigate, we should question people at the aquarium...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Please give that to Sasha Buckler! It's very important that she has it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're pretty considerate, aren't you, even to a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Of course! I treat everyone justly and fairly, no matter who they are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, you'll share the prosecution's information with us, right? It's only fair.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm. You've got a point there, but... Hmmmmmmmm... Quite the pickle...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...His heart is filled with confusion. I don't think we'll get him to listen now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I didn't really think that was going to work...</line>
<line speaker="Wright Anything Agency">Talk</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So Sasha Buckler got arrested, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Do you know Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">One of my magician friends told me about her. He said she was a great performer. He said she was like a different person when she gets on stage. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well... she does wear a mustache during her act...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? A mustache? Maybe I should wear a mustache, too. Or cat whiskers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you think that will help your act, I say go for it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Remember, investigation and questioning people are a lawyer's two main tools! Even if you've already checked a place, you might find something new if you look again. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, listen to you! You sound like a regular little lawyer lady all of a sudden. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you haven't worked as a lawyer for a long time. I'm worried about you! It's just like magic. If you don't keep practicing, you get rusty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You have a good point there, Trucy. So we lawyers have to keep mowing the prosecutors down, to stay sharp?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's one way of putting it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Congratulations on your big comeback, Daddy! You look sharp in your suit! ...But I'm a little sad, too. Now I'm the only entertainer left in our agency...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not true. We still have Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet Apollo could be a first-rate talent in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you're right! He'd be great as my magician's assistant, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, we're all basically entertainers here when we don't have a legal case to work on.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Really?! I'd better start working on an act, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was just kidding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That Swashbuckler Spectacular at Shipshape Aquarium is my number-one competition!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, is it, now?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They talk about that show a lot at the Wonder Bar. I've been studying up on their format, you know. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think your magic show is pretty great just as it is. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks, Daddy! But I'd like to do an underwater magic show someday, too. For example, I'd love to do one of those underwater escape acts!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absolutely not! Too dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You want me to do that magic trick where I instantly turn a whole fish into just bones?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean that "magic trick" where you EAT the fish?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How about the trick where I turn a fish into a dish?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now you're just rhyming words. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can turn a fish into a fist, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm starting to wonder how far you're going to run with this one. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There are unlimited possibilities when it comes to my Magic Panties trick!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Did you buy that for me to do a magic trick with?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but this is evidence. I'll have Apollo buy you something instead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe it! Just when we prove Orla innocent, Sasha gets arrested! I'll never forgive that Prosecutor Blackquill and Detective Fulbright! This stress on my heart is just too much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Athena. She's really upset...</thought> We'd better do some more investigating if we want to save Sasha. Let's check the orca pool room again and question everybody involved.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, Mr. Wright! You sure know how to stay calm in a crisis! I can top that! LOOK HOW CALM I CAN BE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, the very definition of "calm," I'd say...</thought> Good for you. Now let's get back to the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I had a thought. How about if I try getting on Taka's good side? Then maybe he wouldn't attack when that awful Prosecutor Blackquill told him to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not sure it's that simple, but, anyway...</thought> How are you going to get on his good side?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if I made myself smell like meat, he'd start to like me! The way to a bird's heart is through his nose, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd rather you didn't smell like meat while you were standing next to me at the bench.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm so glad you got your attorney's badge back, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me too. I guess I was always meant to be a lawyer. I'm going to polish it up, shinier than it's ever been!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can top that! I'm going to polish mine until the finish comes off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind. You win.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, the Swashbuckler Spectacular is so exciting! I could watch it a hundred times! The fierce fighting, the graceful moves! Oh, Orla and Sasha are so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you love the show so much, why don't you try auditioning to be in it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, I know! The whole office could be in it together! We could be the "Anything Pirate Band"! You know, from the name of the agency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like a pretty pathetic pirate band to me. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you talking about?! It sounds cutthroat! It means we'd do "anything" to get our hands on treasure! Anything, no matter how brutal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes. We're a brutal pirate band?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Phwiiiiip! Phwiiip, phwiiip!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't ask if you could blow it. It's such a weird whistle, anyway. It doesn't even make a proper "whistle" sound.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Most people can't hear it, but I think I can hear it a little bit. It's like a message that only Orla's heart can receive! Aw, that's so sweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the same idea as a dog whistle, so I wonder if dogs can hear it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! Now you ruined it! You don't know anything about girls, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. That smells awful! Please keep it away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you're the one who wanted it. Why do I have to carry it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla sure eats a lot, doesn't she? I used to eat a lot when I was a kid. Took lots of naps, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you still take lots of naps, right here at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! You knew about that?! I-It's this new thing I'm trying out! Um... sleep learning! Yeah, that's the ticket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not buying it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just horrible! How could Ms. DePlume write such mean things about Orla?! This awful book made the judge doubt her innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Especially since he's a fan of Ms. DePlume's work. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I read the book, too, you know... I hate to admit it, but it's a real page-turner. It really brought the scenes to life. Ms. DePlume is a powerful writer. She knows how to capture the reader's imagination. ...Maybe I'll ask her to sign the book for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what do you know. Looks like you really DID become a fan.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it. Your current state of mind is: "Gather all the information we can get." But let's concentrate on USEFUL information from now on, okay, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? That door is open. It was closed yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, Boss! We sneak in and check it out! </line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you two! Who barges into a person's lab without permission?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeek! We're sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My apologies, sir. She insisted... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't throw me under the bus, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="???">The polite thing to do is nock and ask if you can come in! Now, start over!   </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yes, siiir!</line>
<line speaker="???">Come in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you! Sorry to bother you!</line>
<line speaker="???">Now, what can I do for you? Medical problems?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, well, yes... I'm not feeling super good at the moment... We're not making any progress on this murder investigation, and--</line>
<line speaker="???">...Hey, Miss? Where is the patient? Don't you have your pet with you? ...Oh, wait a minute. That was my last job. This is the aquarium... I was exhausted from all that questioning... I must've fallen asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What's with this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...My apologies. I just woke up, and I was a little groggy. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'm Dr. Herman Crab. I'm Shipshape Aquarium's resident veterinarian. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! You're the "Dr. Crab" Mr. Rimes mentioned yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And Rimes also mentioned he hadn't seen Dr. Crab around... I wonder where he was?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Son of a gun. This little thing doesn't let me get any sleep.</line>
<line speaker="???">*peep!* *peep, peep, peep!*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaw! What a cute little thing! Who is it?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">A penguin chick, a member of the Little Penguin species. She lives in my hair. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're so lucky! I wish I had a pet to live in my hair!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, no pets allowed in my office. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, you're no fun... </line>
<line speaker="Crab">If you two don't have any particular business with me, please leave. I have to get ready to make my rounds. ...Back in you go, little one. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! We'd like to ask you a few questions, to save Ms. Buckler!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hold on... Don't tell me you're the curious pair who defended Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Please let us ask you a little about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Crab, were you gone from the aquarium yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. I had some minor business at the Supermarine Aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"S-Supermarine"? That's a funny name for an aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Supermarine Aquarium is the nation's biggest dolphin therapy treatment center! I go there, myself. I'm friends with their dolphins!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You and Apollo were talking about animal-assisted therapy yesterday, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I go to the Supermarine once a month, but I live here, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You LIVE here at the aquarium?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. I have a sleeping bag here, and sometimes I use the nap room. I'm responsible for the health and well-being of all the marine creatures here. If any of them have a sudden medical emergency, I'll be here to help them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. You're kind of rough around the edges, Dr. Crab, but you care about your work!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Hey, buddy? Is this young lady trying to pick a fight with me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I apologize for her, sir. She tends to be too honest. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, you're no paragon of politeness either, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can we see the penguin chick again?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Stop! Don't come any closer!</line>
<line speaker="???">*peeeeeeep!*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">OWWWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'm sorry she attacked you. She doesn't like anyone but me, I'm afraid. I was the first one she saw when she hatched, so she thinks I'm her parent. She targets people from my hair, so please be careful. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's just like a little sniper, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Exactly. That's why I named her "Sniper." Her mother's name is "Rifle."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Sniper" and "Rifle," huh? What a dangerous-sounding mother and daughter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So this is Rifle's daughter! ...Which means both mother and daughter now hate me. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Little Penguins are generally belligerent little creatures. It's hard to get them to warm up. But they're nocturnal, so you might be able to touch them during the day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You and Sniper get along well, don't you? Just like Sasha and Orla. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">But unlike Sniper and me, the two of them seem to truly understand one another. This one keeps me awake every night! Looks like I won't sleep until she leaves the nest. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It must be rough for him... but it's pretty cute to watch for us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me anything about Jack Shipley's murder?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Gah! ...I still can't believe Jack is gone... He's the one who brought me on board. How could he up and die on me?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you and Mr. Shipley get along?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">He loved all animals and fish, but I'm not like that. ...But I still took pride in my work as a vet, nonetheless. We got along well enough as business associates. And it's thanks to him my laboratory is what it is today. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It IS a pretty amazing laboratory. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Ah, you have discerning taste, I see. I could tell you more about my lab, if you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This place is just filled with electronics! What are those monitors for?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Essentially, they're digital medical records for all the creatures here. I can also view the feed from the visitor's corridor security camera here. That way, I can see that silly mother penguin when she tries to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were the one who gave this security footage to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No, I wasn't here yesterday, but I did give my permission for them to take it. And I gave them a statement about Jack and Sasha arguing. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! So you were the one who witnessed it?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. It was late in the evening of the 19th, maybe about midnight. I saw them fighting near the Aqua Tunnel. I don't know what their argument was about, though. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you should be talking to us about this?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'm not taking sides. I'll give information to anyone who wants it. What you do with that information at Sasha's trial is up to you. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. You're kind of rough around the edges, Dr. Crab, but you're a pretty nice guy!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hmph! You ARE trying to pick a fight, aren't you, young lady?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, isn't that cute! He's easily embarrassed!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun! How could you die before fulfilling your promise to me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Shipley promised you something?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">He promised he would make Shipshape Aquarium the greatest aquarium in the world. It was because of that promise that I agreed to become the resident vet here. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you were just a regular veterinarian before this?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. Big or small, there is no living creature I cannot treat! Would you like me to examine you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! You can treat people, too? You're amazing, Dr. Crab! </line>
<line speaker="Crab">...I was joking, of course. Ooh, you walked right into that one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">GRRRRRRRRRRR! You're awful, Dr. Crab!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, so that makes him... amazingly awful...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hmm? Don't waste my time with useless nonsense. I'm sleepy, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He won't even glance at it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sniper">*peep*... *peep, peep, peep!*</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Huh? Son of a gun. Are you hungry again already? And that silly mother penguin's nowhere to be found again...</line>
<line speaker="Sniper">*peep* *peep, peep, peep!*</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Gaaaaagh! Would you quit peeping in my ear?! According to her walkie-talkie, Rifle is somewhere around the Aqua Tunnel. If you see her, could you bring her to me? I have to go examine some other creatures...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No sweat! And this time, I'll get her to like me, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rifle has escaped again? What is she, she the Houdini of the penguin world?</thought> There's no guarantee we'll find her right away but let's head for the Aqua Tunnel.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Aaaaagh! It's you two! The blue and yellow duo! I'm very angry about what you did this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. We ran into the sea lion before our penguin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I write the truth. And I will find the truth with my own eyes! I won't be bested by the likes of the blue and yellow duo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When did we become the "blue and yellow duo"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">Athena will never give up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, I'll leave the questioning to you, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks a lot, Widget. Well, at least she's a worthy adversary! Okay! Let's do this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. You'll do great! <thought>You know, being the boss isn't half bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Have you been gathering material about last year's incident ever since?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That is correct. An acquaintance of the victim asked me to look into it, you see. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An acquaintance of the victim? </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I refuse to divulge any information about my clients. The aquarium is saying it was an accident, but I don't believe that's the truth. It seems to me they're all hiding something -- every last one of them! The only thing I can think is that the killer whale murdered that poor girl. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you don't even know if that's true or not! </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That's enough out of you, yellow girl! As I said, I'm still investigating the matter... Once I learn the truth, I plan to write a sequel to this book.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's completely taken with her "investigation"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I came to make a report on the anniversary of the previous trainer's death... ...only to find the aquarium owner murdered! I was deeply shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this incident happened on the exact same date as the last one...? It can't be a coincidence... Anyway, we'd better ask Ms. DePlume about today's trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you heard Orla singing, and that's when you realized something was happening?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Correct! ...Ooh, it's all so galling! I still can't believe the culprit used ME, Norma DePlume! In any case, I swear that killer whale song brings misfortune. First last year, now again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A fun song like that?! How could it bring misfortune to anyone?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">You think that barbaric song is "fun"? I'll never understand the tastes of children...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't remember that Swashbuckler Spectacular song being all that "barbaric"...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, if you don't remember it, I will gladly sing it for you!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Avast, mateys! Landlubbers, ho!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...That's how it goes. Now, what is "fun" about those lyrics, pray tell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seemed to be enjoying it well enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait a minute! That isn't the Swashbuckler Spectacular song! THIS is the song from the Swashbuckler Spectacular!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh we be pirates. We love to sail the seven seas.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">............What was that? I've never heard that song before.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? It's the song they use in the Swashbuckler Spectacular!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">But that can't be! It's completely different from the song a year ago!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! She's so stubborn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if it's proof she wants, it's proof she'll get of the Swashbuckler Spectacular song.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">A Swashbuckler flyer? I have more than enough of those already. Do you have any idea how many times I've visited this aquarium?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, what are you yelling at me for?</thought> Don't you ever get tired of coming here?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Hmph! You obviously don't know anything about Shipshape Aquarium. They feature different marine creatures each month, so visitors never get bored.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you're a fan of Shipshape Aquarium, like me?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh, please! I'm here to gather information-- the fundamental work of a great writer. But I don't suppose that's something you common folk would understand...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! That woman makes me so mad! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. Why don't we "common folk" just get back to our investigation?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Don't thrust that under my nose! I won't watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you usually pretty photogenic, Ms. DePlume?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Of course I am! I've been compared to a movie star! It's little wonder, with my perfect makeup and stylish figure. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She wants me to agree?!</thought> Let's get a woman's opinion on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? You're asking me?! Well, uh, let's see. I DO think you're very pretty, Ms. DePlume.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Hmm? I get the distinct impression your words are full of hidden meaning...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... I wouldn't say "full" so much as "full-figured"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Athena! I'd stop right there if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">If it's an autograph you want, I give them out to anyone, no matter who it is. But make sure you've read the entire book before you ask. After all, the worth of a book is not who the writer is or what the cover looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. That actually made sense.</thought> ...I'll be sure to read it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I read it! I hate to admit it, but I thought it was very well-written.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, well, yellow girl. I just might have to learn your name.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! It's Athena Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I simply wrote "to banana girl" when I signed your book. Because of the yellow, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"B-Banana girl"?! That's the worst one yet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, do you regret being a fan now?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I have no interest in looking at meaningless trifles. As a matter of fact, I have no interest in looking at you, blue boy. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What, so now I'm a "meaningless trifle," too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This recording contains the Swashbuckler Spectacular song. In it, you can see Ms. Buckler and Orla singing together.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe fwe fweet. Fwe fwe fwe fweeet!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">We swim through storms and waves, all because, you see...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">! B-But I've never heard this song before!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? But they always sing this song during the Swashbuckler Spectacular... </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, I haven't seen the show recently... A year ago, they used the song that I sang to you. I'd recognize it anywhere! Perhaps that killer whale can sing two songs?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Ms. Buckler, Orla only knows one song.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Then... what was that song that I heard...? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We wish we knew... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The orca sang a song she isn't supposed to know how to sing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">It's obvious I have a lot more investigating to do on Shipshape Aquarium. And perhaps I'd better look into the Center for Dangerous Animal Control as well... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Center for Dangerous Animal Control? What's that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell us about this "Center for Dangerous Animal Control"?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Just as the name implies, it's an organization that monitors dangerous animals. The center demanded that the aquarium put the killer whale down a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Put her down?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">But the aquarium owner refused their demand, saying it was an accidental death. But I hardly think a persistent organization like that would just give up and go away. I'm quite sure the power of money helped convince them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Once a month, the owner and the vet disappear from this aquarium. And I came to find out that, each time, a large amount of money was being paid out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! And you think the money was going to this Center for Dangerous Animal Control?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...I'm looking into it now. You'll have to wait until my book comes out to see! In any case, I can't catch that man out on anything... ...but that veterinarian is not to be trusted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dr. Herman Crab... There's still so much we don't know about him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't see Rifle here. What do you want to do next? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we'd better stop by the office and discuss a plan of action.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I can't believe it! A song I've never heard before... Of course, I haven't seen the show since the incident a year ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Because the owner was in the show, and I thought it best he didn't see me. I've been banned from the aquarium, after all. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Being able to say that with your head held high proves you're somebody who matters!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And being able to say that right in front of somebody proves you're a newbie, Athena.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">3, 2, 1...... Ta-da!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow! You pulled Mr. Nick's cell phone from your Magic Panties! That's Amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee. That's all for Trucy's magic show! Come back and see me next time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great job, Trucy. You never fail to impress. I have no idea how you did that, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're back... Oh, Pearls! Stopping by for a visit?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. Hello, Mr. Nick. Are you missing something...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, thanks... <thought>From out of the ol' Magic Panties, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How is the investigation going, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't have much time, but we didn't get a chance to check out the crime scene yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! Speaking of checking out the crime scene, Daddy... You should bring your forensics kit with you! Fingerprint powder to check for prints, and luminol testing fluid to look for blood!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, Trucy! I didn't know you had stuff like that, too!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee! I got them from a detective friend of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I'd like to help you with your investigation! Can I borrow your forensicking kit?  </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I feel bad making you work when you're supposed to be here having fun.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I don't mind. And I'd like to see Rifle again, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you have anything for me to do, I'd like to help, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah? Thanks. I'll be sure to ask you if anything comes up, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I'll be right here... hanging around watering Charley... if you think of anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. I appreciate that, Apollo. <thought>I've got some good kids, here.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The return of a legendary lawyer! It's kind of exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Kind of"?</thought> So how do I look with it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow! You present that thing like a real pro! You must've done it a thousand times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It never really seems like enough to just have it pinned to my lapel, for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get wanting to show it off. When I first became a lawyer, I flashed that badge left and right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, you still do that, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Something you wear around your neck?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a whistle they use to make the orca do her tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I blow it at you, will you do a trick?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What am I, some kind of circus animal to you two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you ARE one of the talents here at our Wright Anything Agency, after all. The least you could do is learn a trick or two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Need I remind I'm a lawyer?! Besides, Athena doesn't know any tricks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! That's what YOU think! I've got a special trick I've been waiting to bust out. I can chug an entire glass of OJ without taking a breath, all while doing squats!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... that's, uh, really something, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I want to see Athena do squats...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Apollo. Think you could whip us up a little meal with these?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fish? I haven't had fish for a while, come to think of it... ...The obvious question, though, is "What are you doing with a bunch of raw fish?!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's to feed the penguin with!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Penguin?! So why are you giving it to me to cook?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I dunno. I just happened to think of it, and I was hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then why don't we all go out for sushi when you wrap up the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're going to treat us?! How sweet of you! I'll start with tuna!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's really generous of you, Apollo. Don't forget to invite Trucy, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why did I even open my mouth?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena already made me watch it so many times, I remember the whole show. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When this case is over, we should go see the show live. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I bet Trucy would like it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, I sure would like to see a head-to-head between Sasha and Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Magician versus pirate, huh? That would be one wild show, I bet. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we could join the fray as a band of lawyers! Right, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be even wilder than a day in court, I bet...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence...? Does this mean you want me at the defense's bench in court?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I just wanted to see what you think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. Darn... In that case, I don't think you want to hear what I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, team, let's do our best! I have faith we can save Sasha all together. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sure feels nice to be part of a great group like this! I just want to say that I really love working here, with all of you fabulous people. Thank you for bringing me aboard, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Same here, Athena. <thought>She's so earnest, she's making me blush.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay! Let's all run over to the aquarium!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I hope I can be of some use with the forensicking kit! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey, wait up, you two! <thought>They left without me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust! Good timing! We're done with the crime scene for now... ...and we're just about to examine the show stage. Marlon Rimes helped with the cleaning, so we've got to go talk with him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I thought he'd be more tight-lipped than this, but hey...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You're welcome to look around here now, if you'd like!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you. I think we'll do just that.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, by the way... If you want to examine the bottom of the pool... ...I recommend using that hoist over by the ladder to get down there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That crane-like thing hanging from the ceiling, right? Got it.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Just stand on the ladder platform, and the police guard will operate it for you. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. <thought>Why couldn't the pool be less deep...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, good luck to us both! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now that Detective Fulbright's gone, we can do anything we want here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The guard is still here, so keep your voice down when you say stuff like that, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Orla pulled this pirate flag and made the stuff fall down, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey. Doesn't this pirate flag look like a transport stretcher to you? And judging by the size, it's probably for Orla. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right. There are holes for her flippers, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that pirate flag design... Mr. Shipley sure was into the whole "pirate" thing. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We need to get serious about the whole "lawyer" thing, too. We can't let Prosecutor Blackquill outdo us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the water was drained for the police investigation. It seems kind of... sad, somehow, without the water.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When something that was there before is suddenly gone, it has a psychological effect. Like, for example, if all the magic props in the office were suddenly put away neatly. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think that's ever gonna happen as long as Trucy continues to practice magic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, she might not always be interested in magic, you know. She's at the age when young women start to worry about their future. The same thing happened to me, and I ended up becoming a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure Trucy will always be interested in magic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">One of the giant octopus's legs has been broken off. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla's spikes sure can do a lot of damage. Mr. Shipley must've been really strong to be able to return those hits.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm pretty amazing, myself, when it comes to strength! I run every day, and I go mountain climbing, too! I bet I could return Orla's spike... Well, I'll be able to someday, anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you really have to turn every little thing into a competition?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A setting sun... Sunsets always remind me how quickly the day goes by...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Boss! It's just a painted backdrop, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Down, Athena. Of course I know. I guess they use it for the Swashbuckler Spectacular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks handmade. Ooh, I just got an idea! Why don't we make our own "not guilty" backdrop?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And present it to the judge when things aren't going our way?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, we put psychological pressure on the judge by hanging it behind the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... almost want to see how the judge would respond to that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yesterday, I asked around about this orca pool room, you know. They said that this hoist is used to move equipment and even Orla herself. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do they move Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! I thought you'd ask that! Apparently, they use a stretcher made especially for an orca.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, what do you know. <thought>Athena looks pleased with herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of meat and a plastic hoop suspended from the ceiling. Talk about a clashy décor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Orla really likes meat. Who knew they fed her such huge chunks, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, all orcas are carnivores. You knew that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, silly! And I love meat, too! Protein is your body's basic building block, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that meat is made out of rubber. I doubt Orla could really eat it, even if she wanted to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean to tell me she jumps all the way up there and doesn't get her reward? The poor girl! After all that effort!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think Orla is as dumb as you think she is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only the victim and Sasha had security cards for this door. And Sasha was the only one who had entered the room up until the time of discovery.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... It won't be easy, but we can do this! Kein Problem! Sasha was devastated by Mr. Shipley's death. That means the true culprit has to be somebody else. So, chin up, Boss! Onward and upward!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As the boss, shouldn't I be the one giving her a pep talk?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, there's a cannon in the shape of a shark! I'd love to try firing that thing! Boom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are these cannonballs supposed to look like fish eggs or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? But why fish eggs? Why not baby sharks? Think about how crazy it would be to have sharks go flying through the air! Watch the thrilling life-or-death struggle as the little tykes fight to stay alive out of water! I can see it now! The drama! The mayhem! The whirlwind of teeth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A tornado of sharks? Not even Hollywood could conjure up something that insane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the control panel for that crane apparatus. There sure are a lot of buttons...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When I see this many buttons, I start to get fidgety.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know what you mean. You start itching to push them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nah, I start itching to make a psychological study of people who want to push buttons!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Need I remind you that I'm your boss, not your guinea pig?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The victim fell to his death and was kept down at the bottom of the pool. But Orla brought him up to the edge of the pool with her lifesaver trick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if Orla was actually trying to save him? I'm convinced she knocked down the equipment to call for help, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I bet that's what really happened. Because she loved him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's use the hoist to go down to the bottom of the pool...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be Orla's bedroom. There's even a sofa and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla! Congratulations on your "not guilty" verdict! But... we have bad news... Now Sasha has been arrested instead.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweeeeet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla seems sad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sure she is. I can sense the sadness filling her heart. Don't worry, Orla! We'll save Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think Orla's wishing us good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla really seems to understand what we're saying.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She can't understand our words, but I bet she can understand our hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! Look at all that treasure! Those jewels and that crown are huge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They sure are. I guess everything is size "large" around here. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, everything is size "Orla."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I stand corrected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">A map, a compass... and a spooky, skull-shaped rock! Orla's room is filled with pirate pizzazz!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that skull rock seems out of place. It doesn't go with the other things...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, it does seem pretty weird to have a big skull rock next to your desk... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe Sasha wasn't finished arranging the set?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When it comes to Orla, Sasha doesn't seem like the type to leave something half done... Her state of mind when she put it there... That could be the key to this mystery! And I bet it's a mystery I can solve! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind that mystery. Let's get back to the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They called this the "Captain's Cabin" on TV! Every night, by the light of the lantern, Orla pores over her treasures. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Sounds more like a miserly housewife going over the family finances...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing special here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Is this a good time to get started, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Started with what?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">This is the crime scene, right? So this should be the perfect place to start forensicking!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hooray! I get to help! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. We'll need these...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... what's with the glasses, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not like they're a fashion statement! We need them to see if there's any blood! All right, Pearls. You spray the luminol wherever I need it, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Got it, Mr. Nick! I won't miss an inch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got your glasses on, everybody...? Good. Now to check out the bottom of the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh no! I'm so sorry! I got some on Orla by mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Calm down, Pearly! It's okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look! There are luminol reactions on Orla, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The poor thing was bleeding yesterday... The luminol must be showing her injuries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wait a minute. Ms. DePlume said the blood disappeared when Orla put on her hat. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? So shouldn't her injuries be under her hat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this blood isn't from Orla's injuries, then what could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are luminol reactions on Orla, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The poor thing was bleeding yesterday... The luminol must be showing her injuries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wait a minute. Ms. DePlume said the blood disappeared when Orla put on her hat. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? So shouldn't her injuries be under her hat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If this blood isn't from Orla's injuries, then what could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Look! I see something!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If your deductions are correct, Boss, I guess this luminol reaction means... ...that the victim hit this skull-shaped rock when he fell to his death...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If your deductions are correct, Boss, I guess this luminol reaction means... ...that the victim hit this skull-shaped rock when he fell to his death...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so. The luminol doesn't lie, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's about it for inside the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then let me just get a quick photo to remember the occasion by! It's not every day we get to see the bottom of an aquarium pool! Yeah! That's a good shot!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll mark where the luminol reactions were. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yay! My first collaborative work with Pearly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? I hear something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla...? Boss! Something's wrong with Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You're right! She's listless... and she's sinking!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh no! Maybe it's because of that luminol I got on her! Wh-What do we do, Mr. Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't do anything for her ourselves! Let's get Dr. Crab!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll run and get him!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">What's Orla's condition?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's listless and sinking! Maybe she's unconscious?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">The pool is drained. Son of a gun! Who did this?! She'll drown unless we do something. ...Here. Give me a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Us?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No, I meant the Steel Samurai. Of course you! Just help me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What...? A-All right! What do you want us to do?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">There's no time to fill the pool to get her up to the top. Get the orca stretcher! It's a piece of black cloth with a skull and crossbones on it. Looks like a pirate flag. When the stretcher is ready, press the hoist button!  </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay! We're on it!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No time for chit-chat! Get going on that stretcher! Both Orla's right- and left-brain hemispheres are completely asleep now! She'll drown if we don't do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does the stretcher look like again?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">It's a piece of black cloth with a skull and crossbones on it. Looks like a pirate flag. Once the stretcher is ready, press the button on the control panel to move the hoist! And hurry! I have to get back to prepping her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this pirate flag is a stretcher for the orca, huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We can't use it with all this stuff on it! Let's clear it off!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Good! Now push the hoist button and lower the stretcher! The control panel is on the wall to your right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is no time to be examining this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! This must be the button to move the hoist...! Dr. Crab! The stretcher is ready!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Good! Let's get it under Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'll take it from here. Stand back. I have to treat her immediately... Hmm... There's something in her stomach...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">There. I got it all out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Will Orla be all right, Dr. Crab?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Yes, she'll be fine. She's just sleeping now. Orcas are mammals, so they won't die if they're out of the water for a little while. But their own weight puts stress on their organs, and their skin starts to dry out. I put some of my special handmade cream on her skin as an emergency measure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Feel better soon, Orla...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, if only I hadn't gotten that luminol on her...! </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Luminol? Nah, no problem there. That stuff just washes right off. Orla's condition has nothing to do with you, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really? Then what is wrong with Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I don't need to share that information with you people! It's none of your business. ...I have to get back to my rounds, so I'll leave the rest to the crew. Please keep an eye on Orla while I rouse up some crew members.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dr. Crab sure is acting funny... He seems to be hiding something... Maybe we should check on Orla's condition before the staff get here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we don't need to examine the bottom of the pool again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is the button we used to raise Orla in the stretcher. There's no need to push it now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla! Open your eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know how you feel, Athena, but we'd better let Orla rest right now. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">How did this happen? Mr. Wright! We have to examine her ourselves, right now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wish we could, but we're lawyers, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But there must be something we can do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we can investigate the cause of her condition. <thought>Didn't we have evidence that might tell us something about the cause...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all those pirate hats! Orla must really love those things.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The pirate hat, the star above her eye, and her white mustache are her trademarks! Without those things, she'd look just like any other orca.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even with a hat, she still looks like any other orca to me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet no ordinary orca could do that lifesaver trick! Hmph! How could you lump Orla in with all the other orcas like that, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. I forgot how much of a fan Athena is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, there's a poster of Mr. Rimes here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Wanted," huh? Very piratey. Looks like they list the staff's likes and nicknames and other stats, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And there's a reward amount listed, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A reward?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, they have this special event where they give you a prize for tagging a staff member. The bigger the reward listed, the better the prize. The crew tries hard not to get tagged... Sounds like my type of event! I would totally DOMINATE in a game like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Her competitive fire is starting to blaze out of control.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We should check out the contents of Orla's stomach... I guess... Hey, I see something mixed in with the fish.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks like a medicine capsule. There's something written on it. I think it says... "3 Zs"... What would it be doing in Orla's stomach? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what kind of medicine it is? Let's ask Dr. Crab. It might have something to do with Orla's condition!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe we'd better not ask. He must've noticed it himself, yet he didn't mention it. I think he's hiding something about Orla's condition. If we show him the capsule, he might try to take it away from us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I guess he was acting pretty sketchy. Okay, let's look into it ourselves, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. When we get back to the office, we can ask for Apollo's help.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess that wraps up our investigation here. Orla still isn't fully awake yet... Oh, here comes some staff! Looks like they're going to put Orla back into the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I guess they're going to fill the pool back up. I bet that will take awhile... Well, I guess we can leave Orla in the staff's capable hands now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Right! So, where to now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's head to the show stage next. If we're lucky, the police will be done with the place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're starting to get quite a bit of evidence. I still can't figure out who the culprit is, though...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe we should look for information in other places besides the crime scene! Investigating is key, but questioning people is vital, too! I know! Let's make it a competition to see which of us can find the best evidence! The loser buys the winner a glass of OJ!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Fine. <thought>Whatever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why are the Swashbuckler Spectacular songs Ms. DePlume and I know different? I get the feeling it has something to do with this case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Why would there be two songs...? It must mean something...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hate it when I don't know the answer! I'm going to go for a little run to let off steam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, wait! Better not. You might forget what made you want to let off steam in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we already examined this area, but let's take another look around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the capsule from Orla's stomach, isn't it? It says "3 Zs" on it. I wonder what this drug does?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know, but maybe it had something to do with Orla's mysterious condition.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who would do such a thing to Orla?! If I get my hands on them, I'll... I'll rip them to shreds, that's what I'll do!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just stick to lawful acts, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Wright Anything Agency">Talk</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you like to help out with the investigation, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You bet I would! What do you want me to work on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Let's see... Do I actually have anything for him to do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay... And it's suddenly crickets...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I know, Boss! Let's have Apollo look at the evidence we collected!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, good idea. He might notice something that will help us win the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, there's something I'd like your help with.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have work for me?! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you have this capsule checked out? I think it's some kind of medicine. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure thing, Mr. Wright! I'll go to a hospital or something and have somebody take a look. Let's see... I'm pretty sure the closest one is Hickfield Clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good luck, Apollo. And thanks. I guess we should head back to the aquarium and check out the show stage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is where they hold the Swashbuckler Spectacular, huh... Looks like the police are done with their work here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're sorry we couldn't prevent her from getting arrested... ...but, as her lawyers, we'll do everything we can for her.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ Sorry I got upset... If there's anythin' I can do to help Sasha, just say the word. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Marlon, you can trust in Mr. Nick. I'm going to do what I can, too, with this forensicking kit! I'm going to cover this whole area with forensicking!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Thatta girl, Small Fry! You can have free rein of this place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I want to check this place out, but I'd better talk to Mr. Rimes, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hear you helped Sasha with the cleaning, Mr. Rimes.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, not really "helped." I was just takin' care of the orca here while she cleaned. Sasha felt bad for making Orla stay up so late, so she asked me to give her a snack. It was a little bit less than her ordinary meals, but she seemed satisfied. Oh, yeah. And I put Orla on the transport stretcher, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Transport stretcher?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">See that hoist up there on the right? The stretcher can be suspended from it. This stage show is right next to the orca pool room... ...and we use the hoist to move the orca or cargo between the two areas. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the rail we saw in the orca pool room runs all the way here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Why? Did ya wanna take a ride?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aerial investigation, huh? Sounds good to me! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. That's okay. <thought>I like my investigations on sweet terra firma.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Actually, the hoist can only be operated from the orca pool room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, that's right. I remember seeing the hoist control panel in there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">So, I'm sorry, but I can't give ya a ride without somebody on the other end. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No need to be sorry. <thought>Whew... Dodged that bullet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If it wasn't Ms. Buckler or Orla... who else could've killed Mr. Shipley?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, I know Sasha is innocent, but I'm not so sure about the orca... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? But we proved her innocence in court this morning. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">But a few days ago, that orca attacked Sasha right here in the show pool! I saw that orca take Sasha's body into her mouth and squeeze her chest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her chest...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">They were probably practicing the lifesaver trick. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">But Sasha was being crushed so bad, she couldn't even blow the whistle. I wanted to help her right away, but... I hate to admit it, but I froze. I... I'm a weak man. I can't protect anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I doubt there are many people who would pit themselves against an orca.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Everybody tried to talk her out of it, but she wouldn't give up on practicin'. When we said Orla could kill her, she said she trusted Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... While everybody else seems to think Orla is a killer... </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">How can ya trust a creature that can't speak? You can't even know what it's thinkin'.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But with orcas and dolphins, you can have communication of the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say Ms. Buckler was mad... Was it because of the new show?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ugh... Me and my big mouth. Okay, but ya never heard it from me! There was a rumor that the captain wasn't gonna let Sasha be in the new show. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaaaaaat?! But why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I dunno. It was just a rumor. I don't know if it was true...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Mr. Shipley was going to do the show all by himself?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't even imagine the show without Ms. Buckler! It would be like, "Where's the beef?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is she trying to say it would be like bones without any meat on them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sasha wanted to go back to the old Swashbuckler Spectacular. But now that the captain's gone... who knows what's gonna happen with the show...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! There's a skeleton adrift!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh. It's just a prop. Were you really scared?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little bit... <thought>...by your screaming.</thought> Is this skeleton an enemy defeated by Orla's pirates?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, he's an informant named The Skeleton Kid. A dashing, spirited character, neither friend nor foe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying he's alive in the show?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This galleon was in the Swashbuckler Spectacular, too, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at that cute figurehead! It looks just like Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is cute, but it looks like it's also a cannon.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The enemy lets their guard down and then, blam! Very piratey, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought Orla and Sasha were supposed to be the good guys?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should do the same thing in court! Lure 'em in and then, blam! Present evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think the judge would appreciate any "blamming" in his court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at this pool! It's huge! So this is where they do the Swashbuckler Spectacular. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">This show pool is the same depth as the orca pool. They practice the tricks in the orca pool, and then do the real show here. Are ya interested in the Swashbuckler Spectacular?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, of course! I've only seen it on TV, though.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, I'm new here, so I've never even seen it once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena is a big fan. She watches the recording over and over. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I love the show and the ocean! Standing here makes me feel like I'm at the beach!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Especially with it open to the sky. You can even hear the sound of the surf nearby. Why don't you take a dip in the pool?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! I can?! In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! What are ya talkin' about?! You can't swim here! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were just joking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right...... O-Of course! I was just joking, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell me she was actually going to do it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This ladder only goes down to the surface of the water.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it's not like a public pool. Everybody who gets into this pool knows how to swim. Just like in the courtroom! It's sink or swim in there! A newbie could really get hurt. You know, like last time in court... I could've really gotten injured. I was an inch away from getting attacked by a witness. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... A trial with Apollo can be a pretty dangerous affair...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We saw this same device in the orca pool room, too, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, we used it to lift Orla when she was on the stretcher. In the show, Sasha makes her grand entrance by hanging from this thing! Ooh! We should think of a cool, grand entrance for us, too! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've always wanted to burst into the middle of somebody else's trial with a loud bang!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've always wanted to crash in through the ceiling! I bet that would really knock the socks off the judge and the gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just what exactly was this girl learning while she was in Europe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This colorful sign... Did Ms. Bucker [sic] make it?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Wow! How did ya know? Yeah, that sign is for the new show. Before she went to clean, she painted it and left it to dry. She told me to keep an eye on it while I was takin' care of the orca. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Isn't that the skull rock there on the right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, is the skull rock a part of the set for the new show?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If they were going to use it in the show, what's it doing in the orca pool?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This sign is so eye-catching, with all those twinkling stars!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I think they're supposed to be starfish. It's for the pirate show, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... A few of them look more like leaves to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sasha put so much effort into makin' this sign for the new show... No wonder she was mad about what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(Huh? I wonder what he's talking about? I'd better ask...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing special here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We already checked this out, but another round wouldn't hurt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">With this flyer, you can get a penguin sleep mask the next time you come in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah? That would be nice, especially if it's free.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That'd be perfect for taking a nap at the office after going for a run or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I prefer you DIDN'T take naps at the office, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, I feel ya! Sometimes I fall asleep when I'm feedin' the animals.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Heh heh. We're kindred spirits, my sister. Kindred spirits. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Two peas in a pod! Birds of a feather!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suddenly feel so alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, about this fish...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I'm the master keeper! No way you can beat me! You're a pro lawyer, but an amateur feeder! Ya'll [sic] ready for a feeding throw-down? Rifle c'mon! Time to defend da crown!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Uh, it doesn't look like Rifle's coming...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............I guess not, huh? Sorry about all that "throw-down" stuff, then... I just wanted to show ya the inner secrets of animal feedin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are "inner secrets"?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">You know, stuff like how to debone a fish. Great care goes into each animal's food. Then of course there's the way of tossin' the food to 'em. It's different for each one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see. Sorry to have bothered you with mundane questions from the uninitiated.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">That's Sasha's calendar. ...Sorry I didn't tell ya sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess you were worried about Ms. Buckler. It's understandable.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I dunno why she was supposed to meet with the captain... ...but I know she definitely didn't kill him. She'd never do anythin' like that. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We know that. And we're going to prove it in court!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">If ya mess up, I'm gonna write a rap dissin' you two! And even before it comes out on CD, I'm gonna play it all over the place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What does "dissing" mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">To "diss" somebody means to insult them or put them down. It's short for "disrespect." </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ouch. That's harsh.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I'm new here, so I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't really think being "new here" has anything to do with it in this instance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I found some peculiar fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pearls! I almost forgot she's been "forensicking" for me all this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Who's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill! What are you doing here?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Just some business to attend to.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Prosecutor Blackquill insisted, so I brought him along to get a little exercise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it business with us...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...No, not you. My business is with that animal keeper there. Marlon Rimes... You will be a witness for the prosecution tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ya gotta be kiddin'! Why would I wanna testify against Sasha?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What you "want" does not matter. ...Now, come along.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">But if I leave, who's gonna feed the orca? The other animal keepers are too scared to go near her now.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, maybe I can help? I'm concerned about Orla's health... and this way, I can stay close and look after her. I can feed her and do a telecast, too, if you need me too! I'll do anything to help!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like Pearls wants to do something nice for Orla and make sure she's okay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Small Fry! Are you trippin'? That orca is... dangerous, ya know. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. I'll be fine. I'm just happy to help. Oh! But I don't have a TV phone... I won't be able to contact you if I have to do a telecast... Marlon, may I please borrow yours?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What? ...Sure, Small Fry. Anythin' for you! Especially when you're goin' out of your way to help like this. I dunno if I'm gonna testify, but I guess I can at least hear what the police have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Thanks for your cooperation! Now, justice will be served... with a strategy meeting!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrr! C'mon, Mr. Wright! Let's get back to our investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. How sad. The police have already investigated all there is to investigate. Your efforts are a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing we do to try and save our client is a waste of time, Prosecutor Blackquill. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Today, the orca. Tomorrow, Sasha Buckler. You intend to save them both? Hmph. You say you "believe" in your clients, but isn't money really your true motivation? Why not admit you're only doing this for your own benefit? I could understand that much more readily than your empty, righteous talk. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our own benefit?! That's not why we're doing it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, Athena. Try not to let him get to you.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">All right! We should be off, Prosecutor Blackquill! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrr! I've never been so insulted! Be right back! I need some water to wash away the anger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. She hit Prosecutor Blackquill with that water... He doesn't seem to care, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm... I guess prosecutors these days are more about harsh monochrome than fancy frills...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, wait! What about those peculiar fingerprints you said you found, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. I'll tell you all about them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So tell me about this big discovery you made.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, I don't know if it's a "big" discovery, but... ...I found some odd fingerprints on the pool ladder over there. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... So what's so peculiar about them?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, they're on the left side of the ladder, but they're right-hand prints. Wouldn't a person usually hold the left side of a ladder with their left hand? Plus, I think they were made from above by grasping the ladder with the right hand. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Now that you mention it, that IS strange. I wonder whose prints they are?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I compared them with the prints on file, and they turned out to be Marlon's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did he manage to leave prints in such an awkward position?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So, Mr. Nick, was I helpful? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, you were. Thank you very much, Pearls. <thought>I don't know if they're related to the case yet, but I'll keep them in mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee. I bet Detective Fulbright doesn't know about these prints! I imagine their search wasn't as thorough here as it was at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're probably right. I'm sure they checked everything at the actual crime scene. But I guess they can't do forensics on every inch of the rest of the aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we could, thanks to Pearly! And now we have a new piece of information!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh, you're embarrassing me, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! This pool is about the same size as the orca pool! This is where they do the Swashbuckler Spectacular.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're a big fan, aren't you, Athena? You watch that recording every chance you get. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I get so excited watching the pirates do battle! It makes me want to put just as much passion into our battles in court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I like to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe I should get a pirate outfit to wear in the courtroom? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think you have to go quite that far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This colorful sign... So Sasha was the one who made it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup. Before she went to clean, she apparently painted it and left it to dry. There's a picture of that skull rock for the new show on the right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If they were going to use it in the show, what's it doing in the orca pool?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's really eye-catching, with all those twinkling starfish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think you can say "twinkling" when you're talking about starfish... Besides, a few of them look more like leaves to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're right. Maybe Sasha forgot to finish painting them?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I'm so happy you get to be a lawyer again, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. Thanks. I let our friends know I was back, too.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wish we could all get together. It's been quite a while! Maybe we should throw you a surprise party to celebrate your comeback.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be really nice. But if you tell me about it, it won't be a surprise, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! B-But we could spring it on you after you had forgotten, and still surprise you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was really looking forward to seeing the Swashbuckler Spectacular... It's such a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I bet you would've really enjoyed it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But I was really happy to see such a large marine animal! It was quite an experience! ...I still have yet to see a blue whale, though, the largest marine animal of them all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, uh... I doubt there are any blue whales at the aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh my! Did you go fishing, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, this is for Rifle. We were asked to feed her.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh, that sounds like fun! Do you think she would take food from me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sure she would--from you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...So what you're really trying to say is that Rifle wouldn't take food from ME, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not what I meant. <thought>That IS what I meant, though.</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! I won't be bested! Pearly, it's ON!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What? What's "on"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now, Athena. Let's be adults about this. You've got poor Pearls here all confused.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Isn't it cute? I really love this calendar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's shaped like a penguin. It is pretty cute, isn't it? Maybe I should buy a calendar for the office before I leave. I always run out of room to write appointments in my planner.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't you just put your appointments on your phone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not very good at using electronic devices...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, neither am I. Hee hee! We have something in common!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw, now I feel left out.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You know I'd do anything I could to help you! ...But I'm afraid I don't really know anything about that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right, Pearls. No worries.</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, it's Rifle! We've got to catch her!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Don't worry. She's being a good girl right here on my lap. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha! Well, I'm glad she's been found. <thought>I forgot we were looking for her, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Yeah, thanks again to Pearly... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think somebody's jealous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, I think I'll go talk to the staff about Orla. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Good luck, Pearls! And thanks again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess we're done with things here. What do you want to do next?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How about if we have Apollo check out our mystery evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, that's right. We haven't done that yet.</thought> Good idea. Let's stop by the office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, you're back! How is the investigation going?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's going pretty well, but there are still things we need answers to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let me know if there's anything I can do to help!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It has been quite a while. Let's stop by the detention center and see. We have something to deliver to her, too, don't forget.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They ought to be done with Sasha by now, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True. Let's stop by the detention center and let her know we can take on her defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dr. Crab! We found Rifle!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No answer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess nobody's here. Why don't we come back later?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, Boss! Chin up! We have to lift Sasha's spirits!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha! I like your enthusiasm! </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ahoy there, me hearties! Thank ye for comin'! Arr! I be in good spirits! Worry not about me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............She's trying to cheer us up.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Well, that went over like a lead balloon... I was trying to make up for all your trouble. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the two of you need to take it easy. <thought>I guess they both had the same idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We came to let you know that we can take on your defense, if you'll have us!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! ............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Is something wrong? <thought>Why is she hiding from us?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">P-Prosecutor Blackquill said... ...th-that you two would... abandon me... But here you are... t-to my rescue...! That's why... I-I'm so happy...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like she's crying back there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Of course we wouldn't abandon you...! Uuuuuugh... Sasha...! Don't cry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the two of you need to take it easy. <thought>Great, now I have crybabies in stereo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay! I'm all right now! Thank you for taking on my case! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We're glad to do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, now that you're smiling again, we have a few questions to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the night before the murder, did you enter the orca pool room alone?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. On July 20th, from 3:00 to 6:00 AM, I was there cleaning and organizing. The captain and I were actually supposed to clean together starting at 4:00 AM, but... ...we got in a fight. I couldn't face him, so I went an hour early and started cleaning. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What does the orca pool room cleaning involve?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Well, first we have to move Orla to the show stage pool before we get started.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Rimes mentioned he took care of Orla in the show stage pool.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">After Orla was moved, I drained the pool and rearranged the equipment and props. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And did the captain ever show up?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">4:00 AM came and went, but he never showed. I bet he was mad at me... I wish I'd apologized to him, instead of being all prickly and angry like a scorpionfish...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm glad we could prove Orla's innocence, but we didn't know you would get arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ha ha ha. As long as Orla is safe, I'm happy. I'm so glad I found you two! You guys are the best!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm glad you found us, too! YOU'RE the best, Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I never imagined Orla's tricks would ever be used to commit a crime...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us more about the lifesaver trick?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, sure! There's a little speaker on the captain's clothes and on the training dummies. That speaker can emit sound waves. When a trick command is issued with the whistle... ...Orla uses the sound waves as a guide to find the person she's supposed to rescue. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. Does anybody else know about how that trick works? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The entire crew knows about it. But it takes quite a bit of practice to be able to command the lifesaver trick. It wouldn't be easy to do for anybody who wasn't a trainer. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that's why they suspected Sasha...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">And Orla can only perform one trick per signal. In other words, she can't perform two tricks at a time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... So she can't do the singing trick and the lifesaver trick at the same time...? So what was that song Ms. DePlume heard?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Mr. Wright! I just remembered! We have to return something to Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah. You're right. <thought>I have it right here in evidence... And we have to give Sasha that item Detective Fulbright gave us, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why were you arguing with Mr. Shipley?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The captain knew about my heart condition, and he was worried about me. So he said he wouldn't put me in the new show. See? I'm not in the new flyer. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're right! It's just Orla and the new adversary, Redstache.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I was so upset and frustrated... I was still crying when I went to do the cleaning. And I cried for quite a while before I drained the pool, too. But then, you know what? Orla did a trick to try and cheer me up. She acted out the scene where she defeats the giant octopus by spiking a ball at it! She spiked that ball so hard, she even ended up breaking off one of the octopus's legs. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What a dramatic way to cheer up a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">So that's why we argued, because he wasn't going to put me in the new show. But I was determined to be in the show yesterday. It was July 20th, you see... The anniversary of the death of the trainer before me... ...Azura Summers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The person Norma DePlume wrote about in her book. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I wanted to explain to the audience that it was an accident, not murder. That's why I wanted... that's why I NEEDED to be in that show so bad... So during the cleaning, I moved the skull rock to the orca pool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It was a key prop. I figured the new show couldn't go on without it. I thought they'd be forced to switch back to the old show. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... That was pretty extreme...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Sasha moved the skull rock to the orca pool at the time of the cleaning... And if there's blood on that rock... ...then that must mean that the victim's death occurred after the rock was moved.</thought> Around what time did you finish up the cleaning?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It was about 6:00 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that places suspicion on whoever met with the victim after 6:00 AM...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Azura Summers was the trainer before you?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right! She was a year older than me. She taught me all about how to command Orla. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet Azura and Sasha were like sisters to one another.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">She was the one who taught me the signals for the singing and lifesaver tricks, too. After she died... I swore on this charm... I vowed to become a great trainer someday, just like Azura!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is that charm?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It's a keepsake to remember Azura by. She always wore it. She told me once that she and her boyfriend had matching charms... I never found out who he was, so I couldn't give this one to him... I've had it ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're keeping the memory of Ms. Summers alive.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The captain always carried around a memento of Azura, too: her walkie-talkie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Did the victim have a walkie-talkie on him? Maybe I should show Sasha the victim's photos and see what she has to say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you mean by "protect Orla from the ship's doctor"?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You know, Herman Crab. Ever since the accident a year ago, he's been completely different. When Azura died, he said he was going to "euthanize the orca"! Before that, he always used to say that euthanizing animals was a despicable act! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Euthanize the orca...? That's horrible...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">They all thought that Azura's death was the orca's fault. Nobody believed in her but me... The ship's doctor always keeps poison to euthanize the orca with on hand. And if Orca had been pronounced guilty in yesterday's trial, he would've used it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was going to put her down right away? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That ship's doctor was close with both the captain and Azura, you know... I think he hates Orla...</line>
<line speaker="Sasha">Do you two want to be in the Swashbuckler Spectacular?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have regular people participate?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Of course! We even have a special tour for people who want to be in it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What roles would we play if we said yes?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Let's see... The roles of a blue seahorse and a yellow sea slug are available!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judging by the colors, I must be the seahorse.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And I'm the sea slug?! No way! I won't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But sea slugs are all fluttery and beautiful, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They're... beautiful? In that case, I'll do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her mind is pretty much an open book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ha ha ha! I hope we can do a show together someday!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, have you been using the whistle I gave you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! But I can't get Orla to do any tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe you can command that huge creature. That's pretty impressive, Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Pretty cool, huh? I bet there aren't too many people who can say... ...they literally get to "whistle while they work."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That must be pretty nice for you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But Orla is the one who's impressive, really, not me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's easy to see how much you care about Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You two are a good team.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What...?! But you and I are a great team, right? We can top that!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You be givin' me a fish?! So you be challengin' me to a fight, eh?! Arr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! No! What kind of rule is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's how it goes in the Swashbuckler Spectacular! Present a fish. Start fighting. The gauntlet--I mean, the fish--is thrown down, and the glorious battle begins! Ooh, you're so cool when you're up there jumping and slashing!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Arr! Belay that talk, li'l lassie! Compliments will get ye naught!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! You sound just exactly like a real pirate! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena just eats this stuff up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is your calendar, isn't it, Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Huh? No, mine's at the aquarium. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah? Mr. Rimes said he found this one in the nap room. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Huh. I didn't think anybody else at the aquarium used a calendar like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(The owner of this calendar had </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Grr! That lady! Do you know what kind of terrible things she wrote about Orla?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you knew about this book?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah. I wish I didn't, but all kinds of people kept showing it to me. I tell you, I've haddock enough of that woman and her book! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, okay. I see what you did there...</thought> So what do you think about what happened that day?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">...It must've been some kind of accident. I believe in Orla's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can sense you really do believe in her, from the bottom of your heart. Well, we believe in her, too! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. After all, she was proven "not guilty" in this case, too. We believe in the both of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Fulbright asked us to give you this medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Arr! That bilge-suckin' blaggard had the spine to send me a gift?! Dread Pirate Nostache! Don't stand there gapin' like a weak li'l minnow! Have at ye! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, a real swashbuckling battle! ...Arr! If it be a fight ye want, a fight ye shall have!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you two please not drop into show mode out of the blue?! </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay, sorry about that. ...Yeah, I'll take that medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's acting kind of funny...</thought> What is the medicine for, by the way?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ugh... Well, I guess I can't keep it a secret from you two... I... I suffer from a heart condition. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">A h-heart condition...? Then you'd better get to the hospital right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take it easy, Athena. She's in detention, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Don't worry. it's not as serious as it sounds. They can fix it with surgery...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">NOT SERIOUS?! A heart condition is a heart condition! Don't tell us not to worry!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, I'm sorry... The captain was just as mad at me the day before yesterday... We both got so worked up, at one point, it was like a shark-eat-shark situation. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew. That sounds scary...</thought> Do you mind if I ask more about that fight?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">! How did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Fulbright gave it to us.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Arr! That bilge-suckin' blaggard had the spine to send me a gift?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaat?! S-Sasha...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Dread Pirate Nostache! Don't stand there gapin' like a weak li'l minnow! Have at ye! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arr! If it be a fight ye want, a fight ye shall have!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you two please not drop into show mode out of the blue?! </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oops! Sorry about that. Now what were we talking about? Orla...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Hmm. I get the feeling Sasha was trying to divert the topic away from that medicine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim didn't appear to have a walkie-talkie with him at the time of his death. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Huh? But I talked to the captain on his walkie-talkie before I started the cleaning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's no walkie-talkie shown in these crime scene photos. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I don't understand it... The captain always kept that walkie-talkie with him...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the culprit took it away?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Maybe... But what would be the point of that? I'd better organize the data I have on the victim in the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The captain always kept that walkie-talkie by his side. It was the walkie-talkie Azura used right up until her death. In the middle of the show, the orca brought Azura up to the surface in her mouth. She left tooth marks in Azura's walkie-talkie... The captain said he always kept that walkie-talkie with him so he'd never forget...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the walkie-talkie was really important to the victim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But... now the captain is dead, too... I'm the only one left who can protect Orla from the ship's doctor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Protect Orla from the ship's doctor? I wonder what Sasha means?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Sorry. Sea creatures are the only things I know anything about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right. Don't worry about it. <thought>Gee, I didn't mean to put her in a funk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess we'd better look into Dr. Crab a little more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, let's go see Dr. Crab!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just thinking the same thing. We have a lot of questions to ask him. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's Pearls... and Rifle. What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Rifle came in here, so I followed her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, that's right. We were supposed to deliver Rifle to him. I completely forgot.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Rifle!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">You silly mother penguin! What if you injured my spectacular, genius brain?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Dr. Crab...? Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Huh? Oh. It's you people. I see you brought Rifle for me. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Rifle was really laying into you...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, she hates me because she thinks I took her baby away from her.</line>
<line speaker="Sniper">Peep!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree!* *kree!* *kree, kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, Rifle looks so... happy... Is she actually playing with Sniper...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree, kree, kree!* *kree, kree!* *kree, kree, kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Stop all this cacophony!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The biological parent and the caregiver parent, locked in a struggle over the child...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">*panting* Do you think you could hold this silly mother penguin down for me?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">All right! I will try!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree*... *kree, kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what are you doing? <thought>I think Rifle just threw something up.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Oh, I'm getting food for Sniper out of Rifle. Mother penguins stock up food for their babies in their stomachs. They break it down in there so that it's easier for the baby to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. You sure know a lot about animals. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">...You're trying to pick a fight with me again, aren't you, young lady? Yes, I know a lot about animals. I am a licensed veterinarian. Hmm... Rifle certainly is in a bad mood, even for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is Rifle okay?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Hold on. I'm checking her now. Girl in the strange outfit... Could you turn Rifle over on her back, please?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">All right. Rifle, I'm just going to turn you over, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hmm? What's this? The bottom of her feet are pink. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no! Wh-What kind of sickness is that?! We have to get her to a doctor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, get a hold of yourself. Dr. Crab is a veterinarian, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...It's just something she stepped in, by the looks of it. It's her stomach that's the problem. There's still something in there... Here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree, kree*... *KREEEEEEE!*</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Hmm. Looks like she swallowed something odd. I know this penguin will eat anything, but where did she pick up something like this? Son of a gun... I'll have to talk to Marlon about her care... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dr. Crab, may we see what was in Rifle's stomach?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Huh? Please be quiet. I'm busy right now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Busy? But you're just staring at that weird machine. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'm checking to see when Rifle ingested the foreign object!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He just keeps looking at that machine. He won't even glance our way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm really curious to know more about his monitoring system.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us about the monitoring system you have here?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">It's a collection of electronic medical records for all the creatures here. With this system and the camera footage, I can monitor the creatures 24/7. I won't tell you any more than that. It's private, company business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But medical records are usually just a history of past medical exams and data. I never heard of any that could monitor 24/7. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Good point, Mr. Lawyer. I can see there's no fooling you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would you want to fool me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy's going to be a tough nut to crack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">............I have my reasons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? This looks like the charm Sasha had...</thought> Dr. Crab, do you know anything about this charm?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Charm...? Hey! Leave that alone! That belonged to Azura! What was Azura's charm doing in Rifle's stomach...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's odd... When Sasha was telling us about the charm earlier... ...Sasha said that she had Azura's charm. But that charm is still at the detention center... Hey, wait a minute! Didn't Sasha say Azura and her boyfriend had matching charms? So this second charm must be the one that belongs to Azura's boyfriend.</thought> Dr. Crab, is it possible this charm belongs to Azura's boyfriend...?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I refuse to talk about such personal details of the deceased. Subject closed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right... <thought>He sure is touchy when it comes to Azura...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Azura Summers... Yesterday was the anniversary of her death, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...That's right. She was killed by the orca. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you really think Orla killed her? I... I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Who can say if the orca did it on purpose? But the fact remains that she killed Azura. I was right there, the day of her death a year ago... I saw the orca bite Azura with my own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But... is that really the whole truth of what happened...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess only Orla knows what really happened... both a year ago and this time...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That charm... Azura always wore it. It meant a lot to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Azura Summers... The trainer who died a year ago, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Was Ms. Summers special to you, Dr. Crab?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hmm? What are you talking about? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I'm sorry! I just thought I sensed a hint of romantic feelings...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">She was my co-worker. Nothing more than that. Now, if you ask me any more inane questions, I will lose my patience!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry about that. I guess I touched a nerve. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems everybody here at the aquarium loved Azura Summers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">2 PSYCHE-LOCKS</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want you to tell me about the monitoring system here.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">You don't let up, either, do you, Mr. Lawyer? They're just electronic medical records and feeds from security cameras. With these, I can monitor all of the animals 24/7. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And I say that's not true. I have proof that you can't monitor the animals 24/7 with this system.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">The only thing that evidence proves is that you are mistaken, Mr. Lawyer. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... <thought>I guess I got it wrong.</thought> But I still say it can't be true. And that's because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security camera doesn't begin recording until 10 AM. If that's the case, how could you possibly monitor the animals 24/7?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Okay. You got me. I guess that was a pretty weak explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">You're right. I guess I can't monitor the animals 24/7. But if I see anything unusual on the camera feeds, I can spring to action right away. And if I can examine an animal, I can usually tell exactly what is going on with them. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. He's really confident in his abilities.</thought> But I still say you can't do that 24/7. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">But I'm here at the aquarium most of the time. And I can go anywhere at any time to examine an animal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anywhere? I say that's not true, either. I have proof that there's a place you can't go! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Crab:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! <thought>I guess I got it wrong...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">I'm telling you, I can go anywhere at any time to examine an animal. Why are you trying to argue that I can't?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because I know it can't be true. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only people who have access to the orca pool room are the owner and Sasha. So how can you say you monitor all of the animals?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun. So you knew about the security card, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Yes, tighter security was imposed on the orca a year ago as a precaution. Due to Sasha's objections, I wasn't allowed to have a card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she was trying to protect Orla from him...</thought> So you're monitoring the animals with a system that's "private, company business." But I have to insist you tell me about this monitoring system. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Now YOU'RE trying to pick a fight with me?! Very well. I suppose it's only fitting that the spoils go to the victor. I'll tell you about Shipshape Aquarium's ecological data organization system.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what does that machine you were using do?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">It's a system of ecological data organization developed in Europe. I call it the TORPEDO! What do you think? Pretty impressive name, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Torpedo"? As in "Man the battle stations!" and all that?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No, no! It's the name I gave to this data organization system. "TORPEDO." It stands for "TeleObservation Realtime PErtinent Data Organizer." </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Quite a name... I wonder if it's super admin restricted desktop access pass-protected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">The TORPEDO collects data through sensors placed on or near the subjects. Temperature, heartbeat, vocalizations, etc. It gathers this information 24 hours a day. All of this data is then sent to my terminal and these monitors. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! This TORPEDO sounds amazing! Does Rifle have a sensor on her, too?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Yes, she does. Where and what kind of sensor is attached depends on the animal. The penguins have theirs attached to the ID tag at the base of their flipper. The TORPEDO doesn't tell me where Rifle is when she escapes, though. It's hard to attach sensors to the orca or fish, so theirs are on the tanks themselves. Places where the creatures don't normally live, like the show stage, don't have sensors. ...Okay, here we go. It's telling me the time Rifle swallowed the foreign object... "Approximately 4:00 AM on July 20th"... What an odd time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was when Sasha was doing the cleaning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe that's why she wouldn't take my fish, because she was full from the night before. But at least Orla ate it, so that's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Orla ate another animal's food? That's odd. She's never done that before. And then she had that episode, too... I'd better take a look at her data... ...Huh? She didn't eat anything from the evening of the 19th to yesterday afternoon. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Rifle had a late-night snack, but Orla went hungry, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">It appears so... But let's see... She's been eating normally since yesterday afternoon. ...Come to think of it, Jack was supposed to feed Orla yesterday morning... Maybe he died before he had the chance...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm worried about Orla's condition. I'd better remember this TORPEDO data...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I still wonder why he wouldn't tell us about the TORPEDO...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Crab, why did you want to hide the existence of the TORPEDO system? </line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Well, it's a safe system that has been approved for use in other countries... ...but it hasn't been legally approved in this country yet. That's why I always carry this terminal around with me. It's not something I want the police poking their nose into...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean... you're breaking the law?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Which is why I was keeping it a secret. It would create a problem for the aquarium. I had Jack's permission. He felt the animals' care was more important than the legality. But we wanted to shield the rest of the staff, so we kept it a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But breaking the law is breaking the law!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...But, in some cases, lives can be saved by breaking the law. Do we simply allow the lives of our animals to be lost while we wait for laws to change? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Ugh. Now you're twisting things around...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to use this evidence during the trial tomorrow. But it may result in you and Shipshape Aquarium being brought up on charges...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, I followed my own convictions, and I have no regrets. You're only doing your job. I can't blame you for that, Mr. Lawyer. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I appreciate that.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Ah, you're interested in my TeleObservation Realtime PErtinent Data Organizer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "TORPEDO," huh? So it allows you to gather data and observe all the animals?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, Dr. Crab. The names you pick all seem to have something to do with weapons. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, I do make a hobby of collecting air guns in my spare time. I picked "Sniper" and "Rifle" from a list of over one hundred gun name candidates.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were some of the other names on the list?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">"Grenade" and "Launcher." "Revol" and "Ver." Things like that. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Couldn't you come up with anything a little cuter?! </line>
<line speaker="Crab">What? But those names are so cool! The young lady apparently just doesn't understand the masculine spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, well... You know... <thought>Apparently, I don't, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that sound? Another penguin...?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............That's my ringtone. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, Dr. Crab sure likes cute things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe he wanted it to sound like Sniper?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hello? Crab speaking... Son of a gun! You people again?! Stop harassing this aquarium! Orla was found not guilty! Why on earth should she be put down?! Huh? Come there on the 26th and explain? Fine. Just let me write it down in my... Son of a gun! Where did my calendar go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His calendar! Could he be talking about THAT calendar...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">...I realize that. If it comes to that, I'll use that drug to euthanize her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! He s-said, "euthanize her"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd better ask him more about this. <thought>And I should try presenting that calendar to him, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was that phone call from?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun. You heard that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who didn't hear that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">It was the Center for Dangerous Animal Control, calling with a demand. They said that the orca may have been found not guilty this time... ...but that if she ever attacked a human again, we would have to put her down. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Put her down?! But that's horrible! Did you agree to their demand?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Animals sometimes do attack humans. And, of course, humans sometimes do kill animals to protect themselves. If it comes to that, yes, as a veterinarian, I am prepared to carry out euthanization... ...using this poison.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh?! That capsule... It has the same letters on it as the one that was in Orla's stomach! Did Dr. Crab... try to kill Orla...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Crab, isn't this your calendar?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">! Yes, it's mine. What are you doing with it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes found it in the nap room. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Oh... I must've forgotten it there when I tried to get some rest... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sure is a cute calendar. I guess you're crazy about penguins?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Somebody gave it to me, okay?! Now, please don't tell anybody about it. It's embarrassing. Azura designed this calendar. This one here is a prototype. She designed a calendar for this year, and then she died before it went on sale... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Were you and Ms. Summers... romantically involved?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">What?! What gave you that idea?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just that I sensed... sadness in your heart when you talked about the calendar...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Of course we weren't romantically involved! I don't believe in romantic feelings!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He looks shaken, though...</thought> By the way, did you meet Mr. Shipley at 7:00 AM on July 20th, as scheduled?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............No. We were supposed to meet, but Jack didn't show up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that really true? Sasha finished cleaning the orca pool room at 6:00 AM. If Dr. Crab managed to get in the pool room somehow and meet with the victim... ...then he would have had the opportunity to kill Mr. Shipley!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please let me ask you one more question, Dr. Crab. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">What is it, Mr. Lawyer? You look so grave. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard something disturbing from the writer Norma DePlume...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">The center demanded that the aquarium put the killer whale down a year ago. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Put her down?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">But the aquarium owner refused their demand, saying it was an accidental death. But I hardly think a persistent organization like that would just give up and go away. I'm quite sure the power of money helped convince them! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Once a month, the owner and the vet disappear from this aquarium. And I came to find out that, each time, a large amount of money was being paid out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think Shipshape Aquarium might be keeping some kind of secret... ...and that it has something to do with the recent murder!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>F-Five Psyche-Locks?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">That writer... She just has to stick her nose in everyone's business. Son of a gun... I should have dealt with it all more carefully... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How am I ever going to remove all those locks?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sorry to interrupt, but Prosecutor Blackquill wants Dr. Crab. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Detective Fulbright! </line>
<line speaker="Crab">You again? You couldn't possibly have any more questions for me! </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, you see, we're having a little problem... We were going to call the animal keeper as a witness for the prosecution... ...but he's being very stubborn and refusing to testify. And so we thought we'd ask you to be a witness in tomorrow's trial!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Hmph. Did you really, now? Well, I'm not taking sides. I'll tell what I know. No more, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That would be fine! Now, if you would please come along with me!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, it looks like we'll have to continue our talk at the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know what secret you and this aquarium are hiding... ...but I'll uncover it if it'll help save Ms. Buckler.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Give it your best shot, then. I'll see you tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it looks like we'll be going up against Dr. Crab in tomorrow's trial. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet he'll be one tough customer. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, we'd better get our evidence organized for tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll have Athena hold on to the evidence I don't think I'll need in court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright! I went to Hickfield Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Apollo, use your indoor voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry about that! Anyway, I found out a lot, so I wanted to tell you right away! It turns out that mysterious capsule is a powerful sleeping drug. Apparently, the brand name is "3 Zs."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, yeah. It says "3 Zs" right on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And they said the Shipshape Aquarium vet recently bought a large quantity from them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The vet...! <thought>Dr. Herman Crab...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"3 Zs" is supposed to be for people. But Dr. Crab told them it would work on other mammals, like orcas and dolphins, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Dr. Crab's "euthanization poison"... was actually sleeping pills...? When Orla almost drowned today... was it because she'd been given sleeping pills...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I found out more than just about that capsule! Dr. Hickfield himself gave me some information. Shipshape Aquarium had someone on their staff named Azura Summers, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the one who died a year ago. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Azura Summers was getting a certain medication from Hickfield Clinic last year... ...the same heart medication as Sasha Buckler! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! <thought>Azura Summers had the same heart condition as Sasha...?</thought> Nice work, Apollo. Thank you. We'll be coming back to the office soon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay. Trucy and I will be here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we'd better get back to the office and get ready for tomorrow. What are you going to do, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I thought I'd stay overnight here and be with Orla and Rifle. I'll be ready for a telecast during the trial tomorrow! Good luck to both of you! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Pearly!! That way, when we prove Sasha's innocent she can see Orla right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd love to see Sasha and Orla back together again, both free and clear! But before that can happen, I have to prove Sasha's innocence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That looks like an old charm. Is it yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's evidence. But I have a charm of my own, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You do? Better keep it safe, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're talking about that locket, right? The pendant you keep in your pocket? ...The one with Trucy's picture in it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. So you knew about that, huh? I'm a little embarrassed, so don't tell Trucy about it, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I have enough evidence, but maybe I'd better think about it a little more.</thought></line>
</xml>