<xml>
<title>Turnabout Corner</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What a train wreck that was. I'm glad we made it out of that trial alive.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I had fun! And Wocky made it through the day, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Everyone was too obsessed with panties to bother with the real case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But it was good publicity! Imagine the crowd at my show tonight! You should come, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Amazing Mr. Hat will be making an appearance!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Hi, folks! I'll be here all week!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's about enough of him.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Hello...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! Ms. Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Thank you for today. The trial... went well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right! No problem!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Do you think Wocky will be OK?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, he's not guilty... yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Please, you have to help him! We're supposed to get married next month...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, congratulations! <thought>Gah, way to put the pressure on a guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Please let me know if there's anything I can do to help!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Some magic books are mixed in with the law books here. The magic books all look well-used, but the law books are just gathering dust. ...I feel kinda sorry for them. Maybe I'll read some next time I'm around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's Charley, the houseplant. They've had it for years, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's "Mr. Charley" to you! He's been here longer, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm sorry, Mr. Charley. He was raised by a tribe of heathens.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's saying something to the plant as she waters it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Charley forgives you. This time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is there anything else I might do to please His High Leafiness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A giant hoop used to levitate people. So, tell me, how does it work?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo... Don't you know you should never ask a magician to explain a trick? I mean, you're hardly better than Mr. Stickler!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I object to being placed in the same category as that panty-snatcher.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Enjoy the mystery! That's the way to appreciate magic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those boxes frighten me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I bet I'm the first magician to figure out these make great shelves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She does seem to be putting them to good use...</thought> But, if you ever want to put it back together, you have to take everything off.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... Don't worry, I'll clean it up soon... and then we'll try cutting you up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-Thanks, but I'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An old, sepia-tone photograph of a man in a silk hat. His outfit looks a lot like Trucy's, come to think of it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aren't those clothes the best? I had mine made to match! If you're going to be a magician, you gotta look the part!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy is big on appearances, I've found...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are all sorts of strange paraphernalia sitting on top of the piano. It seems a shame to have all these props and not do a trick or two.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You asked for it!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Heeeey, Mr. Righteous, was it? Wakka wakka!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Justice", Mr. Hat! "Apollo Justice".</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Just is? Apollo just is what? That's what I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you're hopeless!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Please, make it stop.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just let me know if you ever want a visit from Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Any other trick but that one, please...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A blue silk top hat, just like the one Trucy's wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's my trademark color! "Trucy Blue"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think you can trademark the color blue.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Standing out is everything when you're up on stage! Bet you didn't know you've got your own color, too, Apollo! "Crimson Justice"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You make me sound like some second-rate superhero.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">At least it's better than being a first-rate super zero!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A dish of plastic spaghetti like some restaurants put on display. Where did you get this, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was a birthday present from Daddy! I was so happy... You don't know how long I wanted one of these! I fell asleep with it, cradled in my arms, and the spaghetti bent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mental note: What she really wants for her next birthday: A bowl of plastic food...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A hot water pot sits on a magic table. Why is the stand for this table so flimsy looking?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Hmm. Maybe it looks better that way?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I was hoping for a more professional explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well... Maybe to show that there's no tricks involved?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Not bad.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still think it's just that it looks better that way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure about marrying into the Kitaki Family...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I'm fine with it. And I love Wocky with all my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aw, that's so sweet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So it doesn't bother you that you'll be, erm... ...Married to the mob?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I don't think so... My parents are against it, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Say! Where did you and Wocky first meet, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Good question... Ms. Tiala doesn't look like the type to have gangster connections...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh... We met at my old job, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah, office romance!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's not very forthcoming with information about herself, is she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Did you know that the boss is trying to get out of the "business"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really? <thought>Mr. Kitaki wants to quit being a gangster!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">He's trying to transfer his assets into a normal company. He only announced it recently, out of the blue... I hear there's quite a lot of confusion in the ranks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. I wonder if this explains that apron?</thought> ...I can't imagine Wocky going along with that.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Hee hee. He's highly motivated, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, that's not the word I would have used.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He said, "I'll be the next Big Boss, and keep the Family alive." I think he's at that age when boys want to make a mark on the world.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's not the way I would have put it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">His father moves in a lot of circles... He's really focused on profits. The Kitaki Family's been making a killing recently!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Again, not the way I would have put it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">But Wocky says it's not about the money. They have the gangster tradition to uphold.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, a generation gap! They've even got the ever classic "what about the family business" thing going...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Usually, it's the father worried about tradition...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I ask you a question about Wocky? I understand he was operated on by the victim, Dr. Meraktis.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Apparently, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I was in his clinic 'bout half a year ago. He messed up my op something bad. And then he just lets me go, without a word. See ya later, bye! So I gotta go in, get another doc to patch me up again!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Yes, it sounded horrible. Wocky has always been fond of fighting, I'm afraid...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure it qualifies as "fighting" when pistols are involved.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin was saying his life might be in danger, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">N-No, that can't be right! I'm sure he was just trying to scare us.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's scary to think that a surgeon might make a mistake... ...but it's even scarier when he tries to hide it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd like to know a little more about this "operation". Maybe it's time to pay the Meraktis Clinic a visit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I'm sorry, I don't know much about the case. I... I feel so helpless. You're my only hope. Please, help my Wocky-Pocky...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-R-Right! L-L-L-Leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, I think you're only making her more nervous...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry! I'm new at this, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Tee hee. It's alright. I believe in you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A bottle of Mr. Wright's favorite brand of grape juice. Me? I haven't been able to touch the stuff since that first case. ...Not a problem for Mr. Wright, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A swaying, spiraling stack of DVD cases. Better stay away or it'll become a crashing cascading cavalcade of DVD cases.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright's bed. My, it's messy. Trucy must clean up after him at home.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A toy piano, one that might be played by a child. Correction: A pink toy piano. I guess the man likes pink. Nothing wrong with that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The TV's been left on. Hmm... Looks like the Steel Samurai's in a spot of trouble. I'm sure he'll come back to win in the end. Mr. Wright likes those kind of stories.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Several colors of paint have been splashed across the gate. Most of it's pretty much dry, too. This is going to be one heck of a cleanup job.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like the old lady's at it again...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Look, I told you yesterday the park's off limits!</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">And I told you yesterday this is how I go home! OK. You want me to go around? How about giving me five bucks... like yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...The con artist strikes again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The park crime scene is off limits to the public. The police officer on guard by the gate is yawning. Ah, he noticed me staring and snapped his mouth shut. Too late, Mr. Officer! I saw you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This trash can... This is where we found the mirror!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come to think of it, wasn't there something else in here? Something near the bottom... ...Look at the paint on these. That means... ...these must have ended up in here after Mr. Wright's accident. Maybe they're connected? Let's pick them up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A large trash can sits by the entrance to the park.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What, you aren't going to dig through it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No. What? I'm serious! I have no intention of looking through this trash can!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, please, don't hold back on my account.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think that whatever you think about me and trash cans, you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder... Could this be a print?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why would there be a finger... Oh, you mean a toe print! Good call, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I bet we can analyze it just like a regular print.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This could be a vital piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! It worked! That looks like... a big toe, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, I feel like the case is solved already!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was next? We have to match the print, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! Let's match it! ...... Wait. The detective didn't give us a list of toe prints, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, good point.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe we should ask her? Get some "expert" advice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess so... <thought>I'm not sure she really qualifies as an expert...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, we have a toe print now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not sure what good it's going to do us without a list of toe prints to check it on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe our detective friend can help us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blue plastic tarps cover the ground around the stand. They were apparently put here to preserve the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A knife is sticking straight into the ground. Remember what Wesley Stickler said in the trial today... Wocky was very likely pointing this at the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Like he wanted to kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, that's the problem.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A mannequin put in place of the body. I think I've seen him by the police station. The way he's forced to look at the ground now, day in and day out... It's kind of sad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Poor Mr. Eldoon. His stand's been standing here since this whole thing started.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It almost looks at home here in the park now. I think it should be made into a playhouse for children!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think its owner would disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A trash can sits next to the path here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And I guess now we know it was Mr. Stickler who hid Little Plum's bloomers here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right, Trucy. And what a web of lies grew from that one little act.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can still remember that moment... You brandished those bloomers on high, and shouted... "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Here's what I want you to do, Trucy. Take that memory, gently lock it away deep in your heart, and never speak of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The front entrance to the Meraktis Clinic. The walls and posts are so highly polished I can see my face in them. ...Wait. My hairdo's a little flat. ...There. Perfect.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A lone Eldoon's Noodles bowl lies on the ground. The lone bowl, tipped on its side... It's kind of surreal. You'd think he would have picked it up by now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An oil drum for catching rainwater. ...Ack! A flock of crows just flew over and... That's gross! Their aim was uncanny... almost as if they'd been practicing here a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is where we found your panties, isn't it, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And I can't thank you enough, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, thank you for saying thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I'm always polite! It's part of being a performer. You know what Daddy says: "It doesn't cost anything to be polite, and it could bring you more business."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Typical.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just kidding! I really am grateful!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Looks like Wocky's out for questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I really need to talk to him. I guess we'll come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">The other suspect is all through with questioning, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The other... Ah! You mean the panty-snatcher!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wesley Stickler. <thought>So they arrested him, too?</thought> Alright. Let's have a little chat with Mr. Stickler. <thought>I hope I don't regret this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He is a valuable witness!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He is a bit "precious", I'll give him that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Please, keep this brief, if you would. I'm quite busy. I need to finish this paper... Nyurk! I-It's you!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Mr. Stickler. We'd like to have a few words with you.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...... ...Very well. As long as they're few.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nothing would make me happier, believe me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler. On the night of the murder, you stole...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wait! I can't help but feel that I'm being misunderstood.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...How, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yes, that night, I obtained a pair of panties, it's true. However! It was my burning curiosity that drove me to do it! Nothing more!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You wanted to know the trick to my panties, right?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Y-You're here, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Oh, Great Trucy! Teach me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I must know the secret of your panties! My very existence hangs in the balance! Please, make me your apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Help!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I dunno, I think he'd make a great "lovely assistant".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't say that, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you relate what you saw the night of the murder to us one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...Why not. Though it hardly differs from the testimony I gave in court. The defendant was there in the park that night, of this I'm quite certain. He was pointing a pistol... or </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this is all true? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">My panties are gone. My innermost heart revealed. What further reason could I possibly have to lie?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't think of anything he'd want to hide more than panty-snatching, true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It sounds like Wocky was at the scene of the crime, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How I wish it weren't so.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Th-That's it! The mystery! The unanswerable riddle!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Actually, they're just a normal pair of panties.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wh-What!? How is that possible?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It just takes practice, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Then you must teach me! You must! To think, if I could produce a pencil, an eraser, a text book, and a lunch... ...all from a pair of panties! My life would be complete!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's serious, isn't he.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... <thought>...Fine, ignore my evidence. See if I care. I wonder what he's thinki... On second thought, let's not go there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If everything that panty-snatcher said was true... ...it doesn't put Wocky in a very good position, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was at the scene of the crime, that's pretty clear. <thought>There's got to be a different angle on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's get investigating! No time like the present!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So? Any leads?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... One moment... ... Shazam! Allakhazam!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! Evidence keeps flying out of nowhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ta da! That's all! Neat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah, real neat. <thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aren't my panties amazing? They were a big hit in court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They were the star player of the day, that's true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What should I show them in court tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If only I could count on panties to save the day every day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yipes! She's back!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Hey. You two. Over here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">U-Uh, us?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yo, Little Plum! Wassup!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think all this gangsterese is a negative influence on Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">I heard you retrieved my bloomers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, I was j-just doing...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Bah! A man speaks clearly, and takes credit where it's due! You caught the thief, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, y-yes! Sorry! I caught him!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're cute when you're nervous, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'll deal with you later.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">But enough about bloomers! What about my son, Wocky!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wocky? Er, well, he's, um...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, ma'am! <thought>This is why I was kind of hoping we could avoid coming back here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's really everything you'd expect in a Boss's son! "I'm going to be a gangster, dude!"</line>
<line speaker="Plum">The life does have an appeal for that age... Particularly for boys.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Don't look at me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">He was shot in a turf war about half a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes... We heard the story from Wocky.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">...But he didn't tell you the whole story. You know, even if he had a pistol then, he couldn't have shot anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">He acts like he's "hard", but he couldn't shoot someone to save his life. I should know... I'm his mom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her words do have a certain weight to them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Hopefully, when this is all taken care of... ...he and the Boss can sort out their differences.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Boss... You mean Wocky's father?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They didn't seem to be on the best terms, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">It's true... One of our pistols is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So the murder weapon was from this mansion...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We kind of figured, given the difficulty of obtaining a gun these days.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">None of the rank and file have access. Only the Boss, myself, and ...Wocky could have taken it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">I'm sure the cops will continue tromping all over the mansion because of this case. Maybe this is a sign that it's time for a change! Wa ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She doesn't seem too concerned, at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">...Yeah. Wocky's fiancée.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're getting married next month, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">I suppose. She's been staying over lately.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...You don't look too happy about that, Little Plum.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">...! How'd you guess?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Even I could tell that!</thought> Could you tell us more about her?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">...Wocky brought her home one day. Says he wants to tie the knot.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can see why! She's so pretty!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Oh, she's pretty enough. But, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Nah, it's probably just me being suspicious. Stay in this business too long... ...and you start to only see darkness in people. You get a nose for it. A nose for people... A nose for trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. I wonder what the problem is?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's like a gangsters-only version of "female intuition"!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">The Boss may act tough, but that boy means the world to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But Wocky seems, well... It seems like he's against his father's position.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Ah. It's to be expected. We're in a bit of a transition now. Trying to cut our ties to the shadier side of the street and do more on the up-and-up. Wocky isn't too enthusiastic about the change, it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But why the change? Is the gangster thing just not paying the bills?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Wa ha ha ha ha ha! It pays... but we need a lot of money right now. Clean money, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see... <thought>Hmm, something must be up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">He'll see things the way the Boss sees 'em... some day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the mirror we found...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">...From the hit 'n' run, huh? It's funny how it all ties together like this. You chase after a hit 'n' run and end up Wocky's attorney. Of course, you'll find the real killer soon. Won't you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about these...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Hey, my bloomers! Thanks for that. I owe you one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I thought you might like them back, so...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Eh? Oh no, no. Why don't you keep 'em as a souvenir?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh no, I couldn't, really! Thanks for the offer bu--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I could use those in my Magic Panties act! I'll pull shivs and pieces and godfathers out of them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great, now your props are going from bland to dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell me if this knife belongs to Wocky?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Oh, that's his knife alright. Bought it for him for his birthday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow, that's a pretty hardcore present.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">I remember him falling asleep with it clutched in his arms.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I know the feeling! I'll bet he was just as happy as I was with my plastic spaghetti!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this pistol belongs to the Kitaki Family... Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">It's one of the pieces we keep around. That is, we used to keep around. They're all gone now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Police came yesterday and took everything. ...Everything but my "broom".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't you think you should have given them that, too?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">You kidding? Can't clean up very well without a broom!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, it's Mr. Eldoon! Oh Mr. Eldooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...Hrmph.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...So, you found my stand. That's why I'm here. To thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">But now it's a crime scene and they won't let me have it back!!! That's also why I'm here. I got no other place to go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">How can a noodle stand be a crime scene, that's what I don't get, Trucy-doll! Even in death he's after my neck, I tell ya! Bah! Can't even cook an honest noodle...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"He"...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Even in death"... You mean the victim, Dr. Meraktis?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">I tell ya. It's enough to drive a man to make his soup even saltier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Remind me never to eat his noodles when he's in a bad mood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">That stand... For generations, it's served up the very best noodles us Eldoons could make. A tradition of noodles and salty broth. It's more than a stand, it's history, I tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Watch what you say or it might become true...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's a great story, Mr. Eldoon! A single stand, passed down from generation to generation!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">'Course, to be honest... I didn't plan on doing it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right. You said something about that. About you "rebelling" against your pops, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Good memory, Trucy-doll. Aye, I was a go-getter back in my day... Until my friend next door butted in. In the end, I was left with nothing but this dusty old stand to earn my fortune.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon, I don't mean to pry... ...but what exactly did you do before you became a chef?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Bah! Let old noodles lie, that's what I say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm starting to get an idea of what he did, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">He stole my dreams and left me with nothin' but noodles. And now I don't even have that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon, if I might ask... What exactly happened between you and the Meraktis Clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Eh? Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I couldn't help but sense enmity there...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Enmity? I hate 'im! Er. Hated. Him actin' like he smells like roses when he's rollin' in mud!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">He's the only doctor at that clinic, you know. Pretty impressive, eh? I'll tell you the secret to his success... The mob!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean... the Kitaki Family?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">They're always having one of them "turf wars" or whatnot. Always an injury or two that needs fixing. Meraktis saw a chance for some business. So he started giving the Kitaki Family a good deal...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A deal...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Every fifth operation for free! He stole the idea from my pops! One free bowl of noodles a week, he used to say.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can a doctor just decide to do that? What about the insurance companies...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Oh, no doubt it's illegal. But, it got him in good with the Family. Pretty soon he was getting all the business in town. Leavin' me here, in the dark! Up t'my neck in soupy noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I've figured out Mr. Eldoon's former occupation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can't hurt to ask, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon... or should I say "Dr. Eldoon"...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Figured it out, did ya? That's right, I was a doctor. A surgeon... until the year before last.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So Mr. Meraktis was your rival?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...You like those onions they put in the soup broth?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, yeah, kind of.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You take a spoon, you drink some broth... Those onions will find their way in there. For people who like 'em, why that's just fine. For people who hate 'em... ...I hate onions. Hate 'em! Always sneaking in from the side, gettin' in the way of a good tastin' spoonful. Well, that's what he was. An onion! Onion-boy, that's what I called 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you weren't exactly friends.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Hah! Me 'n Pal Meraktis... Ever since pre-school we were getting in each other's face. No matter what I did, sure enough, he'd come followin' along. Then he'd do it better than me. Just blow right past without so much as a "howdy".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">That's right! I was a surgeon long before he was, you know. Then that no-good onion-boy comes along...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Trucy, looks like we found ourselves a new suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't say that!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Thanks to him, I was forced to trade in my scalpel for a ladle! ...Sorry, pal. Didn't mean to weigh you down with an old man's ramblings.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's fine.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">By way of apology... You ever get yourself in a spot of trouble, you drop by.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You're investigating Meraktis, aren't ya?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Well, you want to know about a doctor, you ask a doctor. That's all I'm sayin'. You just think of me if you need something, Trucy-doll.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! Thanks, Mr. Eldoon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. I guess the time spent listening to him complain wasn't entirely wasted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">That's right, sonny! When're you bringing my stand home!? I'm ready. Can't you see I'm ready!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">Until that stand is back home, the case is not closed! You hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I'll avoid talking about his stand in the future.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but what about the guard?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No harm in asking! Um, excuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Hey, it's you two from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's the same officer that was standing out by the park yesterday!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Your business is over in the park, isn't it? The clinic's off limits. It's not involved.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">What part of "off limits" do you not understand? Show me proof that the clinic is connected to the incident in the park, or beat it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No harm in asking... No gain either. No point in sticking around here, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I was hoping to meet with my client?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Wocky Kitaki's just finished questioning. I'll bring him out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Great! Finally!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yo, 'sup, my little imposter!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeek! Wh-What did you call me?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Dizzam! It's you!? Sorry, G, thought you were Alita.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"My little imposter" sure is a strange nickname.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">It's a clink thang. You wouldn't understand. D-Did I say "imposter"? I meant "poster"... like "poster girl", 'aight?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you're going to drop part of that, why not drop "poster" and just call her "girl"?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Cause she's so much more than that, G. She's like... She's like an angel. A fallen angel. ...So. What can I do you for?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...You don't look so chipper today, Wocky.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Worried about your, um, heart condition, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That was the wackest thing of all! All us G's lining up, taking eye exams... Better to die young than fade away, bizzzoy!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A relief to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Eh? Wh-What's a relief!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? Did your father not tell you? That bullet you carry so close to your heart... if not attended to immediately... ...It could kill you.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">M-Man... I ain't trying to hear that! A man fights to protect what's valuable to him, you know what I'm saying? ...I miss my fallen angel! Hey, you go get Alita for me. You're my lawyer, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lawyer, not gopher...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I hear you're to be married next month?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Straight up! We poured the nuptial 40 out on the stoop! Alita! Oh, snapplecakes! She soooo foine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think he's smitten with her in his own weird way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was wondering, how did you two meet? I asked Tiala, but she  was... very vague.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Huh? Well, man, if she wouldn't tell you... I'd best hold my tongue, you feel me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wha--!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Man, what's past is past. She knows that. When I'm with Alita... I feel like there's things worth protecting out there. You feel me? And my Alita, she's down with that all the way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, so both of them are mum about their past...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think you could tell us what happened with you and Pal Meraktis...?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...There's something you should know. We Kitakis are having what you might call a feud with the Rivales Family. So, 'bout six months back... I go into Rivales turf, packing a knife, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And... You were shot?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Coldest thing I ever seen. One shot, to the heart, but my homies weren't too late. It's a miracle that I lived. It's already considered one of the seven wonders of the Kitaki Family, you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you were taken to the Meraktis Clinic then?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You shoulda seen their faces when they wheeled me in. You can't just let the Boss's son die, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd hate to have been in that doctor's shoes... Mr. Kitaki's scary enough when he's not angry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But the bullet that hit you... ...it was never removed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And it's still threatening his life!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That doctor... He did it on purpose! The Rivales paid him off, I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I need to hear more about the night of the murder, that much is clear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Life in the Family is a G thang. It's about being a man. ...You know what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sorry, I'm not up on my G things. I'm not even sure what a G thing is...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">But my old man, he's gone soft. He says the old rival gang days are over. He just wants to make money!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Isn't that a good thing?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Man, there ain't no soul in making money! Better to live fast and die young. Fo'shizzle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Wait till I run the yard. Then everyone'll know what time it is. That's right! O.G. time all the time. Represent!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, why does he keep talking about "Old Guys"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think that's what "O.G." means, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Actually, there's a question I've been wanting to ask you for a while now. That is, uh... Did you do it? Did you shoot him?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">... I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">The day of that check-up, when I found out about the bullet by my heart... ...I... borrowed a gun from the Family's stash. Figured I'd give that doctor a taste of his own bad medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh... I don't like where this is going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... you were carrying a knife, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Oh that? Yeah, well, never can be too careful, I say. So I'm on my way to the clinic, right? When I run into him in the park... and he's dragging this noodle stand behind him!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, you didn't put him up to that? Like, you know, in the movies? "If you value your life, you'll bring the stand..."</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...Shorty, you're more wacked than I am. And that's saying something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...But I was serious!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">The thing is, I don't remember what happened next all too well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't remember...?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">But, the way I see it, if there wasn't anyone else there that night... ...then I guess it probably was me who did him in, you know what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About these weapons... the pistol and the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">They belong to the Family. I snuck 'em out that night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the "killer" Mr. Stickler says he saw that night was...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I guess it was me. I was there, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gak...! <thought>We're finished...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... Yo, Wocky! Do you think you could tell us exactly what happened that night?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Heh... You don't beat around the bush, do you? I like your style, shorty.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">... Yeah, whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He seems preoccupied... I'm not sure he even looked at my evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Alita, man. Alita.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Look at that crowd over by the park!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Probably people trying to get a glimpse of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... why are those girls screaming? I think I just heard one say "Omigod, it's him!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, that motorcycle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah! If it isn't Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some fans found me on my way out... Just my luck.</line>
<line speaker="???">Omigod! Omigod! He's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thus the screams...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">New album just came out, you know. Try waving to them. They love it.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oooh! Oooh! He's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha. They're so excited, it doesn't matter who waves to them, see?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is surreal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, so you were here investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And I was on my way home... when my hog gave up the ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your hog...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My motorcycle won't start. A clogged exhaust pipe...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad! It looks like such a nice bike, too. Hard to believe that it could break just from that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ach, it's my fault. I think I was using the wrong oil. Cars, motorbikes, they're all the same. Clog the exhaust, and they won't run. Ah, machines. Tell me you share my angst, Herr Forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I ride a bicycle, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah. Heh. In any event, I'm off to the shop to get her fixed. The detective in charge of the scene isn't fond of me, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The detective... You mean, the one in the lab coat?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ja. She's in a foul mood, too. Be gentle. ...Auf Wiedersehen, baby!</line>
<line speaker="???">Omigod! Omigod! There he goes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the forecast for the park today... Gloomy Skyes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, nothing to do but head on in. Let's hit the park, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Does something about this scene look different to you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The blue tarps are gone! Maybe that's it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I think you're right. Look over there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The white-frocked detective from yesterday. She seems to be apologizing reverently... to the trash can.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's... under a lot of stress. The investigation's probably not going so well.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, you there! If you're going to talk about someone behind their back, do it more quietly, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, Detective Skye. Hello.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You seem as gloomy as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is miserable! Miserable! I just got a new kit, and I can't get the stuff to work. And everyone's all smiles for that glimmerous fop.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Glimmerous...? Does she mean Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">More to the point, doesn't she mean "glamorous"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">When he walks his shiny chains catch the sun and glimmer in my eyes! It's distracting. MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Speaking of distracting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">*sigh* I guess I just have to accept the fact that I lack talent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like she's trying out some sort of new forensics technique...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The tarps that were here yesterday are gone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder why Detective Skye put them out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... The only thing they were covering is the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! You know, I think I see something there... a print!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... "print"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye, you know Mr. Wright, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How do you know my daddy!? I want details!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah? Ah... Well... ...He helped me out a long time ago. You might say he "saved" me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wasn't she saying something about "getting involved in an incident"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can't stand it when things are vague... especially in a case. I went to study to become a forensic scientist... in Europe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... you're a detective now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well... I failed the test. But, you know, rank and title don't matter! What matters is what's inside your heart!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've always thought that, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And my heart is full of science! That's why I bought this kit through mail order. And I'm going to test it here before the forensics team arrives!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Are you sure that's OK...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I won't lie, I'm not fond of the man. Those glimmerous types always rub me the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Glamorous"... right.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A prosecutor should be cool of wit and furrowed of brow. Less "glimmerous" and more "simmerous"... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No, actually, I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, that, and what happened seven years ago! Prosecutor Gavin was the one who stripped Mr. Wright of his attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaaaa--!? Really!? <thought>He was the one!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...You mean you didn't know? I thought you were one of his boys!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm neither a "boy" nor one of his... but let's see what she has to say.</thought> Um... What exactly happened seven years ago? I never actually heard the details.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Then investigate. It's better you learned it for yourself, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Do you mind me asking exactly what it is you've been doing... ...squatting down on the ground like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh! You want to know? Do you? Well, I splurged on a new toy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You splurged... You mean, it wasn't police issue?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it? I see a roller... and glue?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This is a footprint analysis kit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Footprint...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It was raining on the night of the murder, which means that footprints were left!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, does that have anything to do with those blue tarps?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. The ground was muddy, so I had to protect it as it was that night. Ever wanted to know exactly where someone was standing? Like your panty-snatching student witness, for instance?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah ha! So with that kit...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Want to try this stuff out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Are you sure? I mean, we're sort of on opposing teams and all...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, pshaw! You're friends! And... to tell the truth, I'm not so good at doing this. Guess I'm a little clumsy. I could use your help.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I'm good at stuff like this! I used to make magic bunnies out of paper mache!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Footprint analysis, huh? Well, should I give it a go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I'll pass. Wouldn't want to waste a kit if I  messed up.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? That's too bad... I really could use the help.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aww, I want to try! It'll be just like making pancakes in the dirt!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess I can always talk to her again if I change my mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK... I'll give it a go!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's the spirit! Right, allow me to explain! Ahem, one moment...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's reading the instructions for her kit...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why does this not fill me with confidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">First, we have to pick the footprint, or in this case, shoe print we want to analyze! I've taken the liberty of marking all the shoe prints in the park. Well, which shoe print should we start with...? If we're going to verify the defendant's account, here's the place to start! Shoe prints, prepare to be examined!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! This is so exciting!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right, here goes! First... "Pour the plaster into the print until it's full." ...You try it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How am I supposed to do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just touch the screen where you want to pour the plaster. Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, that doesn't look too hard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">If you run out of plaster in your beaker before you're done, you have to start over!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you doing!? Out of plaster already?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, give me a break! I'm just a beginner at this!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm not that far ahead of you believe me! ...Fine. I'll make another batch. Don't mess it up this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Plaster, here comes Justice! *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not bad. You're handier with that than you look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">On to the next step! Um... "Dry the plaster until it turns white." Right! Just touch to direct the dryer! ...There, give it a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Looks like it's hardened nicely. Let's take a look! Hmm... Yes, that's a good one. Next, the ink! Ready for the next step? Use the roller to ink just the shoe print part. Hold on to that roller tight now, and roll it up and down. Keep going till you get enough ink on there for a good print!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right, now the moment you've all been waiting for! Let's take our print! Ready? Here goes! Let's see if we get a match.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm, no good. Must have messed up somewhere. Shall we try on another print?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the shoe prints belong to Wocky Kitaki after all...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He was in the park on the night of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! I can almost see the science at work!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't you love it!? Ahhh! Nothing feels better.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's definitely waaaay more into this than I am...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just let me know if you want to do some more. I'll be here, solving the case... with science!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, that certainly brightened her mood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm? Still interested in the bleeding edge of forensic science? Why didn't you say so in the first place!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye? Mind if we give it another go?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right on! Leave no print un-analyzed, I say! ...Now to pick which print you want to analyze!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...OK! Looking good. Next, to dry the plaster!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's take out the mold! Hmm... Yes, that's a good one. Next, the ink!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right, now the moment you've all been waiting for! Let's take our print! Ready? Here goes! Let's see if we get a match.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm, no good. Must have messed up somewhere. Shall we try on another print?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So these shoe prints belong to Wesley Stickler. This confirms his testimony. The final version of it, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now we know where the panty-snatcher was standing!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...OK! Looking good. Next, to dry the plaster!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's take out the mold! Hmm... Yes, that's a good one. Next, the ink!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Huh. That's a funny shoe print. Is that even a shoe?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It is strange. So smooth...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Except for the part with the leaf.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can say without even looking that this print doesn't match any print on our list.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... A mystery print.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Giving up already? Suit yourself. If you want to take another swing at it, just let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye? Mind if we give it another shot?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe you're beginning to appreciate the wonder that is forensic science!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye? Mind if we give it another shot?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wish there were more prints to analyze... *sniffle* I know! Quick! Step in that mud over there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, I don't think analyzing my footprint is going to do us much good.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">*sigh* I would have had fun.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This print is far too smooth to be from a regular shoe.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It is a shoe print of some kind though, that's certain.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Still, you have to wonder what it's doing here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's right next to the Eldoon's Noodles stand!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It does make one wonder... ...Hey, you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why are you so quiet all of a sudden? ...You wouldn't happen to have something in mind? Something that might have left this mystery shoe print?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This mystery shoe print does remind me of something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... No, sorry. No idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Too bad. I wonder what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something's familiar about that smooth surface... so smooth it's almost slippery.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Well, if you think of something, I'm all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm pretty sure I've seen something that would leave a print like that.</thought> You know, I think I have our culprit right here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Know what I'm eating?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Snacks?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Snacks. More precisely, whenever I'm in a bad mood, I eat chocolate Snackoos.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think she means you picked the wrong evidence, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I had no idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think it's these slippers, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Slippers... What would slippers be doing out here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But look at the bottom! See?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's covered with paint! Except for...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">See, right here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, that spot is shaped like a leaf!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if a leaf was stuck on the bottom, and came off when the slipper stepped in paint? ...Makes sense, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait, something's written on them... ..."The Meraktis Clinic"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly! The victim's clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, that means... ...that someone from the clinic was involved?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why is she just standing there eating?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, Detective Skye? I have a favor to ask!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you get us access into the Meraktis Clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The police won't let us in! They say the murder and the clinic are not connected. And it's off limits until we prove they are!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I should be able to do something for you, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, you did my work for me here with the shoe prints. Seems like I should return the favor.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thank you, Detective Skye!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, show this to the police officer on duty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right! Meraktis Clinic, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Fingerprint analysis is the very basis of modern forensic science!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I guess you could put it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And you two know how to dust for prints on your own now! Make sure to examine anything you find that might have prints on it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They say "The Meraktis Clinic"... Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This slipper... Look right here! I think I see a toe mark!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A toe mark... You think we can get a print off that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure! Toes have prints just like fingers do, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This little clue might be a gold mine!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... There's one problem. The police station doesn't keep a record of toe prints. So we won't know whose it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I guess that would be too much to hope for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Still, it might be useful somehow! Let's analyze it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She put a little heart by her name! How cute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't she a little old for cute?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Shame on you! Cute is eternal! Cute is timeless! No matter how old a woman gets she always carries a little innocent maiden inside her!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...R-Really now. I suppose. I've never heard it put quite that way before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When I sign my name, I always put in a little diamond! "Trucy ◇ Wright"... See? Cute, don'tcha think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a little confusing. Won't people think your middle name is diamond?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! You could write your name like "Apollo {{{2}}} Justice"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do like justice, but that's taking it a bit far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, the prodigal attorney returns! Welcome, Apollo. I heard you did well in the trial today. Here to discuss something? I could use a little diversion...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What did Detective Skye say? If you want to know something, you have to investigate it yourself...</thought> Mr. Wright! Tell me what happened seven years ago... please. I want to know. I need to know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You certainly didn't waste any time getting to the point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Seven years ago, I was standing in a courtroom... on behalf of a client. The case involved the death of a certain "magnificent" genius... I'd be surprised if you hadn't heard about it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It was all over the news, I remember that. You were up against Prosecutor Gavin, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, he was only 17 years old at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>17 years old...? That's still high school!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He took the bar exam abroad... in Europe. They're progressive over there, you know. I was defeated by a 17-year-old newcomer. In my shame, I left the practice forever. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's all...? How could that be all!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about what they were saying on the news about forged evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They said you forged evidence and had your attorney's badge stripped from you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me... how does it feel? How does it feel to stand here before Phoenix Wright, the Forgin' Attorney himself?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-How does it feel...? <thought>I... I don't want to believe it's true! But what about what happened in my first trial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you notice in today's trial? There was a single piece of forged evidence. I'm talking about evidence that shouldn't have existed. A naughty magician's trick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha ha ha! I don't see you jumping to my defense on this one... Maybe I did forge evidence, maybe I didn't. ...It doesn't really matter now, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not an attorney anymore. ...That's the only truth you need to know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mr. Wright... Looks like he doesn't want to talk about the accusations of forgery... for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, so that was what led you to the guilty party.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! Thanks to you ripping the mirror off the car, I was able to deduce the...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You make a good point, Apollo. In fact... It could be said that I'm to thank for finding the criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Think what you want, Mr. Wright. Knock yourself out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And we found these, too! They're Trucy's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Apollo. Though, I have to admit, as a father, I wonder... ...why are you still carrying my daughter's panties around in your pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That'll teach me to show off my evidence to Mr. Wright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, the time of the decision is upon us! Which one of our two jailbirds do we want to talk to?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Excuse me! Both detainees are currently in questioning to corroborate their accounts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler and Wocky? Both of them? <thought>I pity the questioner...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess we'll be back then!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah, you two again. When, oh when will you learn. Look at me however you want, you're not getting in today.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wouldn't be so sure if I  were you! Look what we have!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">What's this? ...Detective Skye! ... Yesterday, it was Prosecutor Gavin, today it's Detective Skye. Who are you two? Really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now he's suspicious again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">...Well, you got the orders, I gotta let you in. Have fun.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks, Mr. Officer! Let's hit it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh, kind of an at-home sort of place, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This place has a connection to the murder in the park... I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The police guy out front wasn't so sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Beyond it being where the victim lived. <thought>Looks like the police team's gone home for the day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There might be some clues lying around! Let's get cracking, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look at all these bowls...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're from Eldoon's Noodles! There's Mr. Salty!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then, I think we've figured something out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we have.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Eldoon must do take-out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... <thought>Not exactly what I was thinking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All the bowls have been washed clean...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we've found our first clue, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A plate on this door reads "Doctor's Office".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That was pretty intense, wasn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If we'd gone in there one second earlier, we might have met the burglar!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, Apollo... What would we have said if we did see them? We can't exactly shout out "Hey! Who are you!?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... It does lack a certain punch.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's think of something cool to say for the next time we do meet a burglar!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The clinic's reception desk. No one's here, of course. There's a small sign on the counter... "Please pay your bill: Remember, we're the ones holding the scalpel." Brutal... but effective.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's a single pair of sandals here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, but why would there be sandals here? Unless they belong to one of the patients.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Or maybe it's a visitor that's come to see Dr. Meraktis.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You'd think they'd use his house entrance instead of the clinic entrance, in that case. And, if this patient or visitor isn't still here...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why'd they leave without their shoes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Better take a closer look at these, just in case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A pair of sandals in a deserted clinic...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a little scary... when you stop to think about it. And how did the lady go home without her sandals?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Maybe her operation here was to add wings, and she flew home?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I've heard of those! Surgical enhancements, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Surgical enhancements are for a different part of the body, and, I was kidding...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">These must be the slippers for patients at the clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The same as the pair we found, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, a single pair is missing from the rack here, too. And ours have paint on the bottoms... Which means they were taken out of here on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... The paint's from the hit and run, after all. <thought>But what were a pair of clinic slippers doing in that trash can? And what were they doing at the scene of the hit and run?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo! You think this is...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh... This could be a toe print.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe we can get a print off of this! Let's try it out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! It worked! That looks like... a big toe, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But wait! I mean, it's great that we got the print... But is there such a thing as a list of toe prints?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, good point. If there is, Detective Skye didn't give it to us. Which means... we can't match this print.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This seems like a good time to ask a detective's advice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, we have a toe print now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not sure what good it's going to do us without a list of toe prints to check it on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe our detective friend can help us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! This door says "Doctor's Office"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think this is the victim's private office?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's not locked... Too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why "too bad"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I like opening locks! It's kind of a hobby of mine. Like those little bike locks? Don't even bother putting them on when I'm around!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's probably not a hobby you want to tell too many people about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......! Ah... Apollo! That sound... It came from behind this door!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Someone's in there!</thought> L-Let's check it out, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A break-in! They left through that window!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, Apollo! You're too late to catch them now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That must be her experience as a panty-snatcher chaser talking.</thought> Well, we should tell the police!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's check the room out, first, Apollo! If we call the police now, we'll lose our chance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You're right. <thought>She's better at this than I am!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, one thing's for certain. This clinic and our murder case are looking pretty related now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! What are those? The wall is covered with beakers...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeek! Something's moving inside that one! ...You look, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Hey, look yourself! You can't... Oh. ...It's a goldfish.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, they're all fish! So many kinds!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoever designed this had a sick sense of humor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Kind of an expensive-looking lamp, isn't it? Hey... The bulb's broken.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Broken? Don't you mean burned-out?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No. Our cat burglar must have dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But why is it standing up on the floor like that then?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, look at the cord...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? There's a red splotch on a part of the cord...</thought> You think that's... blood?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a little bright for blood. Almost pinkish.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something's definitely odd about this lamp, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kind of an expensive-looking lamp. The bulb's broken. <thought>And here I thought light bulbs were usually pretty resilient little buggers.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe the burglar dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Funny that it's standing upright on the floor then.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's bit peculiar [sic], isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The window is ajar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That must be how our burglar escaped!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe it was just a burglar who happened to pick here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but there's a patrol car sitting out front. If I were a burglar, I'd come back the next day at least.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'd give it a month, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoever broke in obviously needed to break in today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Books and papers are scattered around the room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, what a mess. This is worse than Daddy's room! The burglar must have left in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even the cup on the desk here is lying on its side. Huh? The juice that spilled out of that cup... It's dry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, the messy one wasn't our burglar just now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone knocked this cup over a while ago and left it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This potted plant has seen better days. Hmm... That doesn't make sense either.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What doesn't?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Normally, burglars are looking for valuables, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's true! That's what I would do! If I were a burglar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So why look under a potted plant?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they were looking for the key to the safe?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've heard of people putting their house keys under plants, but the key to a safe...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then maybe the burglar was looking for the house keys!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is getting nowhere fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a cute little safe!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, looks like a four-digit lock.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...! Someone's already entered in two numbers, Apollo! 7...9... Wait, do you think...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That burglar just now was trying to open it!? <thought>I wonder what's inside this safe...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm, is there any way we can figure out the last two numbers?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we know the first two are 7 and 9...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe there's something in the Court Record? Something that can help us figure out the last two numbers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would be a bit too lucky, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I suppose... If only there was something that could finger which buttons had been pressed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something that could "finger which buttons were pressed", huh? Maybe there is a way after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I have an idea...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I knew it, Apollo! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well... All we have to know is what buttons have been pressed!</thought> We can use this to find out what the next two numbers are!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... I'm not sure how that's going to help us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Neither am I, come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If only there was something that could finger which buttons had been pressed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something that could "finger" which buttons were pressed", huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...When you press the buttons, you'd have to touch them... ...with your finger, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It would leave a print!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you open a safe, you don't press any other buttons but the right ones, right? So, if we can find the buttons with fingerprints...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We'll have the safe code! Not bad, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look! You can see the oily finger residues clearly. Look at 7 and 9...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">These are glove marks. The burglar must have been wearing gloves.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we might not be able to identify the burglar, but we can open this safe! Let's give it a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's enter the code, Apollo! We know the first two numbers are 7 and 9!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It opened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This looks like a bullet hole!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm, you can still see the bullet sticking out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why is it in the middle of a safe?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, the bullet came out! The tip is all squished.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not surprising given that it was fired into a metal safe. <thought>This bullet's got a story behind it, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A bullet hole remains in the back wall of the safe. Now why would someone shoot a bullet into a safe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This looks like... a medical chart. There's an X-ray in here with it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An X-ray...? Hmm, can't make heads or tails of it. And I can't read the chart either, it's all in medical-speak.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, the names are easy enough to read. Look, by "Patient" it says... "Wocky Kitaki"! So this is Wocky... our client's chart, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would this one chart be here in this safe...? Let's see, the physician's signature says "Pal Meraktis". Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look here where it says who filed the chart...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... "Nurse Alita Tiala"...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alita Tialita is Wocky's fiancée!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's one "ita" too many, Apololo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Never mind that, what's her name doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How should I know? Though... I guess it means she's on staff at this clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Odd that she neglected to mention this before now...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm sure she had her reasons.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Alita Tiala worked at the Meraktis Clinic... And she had access to Wocki Kitaky's medical chart!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You got the "I" and "Y" wrong, Appolo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd be very interested to find out what this chart says. <thought>Who could help us decipher this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wocky's medical chart was hidden inside a safe... And Alita Tiala was the one who filed it.</thought> We have to figure out what this chart says. <thought>I wonder if there's anyone who can help us decipher it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The bulb is broken. It won't turn on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? How is it broken...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't touch that. You'll cut yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, yeah, fool me once, shame on me, fool my twice...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">M-My finger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Y-You're bleeding! Let me see that... ......Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Magic blood! Tee hee! Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Please don't do that again. I have enough to worry about without my co-workers injuring themselves on the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This cord runs to the lamp. It has a red stain on it. Hmm... Gotta wonder what left that stain.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait! I know! Maybe it was left there by a red marker! Like, they were trying to write their name, and slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would anyone write their name on a lamp cord?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I used to write my name on my magic ropes...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! It's all mushed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was one tough safe.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, it looks kinda yummy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Like ice cream! Mmm-mmm! Caramel!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You certainly have an active imagination, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I know that face. That's the face of someone who's made... a discovery!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, how did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can't fool someone trained in the ways of science!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Next she'll have us analyzing face prints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's ask Detective Skye to help us, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Say, could you take a look at this lamp?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm. The bulb's broken.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Strange, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? I break bulbs all the time. My desk is a mess and my lamp is always falling over. ...Not too bright, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still think it's kind of odd...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Detective Skye, I was wondering about this...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack, Trucy! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's vital evidence there. You can't show her that! That's our secret weapon in tomorrow's trial for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Clever, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...What did I tell you before? If you're going to talk behind someone's back, do it quietly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Detective Skye, I was wondering about this...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack, Trucy! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This bullet was inside the safe, right? That means the police don't know about it yet!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, right! We can use this in the trial tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Do I have to repeat myself every time? If you're going to talk behind someone's back, do so quietly!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, the slippers... That's quite a clear print there. ...A toe print.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad we don't know whose toe it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, there is a way of finding out, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There is!? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All you need is a sample of the same toe print, off another shoe, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. So if the prints matched, you'd know the same person wore both. <thought>Hmm. Do I have another shoe worn by the same person?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... I can't think of anything I might have with a toe print on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah well, it was too much to hope for, I suppose. Let me know if you find something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A toe print sample... Hmm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I just might, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm beginning to suspect something here...</thought> Detective Skye! Can you compare this sample with this other print?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with the scowl?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's got a toe print on it, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Of course it matches. It's the same evidence as before!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you thinking, trying to compare something with itself!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better stop messing up or I'm gonna get struck down by lightning from the Skye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Try again! And... try scientifically, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, another toe print. Right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I did say "toe print" sample, didn't I? Where exactly is the toe print on this evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops. Stormy Skyes ahead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Try again. Scientifically this time, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, a toe print. Right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This pair of sandals, toe print and all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh! The print on these is nice and clear, too. That makes our job easy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you analyze it for us?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course! Hang on...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bingo! Gosh, I'm good.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, we were the ones who found the prints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">A perfect match! The same person wore these sandals and slippers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was afraid of that...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All you have to do is find out who these sandals belong to! Or... do you already know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... can't say. Not yet. <thought>Well, that's one big step closer... ...to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... Yes... Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you find something?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, scientifically speaking... These are a pair of woman's sandals. Pretty cute, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We found them in the lobby at the Meraktis Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm? Say, this sandal has a toe mark...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A toe mark... You mean a toe print?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That I do! You can analyze it just like a fingerprint!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This little clue might be a real windfall!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh... There's one problem. The police station doesn't keep a record of toe prints. So we won't know whose it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I guess that would be too much to hope for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Still, it might be useful somehow! Let's analyze it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">These sandals... That's quite a clear print there. ...A toe print.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad we don't know whose toe it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, there is a way of finding out, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There is!? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All you need is a sample of the same toe print, off another shoe, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. So if the prints matched, you'd know the same person wore both. <thought>Hmm. Do I have another shoe worn by the same person?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... I can't think of anything I might have with a toe print on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah well, it was too much to hope for, I suppose. Let me know if you find something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A toe print sample... Hmm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I just might, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm beginning to suspect something here...</thought> Detective Skye! Can you compare this sample with this other print?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with the scowl?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's got a toe print on it, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Of course it matches. It's the same evidence as before!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you thinking, trying to compare something with itself!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better stop messing up or I'm gonna get struck down by lightning from the Skye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Try again! And... try scientifically, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, another toe print. Right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... I did say "toe print" sample, didn't I? Where exactly is the toe print on this evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops. Stormy Skyes ahead...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Try again. Scientifically this time, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, a toe print. Right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This pair of slippers, toe print and all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh! The print on these is nice and clear, too. That makes our job easy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you analyze it for us?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course! Hang on...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bingo! Gosh, I'm good.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, we were the ones who found the prints...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">A perfect match! The same person wore these sandals and slippers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was afraid of that...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All you have to do is find out who these sandals belong to! Or... do you already know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... can't say. Not yet. <thought>Well, that's one big step closer... ...to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, if the prints on these slippers and these sandals match, which they do... ...it means that the same person was wearing them.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, I thought that's what it might mean! Science is amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It is, isn't it!? I've never felt so alive!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't know about science, but this is a major lead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The toe prints match... Which means the sandals and the slippers were worn by the same person. And the slippers are from the Meraktis Clinic. These have to be connected to the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The toe prints match... Which means the sandals and the slippers were worn by the same person. If only we knew who these sandals belonged to...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Don't cry angel, Daddy's back and Daddy's... ...Oh. You again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you always have to announce your entrances like that?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Man, my old man, he... Man! Now I'm all in a funk, and it's his fault.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>One can only assume that his father tried to teach him a lesson. And failed, clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You two got your work cut out for you, straight up. Course I don't care if they lock me up. I'm ready to go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Some days, I wonder why I do what I do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey man, you won't see me bugging 'bout one or two guilty charges.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But what if you're found guilty of murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey, it's all experience, you feel me, shorty? Like a badge of honor. ...They don't give the death penalty, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...You didn't really do it, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">... Maybe I did, maybe I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If I've learned one thing today... it's that "silence" speaks louder than words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Man, my old man is wack. Disappointing, that's what he is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I heard he wants to leave the mob?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Over my dead body! I spend my life, trying to keep it real, being an O.G. and never stepping down. Now my old man wants to go soft? Fine, let him. Just leave me out of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">The day I get out of the clink... That's the day Alita and I start the next generation of the Kitaki Family.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Please don't talk as though it's assumed you're going to jail... for my sake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">'Bout half a year ago, I was shot during a little turf war with another family. I was ready to die, sure. But they came in and got me, hauled me off to the doc's.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...The Meraktis Clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That's where I met her. My fallen angel...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean Alita Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">She was scared of me at first, turns out. But you know what they say -- the bad guy always gets the ladies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">She was done with that clinic anyhow. So I was like, I'll take you on, woman! Straight gangster style. Guess what she said?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What did she say?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">C'mon, give it some thought! She said it real quiet-like, on the down low, know what I'm saying? "I'll leave... if you'll marry me."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... that was the proposal?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You know it! An oath of love, right there in the hospital room. Just like that, the op was done, and we were outta there. See ya later, bye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about that "op"...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah. Didn't go so well after all, did it? I know about the report. I know it's still in me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This health check-up was the Boss's idea, you said?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah. Can you imagine? What's the point of living healthy when you're a G, you know what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But didn't you learn about the bullet at that check-up?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah... That's when I knew that doctor had to pay. Figured I could get that cap pulled after I got my revenge. And hey, I'm still living large now, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Incidentally... had you ever had a health check-up before?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Naw, my old man suddenly gets this idea that we all gotta get check-ups! Guess he's getting old. Older, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wocky... You don't happen to recognize these, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey! Sure I do! I was the one who bought 'em for her.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">For... Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah. A birthday present. She's got mad little feet. Mad! So cute, man.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So these sandals are hers...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... I kinda had a feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">What's up with the funky vibes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Huh? What's that? Some kinda X-ray? Wait...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right, Wocky. It's yours.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey look, I don't smoke or nothing. I'll live long, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't think he gets it, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, take a closer look. Here, in particular... ...where it says "Nurse". ...It's signed "Alita Tiala".</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...Huh. You lawyers do your homework.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, you met Ms. Tiala when you...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah, I met her at the clinic. So?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you tell us a bit about the circumstances of your meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Fine, fine! I'll tell you how we met if you want to know that bad.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">... Man... that is so far off the hook, it's off the chain, G!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He seems preoccupied with something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...Wonder how my Alita's doing. Man, I miss her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If these sandals belong to Ms. Tiala... ...then is this print hers, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... Nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Eldoon! We've been looking all over for you!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">What's the matter, Trucy-doll?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Show him what we found! Nothing like expert advice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I... suppose he is a doctor still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon! Is everything OK?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">I'm just *sniffle* so happy! I just thought my doctor days were gone for good. *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Mr. Eldoon, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Hrm? A medical chart? Hey, you shouldn't go around taking these from clinics! ...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why the sudden silence, Mr. Eldoon?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">What...? What's going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's what we want to know! That chart belongs to my client.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's on trial... On suspicion of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">On trial! That's crazy! You can't put him on trial! He's ABD!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...ABD?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">All but dead. He's knocking on the Pearly Gates, and someone's about to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C-Can you tell us why?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">... Well, permit me to speak as a surgeon... You listen up good now, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No way... It's like he's a completely different person...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">Well, according to this chart... this "Wocky Kitaki" feller's not doing so well. He's got a bullet right up side his heart!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Yeah, but this chart talks about the post-op... In other words, the operation is already finished! ...But you can still see that bullet stuck in there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would it still be in there after the operation to remove it?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Well, 'bout the only reason I can think of is, it was too tricky to operate on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">That bullet's snug as a bug there next to the aorta, which is connected to the heart. Heck, that scrap of metal's just surrounded by blood vessels. Kind of a miracle. Two millimeters to either side and there'd be some serious bleeding going on in there. Not something yer average doc'd be eager to fiddle with.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Y-You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">It took a miracle to get that bullet stuck where it is. I'd take more than a miracle to take it out. It'd take a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... I'm only up to making rabbits disappear. I haven't learned bullets yet.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">'Course with the heart pumping and lungs working... That bullet's on the move. I'd give him another half a year, tops.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But Wocky's operation was already a half-year ago!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">That's why I'm saying you're outta time! This kid shouldn't be on trial! He should be on an operating table!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great... Just great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Mr. Eldoon, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You think we got time for that? Well, we don't. You see me without my bowl on, you're looking at a man who means business. So stop beating around the bush and get cutting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Better hear what he has to say while he's in a talkative mood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How could Dr. Meraktis do such a terrible thing? How could he just leave that bullet in there?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">I got a pretty good idea of how he felt... An emergency operation... He's got the kid's chest open on the table. Then he finds that bullet... That's despair right there, Trucy-doll. Cold despair.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Despair...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">'Bout the only thing he could do is sew the boy back up. He wasn't exactly in the situation to go admitting he couldn't take it out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Kitakis...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You bet. This kid's their only son, I hear. So, he skips the operation, and Wocky's back on the street living his life. 'Course, it's only a matter of time before his heart hemorrhages and he drops cold.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How awful...!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">And which doctor would they take him to? Meraktis. He's got enough ties to them, he could probably cover up the truth of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's just horrible! He left Wocky to die!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">There's a darkness in this world, Trucy-doll. Waiting, hungry. Compared to it, these gangs' turf wars are like kid games. When you're up against real evil... Well, it don't matter if you're weak or strong. It'll take you all the same.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... You were a surgeon, right Mr. Eldoon!? You could operate on Wocky, couldn't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...I wish.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">I'm afraid there ain't nobody in the country that could. Maybe not even in the world...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... So Wocky...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">He's real lucky to be alive even now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's one problem...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This chart... Look at the "Nurse" section... ...Alita Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! This operation was how they met.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, the problem is, she knew. She knew about Wocky's condition, guaranteed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't she ever tell him?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It doesn't make sense... If she knew her patient was in serious danger... ...you'd think she'd want to get that second operation before getting engaged!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What was she thinking!? Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What were you thinking, Alita Tiala...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Giving up already? Suit yourself. If you want to take another swing at it, just let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you doing!? Out of plaster already?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, give me a break! I'm just a beginner at this!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm not that far ahead of you, believe me! ...Fine. I'll make another batch. Don't mess it up this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Plaster, here comes Justice! *sigh*</thought></line>
</xml>