
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reclaimed</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My name is Phoenix Wright... ...head of the Wright Anything Agency, and a lawyer. Although, I was doing something else entirely for a while there. As for why I decided to formally get back into lawyering... ...let's just say there's unfinished business to take care of. Anyway, I thought I'd reminisce about my first case back on the job. And what a case it was! It happened only a few months after Athena joined our office...</line>
<line speaker="Whale">*Fweet!*</line>
<line speaker="Female pirate">Cap'n Orla! Ye made it just in time!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">*Fweet fwe fwe fwe fwe fweet!*</line>
<line speaker="Female pirate">Oh we be pirates. We love to sail the seven seas.</line>
<line speaker="Crowd">YEAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Today is my first day back on the job as a lawyer. Putting this attorney's badge on again really makes it hit home. Boy am I pumped! Even Trucy said, "Looking good, Daddy!"</thought> So Athena, Apollo, what do you think of the ol' attorney's badge?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! This Shipshape Aquarium's show is great! I can't get enough of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still can't believe they showed the Swashbuckler Spectacular on TV! Good thing I recorded this! ...Now, who's ready for another viewing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You've already watched it five times! Let's watch something else now!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How can you even suggest such a thing?! This show is therapeutic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, boss here, asking you guys a question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's so "therapeutic" about watching a killer whale?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Don't you know anything?! Animal-assisted therapy is an established psychiatric treatment!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're kidding. That kind of thing really exists?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a real thing! I've been to the aquarium myself to try it, and it really helps. I still go to there every now and then to further my psychology studies. The last time I went, I saw a dolphin and an orca swimming around together! It was so--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, do you two think you could quit goofing off and do some work for a change?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Work? But we've already cleaned the toilet... Twice. Each. ...Hey, wait a minute. Is that your badge I see?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! Congrats on getting your attorney's badge back, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. Starting today, I'm officially a lawyer again! <thought>Sheesh. Took 'em long enough to notice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gee, Mr. Wright... With that badge on, you suddenly look so... capable!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. Um, thanks? <thought>It's not like I was some lazy bum, you know!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what made you suddenly so fired up to get your badge back, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, well... I made a promise to a certain someone... An important promise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What could be so important...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, we have three lawyers now, so we'd better start taking on lots of work!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm all for that! Let's get this agency hoppin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, we have plenty of enthusiasm. All we need now are some clients... It's been eight years since I last wore this badge. I feel like a rookie all over again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="TV">...And this just in... The owner of Shipshape Aquarium, "Captain" Jack Shipley... ...has been murdered. The suspect in the case is reportedly already in custody inside the aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't that the aquarium we were just watching, Athena?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It is! ...I can't believe it! A murder at Shipshape Aquarium...?! But I love that place! We need to get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="???">R-Really? I guess I'm in luck, then! I need Phoenix Wright to save my friend!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-Who in the world is this?!</thought> Um... are you a client...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait... That costume... It looks just like... I've got it! You must work at Shipshape Aquarium!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right! You min-now it! I'm Sasha Buckler! I perform like an agile catfish in our pirate show! It'll blowfish your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Minnow"? "Blowfish"? Those puns floundered a bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! I figured out the client's identity! Chalk one up for analytical psychology!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">My friend is under suspicion of murder, so I really need some help. That's why I've gotta find this "Phoenix Wright" guy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm Phoenix Wright... And this is Apollo Justice and Athena Cykes. They're lawyers, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If there's anything you need, all you have to do is ask!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The same goes for me too, Ms. Buckler!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ha ha! Just call me "Sasha." And I'll call you all by your first names, too, if that's all right. Phoenix, Apollo, Athena, you have to help me! Please save my friend!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess we'd better start by asking her more about her defense request.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Buckler-- Sasha, could you tell us more about why you need our help?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">My friend is suspected of murdering the captain of Shipshape Aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Captain"? I thought the victim was the owner of the aquarium?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, well, our aquarium has a pirate ship theme. That's why we call the owner our "captain." We call the employees "crew," too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a pretty unusual aquarium you've got there.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Anyway, one of the crew members, my friend, is being suspected of the captain's murder. They've already decided she's guilty. I think they're going to give her the death penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?! <thought>What happened to "due process"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But my friend is as sweet and gentle as a whale shark! She wouldn't hurt a guppy! I know there's no way she murdered anyone, but they won't believe me! But with a name like "Wright," I figured you'd be able to help me set them straight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a minute... Don't tell me she picked you all because of a bad pun...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. I see my reputation doesn't precede me... <thought>But seriously. My name can't be the real reason she's here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Adds talk option">"Why request me?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the real reason you picked me, Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">...Well, to be honest, I asked a whole slew of lawyers, but they all refused. They said stuff like, "There's no merit to taking your case," or "I'm not sure I can help." They're all as cruel as sharks, with hearts punier than whitebait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! I can really feel Sasha's frustration!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With nobody on her side, she must feel all alone... But helping people like her is the whole reason I became a lawyer in the first place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">And then I heard about a lawyer named "Phoenix Wright." They say he defends clients to the end, no matter how bleak the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, guess my reputation DOES precede me. ...Not sure how well-deserved it is, though.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I thought to myself, if anybody can save my friend, it's you, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Quite a tall order there for a man who just got his badge back... But I don't want to let Sasha down... or her friend!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's help her, Mr. Wright! Let's save her friend!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's just what I was thinking. Sasha, we'll accept your case.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Y-You will?! Oh, thank you! You're a life-saver, literally!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Sorry. Sea creatures are the only things I know anything about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right. Don't worry about it. <thought>Gee, I didn't mean to put her in a funk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Well, no time to stand around and mullet over things! I want you to meet my friend right away! Come to Shipshape Aquarium with me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'll go, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I need you to stay here and keep an eye on the office until Trucy gets back. You never know when a new client might stop by.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How come I'M the one who has to stay behind?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks a million, Apollo. Well, ladies, let's move to the aquarium, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you think about this case, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder of the owner of Shipshape Aquarium? ............Gah. I can't think with you looking at me so expectantly. I don't really have any ideas. Sorry I'm not any help.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you ARE a help! As long as you're the one playing officesitter, you're "fine"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, there's Apollo's favorite word! I think I'll say it a few times, too. I'm fine! I'm fine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you two making fun of me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who, us? Of course not. <thought>Just yanking your chain a little.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, any ideas for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think you should give that Swashbuckler video a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Starting to become a fan, too, huh? I knew you'd like it if you gave it a chance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not so much that... I just thought it might give you some leads, seeing as it's the scene of the crime and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a good idea. I'll take a look when I get a second.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've got nothing better to do, so maybe I'll watch it a few times myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo... Please try to find something better to do...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The return of a legendary lawyer! It's kind of exciting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Kind of"?</thought> So how do I look with it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow! You present that thing like a real pro! You must've done it a thousand times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It never really seems like enough to just have it pinned to my lapel, for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get wanting to show it off. When I first became a lawyer, I flashed that badge left and right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, you still do that, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, this is gorgeous! It's just like being under the sea!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, this is the Aqua Tunnel, our pride and joy. I'm r-eel-y glad you like it! I'm going to go on ahead and fill the detective in on your arrival. Take a look around the tunnel, and then come meet me at the pool up ahead on the right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Boss! Look at this cute little fish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mmm... I bet it would be delicious grilled.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Seriously? Is that really all you can think of?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I didn't get to eat lunch today-- Ooh! And here comes some grilled chicken!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not a chicken! It's a penguin! C'mere, little cutie!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........It ignored me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it was hungry, too... Oh, look. It dropped something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! It's an ad for the Swashbuckler Spectacular show!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That penguin had a whole bunch of these stuffed in its backpack.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So it's passing out flyers, huh? How cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A carrier penguin that distributes flyers? ...We could use one of those for our office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, can't keep the client waiting! We'd better get going.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, you're right. Time to roll up our sleeves!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I don't see Sasha...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! Are you two the lawyers Ms. Buckler mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Detective Fulbright! Are you the lead detective on this case?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right. As long as evil exists in this world, there'll be no rest for me! And who is your sea urchin-like friend there? I don't believe we've met...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he talking about me?</thought> I'm the defendant's lawyer, Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I'm Detective Bobby Fulbright! People don't usually get to see this area. It's only open now because of the investigation. You two are pretty lucky to get this peek behind the scenes of an aquarium!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lucky... Right... <thought>This guy is even louder than Apollo...</thought> So, where is the suspect being questioned? And where is Ms. Buckler?</line>
<line speaker="???">Here I be, me buckos!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Shiver me timbers! There be one of Dread Pirate Nostache's scurvy swabs!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I beg your pardon?! I'm not anyone's "swab," "scurvy" or otherwise!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">More shameless than a sea lion ye be, tryin' to make off with me best bucko! If ye want to pick a fight with us, ye'd best bring along an army o' great white sharks!</line>
<line speaker="???">*squeek*... Fweeeeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sasha, what's going on here...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Let me introduce you! This is the friend I was telling you about! Her name is Ora Shipley... ...but she only responds to "Orla," so that's what people call her. I'm her trainer. She's the suspect in the murder, but she'd never hurt anybody.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">SHE'S the suspect...?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, and thank goodness you came before they put her down! I'm r-eel-y grateful to the two of you. I just know you'll save Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Don't tell me you didn't even know who your client was?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-An orca is the suspect? Our client is an orca?! Is this for real?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, did I forget to mention that? Oopsie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's one VERY BIG OOPSIE!</thought> By the way, what was with that mustache earlier...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, this be part of me costume for the Swashbuckler Spectacular! When I be wearin' the mustache, I be one of Cap'n Orla's Swashbucklers! A transformation as dramatic as a puffer fish's, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I would ever say that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's a pirate-themed aquarium, so that's why Orla is wearing a pirate hat, right?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yup! She really loves wearing hats. She puts them on all the time. But her fake mustache keeps falling off, so that's a problem...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... Well, why don't we start with you telling us a bit more about Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're really serious about me defending Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Of course I am! You're the only one who can do it, Phoenix! I heard you once questioned an animal during a trial, and that got your client off the hook!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! You did that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, ah... might've tried something like that at one point in my career...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, you're gonna have to tell me all about this later, or I'll ask Apollo for all the juicy details!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">When I heard you didn't discriminate against animals, I knew you'd hear me out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to warn you, though. I don't know anything about orcas. I mean, they don't... eat people, do they...?</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! FWEEEEEEET!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YIKES! <thought>I think I made her mad!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I won't have you talk that way in front of Orla! Orcas have feelings too, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, Boss! They have emotions just like we do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! <thought>Is anger the only feeling I inspire in women?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Don't worry. She says she forgives you! Besides, orcas are very picky eaters. Orla here only eats fish. The captain went to feed Orla this morning, and then he was found dead in this very room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us more about his death?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the owner of the aquarium, Jack Shipley, was discovered murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah... It was about 10:10 this morning, just after the aquarium opened. A visitor was viewing the orca pool from the visitor's corridor and screamed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The orca pool is this tank here?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, that's right. This pool is built so that guests can see into it from the corridor on the first floor. The security guard and I heard the scream and came running into this pool room... ...where we found the captain dead at the side of the pool in his Swashbuckler costume. He was as big and tough as an ol' crocodile, the captain. I still can't believe he's dead...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Shipley was very important to you, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Sorry. I didn't mean to get all sad goldfish on you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sad goldfish...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay. Time to snapper out of it! When it's showtime, it's time to smile! That's what the captain always said.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...By the way, do you know why exactly Orla is being accused of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you think of any reason why Orla would come under suspicion?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The police think Orla went berserk during practice for the Swashbuckler Spectacular. But Orla would never do anything like that! Right, Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweeeeeeet! Fwee, fwee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw, just look at that face! Isn't she adorable! The charges just HAVE to be false!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hate to break it to you, but the police don't usually base its decisions on "cuteness."</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! We base them on facts! Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A photo of the victim, huh?</thought> He's got a wound on his head.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Very perceptive! The victim and the orca were the only ones here. What's more, we couldn't find a weapon of any kind around.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So what's the theory on how Orla supposedly killed the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">They say orcas sometimes kill their prey by ramming into them underwater. We believe this orca did just that by pulling the victim into this 65-foot pool... ...and then ramming into him while they were in the water!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Without any suspects besides Orla, this could be one tough case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No official autopsy has been ordered, but an orca attack makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why hasn't one been ordered?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Accidental death due to a failure to exercise proper oversight over an animal. The medical examiner said it wasn't a homicide, so we don't need an autopsy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Orla's going to be put down without a proper investigation?! That isn't fair! That's nothing short of police negligence, Detective Fulbright!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The incident wasn't determined a homicide, so there's nothing we can do, Ms. Cykes! Ordinarily, the owner of the aquarium would be held responsible for the oversight failure... ...but the owner is the victim himself, so all we can do is hold the orca responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Phoenix! Isn't there anything you can do?! They're going to put Orla down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sasha and Orla are depending on me. I want to do everything I can to help them! But how do I help an orca? Wait... Yes, I can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll find the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, thank you, Phoenix! And I'll do everything I can to help you!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Wait just one moment! You're not a police officer or a prosecutor! You're not even officially the defendant's lawyer! You have no right to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not officially Orla's lawyer, huh...? In that case, I know exactly what I have to do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll set Orla free.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay! I'll go open the water gate!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">If you think I'll just let you set the suspect free, you've got another thing coming!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Pollocks to you, punk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess until I can actually try to prove Orla's innocence... ...I can't truly set her free... Which means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sasha">Do you two want to be in the Swashbuckler Spectacular?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have regular people participate?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Of course! We even have a special tour for people who want to be in it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What roles would we play if we said yes?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Let's see... The roles of a blue seahorse and a yellow sea slug are available!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judging by the colors, I must be the seahorse.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And I'm the sea slug?! No way! I won't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But sea slugs are all fluttery and beautiful, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They're... beautiful? In that case, I'll do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her mind is pretty much an open book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ha ha ha! I hope we can do a show together someday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I got my badge back now, so I know exactly what I have to do.</thought> ...I'll defend Orla in court.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even an orca deserves a fair trial. If the one responsible for Orla is dead... then I'll take responsibility for her!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'll what?! I guess doing crazy things just once in your career wasn't enough, huh? But what the heck! I'll take responsibility for her, too!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Are you two insane?! This is a case of accidental death caused by an animal! It's not a murder case! With no evidence of foul play, this case will never go to court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then let us investigate the crime scene. If we can prove this was a murder, we might be able to take it to trial. And then Orla would certainly need the help of a few good lawyers!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... I guess so... But who's ever heard of a trial for a killer whale?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just because it's never been done before doesn't mean we can't do it now!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But... Hmmmmmmmmm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please, Detective Fulbright! For justice's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">............ The police have determined that an animal that has harmed a human should be put down. But I don't know for sure whether that was a just decision... If your sense of justice compels you to take on the defense of this animal... ...then my sense of justice tells me to let this case be reexamined for possible merit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You mean it?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! That's fantastic! You're not such a bad guy after all, Detective Fulbright!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Just remember, this case hasn't been officially recognized as a homicide yet. I'll get in touch with the prosecutor's office, but I'm not making any promises. Anyway, I'd better be off!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You two are our lifeboat! I'll be right here if you need me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. I've got a feeling we'll really need your help with this investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We're still not sure if it'll go to trial, but as Orla's lawyers, we'll do everything we can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To get this case into court, we'll need a prosecutor to make an indictment... ...so we have to find enough evidence to prove it's a criminal case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There just has to be something that shows the culprit was somebody other than Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Detective Fulbright said there were no weapons in the area, other than her... ...so we'd better look for something to prove him wrong. I'd better make a note of that so I don't forget.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You sure are organized, Boss! Maybe I should get a notebook of my own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just like to jot down Notes on the case in the Court Record as I go along. We can use it as a sort of "To Do" list.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great idea! I'll add things, too. And whenever we're stuck, we can just refer to the notes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To read the Notes, I just open the Court Record (R</thought>. The I can switch between the tabs by touching them, or with R and L.) There! Note jotted. Now let's investigate this crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There has to be some evidence here we can use in court! Examining the crime scene from every angle is the key here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. If we change our perspective, we might come across new evidence. To change perspectives, I can touch the arrows on the bottom screen or use [D-Pad].</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or, if there's a particular spot that's got your attention, get right up to it and look away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like that outline of the body in the far right there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, talking to everybody involved is one of the keys to good investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. And if we Present items to people, we might learn even more.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right! It all boils down to thorough legwork! Well, let's get started!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let's run through why Orla is under suspicion one more time, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The police think Orla went berserk during practice for the Swashbuckler Spectacular.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No official autopsy has been ordered but the victim's head injury can be seen in the photo. The victim and Orla were the only ones here, and there was no weapon of any kind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">They think Orla dragged the victim into the pool, which is about 65 feet deep... ...and then rammed him in the water.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But Orla would never do anything like that! You two believe me, don't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We do. We agreed to take on your case, and we'll believe in you to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great! It's all settled, then. Let's start the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is that show makeup above Orla's eye?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. It's a starfish. Kinda makes her look like a punk-rockin' pirate, dontcha think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A punk-rock pirate killer whale...? *groan* It's official -- society's on the road to ruin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I think Orla is one hot rockfish! Speaking of rockin', how do you get Orla to do what you want during the show?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I give her signals with this whistle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? But I didn't hear anything just now.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The sound's out of the range of human hearing, just like a dog whistle. Orcas have better hearing than people do. They can even hear the whistle underwater.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's so cool! I wish I could give commands to Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Anybody can do that. All they'd have to do is learn the signals. Here, Athena. You can have one of our whistles. Consider it a present!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gee, thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">As for the actual commands, I'm afraid I can't teach them to you. They're top-secret.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is that show makeup above Orla's eye?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. It's a starfish. Kinda makes her look like a punk-rockin' pirate, dontcha think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A punk-rock pirate killer whale...? *groan* It's official -- society's on the road to ruin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I think Orla is one hot rockfish! Speaking of rockin', how do you get Orla to do what you want during the show?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I give her signals with this whistle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? But I didn't hear anything just now.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The sound's out of the range of human hearing, just like a dog whistle. Orcas have better hearing than people do. They can even hear the whistle underwater.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's so cool! I wish I could give commands to Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Anybody can do that. All they'd have to do is learn the signals.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Orla's not going to notice me from here. I'd better move around to the front...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't look like the ladder goes all the way down to the bottom of the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But there's usually water in the pool, so it doesn't need to. So apparently, the pool spans two whole floors. Ordinarily, visitors only get to see what they can from the first floor... ...but they said on TV that they sometimes give behind-the-scenes tours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds likes that Swashbuckler Spectacular show you recorded is really coming in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! Look at that huge octopus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be a show prop, too. One of its legs is missing, though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wouldn't it be exciting to take on a huge enemy like that?! I'd like to give it a try, myself -- as a lawyer, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You know you have an insufficient number of limbs to out-object it, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A setting sun... Sunsets always remind me how quickly the day goes by...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Boss! It's just a painted backdrop, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Down, Athena. Of course I know. I guess they use it for the Swashbuckler Spectacular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It looks handmade. Ooh, I just got an idea! Why don't we make our own "not guilty" backdrop?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And present it to the judge when things aren't going our way?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, we put psychological pressure on the judge by hanging it behind the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... almost want to see how the judge would respond to that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look! There's an apparatus here to hang from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's for people to hang from. It looks more like a crane to move things with.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Sasha was hanging from it during the Swashbuckler Spectacular. I bet there are all kinds of ways to use it, not just to move things. C'mon, Boss! Try thinking outside the box!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is she trying to say I have a narrow-minded view of things?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a piece of meat and a plastic hoop suspended from the ceiling. Talk about a clashy décor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Orla really likes meat. Who knew they fed her such huge chunks, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, all orcas are carnivores. You knew that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, silly! And I love meat, too! Protein is your body's basic building block, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that meat is made out of rubber. I doubt Orla could really eat it, even if she wanted to.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean to tell me she jumps all the way up there and doesn't get her reward? The poor girl! After all that effort!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think Orla is as dumb as you think she is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The doors are slightly open, and there are police officers standing guard outside.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess they're watching to make sure we don't try any funny business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, now that you've said it, I suddenly feel the urge to do something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How about if I suddenly break out some squat exercises? That would be pretty funny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... that might cause a few raised eyebrows in ways you don't want, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, look. There's a ball in the water. Is that another prop for the show?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's one of Orla's toys. She plays volleyball with it. It's usually in the bin. Guess I must've forgotten to put it away yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, I wish I could play volleyball with Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You have as much fight in you as a mean, old lobster! I like it! There aren't many people who wanna be on the receiving end of Orla's fast ball!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Her fast ball?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah. She likes to be naughty and slam the ball into things around the pool. You should hear the sound that ball makes when it crashes into stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">U-Uh, well, maybe some other time...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She suddenly went from "fighting lobster" to "reluctant hermit crab"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, there's a cannon in the shape of a shark! I'd love to try firing that thing! Boom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are these cannonballs supposed to look like fish eggs or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? But why fish eggs? Why not baby sharks? Think about how crazy it would be to have sharks go flying through the air! Watch the thrilling life-or-death struggle as the little tykes fight to stay alive out of water! I can see it now! The drama! The mayhem! The whirlwind of teeth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A tornado of sharks? Not even Hollywood could conjure up something that insane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the control panel for that crane apparatus. There sure are a lot of buttons...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When I see this many buttons, I start to get fidgety.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know what you mean. You start itching to push them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nah, I start itching to make a psychological study of people who want to push buttons!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Need I remind you that I'm your boss, not your guinea pig?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's too far away to get a good look. I'd better get a little closer first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What a mess! Was all this stuff knocked over when the victim struggle [sic] with his killer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's possible, but it would be hard to prove. Let's take a closer look, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at all this stuff scattered everywhere! I see some swords! I wonder if they have anything to do with the case?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're made of rubber. I doubt they could be used as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I still bet if someone got whapped with one, it would sting quite a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, I guess it would.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I think I could stand the pain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah? Good for you... <thought>Oh, look. There's a blow-up dolphin and an anchor, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Are you even listening to me? Stop looking at those toys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! Guess I've been caught red-faced!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. So this is where the body was found, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If they suspect Orla, maybe they found some evidence of an attack on the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla didn't attack the captain! She loved him! The captain rescued Orla when she was little, after she got beached on the shore. He tried to release her into the ocean, but she kept coming back. I can tell Orla's sad about losing the captain. She's just not her usual chipper self.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla must really love this aquarium and the captain.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">She's the only one around here big and strong enough to play with the big, tough captain. Every day, she made a point of head-butting him and stealing his hat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! I guess you weren't kidding when you said the captain was a really strong guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing much to see here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Under different circumstances, I would've loved to see the Swashbuckler Spectacular...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The three of us always performed the show together -- me, Orla, and the captain... Today's show has been canceled, but we could put on a little performance for you now! We be Cap'n Orla's Swashbucklers, me buckos! We love to sail the seven seas! We've come to rout that mangy blaggard, Dread Pirate Nostache! Avast! There he be, Nostache himself! Prepare to feed the fish!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... am I playing the role of "Nostache"?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, Sasha has a "stache," and you don't, so I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Hit 'im with yer water cannon, Cap'n, and spare no quarter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe fwe fweet. Fwe fwe fwe fweeet! Fwe fwe fwe fweet fwe fwe fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">We swim through storms and wave all because you see... Grand treasure and adventure's waitin' just for me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! That was awesome! Your performance packed quite a wallop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I, for one, feel like I took quite a beating...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Sorry 'bout that! Can't have a show without a bad-guy role, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But a singing orca, huh? It must've been tough to train her to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's Orla's best trick. She can only sing one song, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, she's still got one up on a pianist who can't play even one song...</thought> Well, now that we've had a taste of the show, we'd better do some more investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good idea. Let's go to the Aqua Tunnel!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, have you been using the whistle I gave you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! But I can't get Orla to do any tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't believe you can command that huge creature. That's pretty impressive, Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Pretty cool, huh? I bet there aren't too many people who can say... ...they literally get to "whistle while they work."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That must be pretty nice for you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But Orla is the one who's impressive, really, not me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's easy to see how much you care about Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You two are a good team.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What...?! But you and I are a great team, right? We can top that!</line>
<line speaker="Wright Anything Agency">Present</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Something you wear around your neck?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a whistle they use to make the orca do her tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I blow it at you, will you do a trick?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What am I, some kind of circus animal to you two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you ARE one of the talents here at our Wright Anything Agency, after all. The least you could do is learn a trick or two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Need I remind I'm a lawyer?! Besides, Athena doesn't know any tricks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! That's what YOU think! I've got a special trick I've been waiting to bust out. I can chug an entire glass of OJ without taking a breath, all while doing squats!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... that's, uh, really something, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I want to see Athena do squats...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence...? Does this mean you want me at the defense's bench in court?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I just wanted to see what you think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. Darn... In that case, I don't think you want to hear what I think.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We have to find some evidence that shows the culprit wasn't Orla! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're really fired up for this, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'm getting pretty good at investigating, thanks to that last case. So I want to show you how much I've learned! Vamos a hacer esto! Let's check out the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... I have noticed there's an amazing chemistry between Orla and Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not those kinds of ideas. I mean, any thoughts on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My thoughts are that we don't have enough information yet. That is what my heart is telling me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, you don't have any ideas. Got it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm so glad you got your attorney's badge back, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me too. I guess I was always meant to be a lawyer. I'm going to polish it up, shinier than it's ever been!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can top that! I'm going to polish mine until the finish comes off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind. You win.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, the Swashbuckler Spectacular is so exciting! I could watch it a hundred times! The fierce fighting, the graceful moves! Oh, Orla and Sasha are so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you love the show so much, why don't you try auditioning to be in it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, I know! The whole office could be in it together! We could be the "Anything Pirate Band"! You know, from the name of the agency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like a pretty pathetic pirate band to me. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you talking about?! It sounds cutthroat! It means we'd do "anything" to get our hands on treasure! Anything, no matter how brutal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes. We're a brutal pirate band?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Phwiiiiip! Phwiiip, phwiiip!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't ask if you could blow it. It's such a weird whistle, anyway. It doesn't even make a proper "whistle" sound.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Most people can't hear it, but I think I can hear it a little bit. It's like a message that only Orla's heart can receive! Aw, that's so sweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the same idea as a dog whistle, so I wonder if dogs can hear it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! Now you ruined it! You don't know anything about girls, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it. Your current state of mind is: "Gather all the information we can get." But let's concentrate on USEFUL information from now on, okay, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So you all done investigating the pool already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We had a good look around, but now we're moving on to other areas.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How is the police investigation going? Did you -- say, for example -- find any other suspects besides Orla...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Wouldn't that be fortunate for you if we did? But no, I'm afraid not. And even more unfortunate for you... ...I'm afraid we found decisive evidence of the orca's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What?!</thought> P-Please tell us more, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So what's this "decisive evidence"?! Don't hold out on us now, Detective Fulbright!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I'm very sorry, but I can't share classified information with the defense. Especially not security footage that shows the moment the orca attacked the victim! Yup, I'm to personally see to it that this baby stays safe! It will never leave my side!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">'Scuse me, but there's a call for you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I'll be right there! Sorry guys, you know how it is!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, he never said that HE wouldn't leave ITS side, I guess... Now, let's sneak a peek! Wh-What the--?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is this supposed to be  the moment Orla attacked the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This little bit of footage doesn't prove anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. I believe in Orla and Sasha. Let's just continue with our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good idea! ...Huh? There's a sticker on this camera that says, "Return to the Pub O' Danger."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess somebody there manages the cameras? Let's check it out later.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sorry about that. Prosecutor Blackquill called to remind me to go feed Taka. So where were we...? Oh, that's right! You two got any more questions for me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, we're good. Thank you. <thought>For leaking all your info!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">So that's your symbol of justice, is it? Well, this is MINE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Wow. He can whip that badge out pretty fast...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">We can top that! Take THIS! Twin attorney's badges!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aaagh! No fair! Two against one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No fair! Your police badge is bigger and flashier!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What?! You dare to call me... "unfair"?! Me, the very model of justice itself?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss! I'd say we won this round!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, in this battle there are no winners...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The poor victim... It's heart-wrenching! Crime cannot go unpunished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't want crime to go unpunished, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we'll do our utmost to defend our client.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm. Your form of justice or mine... Which is true justice? I guess we'll see how it plays out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, he doesn't have enough information right now to make up his mind. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for the translation, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! I have NOTHING to say about that! If you're lawyers of any mettle, you'll find the answers for yourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This looks like one of those hands-on exhibits. It has a real air of danger, don't you think?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the banner does say it's the "PUB O' DANGER"... </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see. According to the description, this room is... ..."A pub where pirates gather. Explore and interact with sea creatures! Actually feel the electricity of electric eels and feed real piranhas! Experience the terror of the seas with these dangerous experiments!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All of those sounds less like "terror" and more like "torture" to me!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem! I'd thank you to keep it down there, blue boy. I'm conducting an experiment! Do not disturb me, unless you wish to be zapped with an electric eel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-My apologies, ma'am. <thought>Wow. She seems intense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Excuse me, but who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">Before you ask others, shouldn't you give YOUR name first? Basic manners, young lady. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh, yes! Of course! My name is--</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Never mind. I will simply call you "yellow girl." It's easier that way. I am Norma DePlume. I am very interested in Shipshape Aquarium, and am a frequent visitor here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But... I don't want to be "yellow girl"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think I want to be called "blue boy"? ...*sigh* Let's just see what she has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You say you're interested in the aquarium, but you don't look like a staff member. Hmm... Let's see... I got it! You're someone completely unrelated to this aquarium!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's some deductive reasoning there champ.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I am a visitor, a patron, a customer, a guest... And  what might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not a "what"! I'm a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, that's what I was going to say!</thought> A-And I run a law office!   </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, whatever you are, I don't have the slightest interest. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! Just who does she think she is, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"A visitor, a patron, a customer, a guest," remember?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought they closed the aquarium and weren't letting members of the public in?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! But I have special permission, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why exactly is that, if I may ask?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, because of the incide-- Heavens! I've said too much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I remember this...! Psyche-Locks!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Psychedelic rock? Cyborg clocks? What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. "Psyche-Locks." It's the power of this Magatama. It gives me the ability to see the  secrets locked away in somebody's heart. If I can remove the locks, I can uncover their secrets. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't know you had a magical item like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like this lady knows something about what happened. I'll just use my Magatama and undo her Psyche-Locks. <thought>Huh? I can't see the locks anymore!</thought>      </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? The color of that stone looks different from before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's funny. Maybe it's just out of juice...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-It can do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. A certain girl I know poured her spiritual power into it for me. Without that power, I can't undo the Psyche-Locks.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Hmph! Why do I have to keep quiet about it, anyway?! I've never been any good at keeping secrets. But I did promise after all, so I guess I had better keep my mouth shut... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who did you promise what to?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">No comment. Now, go away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">&#42;sigh* Just when I thought we could find out more about the case...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's go try to find some other way! I'm sure we'll find something!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought they closed the aquarium and weren't letting members of the public in?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! But I have special permission, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why exactly is that, if I may ask?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, because of the incide-- Heavens! I've said too much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Without some spiritual power, the Magatama can't help me unlock Ms. DePlume's secret. I guess we'll just have to think of some other way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">A Swashbuckler flyer? I have more than enough of those already. Do you have any idea how many times I've visited this aquarium?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, what are you yelling at me for?</thought> Don't you ever get tired of coming here?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Hmph! You obviously don't know anything about Shipshape Aquarium. They feature different marine creatures each month, so visitors never get bored.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you're a fan of Shipshape Aquarium, like me?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh, please! I'm here to gather information-- the fundamental work of a great writer. But I don't suppose that's something you common folk would understand...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! That woman makes me so mad! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. Why don't we "common folk" just get back to our investigation?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Don't thrust that under my nose! I won't watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you usually pretty photogenic, Ms. DePlume?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Of course I am! I've been compared to a movie star! It's little wonder, with my perfect makeup and stylish figure. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She wants me to agree?!</thought> Let's get a woman's opinion on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? You're asking me?! Well, uh, let's see. I DO think you're very pretty, Ms. DePlume.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Hmm? I get the distinct impression your words are full of hidden meaning...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... I wouldn't say "full" so much as "full-figured"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Athena! I'd stop right there if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I have no interest in looking at meaningless trifles. As a matter of fact, I have no interest in looking at you, blue boy. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What, so now I'm a "meaningless trifle," too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Detective Fulbright's gone. It looks like the police investigation is over, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's too bad. I was hoping to get a little more out of him. </line>
<line speaker="???">Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo! Cleaner? Nuh uh. Feeder? That's right! Yo girl why you hidin' from me? I'm searching all 'round like this be a bad dream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that somebody... rapping?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Rifle yo sometimes you make me so mad. But now that you're gone I'm just so sad. Yo Rifle just come back to me. We can be together and sing kree kree kree!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with this guy, rapping and making strange bird sounds...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yikes! W-Who's there?! ...You didn't hear me rappin', did ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, well... Maybe...</line>
<line speaker="???">Arrrrrrr! Look, just do me a favor and pretend ya didn't hear nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fine by us. And who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I'm Marlon Rimes. I'm an animal keeper here. But the aquarium is already closed today. Um, at least, I'm pretty sure it is...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Pretty sure? You don't sound too certain... Oh! Are you new here or something?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Wow! Yeah, that's right! Pretty good guess! So who are you guys?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'm Athena Cykes. We're lawyers, and we're going to represent Orla... ...by taking her case to court and proving she's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">A-Are ya serious?! You wanna defend an orca in COURT?! ...Oh! But if you're here for Orla, that must make ya friends of Sasha's... Sorry if I came across rude.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like he's friends with Sasha.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sometimes when I'm by myself, I like to rap to pass the time. Especially when I'm around the animals I love. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I love animals, too! Especially marine creatures, like dolphins!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I like marine creatures, too. <thought>But just the ones you can eat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah? Well, people who like animals are good people. That's what I always say! If there's anything I can do for you two, just say the word! I just started workin' here, though, so I dunno how much help I can be. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Rimes seems pretty friendly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, friendly and agreeable.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, what exactly do you do here as an animal keeper?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Mainly, I clean the place and feed the animals. Wiping all this glass takes forever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can imagine... This tunnel alone must take most of the day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I also prep the food the animals eat. That's the hardest part of all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean, it's really difficult to get the hang of?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Nah, I mean, I'm a vegetarian, so cuttin' fish and meat and stuff up creeps me out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now there's something I never expected to hear from a pirate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about the incident that took place this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah. One of our guests saw what happened and started screamin'. I came runnin', but by the time I got there, I couldn't see the orca or the captain.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Speaking of the captain... what was he like?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Like a strong captain who can turn a wild bunch of ruffians into some great pirates... He always treated us fairly and equally, human and fishes alike. The real deal, man. ...Hey! Wh-what are YOU cryin' for?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm not crying! It's just, I can feel your heart crying, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">G-Girl, whatchu talkin' about?! I'm not cryin', either!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I won't mention that his eyes are puffier than a pair of pufferfish...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I bet Sasha and our vet Dr. Crab are even more upset by his death. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vet? This aquarium has a resident vet?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah... Yo, hold up! I haven't seen Dr. Crab this morning. Staff are supposed to stay put. The night shift has been on duty since last night, but they won't let us go home. Sasha even had to get special permission to go out looking for a lawyer this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... We haven't seen anybody who looks like a vet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Were you rapping something about looking for a weapon earlier? A rifle or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ha ha ha! No, not a weapon! "Rifle" is the name of one of our penguins.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A penguin? Why would you name a penguin something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ahoy! Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo! Prep for the battle, prep for the war! Little lady Rifle gon' even da score! Ya'll [sic] think you can escape with your pride? Nuh uh, you just gon' be straight up denied! Yo! Yo! Yo ho ho! Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo! Anyway, that's what she's like, so we named her " Rifle."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Okay, but did you have to rap it?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">That's just how I roll.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Does Rifle wear a backpack, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, that's the one! So you've seen her, huh? She's always runnin' away! She's such a good runner, we decided to put her to work deliverin' flyers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you really want a dangerous penguin like that running loose?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Aw, Rifle's not dangerous. She only attacks people she doesn't like. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">When we ran into her earlier, she didn't attack us. She straight up ignored us, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Hey, I have an idea! If you run into Rifle again, would ya mind feedin' her for me? She didn't come back to the pool at feedin' time like usual, so I've been lookin' for her. She loves the smell of fish, so she might come over to you if you have some.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I would LOVE to feed a penguin! That'd be okay, right, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't mind, as long as YOU carry the fish.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-U! It smells so... fishy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really? What a shocker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">With this flyer, you can get a penguin sleep mask the next time you come in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah? That would be nice, especially if it's free.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That'd be perfect for taking a nap at the office after going for a run or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I prefer you DIDN'T take naps at the office, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, I feel ya! Sometimes I fall asleep when I'm feedin' the animals.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Heh heh. We're kindred spirits, my sister. Kindred spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Two peas in a pod! Birds of a feather!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suddenly feel so alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, about this fish...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I'm the master keeper! No way you can beat me! You're a pro lawyer, but an amateur feeder! Ya'll [sic] ready for a feeding throw-down? Rifle c'mon! Time to defend da crown!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Uh, it doesn't look like Rifle's coming...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............I guess not, huh? Sorry about all that "throw-down" stuff, then... I just wanted to show ya the inner secrets of animal feedin'.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are "inner secrets"?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">You know, stuff like how to debone a fish. Great care goes into each animal's food. Then of course there's the way of tossin' the food to 'em. It's different for each one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see. Sorry to have bothered you with mundane questions from the uninitiated.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I'm new here, so I dunno.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't really think being "new here" has anything to do with it in this instance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Oh, yeah. Besides Rifle, I've been lookin' for Small Fry, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Small Fry"? Is that another penguin?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Nah, she's a friend I made, a high-school girl. She went off lookin' for Rifle somewhere and hasn't been back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is she... your girlfriend?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! Nah, no way! Sasha is the one I--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you like Ms. Buckler, do you!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, I-I really respect her, ya know? We have different tastes in music, but I admire the way she lives her life! It's not like I "like" her. It's more complicated than that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure that all adds up to "like"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">She tries to put on a brave face... ...but I think the captain's death is hittin' her hardest of all. After all, it was her human show partner that got killed by that orca.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you think Orla really did it?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, I can understand how Sasha feels... ...but she's the only one of us who doesn't think the orca did it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it isn't easy to believe in somebody who can't even speak up for herself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Anyway, let me know if you see Rifle or Small Fry, okay? Small Fry said she was gonna go check the orca pool. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe we'll head back there, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Apollo. Think you could whip us up a little meal with these?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fish? I haven't had fish for a while, come to think of it... ...The obvious question, though, is "What are you doing with a bunch of raw fish?!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's to feed the penguin with!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Penguin?! So why are you giving it to me to cook?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I dunno. I just happened to think of it, and I was hungry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then why don't we all go out for sushi when you wrap up the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're going to treat us?! How sweet of you! I'll start with tuna!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's really generous of you, Apollo. Don't forget to invite Trucy, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why did I even open my mouth?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You be givin' me a fish?! So you be challengin' me to a fight, eh?! Arr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! No! What kind of rule is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's how it goes in the Swashbuckler Spectacular! Present a fish. Start fighting. The gauntlet--I mean, the fish--is thrown down, and the glorious battle begins! Ooh, you're so cool when you're up there jumping and slashing!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Arr! Belay that talk, li'l lassie! Compliments will get ye naught!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! You sound just exactly like a real pirate! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena just eats this stuff up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? There's something on the left side of the pool that wasn't here before...</thought> It looks like an electronic sword...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Hey, you're back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hi, Sasha. What's with this strange sword here?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, that's a walkie-talkie. It's probably Rifle's.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Rifle can use a walkie-talkie?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">She's always running away, so we attached a walkie-talkie to her. If we can hear the sounds around her, we can usually guess where she is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But not if she drops the walkie-talkie on the floor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Every member of the crew has one, too, so we can communicate back and forth. We can even use them to broadcast to specific parts of the aquarium. Cool, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if Rifle's walkie-talkie is here, then Rifle might still be here, too! Rifle! Come out, come out, wherever you are!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Are you okay? You have to be careful around pools, or you might slip right in!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm more afraid of my heart jumping right out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, who's that riding on Orla? Isn't that Rifle?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right! C'mere, Rifle!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">............ *kree*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! She ignored mem again! Why doesn't that penguin like me?! Graaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now you've scared Rifle away with all that yelling...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'm not giving up! I'll MAKE that penguin like me if it's the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! Get back here, you little pipsqueak!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, sorry Rifle. But at least you seem alright.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey... It's... It's...</thought> Pearls?!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! Mr. Nick! I haven't seen you in ages!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could Pearls be the "Small Fry" Mr. Rimes was talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearls">Congratulations on your return to lawyering! I've been thinking about stopping by your office for a visit to congratulate you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is Pearl Fey. I call her "Pearls." She may dress a little funny... ...but that's because she's a spirit medium -- a real prodigy with great power, at that. I've known her since she was little, and she sometimes comes to the office to visit. She's just a little older than Trucy, so she's been like a big sister to her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearls">I guess everyone here knows Mr. Nick, then? He's such a nice guy, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Is she trying to be MY big sister too, now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you doing here, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My summer camp is here on a field trip. I've never been to such a big aquarium before, so I was really looking forward to it! But then that incident happened... and the police just finished questioning me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um...Mr. Nick...? Who is that lady next to you...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm Athena Cykes! I'm a new lawyer at the Wright Anything Agency!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, how do you do! My name is Pearl Fey. My cousin and my friends call me "Pearly."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Pearly" it is, then! Nice to meet you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So... how did the two of you meet...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you know how I used to travel to Europe to study their legal systems, Pearls? I met Athena on one of those trips.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So, tell me more about how the two of you met in Europe. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I thought I was supposed to be asking the questions here!</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Athena">A long time ago, Mr. Wright helped me out of a difficult jam. That's when I started thinking about becoming a lawyer like him.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So you're like her mentor, huh, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, something like that, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright is the whole reason I am who I am today! He was the one who told me my knowledge of psychology could help people in court!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Gee, Mr. Nick, it looks like you've become a real adult since the last time I saw you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've always been an adult the entire time I've known you, Pearls!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I'm so happy you get to be a lawyer again, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. Thanks. I let our friends know I was back, too.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wish we could all get together. It's been quite a while! Maybe we should throw you a surprise party to celebrate your comeback.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would be really nice. But if you tell me about it, it won't be a surprise, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! B-But we could spring it on you after you had forgotten, and still surprise you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I was really looking forward to seeing the Swashbuckler Spectacular... It's such a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I bet you would've really enjoyed it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But I was really happy to see such a large marine animal! It was quite an experience! ...I still have yet to see a blue whale, though, the largest marine animal of them all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, uh... I doubt there are any blue whales at the aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh my! Did you go fishing, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, this is for Rifle. We were asked to feed her.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh, that sounds like fun! Do you think she would take food from me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sure she would--from you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...So what you're really trying to say is that Rifle wouldn't take food from ME, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's not what I meant. <thought>That IS what I meant, though.</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! I won't be bested! Pearly, it's ON!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What? What's "on"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now, Athena. Let's be adults about this. You've got poor Pearls here all confused.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You know I'd do anything I could to help you! ...But I'm afraid I don't really know anything about that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right, Pearls. No worries.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, would you look at that! Rifle loves you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She sure does seem to be attracted to Pearls...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee! I'm so glad she likes me! Penguins are so adorable, aren't they! I even bought myself a little penguin calendar here at the aquarium gift shop. I have it hanging from my bag already!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, how cute! A calendar in the shape of a penguin!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That calendar is a real hit with all our female visitors. I even have one myself! But the rest of the staff thinks it's... too cutesy. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it doesn't really fit the whole "rough-and-tumble pirate" image very well... But, hmm... why does this calendar smell kind of like fish...?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wh-What do you mean, Mr. Nick?! Please don't be rude!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. I got Pearls mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were looking for Rifle, too?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That's right. I was trying to help Mr. Marlon, the animal keeper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">C'mere, Rifle! C'mon!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She went towards Orla instead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrrrr! Why can't I get Rifle to like me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you should quit chasing after her with that scowl of yours...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! How could you speak to a lady so rudely?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. I got Pearls mad... again.</thought> Why don't you try to get Rifle to take some food from you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, great idea! And I have just the thing to offer her, too!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Isn't it cute? I really love this calendar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's shaped like a penguin. It is pretty cute, isn't it? Maybe I should buy a calendar for the office before I leave. I always run out of room to write appointments in my planner.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't you just put your appointments on your phone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not very good at using electronic devices...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, neither am I. Hee hee! We have something in common!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw, now I feel left out.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! Orla ate my love-filled fish! At least it looks like she enjoyed it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think Orla and I just had a bonding moment!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Friendship blossoming with the exchange of some food! Oh, isn't it moving, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think "moving" might be going a bit far... Anyway, how did you get Rifle to come to you so easily, Pearls? I heard Rifle was attracted to the smell of fish...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">M-Mr. Nick! Are you saying I smell like fish?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, maybe just a little, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm... I guess I need to change my clothes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's odd... I wonder why Pearls smells like she's holding a bucket of fish...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Hmm... Orla doesn't usually want to eat at this time of day... And we've even been giving her more food than normal at her regular meal times lately...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there something wrong with Orla's feeding habits lately?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, something's weird. The new guy, Marlon, feeds all the other animals besides Orla. But the captain and I, her trainer, are responsible for feeding Orla. It was the captain's turn to feed Orla this morning. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Orla keeps coming to me and signaling she's still hungry. She wants my fish, chock-filled with love!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How long are you going to keep saying that? <thought>She sure is excited to make a new friend.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But I don't think the captain would've forgotten to feed Orla...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Rifle and that big creature there certainly seem to love each other!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">This is Orla the orca. Rifle and Orla are best friends! They belong together like a clownfish and a sea anemone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Care to phrase that in a way us non-biology majors can understand...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! So this orca is the suspect. I-I read in a book once that orcas eat penguins...!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Don't you worry about that. Orla here's really gentle, and she never eats anything but fish.</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">*kree!* *kreeeee!*</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee... Fwee, fwee...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">She's an ol' sweetheart. As a matter of fact, she even tolerates Rifle picking on her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true, she does seem very gentle. She hardly seems like a "killer" whale...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As lawyers, we have to do everything we can to save this beautiful, gentle creature!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow, you're going to defend her in court? She's... quite the defendant, isn't she...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's the biggest defendant we've ever had. <thought>Literally!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Pearls. I have a big favor to ask. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's about my Magatama... Its spiritual power seems to have vanished. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! That Magatama brings back memories! I remember pouring my spiritual power into it. That was so many years ago... I guess that's why it's almost out now. ...There you go, Mr. Nick. It should be fine now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Pearls! Now I can break Psyche-Locks again. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. I'm glad I could help! Well, I think I'll go find Mr. Marlon now. I have to bring Rifle to him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Pearly sure seems right at home at this aquarium. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, you're right. But didn't she say this was her first time here...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Apparently, that girl was in the staff corridor earlier this morning. That's why the detective was questioning her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was Pearls doing in the staff corridor?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I dunno. I thought she was Marlon's friend or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The staff corridor, huh...? Something about that doesn't sit well with me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if it bothers you, why don't you just ask her about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, good idea. Let's go catch up with her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But we should give the scene another look, too, though. We might've missed something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! That's one of the basic rules of investigating! "The lawyer always returns to the scene of the investigation."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wasn't that "The criminal always returns to the scene of the crime"?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There sure are a lot of interesting characters at Shipshape Aquarium! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll say. It's like a wild pirate ship. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess they really wanted to give the place an authentic piratey flavor. Like the sea-bottom Aqua Tunnel, and the Exploration Corner, "where pirates gather"!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Arr! Let's have some fun, me hearties!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yikes! Widget, you scared me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's save the pirate fun for AFTER the investigation, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. That smells awful! Please keep it away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you're the one who wanted it. Why do I have to carry it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla sure eats a lot, doesn't she? I used to eat a lot when I was a kid. Took lots of naps, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you still take lots of naps, right here at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! You knew about that?! I-It's this new thing I'm trying out! Um... sleep learning! Yeah, that's the ticket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not buying it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Mr. Rimes and Pearls are talking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ahoy! Based Small Fry was so clutch with the assist! Rimes n' Rifle reunion, a tale endin' in bliss! Now animal keeper Rimes ain't gonna get cut! Mad props, Small Fry, this case is now shut! Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. It was my pleasure. See you again sometime, Rifle!</line>
<line speaker="Rifle">Kree...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Okay, let's go Rifle. See ya, Small Fry!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mr. Nick! I didn't see you there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Pearly, you and Mr. Rimes seem to be really good friends.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us more about your relationship?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">&#33; W-Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Pearls, why do I see a Psyche-Lock?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... I'm sorry, Mr. Nick... But I really shouldn't talk about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I don't really feel right about digging into Pearls's affairs... But she was here at the aquarium at the time of the incident... Whatever she's hiding could help us in court! Sorry Pearls, but I'll have to use my Magatama on you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">1 PSYCHE-LOCK</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock... A lock on a person's heart that only I can see... The deeper the secret is hidden, the more locks there will be. Pearls only has one lock, so I should be able to undo it fairly easily. But if I make a mistake, I'll be locked in a loop and won't be able to move forward. Okay, time to give it a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls, you have to tell me about your relationship with Mr. Rimes. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Relationship"? There is no "relationship" between Mr. Marlon and me. We're just a visitor to the aquarium and an animal keeper at the aquarium, that's all. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there are areas where ordinary "visitors to the aquarium" don't get to go... You were here before the incident occurred, weren't you? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Proof...? No, can't say that I do... <thought>Hmm... I'd better give it another try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes! That's right... ...But how did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone told me you were there.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I got confused and went the wrong way. I didn't know it was a corridor just for the staff. But that's all it was, Mr. Nick! It didn't have anything to do with Mr. Marlon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds reasonable. I guess I'd better move on to my next topic.</thought> Actually, there's something else I've been wondering about, Pearls... Why do you smell like fish?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">F-Fish? Wh-What makes you think I smell like fish?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's a certain someone who convinced me it wasn't my imagination. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, I guess not... <thought>When it comes to sniffing out the smell of fish, there's only one nose that I can rely on!</thought> Pearls, I want you to be honest with me. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">R-Rifle...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's apparently very attracted to the smell of fish. Rifle didn't want anything to do with Athena, even though she had a bunch of fish. So why then, was Rifle so attracted to you, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Errr... I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Looks like she's still not ready to talk about it.</thought> You had an object with you that smelled fishy, too. In fact, I think this has something to do with your secret.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearl:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that wasn't it. The key here is something that smells fishy.</thought> Let me try that again, Pearls. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fishy smelling calendar has something to do with your secret, doesn't it, Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A-Aaaaaaah! I... I can't lie to you, Mr. Nick... I'll tell you about me and Mr. Marlon, and about the calendar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew. It was only one lock, but it sure took some work!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me about your relationship with Mr. Rimes.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I became distracted by the gift shop almost as soon as we got to the aquarium. Before I knew it, everyone else had moved on, and I got lost. I was so embarrassed to be lost at my age!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Pearls. I know big, crowded places are hard for you.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I sort of panicked... and went down the wrong corridor. I ended up in the food prep room, and that's where I met Mr. Marlon. I really startled him when I called out to him. He jumped so much, he startled me, too, and I lost my balance and fell down. Oh, Mr. Nick! I spilled so many fish all over the floor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that explains why you smell fishy, pardon the pun.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. And my calendar fell off my bag and got buried in all the fish, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But it doesn't explain why Pearls wanted to keep it a secret.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you want to hide your meeting with Mr. Rimes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Well, I didn't want him to get in trouble over feed sanitation regulations because of me. And Mr. Marlon said he didn't want anyone to know he was in the food prep room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Why not? What was he doing in there?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Before I spoke to him, he was starting at a calendar. But, because of me, he dropped his calendar, too. We had to search for it among the fish.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait a minute... This calendar of yours... It already has writing in it!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It does? But I didn't write anything in it yet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's something written here under today's date. "Meet the captain at the orca pool at 7 am."</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe my calendar and Mr. Marlon's got mixed up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls, about what time did you run into Mr. Rimes?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I think it was about 10:15 when he had the info desk announce that I was lost... So I must have first gone into the prep room at about 10:10.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Do you mind if I hang on to this calendar for a while? It might be a clue to the victim's movements before he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...All right. But be sure to give it back to Mr. Marlon later, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good. Now maybe I'm ready to remove Ms. DePlume's Psyche-Locks, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">You people again? You're becoming quite the nuisance. If that veterinarian won't come out, then I might just have to give up and leave.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Veterinarian...? Is that the "Dr. Crab" Mr. Rimes was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">You are correct. He likes to shut himself up in that back room there and won't come out. But I don't think he's even in there today, so I'm about ready to go home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She sure seems to know a lot about the workings of this aquarium. And maybe a little something about the incident this morning, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! This is no time to be standing there thinking to yourself! It's time to put your psychedelic clock skills to work and uncover her secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's "Psyche-Lock," Athena. "Psyche-Lock."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought they closed the aquarium and weren't letting members of the public in?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! But I have special permission, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why exactly is that, if I may ask?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, because of the incide-- Heavens! I've said too much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All right. Now that I can see her Psyche-Locks again... ...I just have to tap my Magatama to start removing them!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">2 PSYCHE-LOCKS</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume, I want you to tell me the secret you're hiding.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I'll do nothing of the sort! It would mean breaking my promise. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know who you made this promise to... but you WILL tell me. You're not an aquarium employee, and yet, here you are, after the place has closed. That must mean you're connected to the incident involving the owner somehow.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! I don't know anything about any "incident" involving the owner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I think you do. I have a piece of evidence here that suggests you DO know something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...What is the point of showing me that, blue boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... <thought>I guess this wasn't it. I know I have something here somewhere that shows Ms. DePlume knows something.</thought> ...All right, then. Let me try one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to Detective Fulbright, this shows the orca attacking the victim. And the person in this footage... is wearing an outfit just like yours, Ms. DePlume.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh! I suppose there is no hiding this bombshell figure, is there? Yes, it is I.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I think I can guess why you're here at the aquarium. You aren't simply a visitor to the aquarium; what you really are is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are a police investigator.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! You're completely off the mark. I think you know full well that I am NOT a police investigator. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I full well did NOT know that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got it! You are... <thought>Now, what did they call them here again...?</thought> You're a "crew member' of Shipshape Aquarium!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! What amusing jokes you tell, blue boy. Even a child could tell you I am NOT an employee here. And please don't call them "crew members." Have you no self-respect at all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! All right, fine. It's not like I wanted to call them that in the first place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are a visitor who also happened to witness the death of owner Jack Shipley. </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That is cor-- Oh, I want to say it! But I promised the police...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not good for you to keep things inside, you know. I'm sure you'll feel much better once you get it all out.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I-I-I... I give up! I'll tell you everythiiiiiiiiiiiiiing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If she wanted to tell me this badly, why couldn't she have just done so from the top?</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I think anyone would agree that I held it in for as long as I could! But I couldn't be expected to withstand this commoner's badgering any longer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please calm yourself, Ms. DePlume! <thought>And that's "top-class badgering" to you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">You are correct. I witnessed the killer whale's crime with my own eyes! You got a problem with that, blue boy?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, Ms. DePlume's anger is so powerful... ...even I feel like I'm about to explode! You have to do something! Quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please don't explode on me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you start with telling me what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I witnessed the very moment the killer whale attacked the victim. I told the police what I saw as well. I'm the sort of person who simply can't rest until the truth is known.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So both Ms. DePlume's statement and the footage point to Orla's guilt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? Pardon me, but you seem pretty pleased that you witnessed this incident...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">What? "Pleased"? Shame on you! Are you implying that I am happy about an innocent man's death?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No, of course not! I... I just don't get the sense that you were afraid of Orla. It's more like you were... interested in her.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Are you...? You know, I wasn't sure, but I was thinking that maybe... Are you perhaps one of my fans? Is that how you knew... ...that I am THE nonfiction writer, Norma DePlume?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! THAT Norma DePlume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... big fan, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! I've never even heard of her!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, now that you've figured me out, there's no sense in trying to hide who I am, I suppose. Talking to fans is part of a writer's duty, after all! Oh ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But I'm not a fan, I tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what exactly have you written, Ms. DePlume?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh, my. You mean to say you truly aren't familiar with my work? I write the truth. I take great pride in my craft, you know. I've been gathering information on Orla the killer whale for a year now. I've been very worried about Orla's violent tendencies... And today, my concern was proven to be well justified!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla isn't violent! She's a sweet and gentle soul!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! The moment you let your guard down with that killer whale... CHOMP! Shipshape Aquarium has always denied the killer whale's violent streak. But it has been rumored to attack people...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But rumors are just rumors! They aren't necessarily true!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes, I realize that. But I only write the truth. That is why I questioned the owner directly. But he refused to allow my research, and he even had the audacity to say to me: "You're nothing but a nuisance, coming here day after day. Don't ever come back again!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like her "research" was a bit too much to take...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But then... how did you get in here if you've been blacklisted?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I have my methods. Oh ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This lady is shameless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We won't let you speak badly of Orla! We're going to defend her!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I'm only stating what I saw with my very own eyes. I came to the aquarium today to observe the killer whale. But on my way to that thing's tank, I heard its cries. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can hear Orla from the visitor's corridor?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">There are speakers there in the corridor, up near the ceiling. Apparently, that speaker is there so visitors can hear the killer whale's sounds. In any case, as I approached the killer whale's tank, I heard its cries. And when I arrived, I saw something terrifying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you see?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">The killer whale stealing the Swashbuckler Spectacular hat the owner was wearing... ...and then, the moment it bit him and shook him mercilessly to death within its jaws!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla... bit the owner to death...?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust! So I take it Ms. DePlume's just finished telling you what she saw?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Detective Fulbright! I guess you've already heard it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yup, when we took her statement earlier. As you heard, I'm afraid that accidental death is really the only thing it could be.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes! And a dangerous creature like that cannot be allowed to harm anyone ever again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But she's not dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sorry, but the Prosecutor's Office said the case didn't have enough merit to go to trial. There was one prosecutor, though, who expressed an interest in the case... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! Then could we have that prosecutor take a look at the investigation reports?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Unfortunately, I doubt even he'd take action without evidence of a homicide... Look, I understand how you feel, Mr. Lawyer, but maybe you should give up on this one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a chance. We'll just re-examine the crime scene and strengthen our case.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, if that's your version of justice, I won't stop you. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, then! Let's start the re-examination! Pronto! I'm going to go check out that mess in the back one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena! Wait! No running!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Are you okay? <thought>It didn't look like she tripped, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">*groan* I slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Orla? What is it, girl?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena! Are you all right?! <thought>She crashed into all that stuff behind her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">*groan* I tried to get out of the way, but all I did was slip and fall... again... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was a pretty amazing wipeout. Are you hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm okay... But why did Orla spike that ball at me? After all the fish I gave her, I thought she liked me... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe she thought you were the main entrée?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Very funny, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. In any case, let's give the ball back to Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Looks like everything got shifted around when I fell on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. There are things now that we couldn't see before. <thought>Like another ball. I guess Orla really likes them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look! There's something new by the outline of the body, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd better take a good look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla sure can hit that ball hard!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't think she was gonna spike it at me like that. I guess that must mean she likes me! I gladly accept her expression of affection!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Not how I would've interpreted that, but whatever floats your boat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we just found that giant octopus prop's missing leg. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. I bet you could get a whole lot of Carpaccio from a giant leg like that! Ooh, let's go to the ocean and try and catch a giant octopus of our own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but even if we did catch one, how are you planning to slice it up?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Kein Problem! That's what man invented chainsaws for!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've never seen anyone so hell-bent on chomping down some giant octopus...</thought>    Well, I doubt we could catch one that big anywhere near the shore, anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The more roadblocks you throw up, the more I want to do it, you know. Ooh, I can't wait to get started!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It would appear that Operation Discourage Insanity has backfired...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look at this mark on the floor. What do you suppose it is?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's where we stand when we want to play volleyball with Orla. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Volleyball, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah. If we stand there, she'll spike the ball right at us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So when Orla spiked the ball at me earlier... ...that was one of her tricks?! It doesn't mean she hates me?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Nah! She wanted to play with you! She loves volleyball. She used to play with the captain all the time...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw... Sasha looks so sad... </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay, time to snap out of it! This is no time to be all dejected and mopey like a blobfish!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! Time to put on a smile and stay strong, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's a blobfish? ...Or do I not want to know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A coin...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Wright! There's blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right! But it's dried. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you think it could be the victim's? And what was it doing all the way over here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I'm not sure, but now that we've found blood outside the pool... ...it just might help us prove that there's more to this case than just "accidental death."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right! Orla certainly can't leave the pool, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of coins, take a look at this. There are a few coins around the body here, too. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right, Boss! But where did they go? They aren't here anymore. You don't think somebody picked them up, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a broken sword here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... The tip of the blade is missing. Guess it just broke off. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell me it happened when Athena fell over...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'd better not be trying to pin the blame on me, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! N-No! Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No use trying to hide it. It's written all over your face! Besides, the broken part isn't even here. How could it have been my fault?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better watch what I think or I'll get every little thing thrown back in my face.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh no! That child is hurt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Call an ambulance-- Hey, it's just a dummy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-It is?! Oh, I mean, of course it is! I was just testing your response to an emergency.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess we just found that you don't bluff well under pressure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr! I guess I'll just have to keep practicing, then! I wonder what the dummy is for, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, that? We use it to train Orla. It's smaller than a human, but it does the job. Some of our tricks can be pretty dangerous, so Orla practices them on the dummy first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Forget the tricks, those bite marks look pretty dangerous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Sasha? Would you happen to know anything about this coin?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Oh, I guess I missed one. I just finished cleaning up the rest of them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You picked up all of the coins already?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. After the police finished their investigation, they gave me the go-ahead. I haven't found them all yet, though. I'm still missing a few.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if they aren't beside the pool, maybe they're IN the pool. Let's go to that ladder over there and take a peek at the bottom of the pool, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't see anything from here. I'll have to take a look when I'm by the ladder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look! I think I see something on the bottom of the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! I knew it! Want me to go down and check?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't jump in dressed like that! You'll drown under the weight of your clothes! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I won't! I'm a pretty good swimmer, you know! </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Whew! Phoenix! Look at all these coins I found at the bottom! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Sasha. So there really were more of them down there, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We seem to be finding them all over. I wonder how many there are all together?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Including the ones I put away, there are 300 of them. They're for the show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Sounds like they'd be heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">About seven pounds, I'd say. A little lighter than a stringfish. Well, I'd better go put these coins away where they belong!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, seven pounds of coins, scattered around the scene, one of them with blood on it... They have to be related to the case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder how the blood got on that one coin? Wait a minute. Could it be...?</thought> Remember how Detective Fulbright said that they couldn't find a murder weapon? Well, what if these coins were the weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? How could a little coin kill a grown man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, one coin by itself isn't much of a threat, but... 300 coins together could definitely be used as a weapon. All you'd have to do is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet a frozen lump of coins would make for a pretty good weapon. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">But wouldn't it make more sense to freeze just the water into a block of ice? That way, there'd be no evidence of it ever existing once it melted. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I guess you're right. <thought>But, wait a minute. There IS another way to bundle coins together!</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet you could kill a man if you threw them hard enough. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I dunno about that. I think they'd just bounce off. Besides, how could you throw them that hard all at once?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... <thought>Wait a minute...! Maybe there IS a way to bundle them all together...</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you put seven pounds of coins in a bag and swung it at somebody... ...it would make a pretty formidable blunt instrument, wouldn't it? It would explain how blood got on this coin.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I get it! If that bag of coins is the weapon, then we can use it to prove Orla's innocence! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I don't see anything resembling a coin bag around here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe the killer took it with them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it would certainly make it look like Orla did it if they did...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know what I think, Mr. Wright?! The bloody coin alone should be enough to prove this might have been a murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. It shows the possibility of a human killer rather than Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes! This is just what we needed! Let's go show this coin to Detective Fulbright and Ms. DePlume right away!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, you're back! So did you find anything?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Of course he didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Remember, even if you don't succeed, it's the effort you make that's important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is he trying to console me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's show them the evidence we found! The one that points to a human culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Because we won't let Orla be put down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this bloodstained coin.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek! C-Cease and desist, at once! Wh-What kind of a man shows a lady blood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>She doesn't have to get so worked up...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What are you terrorizing this lady with?! Come on, now. Let's see it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found this coin beside the orca pool.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">We did see a large number of coins beside the pool, but not one with blood on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We just learned that there's 300 of these, weighing about seven pounds all together. Now, what do you suppose would happen if a person was assaulted with that many coins?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What?! So you're saying the coins might've been used like some kind of blunt weapon?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the blood belong to the victim, then yes, it's entirely possible!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... But I wouldn't call it decisive proof that the real culprit was human... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You wouldn't?! Why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Because there'd have to be something to put the coins in to make them into a weapon. Without that "something", it's just not going to be enough to pass muster. But I will say that your theory does seem to warrant further investigation. I'll call the Prosecutor's Office and ask to reinvestigate from a possible criminal angle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You will?! Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I really hope Detective Fulbright can convince them...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmmmm... You won't believe the answer I got. When I explained your passion for this case, and the police's investigation... ...they said that the prosecutor I mentioned earlier would be willing to take this to court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?! So does that mean a new suspect has emerged?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No, I'm afraid not... To be frank... ...Prosecutor Blackquill said he just wants to prove that orca's guilt in court!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHAAAAAAAT?! It's Prosecutor Blackquill that wants to prosecute Orla?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's fine, Detective. Thanks for arranging this for us.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I must say you're taking this rather calmly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Defending Orla in court was my idea from the start. And I'll do whatever it takes to save her.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... In that case, I'll do whatever I can as well to see that justice is served. Ms. DePlume, will you be a witness for the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">A trial for a killer whale? I've never heard of such recklessness before in my life! But I will reveal the truth about this killer whale, and then write all about it!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Sounds like a plan! Now, if you'll just come along with me... We have to prepare for tomorrow, and I still have to arrange for an autopsy.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! I look forward to tomorrow! Until then, blue lawyer and yellow fan.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I AM NOT A FAN!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, at least we managed to get the case to go to trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But how in the world do we defend an orca in court, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest, I'm not really sure myself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Plus, Ms. DePlume said Orla bit the victim... This trial sure isn't going to be easy... ...but I love a challenge!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. Then we ought to be just fine. Guess I should go over that Swashbuckler Spectacular you were watching this morning. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! We can have a formal viewing back at the office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I've seen enough of the inside the pool... [sic] but maybe just one more look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I have enough evidence, but maybe I should do a bit more thinking first...</thought></line>
</xml>