
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Airlines</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The murder that occurred in my office... The return of the Great Thief Yatagarasu... Thinking back, everything began on that fateful day, two days ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, everything began high up in the air, 9,000 feet in the air, to be precise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="PA Notice">Thank you for flying iFly Airlines. We are currently experiencing some slight turbulence. We are asking all passengers to please return to their seats and fasten their seatbelts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Nnngh... ..Why do I feel like I just woke up from a horrible nightmare? <thought>6:13, huh... Guess I was out cold for about 10 minutes. Hah, "slight" turbulence, indeed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="PA Notice">Ladies and gentlemen, we are currently experiencing some slight turbulence. For your safety, we ask that you return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose turbulence is to be expected on a flight. Though admittedly, I'm less than comfortable with anything resembling earthquakes... Hm? What's this...? A travel wallet? But it's not mine... How did someone else's travel wallet wind up in my pocket...? Nnngh...! My head... Why won't this headache go away...? I'll take care of this travel wallet later. Or hand it off to an attendant...</thought> Unngh... From earthquake-like turbulence to an elevator... ............ Hmph. What am I doing hesitating like this? <thought>Actually, I know full well why I hesitate. It was when I was still but a young child... I was caught up in a murder that happened in an elevator. But how long am I going to let past haunt me!? It's just an elevator! I'm a grown man now! I need to behave like one!</thought> Wh......What the...!? What in the world happened!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Is there something wrong, sir? I must ask that you please return to your se... ...eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek! He... He-He-He's DEAD!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please calm down! We mustn't jump to conclusions without all the facts...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">What's wrong!? Did something happen!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Y...You MURDERER!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? N-NO! You have it all wrong! It wasn't me!!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Everyone, I am sorry to interrupt, but I have an important announcement. I am one of your flight attendants today, Rhoda Teneiro. Unfortunately, we have just had a minor accident on this flight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">An "accident"!? Don't treat us like we're stupid! I caught a glimpse and it was a murder!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">What!? M-Murder!? What's going on with this flight!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Everyone, please calm down. There's no reason to panic. The flight will stay on course and make its scheduled landing. We are still currently in the middle of a rough patch of turbulence. So until we are out of this area of turbulence, I ask that you please remain seated...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">B-B-But, someone was killed, right!? I mean, what about the killer!? Let me off...!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Please, there is no need to feel threatened. We already apprehended the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I ask that everyone please remain calm.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">What the heck is he talking about!? Why should we remain calm!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My name is Miles Edgeworth. I am a prosecutor and I assure you I am not the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Hah! Being a prosecutor doesn't make you incapable of murder, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now you listen here! I am not the killer! I simply found the body!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So you say, however... ...I am sure that you are the perpetrator of this crime. I swear on my honor as a professional flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I know what I saw. And there's even very strong, incriminating evidence to back me up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What kind of "incriminating evidence" is she talking about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">We've already alerted the proper authorities at our destination. Until we land, you will remain in our custody by the powers vested in our captain. I'm very sorry, but please understand our situation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Your situation? I'm more concerned with mine, and the direction it's going on... I'm not about to just sit idly by while I get accused of murder!</thought> Ms... Teneiro, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering if you might give me a chance.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">A chance? To do what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A chance to plead my case. And a chance to ask what you meant by "incriminating evidence" just now.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To accuse a passenger of such a grave crime without allowing him to give a proper defense... Can the professional flight attendant inside of you really call this action "righteous"?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">......... You have a point. Very well, I'll listen to what you have to say... ...but be wary of what you reveal. I'm afraid you'll only look even more suspicious if your explanation fails to satisfy. I also do not have the time to deal with you all day, so please make it quick.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... Of course. As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Good. Very well then, let's get started.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know for a fact that I didn't kill that man in the elevator. What I don't know is what sort of "evidence" she has up her sleeve... ...but I'm certain it doesn't fit with how the crime really occurred.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I swear to tell the whole truth as a professional flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it...? That's her evidence...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't think you could ask for a more perfect witness testimony. Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Not really. It's hardly perfect when there's a gaping hole in it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I swear to tell the whole truth as a professional flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me, what exactly puts the "pro" in "professional flight attendant" for you?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, it means we are very professional about how we take care of our passengers. Services like fetching papers and responding to calls are done with speed and accuracy. I can assure you that I give testimonies with the same level of professionalism. But I'm sure you have already realized that by now, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a bit hard to "appreciate" your professionalism when I'm the one under suspicion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">And there you have it. My professional testimony is accurate and reliable.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Unfortunately for you, Mr. Edgeworth, I am certain you are the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You certainly seem sure of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Of course! A professional flight attendant can't afford to make mistakes, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps. But you must admit there are few who can look at a murder with a clear mind.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">We attendants all go through extensive training and are always calm and collected. We'll even calmly serve you coffee, if you so wish, as the plane makes a splashdown.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I fail to see how that would be the calm and rational thing to do in an emergency.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Even until the bitter end, we are there to serve the passengers. That is the duty of all professional flight attendants!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You certainly are confident. Anyway, shall we return to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The scene I saw in front of the elevator...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes...? What did you see in front of the elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That's what I was just about to tell you, Mr. Edgeworth. Framed by the elevator doors and bathed in the light coming from within...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">...it was you, standing there, with fresh blood dripping off of the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon, dripping with blood...? Really, now.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I swear that was the grisly scene I saw before me. Thank goodness it wasn't a passenger who saw, or there'd be widespread panic by now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I recall, you were quite panicked yourself at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">............ Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were scared enough to misread the situation and accuse me of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Nonsense! Professional flight attendants cannot afford to be that flustered! I witnessed the murder scene and am now listening to your defense, all with a smile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Apparently, you also lie with a smile on your face.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So, if you would please cooperate, we'll turn you over just as soon as we land.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am not the culprit... And yet, you would keep these restraints on me?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth, please try to understand what kind of situation you're in right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly is my situation?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I have the backing of the captain to keep you bound in this way. We are within our legal right to restrain anyone who might threaten our captain mid-flight. In essence, you're in the same situation as someone who has been arrested by the police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So I am to stay restrained until I can clear up all of her doubts? At least I'm close.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her mistake shines like the sliver lining on a dark rain cloud. And I'm going to capture some of that light with evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-Wh-What is with the yelling all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh. Force of habit. Well, it doesn't matter.</thought> Ms. Teneiro. You say you saw the murder weapon dripping with blood. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. All that blood... Drip, drip, drip... Just recalling that scene sends a chill down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but your so-called "professional" flight attendant training has failed you.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to direct your attention to this! Do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It's... a travel wallet, right? But it looks a little big and bulky...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The thing you saw me holding when I discovered the dead body in the elevator... ...was this very travel wallet, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What!? Impossible...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, do you still think I am the killer? That I killed him with a travel wallet?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But... But...! I...! No, but I... I saw blood dripping from the wallet! I know I did!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you can see, this wallet is clearly stained. But if you would be so kind as to take a whiff... ...I think you'd agree it's grape juice.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah! Then... Then...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. You mistook grape juice for blood! The murder weapon dripping with blood does not, in fact, exist!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">N-Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There. That should clear up that pesky accusation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">W-Wait just a sec! That is... I mean, even a wallet could be deadly if it was wrapped around something heavy! I demand that you show me what's inside... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's trembling, and the tacked on "please" at the end... Sounds like I've got her.</thought> There's no need to look inside. Even you can tell from its appearance that it's light.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">No! I can't be sure of anything until I see the contents of that wallet for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* She's a persistent one. I suppose we have no choice but to see what's inside.</thought> Ms. Teneiro, if you would be so kind as to open the wallet and check its contents for me.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Alright. I usually don't pry into passengers' belongings, but we have no choice here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grape juice stains the outer cover. True, it was I who dropped it in the juice, however, I didn't do it out of ill intentions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that this passport is all that's in here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you saw, there is nothing but a passport inside. This renders your "wallet was the murder weapon" argument moot. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Please, hear me out, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it now...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, I was wondering... whose passport is it exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Can I take a look...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why not? I'm rather curious myself. Th-This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Just as I thought... This travel wallet belonged to Mr. Akbey Hicks... ...which makes it the victim's property.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no money whatsoever inside the travel wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">You... You stole the victim's wallet... ...didn't you...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-How dare you!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">You said it yourself. You claimed to be holding this wallet in your hands when I found you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Perhaps I did misconstrue the wallet for the murder weapon.... ...but it seems that I wasn't wrong about who the culprit is.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">As you claimed, the murder weapon is not the travel wallet...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So even though I didn't have the murder weapon on me, you still suspect me, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">You stood up at the crime scene with the victim's wallet in your hands. How can I turn a blind eye and not suspect you of foul play?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">As you claimed, the murder weapon is not the travel wallet...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shouldn't that be proof enough for you that I did not murder the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Not at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, and why not?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Because, that wallet may not have been what I thought it was...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">...however, it IS something you stole from Mr. Hicks after you were done with the vile deed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think I stole it...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes! I'm very sorry to say it, and I wouldn't usually be so rude, but it must be said!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I never thought I'd see the day, but here I am calling a passenger a thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Maybe I should put on a serious face and say it more directly. I believe you removed the wallet from the victim's personage!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It really doesn't matter how you phrase it. What I'd like to know is why you think I stole Mr. Hick's wallet!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I find it hard to believe myself, but your motive was very simple...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, I don't think I have any sort of motive to speak of. I've never met Mr. Hicks before, and our only connection is this one flight.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But that is more than enough of a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How do you figure?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">He was sitting in First Class, and I think the implication is quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">You were out to steal Mr. Hick's money, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think I was after his money!? Wh-Where did that cockamamie idea come from!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">True, you are also a passenger in First Class, but... ...I thought something was off about you and those deeply-etched lines on your forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-They're not lines!! They're perfectly normal and a part of my natural face!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't think I've ever met someone with such terrible countenance on a flight before.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">And that's when it hit me. You have the face of someone with money trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if I might get a word in, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What is it now!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro. I wonder if you noticed the contradiction within your own testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simply impossible that the motive for this murder was monetary theft. One glance at the crime scene should've told you that! <thought>What about this scene would prove that the motive for the murder was not the money?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This proves that the killer's motive was not monetary theft!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Where am I supposed to be looking...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Please recall how the crime scene looked.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'm trying... but all I can see is you taking the wallet... ...and the deep furrowing of your eyebrows and the lines on your forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk! There's no need to recall those specific details, thank you very much. <thought>Now, what can I show her to prove my point in a way that even she will understand?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I may direct your attention to things strewn all over the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. The floor is covered in bills and coinage. By your rationale, these were the very things the killer was after.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we can assume that the wallet fell during the victim's struggle with his killer. And I would think that the killer would've noticed something like money scattering somewhere. Furthermore, as you can see, there was no effort made by the killer to gather the money!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">B-But...! The wallet...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, yes. the wallet. You will also recall that the only thing in it was Mr. Hicks's passport.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you are really insisting that it was a crime based on greed... ...then you're claiming that it was all for an empty travel wallet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if I might get a word in, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What is it now!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro. I wonder if you noticed the contradiction within your own testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What are you talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Simply put, as you saw with your own eyes... ...the only thing inside Mr. Hicks's wallet was his passport!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I really was "after his money"... ...then why would I steal a penniless travel wallet!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Gnrk! Ah, but that's right! You... Mr. Edgeworth... You didn't know it was empty when you stole it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would like to think that, but that's not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What do you mean it's not possible!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no way the killer didn't know that the wallet was empty to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh? And what makes you so sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How can I show her that the killer knew the wallet to be empty from the get-go?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence shows that the killer would've known that the wallet was empty!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">And what about it shows me that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I am, but all I can see... ...is futile struggling of a professional prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urrk! I think you've scrutinized it for long enough, thank you. <thought>I have to show her something even she can understand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you would recall the crime scene... I admit that the wallet was probably not empty at the time of the murder. That's pretty evident by the bills and cards strewn around the inside of the elevator.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, no!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think you've come to realize the problem with your logic. I would surmise that the victim's wallet fell out during their struggle. And that's when its contents emptied onto the floor of the elevator. I doubt the killer could've missed such an occurrence.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Th-Then, you're saying...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. According to your supposition, if I were the killer... ...I would have been going after a wallet I knew to be empty. And since I clearly was not attempting to gather the scattered money... ...it renders your argument of theft completely invalid!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She... really is making a fool of herself, pursuing this line of logic. I should spare her and present the piece of evidence that contradicts her testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I...I...I... Forgive meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee, pleeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeease!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Hey! What the heck!?</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Are you saying the attendant's wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">So that guy isn't the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Hah! Don't believe it, everyone! It's a trick!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Nnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will you all please be quiet!? Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You lost your cool when you saw the dead body. Plus, the lounge was dark, and looking into the light from the elevator... ...it's easy to see how you mistook the wallet in my hand for the murder weapon. I take no offense that you thought that I was the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you for releasing me.</line>
<line speaker="???">Borginese speaking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What is it now!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Borginese speaking, Borginese speaking?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro, if you could please translate, I'd be much obliged.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I-It sounds like Borginian... But I... ...I don't understand any of it. There's another attendant on this flight who...</line>
<line speaker="???">I said that he is giving the runabout!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="???">I don't require an interpreter! I speak English just well! See! You, the attendant!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="???">I want this person to be under the arrest until we arrive at the airport!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, sir, but what exactly are you hoping for?</line>
<line speaker="???">What is it you want? I am finished talking to the likes of you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, I would like to hear why you would like me to be held under arrest until we land!</line>
<line speaker="???">You! How dare you try to waste my time!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You were the one who stuck your nose into my affairs!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I wanted to spend even at least one more second with my precious art! I have no time for other things! I know what you are! I see through you! Insolvent! Yes, I am pretty sure that's how you say it in English!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, I'd hope that I don't dissolve in water, but I don't think that's what you meant.</thought> I'm sorry, but I don't think I caught your name.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I am Zinc Lablanc II. I am a very wealthy man in the Borginia! But I am not an ordinary rich man! I am an art dealer... a rich seller of beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Lablanc, what did you mean just now?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Pardon!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um, when you said that Mr. Edgeworth was giving me the "runabout"?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I have to explain!? Unbelievable... I will say it once and only once. I do not have even a second to waste! "Time is money" as they say!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, and yet you continue to blather on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I saw it, yes I did. I saw the victim go onto the elevator. Going down to the lounge! It was exactly at 6 o'clock!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">......A-And what's the significance of that time...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At 6, he says......</thought> W-Wait, you saw him at 6!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaah! Wh-What's the matter, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">He understands, I see. Ms. Attendant! What time did you discover the body!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, it was a little after that patch of turbulence, so I would say around 6:15... Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">"Hicks" was his name, was it? Then I say that man Hicks was killed in the 15 minute time span. And the only person in the lounge at that time was this prosecutor, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Y-Yeah! I-I was in my seat the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">M-Me, too! I was watching the movie and enjoying a fine glass of grape juice!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">I was still eating! Still haven't finished, see!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The other passengers have an alibi, so you have no problem with them, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">"No compliant", I see. Not a single word against this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I have no way of discounting what you have put forth at this point, but it wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Oh!? So you say! But do you have, what you say, the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth... Are you really the culprit after all...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc. I suppose you are quite certain in what you saw? Enough to give testimony? .........</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Of course! I was looking at that man the whole time! He was playing with that annoying little... um... small "machine" the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Machine"...?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes, that's what you people call it in English, yes? It was making me crazy with the click, click, click!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>From that description, it sounds like some sort of small computer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I believe what Mr. Lablanc is talking about is a cell phone. I have to say that I did see him playing with it quite a bit, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A simple cell phone? A laptop or organizer I can see, but... That's kind of... low budget.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I hate that noisy little machine in his hand! Not a fragment of beauty! All it produces is ugly sounds! Anyway, I know what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering if I might be granted permission to examine the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What!? You want to... examine the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you would grant me a little measure of time, I'm sure I can produce the real culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph. I don't like the sound of that. "Fox in the duck pen". Yes, I think that is how you say it in English.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's "Fox guarding the henhouse." And I believe my innocence was proven earlier. And if I'm given the chance, I can clear up all the remaining doubts.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro! If you wait until we arrive... ...there is a good chance that some evidence will have been destroyed by then.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">......... ...I understand. Let me see what the captain has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hah! This should not be approved!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Please, Mr. Lablanc! In an emergency, all decisions are to be made by the captain alone. Now, please wait here while I go ask the captain what to do. I'll be right back.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You are not planning to erase evidence when you are doing your investigation, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hah, we will see!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth, you have the captain's permission to investigate the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Wh-What!? Unbelievable!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am in your debt, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">However... there is one condition. I am to supervise you. Can you agree to that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, I see no problem with that stipulation. It's only natural as I am still a suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Grrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I take full responsibility and will watch Mr. Edgeworth's every move.I hope this is reassurance enough that there will be no foul play. Now then, Mr. Edgeworth, shall we proceed? If you should need my help with anything, please feel free to touch the Partner Button.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's time to head to the scene of the crime... the first floor lounge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Are you in need of assistance?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro, I'd like to ask you about investigating the lounge...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">As long as you have the captain's permission, I can't stop you from looking around.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could pass a message along, tell him I'm grateful for his spirit of cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I will. However, please realize that you are still under suspicion. To be honest, I still have my doubts about you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, and I take no offense.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Do you really understand what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, verily.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Do you pinky-swear you do, on your honor as a professional prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I pinky-swear I do, on my honor as a professional prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well! I guess that settles that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I... I feel my honor as a man slowly diminishing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Even if you show that to me, I still cannot allow you free reign. I'm sorry, but I must admit that I still have my doubts about you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Guilty until proven innocent, I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That leads to the emergency escape hatch. You can't go there in mid-flight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the probability that the criminal escaped through here?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">A hundred percent.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">............ Oh! Let me finish my thought. I'm 100% certain they didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>When I'm searching for an answer, only complete thoughts need apply.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but may I have a word with you?</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there!</line>
<line speaker="???">............*yawn* ...If you need something, please ask Ms. Rhoda over there, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What the...? Hey! Wake up, you!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'm terribly sorry that she's being so rude, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No need for you to apologize. I just find it hard to believe she's asleep on the job! <thought>If I were her boss, I'd see to it that her salary was cut so low that it was in the red.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">How did you find your meal to be, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come to think of it, I forgot all about it. I must have been asleep or something.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh! I'm terribly sorry! Let me prepare you something right away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...What are you apologizing for, Ms. Teneiro?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I've failed in my professional duties by letting a passenger go hungry! Please, help yourself! If you see anything to your fancy, feel free!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, I think I'll take my time later, after I've solved this case. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">In order to preserve the crime scene, I'm afraid the elevator is not in service. To get to the first floor lounge, we should take the stairs.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc seems to be protecting the gargantuan vase on the chair rather closely.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It's a marvelous vase, though, isn't it? Yes, I dare say so as a professional attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think there's any real connection between a piece of art and being an attendant...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But I'm not just any old attendant! I'm a PROFESSIONAL flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As though there were such a thing as an amateur flight attendant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a movie poster for... "License to Love, Laugh, Maim, and Murder"...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That's an iFly Airlines sponsored movie. It's a suspense-hardboiled-action-romance-horror-comedy movie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is that the genre listing for this movie?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. It's a movie that can be enjoyed by anyone because it encompasses all those genres!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I can't even begin to imagine what the plot of this movie would be like.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But you have to admit it piqued your curiosity, right? I heard the main strategy with this genre listing was to make people curious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Well then, consider the mission a successful one.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hurry up and investigate! Time should not be wasted! "Precious is human time!" is how you say it, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was Mr. Hicks's seat. I don't see the "machine" Mr. Lablanc was talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Perhaps it's in the elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe. We should probably head down to the crime scene now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's my seat. Unfortunately, I didn't bring anything particularly useful for an investigation. <thought>It's not as if I'm constantly prepared for such a thing to occur...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Unnnnnnnnngh... D-Don't get-t-t-t near m-m-m-me... y-you criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">He said, "Don't get near me, you criminal!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am not the killer, and I intend to prove that starting now.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">B-B-But th-that's c-c-contrary to th-the f-f-facts!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">He says, "But that's contrary to the facts!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can understand his English just fine, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, that's right. I was in the middle of recreating a chess game.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Just an observation, but aren't there too many red knights around that lone blue pawn?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Nonsense. It simply shows that the blue pawn is no match for the red knights' might.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's a lifesaver doing here...&#160;?</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">I-I-I bought it a-at the in-f-f-flight shop just be-beyond the lounge! If-If something sh-should happen, having o-o-one will s-save your life!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think this guy would've been better off not taking a plane to begin with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Hey, miss... How about another glass...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but I was wondering if you know anything about the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">...How about it? How about a glass together?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, sorry, but I must decline.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">I wasn't talking to you! I was asking the cute attendant!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'm sorry, but I'm on the clock right now. But if you need a refill, I'd be happy to bring you another glass at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">You got it, toots!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Th-That's no way to talk to a lady!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I may have a word with you...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">This...*munch*...steak...*munch* *munch* so... *munch*...awesome...*munch*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's great to hear, however, I would like to ask you a few questions...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">I...*munch*...was... here...*munch* *munch*... whole time so...*munch* wouldn't know...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eat or speak. Please pick one.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I think he chose to eat...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, I can hear that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at all these bottles, lined up in a row. It's miracle they made it through the turbulence without a scratch...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Actually, we asked the drink vendor to clean up all the ones that did break earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then you mean to tell me he put all these up here after the turbulence...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">We are simply thrilled to have someone so interested in the variety of drinks available!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think anyone should drink this much. There us such a thing as over-hydration...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One very large parfait... though I could easily finish it off all by myself.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This parfait is an iFly original: the iFly Parfait! The "i" comes from "I love you", while the "Fly" part comes from "Flying". When you combine the two parts, you get "iFly"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I fail to see how the "i" came from "I love you"...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I want to thank you for your help back there, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It was nothing. You should thank the captain for granting you permission. And just so everything is perfectly clear... I still don't trust you to that extent. I don't want you to think your standing with me has changed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. I will bear that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I received an order from the captain earlier. He wanted you to know that... ...we reserve the right to stop your investigation if we feel you are not making progress. And when we do, he asks that you please return to your seat at that time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So my time runs out at his and his crew's discretion, does it? I have to find a way to discredit Mr. Lablanc's testimony before time's up!</thought> I understand. By the way, is there any place you can think of where the killer might hide onboard?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't think so. After every First Class passenger was accounted for at his or her seat... ...we made a thorough search of the plane. As for Business and Economy class... ...no one can move between those two classes and First Class without a staff keycard. And we found no record of a keycard being used at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Which means that I have a First Class Killer on my hands. At least I know that much for sure. And one other thing. No one else has been allowed near this crime scene since the murder was discovered either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, let's get started.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But where would we start from?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Let's start with Mr. Lablanc's statements. The crime occurred between 6 AM and 6:15 AM. During that interval, the only person in the lounge was myself. Which would make me the prime suspect. However, since I did not kill Mr. Hicks, it means that the killer was around somewhere <thought>Where was the killer? – What clues point to where the killer could have been?</thought>...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">If we are to believe what you say is true, then yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... The first order of business will be to gather information to win your trust.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A statue with blood on it lying next to the body of a man who was beaten to death...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh! Mr. Edgeworth! I think I figured something out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The way the blood is on this, it looks like it matches up with the wound on his head!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, aren't we deserving of the Master of the Obvious title...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well? What do you think, Mr. Edgeworth? Don't you think that's worth investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It would appear that this figurine is our murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, I just knew it! I mean, I can't think of any other connection!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, perhaps Master of the Oblivious would be more befitting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>True, there wasn't anyone else in the lounge other than myself right before the turbulence... ...but if the killer was in the elevator along with the victim (In the elevator with Hicks? - If only I could prove that the killer rode the elevator with Hicks...</thought>. then that's a different story.)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have it!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">? I'm sorry, but I don't understand, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can prove that someone other than myself was here around the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What!? R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It's rather simple, actually. The proof is in the pudding. Or rather, the grape juice in this case. These footsteps here confess to me this very fact... ...that someone exited the elevator, alive. Seeing as how the victim is dead, that would mean a second person.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But... couldn't the footprints be from Mr. Hicks himself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but if you take a look at out victim's shoes, you can see the soles are spotless.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Which means...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Hicks wasn't alone in the elevator. In fact, it's quite the opposite. There was actually one other person inside the elevator!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Are you in need of assistance?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you notice anything?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I was wondering whose footprints are next to the elevator.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd say killer's, wouldn't you say? Even if they aren't, I'm sure they are a vital clue to solving this case.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ooh, maybe there are other clues waiting to be found in other places. Come on now, Mr. Edgeworth! Let's go find them together.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A word of advice: Nobody likes a credit thief, so stop stealing my lines.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering if you noticed anything, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes... I can't help but notice the sad atmosphere in here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, hmm, yes... It is a rather tragic crime.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'll say. Robbing the poor man after bludgeoning him to death, talk about rubbing in the salt! I can't forgive someone who would do this to a passenger of mine! I swear as a professional flight attendant that I will capture the culprit with my own hands!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I promise as a prosecutor to solve this case with logic and deduction. <thought>I should go over all the leads I've collected so far one more time. The key to solving this lies at the intersection of my logic and the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If these footprints do, in fact, belong to the culprit... ..then I would say it was very careless to leave them.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">If I was a killer, I swear that as a professional killer, I'd never leave footprints behind!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's all well and good, but I'm afraid it's of little use in our pursuit of the killer. <thought>I feel like I'm still missing a link or two...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This door leads to the flight attendants' room. But please understand that it's off limits to unauthorized personnel.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The room is giving off the scent of women's perfume. One would think that perfume would "smell great", however, to me it simply "smells"... Not that I have any interest in what lies behind this door...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Perhaps we should return to the investigation, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...........................</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, I spaced out for a second there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These bottles and glasses must have been broken by the turbulence.</thought> There is quite a bit of broken glass here. Please be careful when passing through the area.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Thank you very much for the warning, Mr. Edgeworth. However, no matter how kind you are towards me... ...know that it does not clear up any suspicions I have about you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I wasn't warning you for the sake of clearing my name!!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This grand piano is the pride of this plane. It can play the music of whatever CD we insert into its CD drive.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not a piano! It's more like an overgrown music box.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah, but its keys depress along with the music, as though there really is someone playing it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Some people have entirely too much money to waste on overly-complex toys.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These counter windows offer a glimpse of the sky, but these clouds, they tell me nothing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth...? You... look like you're talking to the clouds.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so? Then tell me, what do you suppose I said to them?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't know, but it looked like a rather one-sided conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The clouds... They tell me nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are a few copies of Sky Magazine in the magazine rack.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This month's special is an English trivia quiz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not a bad idea. I've heard that the youth of today don't know a particle from a participle.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Now, now, Please don't go around confusing people with made-up words, Mr. Edgeworth. Who's ever heard of such a silly word as "participle"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Case in point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What, or who, is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This is a bronze statue of the founder of iFly Airlines, Mr. Hugo Ifly. The one on the left is of when he was in his 40's and the other is of him in his 80's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Did the man actually age in the span of four decades? Maybe I need to squint more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This toppled-over chair... Yet another victim of the turbulence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaaah!! Nooo! Look at all that grape juice staining the back...! It may not look it, but this chair was extremely valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes! It was used when the Rocker Pals came to tour this plane. The Rocker Pals' leader sat in this very chair.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but what are these "Rocker Pals"?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I can't believe you've never heard of them! They're all the rage! The Rocker Pals are an extremely popular international band. They added the "Pals" part as they became more popular, especially among teens.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, that explains it. I'm not really one for the music of today. <thought>Maybe I should ask Detective Gumshoe about them later... On second thought... I can already see how confusing the conversation would get.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What floors does this elevator service?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Only the first and second, although, it can also go down to the cargo hold. However, that requires a flight crew keycard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the only floors accessible to passengers are the first and second (Elevator - The victim's body was found inside the elevator that connects 1F with 2F</thought>, huh?)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Money is strewn all over the floor of the elevator. I would guess it was all in Mr. Hicks's wallet at some point.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It's been a while since I've seen this big of a mess. It's terribly embarrassing, but I thought it was an earthquake for a second... ...and I frantically started searching for gas values to shut off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was? <thought>I guess the shaking of the plane was bad enough to be mistaken for a real earthquake. Not that I would know, since I was unconscious for most of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I doubt anyone was expecting to find a dead body in an elevator on this flight.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So Mr. Hicks... He's really d-dead?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. <thought>She's trembling, although I can't fault her for that when there's a corpse right there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Hicks... If you're really dead, then please answer, "yes"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see she's over the trembling now... although a new symptom seems to have appeared... Anyway, I should focus on the victim's body. Let's see...</thought> There's blood on the back of Mr. Hicks's dead... Could this be the cause of death? He appears to have been struck <thought>Blunt force trauma - Wound on the back of Hicks's head suggests blunt force trauma, but what caused it?</thought> very hard... Even his glasses <thought>Broken glasses - The victim's glasses are broken Were they broken during his murder?</thought> are broken...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? There's something sticking out of his pocket. Hope he won't mind if I take a look at what's inside.</thought>.........Hm? It's a picture. It looks like it was taken inside a building somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder what was hanging off of this lanyard? Something's missing from this picture... Now if I could just put my finger on it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The "machine" that should be hanging off of here must still be somewhere on this plane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this... sinister-looking figure on the floor here?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, that's a piggy bank of our company mascot, Mr. Ifly. It's just one of the many pieces of merchandise we sell at out in-flight shop. This bank is a limited edition, and is so popular that we're down to our last one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You have an in-flight shop...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. It's just beyond the lounge to the right. The shutter to the store is closed at the moment... ...but it was open the whole flight ip until Mr. Hicks's body was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's blood on here... Could this have been the murder weapon (Murder weapon: Mr. Ifly - The blood on it is still fresh... Could this be the murder weapon?</thought>?)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This crime scene completely contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">...I'm sorry, but where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, I see the truth here in my mind's eye. I'll try to explain it in a simpler fashion for you.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um, alright...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's something missing from this scene in front of me. And I'll show Ms. Teneiro what's "off" through that piece of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Hicks's "machine" is nowhere to be found.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">His "machine"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ahem, his cell phone, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah, so I guess because it's not here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I think we can safely deduce that the killer took it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's some spilled grape juice in front of the elevator. <thought>I assume it was spilled during the turbulence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, we must clean up or someone might get hurt...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">? What is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've found some very important evidence. What is the important piece of evidence in this scene?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These lines here... They obviously weren't made naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">You're right! But how were they made then, and why are they here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know yet... <thought>But I do know they are important to this investigation.</thought> Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What is it now, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've found am even more important piece of evidence in this scene!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">............ I'm not sure what's so important about that, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait! <thought>Curses. This is no time to get careless!</thought> Allow me to point it out to you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're a little smudged, but I think we can both agree they are a set of footprints <thought>Spilled grape juice – There is some spilled grape juice on the floor in front of the elevator.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So you think...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, these belong to our killer.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, then maybe we should check the shoe sizes of everyone in First Class!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think that will be of any help to us. Unfortunately, the prints are too smudged, which will make it hard to get a definitive match.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Spilled grape juice in a pool at my feet... Unfortunately, the delightful scent of grapes is obscured... ...by the unpleasant smell of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This scent in the air... It's the same smell as the smell of my towels after they come out of my home dryer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I would've never expected something like that by looking at you... <thought>I suppose everyone has something unpleasent about them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Glasses and candles are thrown into disarray by the turbulence.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It's been a while since I've seen this big of a mess. It's terribly embarrassing, but I thought it was an earthquake for a second... ...and I frantically started searching for gas values to shut off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was? <thought>I guess the shaking of the plane was bad enough to be mistaken for a real earthquake. Not that I would know, since I was unconscious for most of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pity that a bronze statue knows not when good drink has been split at its feet.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">This is a statue of our founder, Mr. Hugo Ifly, who was a big fan of grape juice. I'm sure he would be thrilled if he knew so much grape juice was here at his feet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that a hint of hero worshipping I detect...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The in-flight shop is just beyond these shutters. But we don't have permission to open them, so I'm afraid I must leave them closed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must still be clues to be found here in this lounge! I must remain ever vigilant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It says "iFly Airlines". You know, I've seen it occur a lot recently, and it's been bothering me greatly... ...but why does nobody know how to properly capitalize and space nouns anymore!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is some blood on one of the corners. Could this piggy bank be the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What's going on over there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Borginese speaking! Borginese speaking!</line>
<line speaker="???">Borginese speaking... Borginese speaking...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Unforgivable! This is unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="???">.........</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Do you understand what I am saying!? The movie is late! It is the same level of bad as if the plane arrived late!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ummmmm... But the movie...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!? I will not talk to you anymore! You are just wasting my time!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What is the matter, Mr. Lablanc? If there's no emergency, please return to your seat, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Do not tell me what to do! I need not to sit down! Well, Mr. Prosecutor!? Did you prove you are innocent yet!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you would like, I will prove my innocence to you right now.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!? Nonsense! Are you saying my eye-witness testimony is mistaken!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not mistaken, merely that there is room for doubt. I'd be honored if you could please tell me what you saw in detail once more.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Fine, suit yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I am certain I saw Mr. Hicks in the elevator!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Lablanc's conclusions seem to make logical sense. After all, the only person in the lounge at the supposed time of the murder was me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">So! My eye-witness testimony! If you think you can destroy it, then come, let me see! Hurry! Do I look like a man who is having the time to wait for you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why is HE so irritated&#160;? I'm the one accused of murder here! Anyway, I must find a way to discredit Mr. Lablanc's account somehow, and fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I am certain I saw Mr. Hicks in the elevator!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, were you able to get a good look at the inside of the elevator at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Of course, I saw what was inside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you are sure that the victim was in the elevator alone?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes! The only person inside was that Mr. Hicks man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, this last outburst is a bit too important to let go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The only person inside was that Mr. Hicks man!"</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The only person inside was that Mr. Hicks man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was he really alone?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Of course! I will bet even 1 cent!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph, a cheap ante... for a cheap testimony. But if that's how you went to play it, I'll happily take your 1 cent!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">It was when my needles on my pocket watch pointed to the 6 and to the 12!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume the pocket watch in this case is the one you keep checking, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Oh! You noticed! It is a very expensive antique, I will have you know! The feeling is wonderful when I fully wind it up by hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It does look very well designed, and quite classy.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">...I will have to charge you if you want to touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......That's quite alright! Let's continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! What a cheap man you are! Now return the time you wasted back to me! And if we must, I saw Mr. Hicks enter the elevator at 6 o'clock!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The body was discovered 15 minutes after that in the lounge, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's true that I found the victim's body at 6:15.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">And that's when I found the two of them as well.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You see! It all matches my testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Then you, the only person in the lounge at that time, must be the criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is most mistaken way of thinking I've ever heard of!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">No, no, no! Your silly opinion is what is mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Please calm down, the both of you. In a sense, you are both mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well if that isn't the pot calling the kettle back, then I don't know what is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He certainly has a lot of confidence in his testimony. If push comes to shove, I may need to press him for more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph... I spy a little hole in his words. As you wish, Mr. Lablanc, I will now show you proof of my innocence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a very glaring contradiction in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please take a look at the area in front of the elevator. There, at the spilled grape juice.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes, and!? Will you admit you also spilled it with the blood!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it spilled itself during the turbulence. But the interesting thing here is the set of grape juice footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">F-Footprints!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the ones that lead from within the elevator out into the lounge itself. It's evidence that proves that someone other than Mr. Hicks exited the elevator, alive!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Ooooooooonnff!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There must have been another person in the elevator with Mr. Hicks! Now then! I'm done playing games! Why don't you tell us the truth!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Borginese speaking! ...Borginese speaking?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Can you please translate for us?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ummmmmmmmmmm... "No way! That's totally impossible!" I guess is what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">No way! That is totally impossible! I know there was no other person in there! I saw with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">If you want to know what I think, Mr. Edgeworth... ...I don't think Mr. Lablanc is lying to us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I suppose she's right. He doesn't seem to be lying. But then, what does it mean? What about this contradiction?</thought> Mr. Lablanc. Please, just once call more, will you recall the details of what you witnessed for me?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Mnnnnrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I was very upset when Mr. Hicks passed by my seat.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Lablanc, if you would please calm down...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!? Dare you too have an issue with my eye-witness testimony!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaaah! N-No, not at all! Please forget I said anything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yet again, he doesn't appear to be lying. But I can't let this testimony stand as the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I was very upset when Mr. Hicks passed by my seat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, are you still upset now?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I am always upset! The only time I am not is when I have a piece of art in my hands!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's surprisingly easy to believe that about him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">But I was even more upset when Mr. Hicks walked by me!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I was checking the time, over and over again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why were you so attentive to the time?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Because! Because something unforgivable was happening!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, come to think of it, you were yelling about something "unforgivable" earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I was giving a complaint to the attendant about the movie starting time! Return back to me my time!! In money!! ...You understand the point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Movie? Is he talking about the in-flight one that's mentioned in the magazine? Hmm... A summary of the plot and the start time... Interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">They were supposed to show "License to Love, Laugh, Maim, and Murder". I cannot see that movie in my country. You can only see it on international flights. I looked forward greatly to that movie!! I checked my pocket watch whenever possible so I would not miss it! I even set my pocket watch to the destination time when I came onboard. So my watch is not wrong! It matched the schedule! But the movie was still late! Very, very late!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your pocket watch... I'd like to ask you a little more about it, if that's alright.</line>
<line speaker="Change this statement to">"The movie I wanted to see would not start, so I checked my pocket watch many times." and "My watch is set to my destination's time. I always set it when I board the plane."</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The movie I wanted to see would not start, so I checked my pocket watch many times.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this movie you mentioned, is it the one listed in the Sky Magazine?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes! I was so looking forward to watching "License to Love, Laugh, Maim, and Murder"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro, was this movie shown on this flight?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, it was shown at the scheduled time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Isn't it possible you simply slept through it by accident?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Nonsense! You doubt me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No! Now stop pointing at me like that! <thought>Odd. How did he miss a movie that he was clearly hoping to see...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I checked my pocket watch a great number of times! That much I know for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">My watch is set to my destination's time. I always set it when I board the plane.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're sure about what you just testified, Mr. Lablanc?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes, of course! I am a very busy man! I am immediately busy when I land! I have many places to go! And no time to waste adjusting my pocket watch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... That was a very valuable statement you just made.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! Flatter me all you want, but you will not get 1 cent out of me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... That's alright. All I require is this piece of testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I happened to follow that man with my eyes when he passed me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since you only "happened" to see him, it's possible that you missed something in that glance!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Even if I only "happened", I did not miss a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Just because!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would appreciate it if you didn't take my life so lightly with a simple, "Just because!"</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! Well, then I was only making a joke! I saw Mr. Hicks, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">And I saw clearly into the elevator he was entering.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is it possible that someone was hiding inside?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!? You dare insult me!? I have belief in my eyesight! When I look for art to sell, I am told often I have "great sight" for the arts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think the phrase you were looking for was "great sense", although that's debatable.</thought> But isn't it possible someone was just outside of your line of sight...?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You are persistent! I tell you, I looked clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">But, I swear there was no one else inside! No one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you insist that you are absolutely not mistaken!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Because when I say I am not wrong, I am not wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Lablanc, if I may, I think beyond misconceptions and mistake lies the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Funny, that suspiciously mirrors something I told her only a little while ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"> <thought>Mr. Lablanc doesn't seem to be lying... I may need to draw more information out of him before I see anything inconsistent.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I honestly don't think Mr. Lablanc is lying...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I don't think he's lying either. But... I think he might be mistaken about something.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mistaken...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. And I'm going to correct his mistaken recollection with evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">And this professional attendant  shall witness the prowess of a professional prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, you said this just now in your testimony:</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I even set my pocket watch to the destination time when I came onboard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if your watch has been set to our destination's time zone... ...it would mean that your watch is displaying the time of our destination.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes, and? The correct time is worth its 6 cents.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like you to take a look at this. If you believe this Sky Magazine... ...clocks on this flight run in accordance with the time of our departure time zone! Of course, the movie schedule was also created with that in mind. Ms. Teneiro, for confirmation's sake, what time zone is this flight aligned to right now?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, we made a short stop at a transfer point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's right. It was in that small Asian country, the Republic of Zheng Fa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But we didn't re-adjust our onboard clocks at that time. So right now, we are still running on Borginian time!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The time difference between Borginia and out destination is 9 hours. In that case, it's only natural that your watch would be out of sync with the schedule!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Further, with your analog watch set to our destination's time... ...it would appear to be running 3 hours fast when compared to the flight's onboard clocks. It also changes everything about your testimony. And you can bet 1 million cents on that! In light of this information, it means you saw Mr. Hicks 3 hours prior at 3 AM!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Nnnnn...ggggggwwwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! My 1 miiiiiiiiiiiiiiillion ceeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeents!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This should clear up all of the remaining accusations...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So this basically widens the time frame for the time of death, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Because Mr. Lablanc saw the victim enter the elevator at 3 AM... ...it means that the time of death could be anywhere from 3 to 6:15 AM. That question now is where was Mr. Hicks during that span of time and what was he doing?</line>
<line speaker="???">Um, I've got something to say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, um... Oh! I'm Cammy Meele. I'm a flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is it you wish to say?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well, I think your story is a little different from how I remember it.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What do you mean, Cammy?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I saw Mr. Hicks sitting in his seat at 5 AM, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? How can you be so sure of the time?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, that's right! He pushed his call button while we were parked at the transfer point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, the stop we made for refueling and cargo transfer in Zheng Fa, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, it was from 4 to 5 AM according to our clocks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And during that time, did any of passengers leave or did any new ones board this flight?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">No. Not a single person got off or on in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about the flight crew?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The few who were handling the cargo transfer might have temporarily gotten on or off... ...but eventually everyone, including Cammy and myself, came back on the plane.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So basically, I can assume that no one left or got on since our initial take off. Interesting... I should keep that in mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, and I answered his call. I can tell you Mr. Akbey Hicks was there in his seat when we took off again at 5 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, then that puts the time of the murder between 5 and 6:15 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">OK, now what time did you come down to the lounge, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, I remember coming down here almost as soon as we left the Republic of Zheng Fa... Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You! You were here the whole time from 5, yes!? Then you are the only one who could be the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth... Were you really here in this lounge the entire time from 5 AM onwards?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But then, how do we explain the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Is not that obvious!? This man waited for Mr. Hicks here in this lounge. Waited to kill him! And then he put the corpse into the elevator! That is when the turbulence happened! My eye-witness testimony may have been mistaken! But what time I saw Mr. Hicks enter the elevator on the second floor does not matter! Because the entire incident concluded here in this lounge!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Everything happened in this lounge...?</thought> Is that what you really believe, Mr. Lablanc?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Wh...!? Do you have another idea!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I simply feel that there is something out of place in the scenario you presented. <thought>Is there something that can tie this crime to a location other than this lounge?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These footprints. In which direction do you think these are headed?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That would be... the in-flight shop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. They are headed in the direction of the shop.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">But they look disconnected! They end all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are right to point out that they do not from one continuous trail to the shop. However, there is another piece of evidence that connects the shop to our crime scene. <thought>Besides the footprints, what else points to the in-flight shop?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! I don't need to hear your wild desperation stories! "Grasping for weeds" I think is how you say it, yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agnrk...... I didn't mean to pull that piece out! The one that I meant to show you was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! I don't need to hear your wild desperation stories! "Grasping for weeds" I think is how you say it, yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agnrk...... I didn't mean to pull that piece out! I was a simple slip of the hand, I assure you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon... This little piggy bank is sold at the in-flight shop. It is sold there and only there, and is not displayed here in this lounge! How, then, did it find its way here? Don't you find that a tiny bit suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! Such a trivial point! It only means you prepared it, taking it from the shop first before coming here. It doesn't prove you are innocent at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnrrrgh......... <thought>Is there no way to win with this man!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I-If I may...!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um... You see...! Well, it's just as Mr. Edgeworth says!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Oh? And why do you know so well?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well... it's just that... That piggy bank was there in the shop. I saw it with my own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And when was this?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It was... maybe around 5:40 AM...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Isn't that just before we hit that patch of turbulence!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Th-That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You were in the shop just before the turbulence!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um............ Yes, I was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come to think of it... Ms. Teneiro, when I found the body... ...I believe you came out of that door.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, I did...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is beyond that door?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That's the flight attendants' room.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Th-Then! You were on the first floor!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes... I had to do something at the shop and in the flight attendants' room. So I went to the shop first, and then to the flight attendant's room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying you passed by me at some point?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. You seemed really into the issue of Sky Magazine you were reading at the time. I don't suppose you noticed me walking by...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, I vaguely recall someone walking by, but I didn't take notice of who it was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Anyway! The piggy bank was definitely there at the shop when I went there.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Why did you go to the shop in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I... went there for a work-related matter.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Work, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes... The upkeep of the shop is also one of my responsibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Why did you not say anything about that until now is what I want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In any case, I believe it's clear that the shop needs to be investigated as well.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Shall we head over there, then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is it now!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aren't you forgetting something, Ms. Rhoda...? Don't you need the captain's permission to check the shop?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">No, I haven't forgotten. But I have already asked him for permission to search the entire plane. So I think we're alright.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh...? That's weird...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well, I just talked to the captain, see... ...and he said that he didn't give you permission to do anything like that at all.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is the meaning of this, Ms. Teneiro!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">It means she's lying. Go on, admit that you are. You said you had permission to search all over, but you don't. And yet, here you are!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">...You, flight attendant! Wh-What are you trying to do!? Pull the sheep over us!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">The captain's calling for you, Ms. Rhoda. Oh, but don't worry... I already got permission to search the shop from the captain. See, unlike you, I do things the right way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro... Why would you do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........Please excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Looks like I get to be in charge now. Please go back to your seat, Mr. Lablanc. Now then, Mr. Edgeworth... ...if you would follow me, I will be your guide from now on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's something about Ms. Teneiro that has piqued my curiosity. But right now, investigating the in-flight shop is my top priority.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um.. .Weren't we going to go to the in-flight shop?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. I still fully intend it.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">OK, well, the shop is over there. Don't forget now.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Mr. Edgeworth! That's the attendants' room!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, please excuse me. It was a simple mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You made a mistake, didn't you!? Why don't you just come out and say it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's exactly what I just said. I made a small mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't nod off while I'm talking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These bottles and glasses must have been broken by the turbulence.</thought> There is quite a bit of broken glass here. Please be careful when passing through the area.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............ Huh? Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I said that there is glass here, and to be careful...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............ But why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Obviously, common sense does not register, even as a blip, on this girl's radar!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A piano... It's been a while since I played one of these. It might not be a bad idea to brush up a bit after all this time. Of course, that's contingent on the outcome of this case! It's time to get investigating!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! About investigating the in-flight shop...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're of no use to me asleep! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yawn* Huh? What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I need you to come with me so I can search the shop...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Go on ahead without me. *yawn* I'll catch up with you later.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How has this woman not been fired yet?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Ooooooh, I am really mad! You had better hurry and bring to me some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could wait just a little longer while we look into the shop...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! Don't number the birds before they are born!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Don't number the... What...? I have no idea what he's trying to say. "Don't count your chicken before they hatch" perhaps...?</thought> All I ask of you is your patience and cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These counter windows offer a glimpse of the sky, but these clouds, they tell me nothing... Ack! Now's not the time for me to stand here making up soliloquies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are a few copies of Sky Magazine in the magazine rack. The special this month is an English trivia quiz. Of course, I have never uttered a single grammatically incorrect sentence in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What is it!? Why are you looking at me for? Hurry and go do your investigating! I do not believe in this "making haste slowly" saying you have in English!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's something written on the pedestal... "Here lies Hugo Ifly" ............? I don't think that's what they meant to write...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This toppled-over chair... Yet another victim of the turbulence.</thought> There's something written on the back: "In honor of Rocker Pals' Day"...? I have the distinct impression that this chair has nothing to do with the case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've already finished examining this area, but it never hurts to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is money strewn all over the floor of the elevator. I guess this was all in Mr. Hicks's wallet before the incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I doubt anyone was expecting to find a dead body in an elevator on this flight. For the victim's sake, I will do anything in my power to bring this to a speedy end.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like there was just the one picture in this pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Mr. Ifly here was probably used to hit the victim on the back of the head.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Considering which way these prints are pointed, it's likely the killer went into the shop. I should really make my way over there now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Glasses and candles are thrown into disarray by the turbulence. Seeing this reminds me of the ferocity of that last patch. And of... ...No, I can't do this anymore. I've overcome that already. I won't let past traumas control me for the rest of my life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pity that a bronze statue knows not when good drink has been split at its feet. Odd... Compared to the one on the left, this statue appears to be slouching a little. ...It must be the altitude. Yes, that's it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this is the in-flight shop...</thought> It's a quite mess in here...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You think? Guess I'll have to clean things up then, tee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on! You can't "clean up" a potential crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ohhh, thank goodness! I hate cleaning soooo much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I mustn't rush things here. I must remain cool, calm and collected. Because this piggy bank (Murder Weapon: Mr. Ifly - The blood on it is still fresh... Could this be the murder weapon?</thought> was left at the crime scene... ...there is a very good chance that the killer had paid this place a visit.)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... The hat probably used to be on the piggy bank's head. Let's give it a go and see...</thought> I believe this piggy bank was forcibly removed from this display case. <thought>Does this mean that the killer broke the glass to get at it...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Eeeeeehhhh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me you don't know what things go where in this shop.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well, I don't! Ms. Rhoda's in charge of this place. So, come on, how should I know anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense that further inspection of this display case is needed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well? What do you think, Mr. Edgeworth? Don't you think that's worth investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It would appear that this figurine is our murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, I just knew it! I mean, I can't think of any other connection!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, perhaps Master of the Oblivious would be more befitting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">I don't know much about this shop, but you can still ask me about whatever.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what do you think about what has happened regarding this case?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, I don't know. I guess I think you're the killer, though, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can assure you that I'm here in this shop to prove just the opposite...!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, but it was me that got you the permission to look around, you know. So don't forget that, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How am I supposed to thank you properly if you insist on falling asleep!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well, you know what'd really show your thanks? You see that item for sale over there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but you're going to have to make due with my words of appreciation.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I cut my finger on those bad pieces of glass.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't blame the glass for something you did to yourself. Just be more careful.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Same to you! You're the one walking all over broken glass. You sure you're OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm fine. Any glass I walk on, I crush... like this!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">That's nice. Please be careful around the display case, OK? Wouldn't want you to get hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Compared to the glass around my feet, the inside of the case is nothing to be afraid of. After all, no glass fragments appear to have ended up inside.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Then I guess even you can tidy up the case, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perish the thought!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ooh, I'd love to have this piece of jewelry. Can I have it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, you may not! This is a Prosecutor's Badge...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Pooey. Then why did you show it to me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wanted to prove to you that I really am a prosecutor. And that it's not possible for a prosecutor like me to commit such a crime as...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see that I'm just watching my time with Cousin Hair here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ms. Rhoda said that this piggy bank was in this shop, right? Don't you find her a tiiiny bit suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think I can say either way yet. There's not enough evidence to convince me that she was lying about anything back there.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Are you sure about that...?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Like I said earlier... ...I was the one answering people's calls while we were refueling in Zheng Fa. And Mr. Hicks was in his seat at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What time was that again?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">He called at around 5 AM. You were at your seat around then too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do recall people calling for service at around that time. <thought>Even if this turns out to be a waste of time, I must stand firm. I just know that there is a vital clue ot two awaiting me here in this shop.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">So what is that? Are you going to give it to me? Oh, but I'm not supposed to accept any presents. ...Unless they're really worth something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Beautiful flowers in a beautiful arrangement. <thought>I feel cleansed just by looking at them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Mr. Edgeworth, you're getting pollen all over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh... Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Inside this display case is a row of lifesavers and life vests for sale.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">We sell a lot of those when there's some kind of accident or something. But some people buy them even when nothing's going on. How about it, Mr. Edgeworth? Care to buy one?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense that this shop is one shopper away from being sued.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are these...?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, those are our company's completely original line of suitcases! They're practically flying out the door! That's how popular they are! You should buy one and see how you like it! You won't regret it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps that's how things work on this flight, but in the real world you try, then buy.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">No way! But either way, it doesn't really matter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>True. Either way, why would anyone buy a suitcase AFTER they've boarded the plane?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Anyway, see that? Just look at all the Mr. Ifly heads painted on there! Cute company mascot, isn't he!? They're painted on with a lot of care. Doesn't he look like he's about to jump out at you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It is certainly making something jump inside my stomach!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh...? Oh, I guess there's no fooling your refined tastes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You looked like you really wanted to get one... ...and I thought I was going to finally make my first sale, but you saw right through it. Glad that's done though. Never make me try to give you a sales pitch ever again, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But I never showed any interest in it to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Tee hee! It really is pretty horrible, isn't it? You want to know something? This suitcase was designed by Ms. Rhoda!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro designed this?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah. It was a company-wide contest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, well... It does have a very sharp design sense.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ha ha, "sharp"? Like stinky sharp cheddar, maybe. I really have no idea why the big wigs decided to go with it. It's so... bleh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ms. Teneiro designed this, did she? ...It's definitely not what I would've expected...</thought> Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm fine! Please watch yourself, Ms. Meele! <thought>Letting a suitcase (Suitcase - Plane's shaking caused it to roll. In-flight suitcase displays can be hazardous.</thought> freely roll around has got to be a safety violation...)</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Here, I'll put it back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Suitcases designed by Ms. Teneiro... That's one sharp design.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a wide selection of souvenirs for sale in these display cases.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You know what I'd suggest...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but I have no intention of buying souvenirs on this trip.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">OK, then how about you buy something for me then? As a present!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't think of a single reason why I'd want to buy you anything.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">But I've had my eye on that pendant for such a loooong time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Try paying some attention to me when I ask you something, and then we'll talk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are all kinds of luxury name-brand merchandise for sale in this display case. And they're lined up in just such a manner as to scream, "Buy me!" to any passers-by.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The glass from this display case's door is shattered all over the floor. And it looks like there's nothing on display inside either. Hmm? Wait, actually, I think there is something... What's this...? A mini captain's hat (Tiny Captain's Hat - It's a tiny captain's hat...? Hmm... I swear I've seen one of these before...</thought>...?)</line>
<line speaker="Meele">We sell a lot of those when there's some kind of accident or something. But some people buy them even when nothing's going on. How about it, Mr. Edgeworth? Care to buy one?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense that this shop is one shopper away from being sued.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is this the same man as the one portrayed by the statues around the elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, that's a paperweight of the founder of iFly Airlines, Mr. Hugo Ifly. On the bottom shelf we have the cute one, the middle shelf is the realistic one... ...and on the top shelf......... That's the floral version.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">F-Floral...? Are you sure about that? Let me guess. You just said the first thing that came to your mind, right?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Looks I hit the bull's-eye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The glass on this door is broken... Perhaps it was the killer who broke it in order to take the piggy bank? But it's a bit odd that the inside of the case is so devoid of glass shards. Plus, the glass broke rather cleanly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I... I touched the glass, and it cut my finger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Meele">It hurts, Mr. Edgeworth! It hurts!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Please tell me you can deal with such a minor cut on your own!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's not a single piece of glass inside the display case. Which means that the glass was broken from the inside out. The piggy bank must've fallen over from the turbulence and right through the glass. Which leads me to believe that the killer took the Mr. Ifly from here after the turbulence. <thought>But that would also mean that the piggy bank could not be the murder weapon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>For security, there's a lock on this display case.</thought> Ms. Meele, if I may ask you about this lock...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ummm... The one who's in charge of this shop is Ms. Rhoda, so... ...she's got the keys to all of the display cases.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh! I bet you want to buy something! Do you want me to go get the key from her?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, t-that's alright...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">iFly Airlines related books line this shelf. "The History of iFly Airlines" "The Future of iFly Airlines" "The Seven Wonders of iFly" "Fight On! iFly Airlines" "Working Name: GoYou Airlines" "i♥Fly-----------ing" The titles make it very clear that they won't be making the top-sellers list anytime soon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Do you need something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-This piece of evidence is...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Is...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, nevermind. Temporary lapse. <thought>I'm thinking too hard about when the glass broke. It's simple... What was here when the glass broke...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is definitely something very unusual about this!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">About what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the killer had broken the glass to get at the Mr. Ifly bank... ...there should be shards of glass inside the case itself.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ooooooh, I see! Yeah, I guess it'd be like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, there's not a single piece of glass inside the display case.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Nope! No, there isn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means that the glass was broken from the inside out. The piggy bank must've fallen over from the turbulence and right through the glass.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, that's for sure There's so much glass all over the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm willing to bet that this hat was knocked off its head at that time, too.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.........Eh!? ......That's nice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which leads me to believe... ...that the killer took the Mr. Ifly from here after the turbulence <thought>Turbulence - The plane shook so much during it that it made a huge mess of the shop.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take your power naps on your own time, Ms. Meele, and listen when I'm talking!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Wah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the murder occurred before the turbulence... ...which rules this piggy bank out as the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">So you mean the bank's not the real murder weapon? It's a fake?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, at this point, that is a very real possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um, but then what if when the killer went to take Mr. Ifly... ...they broke the glass by accident?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The display case is locked, so that's highly unlikely.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...Yeah, but there's one person who could've.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? And who would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ms. Rhoda, of course. I mean, she's the one in charge of this place, so she has the keys to everything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Rhoda Teneiro, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stuffed toys, just like the one Ms. Meele is holding, are on display here. <thought>They're relatively cheap, which explains why they're displayed so hapazardly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">How about it, Mr. Edgeworth? You know you want one, too. They're great for when you're stressed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why do I envision stuffed animal abuse when she says that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The hat on its head was found inside a display case in the in-flight shop. I wonder if that fact has any bearing on this case...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... There is definitely something wrong here!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Wh-What's with the sudden yelling!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me, Ms. Meele, don't you think there's something strange about there suitcases?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, well, sure... They totally ooze "strange". Like the color and the such...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not what I'm talking now! Now pay attention!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aaah! You're scaring me, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Sorry... Ahem. These suitcases are lined up a bit too prim and proper.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, they look a bit uptight, don't they? But I guess they take after their creator, hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Again, that's not what I meant, Ms. Meele. Don't you find it unusual that these cases are the only things undisturbed by the turbulence? <thought>...Never mind. I'd sooner find an answer by inspecting these suitcases myself.</thought> Upon closer inspection, they really are quite hideous.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Tee hee... I wonder how Ms. Rhoda would've reacted if she'd heard what you just said.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Meele">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...She makes a good point. It would be wise of me to watch what I say out loud.</thought> What's this? I've spotted something that's not quite right... <thought>What is so unusual about this suitcase?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, I figured you thought the design was odd, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never said the design was odd...!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please don't give me that attitude! <thought>Argh! I can't let her get me all riled up. Time to calmly take another good, hard look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, no matter how you cut it, the price is a bit odd, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That wasn't what I was pointing out to be odd... <thought>The answer should come to me if I think back on all that has happened here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what so odd!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I don't think it's that strange at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Well, maybe not to that extent... ahem. <thought>I mustn't over-think this. I should let the answer come to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's something very peculiar about these wheels.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? As in?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As in... ...there are no stoppers in place on these. Without stoppers, one would think that the turbulence would have sent it flying.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...And?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* And so, it is very likely that this suitcase was placed here after we hit that turbulence! Let's take a closer look at it, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was apparently designed by Ms. Teneiro herself. The design has a certain... je ne sais quoi about it. Yes... Perhaps that is the best way to put it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A $1,200 price tag... Not exactly priced by someone with a conscience, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's this? The wheel is completely covered in something... This color and this scent... It appears the substance in question is grape juice. But why would there be juice on the wheel of a suitcase?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, it would appear to be unlocked. Let's take a look at what's inside. A piece of cloth... ...And it's soaked with blood!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aaaaah! It's... It's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that this suitcase... ...is very strongly tied to our murder after all!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">So explain this to me...? What does this suitcase have to do with the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it's pretty safe to say that the killer used this suitcase in some manner. Such as to move something perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ehhhh... But aren't you just talking about the cloth then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That alone is too small. A larger item would be needed to move what I'm thinking of. The "thing" I believe the killer used this suitcase to transport is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Meele">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? Did you say something just now, Mr. Edgeworth? I mean, I don't know... but I don't think that's it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, this? No, no, I was just seeing if you were awake. My real explanation begins now.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is she really asleep...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something that would fit inside a suitcase that is also covered in blood... Sounds like a dead body, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">But... But...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This cloth was most likely in here with the body... Just what was this suitcase used for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would there be blood inside a suitcase like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For there to be this much blood on this piece of cloth... Was the victim wrapped in it at some point? Hmm... There's something very familiar sbout this fabric pattern...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In light of this, I'd say that Mr. Hicks was moved into the elevator from someplace else. Which means that the murder was committed in an entirely different location!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">......... So you're saying that after moving the body into the elevator... ...the killer brought the suitcase in here and just left it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um, nothing... Just that... ...I was thinking about what Ms. Rhoda said about coming here for something...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Excuse me, Mr. Edgeworth... I wanted to give you a bit more time... ...but I'm afraid I wasn't able to convince the captain. I'm very sorry, Mr. Edgeworth. but the captain feels that he has allowed you ample time. He says that he'd appreciate it if you could wrap it up here and return to your seat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand his sentiments, however, if I'm not allowed to complete my investigation... ...the crime scene may become contaminated by the time we land. If I must stop, then I insist I be allowed to oversee the preservation of the two sites. ...Under your supervision, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">If that's your only condition, then I believe we can accommodate your wishes. I'm here to assist you in any way that I can, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Sounds like fun! We can camp out and watch over everything together!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've found proof that the real crime scene was not in the lounge... ...and I have enough evidence to prove myself to be innocent of any wrongdoing... And yet... Regarding that Ms. Meele reminded me about Ms. Teneiro... I can't allow my investigation to end here! The truth must come to light!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know that once we had landed... ...I'm supposed to let the local police take over... And thanks to Ms. Teneiro and Ms. Meele, I was able to preserve the crime scene... But I just can't shake it. I wasn't able to talk with Ms. Teneiro in private... ...so I'm left wondering just what was she up to? Why did she do what she did? There must be a way for me to continue my investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I've been expecting you, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska? I thought you were still in Germany...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I go where I am needed. And wherever there are criminals to be caught.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her name is Franziska von Karma. The daughter of my mentor, Manfred von Karma, she, like myself, is a prosecutor.</thought> Are you heading up this case? It would be a bit of a relief if you are...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't you try to flatter me! Miles Edgeworth... I'm placing you under arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's quite frustrating, actually. I had hoped to exact my revenge on you in a different venue... ...but I'll have to take what I can get. I never thought I'd see the day... ...when a disciple of the house of Von Karma would become a criminal! Have you no shame!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! It has all been a big misunderstanding! I didn't kill the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A misunderstanding!? I heard all about the murder over the police radio from the captain himself. You waited for the victim on the first floor, and then beat him to death.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, do you honestly believe that I killed a man?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.................. I suppose I should reserve judgement until after I have investigated this for myself. I can put your arrest on hold until then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's as it should be.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah! I don't need a lecture on how to perform my duties from you of all people. "To be perfect in everyway." The fulfillemnt of that creed alone is all I strive for!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I have my own creed which I must fulfill, so why don't we solve this together?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I have to get going. The crime scene awaits. Don't you dare leave town.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Trust me, I had no intention to.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Too slow!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owww!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Listen up. I'm leaving you in charge of watching this man. Don't mess up, understand!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth!? I'm supposed to guard him!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A simple yes or no, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! Yes, sir! Understood, sir! You just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth. If you interfere with my investigation, I'll arrest you on the spot. Are we clear? Now then, if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Good to see you again, Mr. Edgeworth, sir! Boy am I glad to see you're OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I believe in you, sir! You can lean on me! I'll get you through this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have to admit I'm a bit curious as to what Franziska is up to. Maybe I should ask the good detective...</thought> Very well. In that case, I have a few questions for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should try to get some information out of Detective Gumshoe first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't believe there's no one manning the counter when a murder has just occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What a view of the planes preparing for takeoff. Besides the turbulence, they're really not all that bad as a mode of transportation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So how is the initial investigation going?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We just shipped the body off to the coroner's office... ...and we're taking statements now, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That sounds like Franziska. She was always good at quick responses to a case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd say she was, uh... a little too quick, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh... Um...! I rushed on over as soon as I got word of the affair, sir! But somehow, when I got here... ...Ms. von Karma was already here barking out orders at everyone! It was kinda creepy! As though she knew there had been a murder or something... ...and had come in advance to await your flight's arrival!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That is sort of odd. She did show up rather quickly, and out of the blue. Plus, I still don't know why she's here in America... There must be some backstory to all of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ms. von Karma just kinda popped up at the Prosecutor's Office about a week ago, sir. Something about chasing down leads related to a certain incident...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No details?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's kinda top-secret, so she can't talk about it, even with me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Knowing her, the only type of talking she likes to do is with her whip. Plus, I doubt the top secret part was what stopped her from talking to you, Detective. Although, I wonder if her case has anything to do with mine...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth, I think something just fell out of your pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? What are you.........gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-So did something fall out or not? I didn't, um, get a good look, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It doesn't concern you, so don't worry about it. <thought>My Prosecutor's Badge, of all things! Gumshoe must never know that I dropped it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Wh-Wh-What is this... this raccoon-looking thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not a raccoon. It's the mascot of iFly Airlines. His name is Mr. Ifly, and apparently, he's supposed to be a monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooooooooooh! I'm feeling some inspiration coming ooooooon! I'm going to make a piggy bank out of the police mascot, the Blue Badger! Then, whenever there's any loose change lying around the precinct, it can go in there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sure, sounds great. <thought>...As long as it isn't any of my money.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So! This design! It's so post-modern, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Post-modern, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, especially this alien-shaped handle here. You can really feel a connection.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...A connection. right. Detective, please stop with your horrible impression of an art critic.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But I was only telling you my honest feelings, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, this is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! Is that for me!? Aww, you shouldn't have, sir! But I'll gladly take anything you want to give to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hands off, Detective! This item is related to the case!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Oh... So, um, what about it did you want to ask me about...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Forget I asked, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This child seems to be happily enjoying the sight of so many planes.</line>
<line speaker="Boy">Wow!!! I'd love to take a run down that runaway!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Oh, the youth of today. So much potential, yet so misguided.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Looking from behind... I think I've seen this man somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">OM NOM NOM NOM NOM NOM! In Soviet Russia, World Flags Lunchboxes eat j00! Urrr...Nnn...F... <thought>&gt;_&lt;;</thought> Found it! LAWL!! Ooh! I feel a wave of CR34T1V3 POW3RZ coming ON! It's over 9000!!! LULZ! For my next L33T movie, it's gonna be "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo"... versus "The World Samurai: Champion of the Earth"! It's gonna r0x0rz so many b0x0rz!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the Steel Samurai is finally getting a movie...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... "Lunchland"... Not bad. I guess it's gotten big enough to warrant its own branch shops.</line>
<line speaker="Customer">Hmm... Which should I go with?</line>
<line speaker="Vendor">I recommend our airport special, World Flags Lunchboxes! Only available for a limited time! We have a variety of lunchboxes made up to look like different countries' flags!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I wonder if they're aiming to take Lunchland to the international market?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man was in First Class with me. He was quite shaken up by the whole affair.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">*quiver*... I... I did it... I made it the whole flight... I'm not scared of turbulence anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He must have been pretty scared. He's repeating the same thing over and over to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, that's about all the info I have, sir. We should find out more as we investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, it is high time to resume my investigation. Starting with talking to the people involved in this case afresh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't believe there's no one manning the counter when a murder has just occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Relax, Mr. Edgeworth! I'm here! I'll make sure nothing else happens!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You are precisely why I can't relax.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What a view of the planes preparing for takeoff.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wanna ride a plane someday and go overseas!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Have you never been to another country before, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nope, not yet, sir! I don't even have a passport! But I've been saving up for that eventual "someday"! A penny a day to be precise!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At that rate, he won't be making any trips until well after retirement!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This child seems to be happily enjoying the sight of so many planes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm all excited to see this many planes, too! Just look at the size of these things!</line>
<line speaker="Boy">Do you like planes, too, mister? The balance between the main wings and the tail wings is really something, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah... It seems that this child derives his pleasure from a different aspect.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, but I've also got a thing for the shape of the wings, too!</line>
<line speaker="Boy">Here, mister! You can stand next to me! So about that plane's wing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Tsk! Thank you, Detective, for leaving me out of this conversation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Looking from behind... I think I've seen this man somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">OM NOM NOM NOM NOM NOM! In Soviet Russia, World Flags Lunchboxes eat j00! Urrr...Nnn...F... <thought>&gt;_&lt;;</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! We've gotta get him some water!</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">Found it! LAWL!! Ooh! I feel a wave of CR34T1V3 POW3RZ coming ON! It's over 9000!!! LULZ! For my next L33T movie, it's gonna be "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo"... versus "The World Samurai: Champion of the Earth"! It's gonna r0x0rz so many b0x0rz!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phew! Good thing it was a false alarm, right, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the Steel Samurai is finally getting a movie...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......Completely ignoring me, as usual. *whimper*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... "Lunchland"... Not bad. I guess it's gotten big enough to warrant its own branch shops.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I've always wanted to give their Steak Lunch a try!</line>
<line speaker="Customer">Hmm... Which should I go with?</line>
<line speaker="Vendor">I recommend our airport special, World Flags Lunchboxes! Only available for a limited time! We have a variety of lunchboxes made up to look like different countries' flags!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you really want one that badly, Detective, why don't you go ahead and buy one?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-Is that OK, sir!? Thanks! Alright, then I'm really gonna get one! Here I go! Excuse me, miss! I'll take a Star-Spangled Banner Lunchbox, please!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I hope he's aware that's the most expensive one on the menu.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man was in First Class with me. He was quite shaken up by the whole affair.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd be pretty scared too if I got caught up in a murder investigation, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Passenger">*quiver*... I... I did it... I made it the whole flight... I'm not scared of turbulence anymore! *quiver*... This life vest is proof I made it alive. It's now my prized possession.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...How could you just take that from the plane!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's OK, Mr. Edgeworth. It's got nothing to do with the murder, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So get this, sir! I bet the victim used this suitcase as his hiding place!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ex-Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know! To stow away onto this flight, sir! He must've been inside all along! But someone found him out and that's when *bam* he was killed! Actually, that was the plot of a movie I saw recently...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. Get your head out of the theater and back into reality.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the victim's blood... Right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspect so, but we won't know much more until it's been processed by forensics.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it's a good thing no one wanted to buy this suitcase!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...How so?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Imagine the shock on their face when they go to open it and out pops a dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose. <thought>Although it's really nothing to get all shocked over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So you must be the captain.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Why, yes, I am! And who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I am the Prodigy Prosecutor, Franziska von Karma, and I have a few questions for you.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ahhh, don't you dare, Captain! Getting friendly with another woman... I'll never forgive if you do!</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Wh-What are you talking about? I-I only have eyes for you, my dear Cammy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wouldn't bet money on our dear captain to be much of a reputable person.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure you don't want to ask the captain some questions, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was in the cockpit the entire time. I highly doubt he would know anything of use. Anyway, I like to leave that type of witness to Franziska and her whip.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Aaaaaaaaah!!!</line>
<line speaker="???">Now see here!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaack! Sorry, sorry, sorry! I'm SOOOOOOOOOORRY!!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">How long do you intend to hold me!? It is impossible for me to be the criminal! I told you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Oh, it is you! Tell this man to stop stopping me from going! Time is money! I don't have even one second of wasteful time to spend!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anything of interest, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, well, I can say that I don't quite know everything about the situation yet... ...so I was just telling myself that I should go ask someone about the stuff I don't know! I mean, just because I don't know it doesn't mean someone else might not know it, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It must be my imagination, but for a second, I think I actually understood his logic!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir, you can't go in there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm Miles Edgeworth. I am one of the prosecutors on this case, so please let me through.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">I'm very sorry, sir. No one is allowed to enter without Ms. von Karma's express permission.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But I'm on the case...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, I understand that, but... ...I also have explicit instructions not to let you through from Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grrr... Why would you do this to me, Franziska...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They've got a piano on this plane!? Hey! Do you think I can try it out, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd think you would know better than to randomly touch things at a crime scene, Detective! Besides, I didn't know you knew how to play.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course I do! I'm practically proficient!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting... The things you learn about people on a daily basis.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can get Do and Re to come out just right, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two notes does not a proficient pianist make, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, man... there's a really pretty lady in that plane over there. Aaaaaaack! She's looking over here! Quick, sir! Wave at her with me, please!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I refuse to be your wingman on this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There are a few copies of Sky Magazine in the magazine rack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This month's special... Oh, looks like it's an English trivia quiz. Oh, I've got one! What starts with "i" and means "boldly rude" and "disrespectful"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The answer is most definitely "insolent".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Time's up! Sorry, sir, but the correct answer is "insolvent"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Detective Gumshoe... Don't tell me your English ability is at the same level as "him"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! This statue...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What about it, Detective? Did you notice something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I saw this guy in a dream last night! The resemblance is uncanny, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw him in your dreams?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, yeah. I saw him, and then I arrested him! I wanted to show you just how vital I am in our partnership!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Being useful in your sleep is of no help to me in the real world, Detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Mr. Edgeworth! You have to see this chair!! It says, "In honor of Rocker Pals' Day".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly is the big deal with these "Rocker Pals"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're a seriously sweet Swiss super-star rock band, sir! Ah... Makes me wanna listen to one of their songs right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, I got lost in that forest of s's just now...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you want me to explain it to you again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You know, Detective, I think I'll have to take a raincheck on that, regrettably.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like we can't go beyond here, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Plus, the body has been sent off to the medical examiner's office for an autopsy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth! What is this super-expensive-looking feast of Jurassic proportions?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's just the food they serve in First Class.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow! I am so jealous, sir! I wanna ride in First Class sometime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Right... When pigs fly and I own my own private jet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's nothing supernatural about earthquakes and elevators! Although... Is it just me or do elevators have a long-standing hatred for me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth, this urn's got a seatbelt strapped tightly around it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It must be of great value to Mr. Lablanc then.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I guess if you don't want to churn your urn, then it's always best to buckle up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Obviously. But did that have anything to do with the case, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Nobody gets my jokes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I may have a word with you, Ms. Meele...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">No, you may not have a word with me. I don't want to talk to any other man except for the captain right now.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Me, too, Cammy! I... I will never talk to another woma.... aaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This definitely looks like a job for Franziska.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, a movie poster! So what's it for, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"License to Love, Laugh, Maim, and Murder", apparently, though I don't know what it's about.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oh, that movie is the in-flight special! I can't recommend it enough!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aaah! When you talk like that, you sound just like Ms. Rhoda! And you know how I hate that.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean for it to come out like that, Cammy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Clearly, the only remedy for this whipped man is a solid crack of Franziska's whip.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You impudent man! If you value your life, you will close that mouth of yours immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, Ms. von Karma's more hard-boiled than the movie.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">What did I ever do to deserve this...&#160;? More than this job, all I truly love is my sweet Cammy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Might I suggest you not say that at this moment in front of Franziska...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I'd like to ask you about the investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth. Can't you see that I'm in the middle of taking his statement? This man is the only captain in title. I'm going to teach him to do his job properly.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Owww!! OK, OK! From now on, I'll keep my focus and take my responsibilities seriously!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's really trembling there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it makes him to take his job seriously, it's not such a bad thing, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why are you looking at me like that, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was the victim's seat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">His jacket's just lying there, and his spilled left-over coffee's still there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't suppose anyone ever expects to die.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was my seat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow! You read law books even when you're flying, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you expecting anything less? Now come along, we must hurry to the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hm? Hold on a sec... There's a different book stuck in here. "The Steel Samurai's Adv..."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Am I going to have to charge you with invasion of privacy!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The man in this seat was the one we just saw out in the airport lobby hyperventilating. If he's so scared to fly, then why take an airplane to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, if he's that scared, he shoulda caught a ferry or a cruise ship or something. By the way, were you OK with all the turbulence, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. Ah, yes. It was nothing I couldn't handle.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I should've figured, right? As if you'd get on a plane if you were scared of them!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth? I think you have too many red knights on this board...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's just your imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And it looks like that blue pawn is being completely surrounded by the red knights.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now you're seeing things.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, sir... I don't think you're supposed to have lots of the same piece like in checkers...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that, Detective! What do you take me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's a really big floaty! But isn't it a bit too early in this year for swimming?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, that is not for swimming. It's a lifesaver.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you can't swim with one of these?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... I mean, I suppose you could, but that's not what they are intended for...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well then, see, it's the same as a floaty! You shouldn't go around confusing people, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>......Why do I feel like I've just kicked a puppy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The man in this seat was constantly drinking something.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, right before payday, I do nothing but drink the soup from my instant noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That much sodium can't be healthy. You might want to go in for a check-up.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho, did you really think I was serious, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Waaaaaaah! I'm sorry, sir!!! I'll never make another joke like that again!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's this!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Detective!? Did you find an important piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A giant parfait on top of bread AND steak!? Paint me jealous, sir! It's a feast!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>Maybe I should just let him have the giant parfait so that we can move on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A mountain's worth of empty bottles are lined up here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And look! All of them have a letter inside, sir. Let's see... "I'll order anything as many times as it takes, just to see your lovely face. My beloved Ms. Teneiro..." is what they all say, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Please put them back in the bottles, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... I can't destroy the beautiful love here by ruining the letters by accident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you finish taking his statement yet?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup, all done, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I do not concern if you're not done examining the cargo hold. I want my cargo back!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">If you make a single scratch on my art, you will pay!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Art? What sort of art?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Lablanc is an art dealer, so he's got a bunch of artwork down in the cargo hold, sir. There's practically a mountain of them, large and small.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">From folk costumes to stone statues, I sell all kinds of arts!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Folk costumes...? Speaking of which, Mr. Lablanc's hat... It kinds of looks like that other piece of cloth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You! I can say you have the guts to show me a piece of art at this time. But from a single glance I can already tell it is mostly worthless.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hah. This has much more value as a piece of non-art, I assure you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You look like you have something to say! Perhaps you are thinking, "like casting pearls before swine"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He actually hit the nail on the head for once!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Ah, so you are finally paying my wasted money?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but there is absolutely nothing inside this wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">How dare you! You are wanting to trick me! I will sue for fraud!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc. Are you seriously considering a courtroom tango with me? I hope not, but in case you are, there is a certain lawyer I can introduce you to.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, can you please take a look at this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hm? Oh! It's a Borginian cloth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I suspected. Your hat is made of the same material, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Yes, of course! This fabric is so famous, orders come from over the seas for more!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then this is the cargo you were talking about earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">No, no, no. My cargo this time is much, much many gigantic! You, Detective! When can I have my cargo moved!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can get your cargo back when we're done investigating, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The stubbornness of you police, it is no good! And it is no good that attendant refuses to exit the attendants' room, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That attendant...? <thought>I wonder if he's talking about Ms. Teneiro?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What is it!? Do you have some use for me? You seem not to understand; I have no time to waste! Let me put it another way! "Le temps, c'est de l'argent!" There! Maybe another language will get through your head!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I understood you perfectly fine in English.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For there to be this much blood on this piece of cloth... Was the victim wrapped in it at some point? According to Mr. Lablanc, this textile is fairly famous.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What a waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did you mean by "that attendant", Mr. Lablanc?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">She was taken into the attendants' room for her interview. And then they still have not come out! They make no sign of coming out either! I was finished with my own interview much earlier, quicker than her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why is Ms. Teneiro's interview the only one that's taking up so much time...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth. You were given free reign to examine the plane, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I was able to obtain the cooperation of the flight attendants. Speaking of attendants, I'd like to speak with Ms. Teneiro. I wonder if you might grant me permission to enter the flight attendants' room?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Before I do... ...you still have to clear up a few issues surrounding your own circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You may have tricked those attendants with your sophisticated talking... ...but you can't pull the wool over my eyes, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Let's not complicate things and go with the most obvious conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. The "likeliest suspect", Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do you have a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, but it's not like you to use such vague wording. You're usually a bit more... absolute.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm simply trying to watch out you. Or my kindness too hard for you to comprehend?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, but your leniency is unnecessary, for I will prove my innocence soon enough! <thought>If I want to continue my investigation, I'll have to break her line of logic, fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Let's not complicate things and go with the most obvious conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you think you're being a bit rash by simply declaring me the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. I like my affairs to be simple. And perfect. I'll show you the meaning of both when I finish this whole thing within three minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You say that like you're cooking a pack of instant noodles! Threeeeeooooowww!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I won't allow even three seconds of useless testimony to be uttered in my presence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I see she hasn't changed a bit. But I won't allow her to send me to prison so easily.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The scene of the crime was here, in the very lounge the body was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So tell me, Franziska, do you know all there is to know about the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I know all that I need to know in order to arrest you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And nothing more?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Are you saying there is more I need to know!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaaaaah! Wh-Why did you whip me, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Sorry, Scruffy. My hand must've slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would appear that Franziska doesn't have all the facts of this case yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">From the time the victim was seen calling for an attendant until his body as found...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by "seen"?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Please stop pretending like you don't know. It's insulting. Obviously, I'm talking about how Mr. Hicks was seen calling for an attendant at 5 AM. And then, from the time after that call until the body was found...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...the only person in this lounge the entire time was you, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While it's true that I was in the lounge the whole time... ...that fact alone does not make me the criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah, we'll see about that at the conclusion of this investigation. However, there is one thing that even you must admit at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This, unmistakably, makes you the likeliest suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Under the circumstances, I suppose I can agree that I am the most likely suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-but I believe in you, sir! I don't think you did it! Ms. von Karma's gotta believe that, too, right! I mean, you two are like siblings...OWWWW!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Quiet, Scruffy! Even if we are related by blood, that's no guarantee that he's not a criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Franziska...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I demand to see some proof that you are not the guilty party!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The likeliest suspect, huh. What a roundabout euphemism. But it would appear that she doesn't yet know... ...about the new evidence that we acquired, and where we acquired it. I'll take care of the gaps in her logic one hole at a time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that you did not have all the information you need after all.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I found a nice piece of evidence just before I was forced to stop investigating. A piece that proves the body was moved from a different location!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer used this suitcase to move the victim's body. Meaning that the real scene of the crime is not this lounge at all!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Now who's the one rashly jumping to conclusions?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">All you did was find this piece of cloth inside the suitcase. That doesn't prove that the body was moved. It could be that the killer simply chose that suitcase as a good place to hide the cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I expected you would come to that conclusion. It would seem I can't escape that easily.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You should know better than that. A Von Karma is perfect in every way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but did you know that the killer definitely wheeled the suitcase around at some point?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">As if there is proof of that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Where is the proof that this suitcase was moved around?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All it takes is one look at this and you'll have your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Indeed, I have my answer now. ......That you are an ignorant whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaaaargh! <thought>Or rather, that you are the unforgiving whipper-snapper. The suitcase ended up in the in-flight shop, but where did it come from? The answer should become clear if I just think about the path the killer took.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The spilled grape juice in front of the elevator...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I'd like to draw your attention to this area here... <thought>Where is the evidence that proves the killer dragged the suitcase through here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We can assume these prints belong to the culprit, and they clearly lead to the shop...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I asked for proof about the suitcase. Give me any unrelated evidence, and you will feel the pain of my whip.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's no need to remind me; my body learned that lesson well a long time ago! These prints are important, but there is something else that is even more so!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what exactly am I looking at here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't like to repeat myself... ...but I suppose it can't be helped if you didn't spot it on your own. Now then, I'll...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Get on with it and tell me the answer already.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I wonder if she saw through my blunder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This mark here... Wouldn't you say that it looks suspiciously like tracks from two wheels?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Further, there is also grape juice residue on the wheels of the suitcase. This means that the suitcase containing the victim's body definitely passed through here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........I suppose this means that the killer... ...did move the victim's body from somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm glad you've come to your senses.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Not so fast! This still doesn't put you in the clear! Not by a long shot!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You prepared yourself and acquired the piggy bank before the plane hit that turbulence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not a bad bit of logic, for something you thought of on the fly.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just what are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That I will show you exactly how flawed your logic is. <thought>No matter how strong of a face you put on, not even you can hide your fears from me. I'll expose all the flaws in her logic in one fell swoop!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You prepared yourself and acquired the piggy bank before the plane hit that turbulence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how do you suppose I was able to take the piggy bank out of its display case? As I recall, the case was locked.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's easy. If the case was locked... ...you simply had to hit the glass... like this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeeeoww! Y-You've shattered my heart of glass!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So she wants to talk about the in-flight shop and the Mr. Ifly bank, does she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That takes care of how you obtained the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And then, you waited for the victim in the lounge, where you beat him to death.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought there wasn't any of the victim's blood found in the lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. I thought you'd say that. What? Did you think I wouldn't have noticed? I think you just found a way to cleverly hide the blood splatter in the lounge! By "accidentally spilling" grape juice on top of it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrgh! Are you accusing me of tampering with the crime scene now!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We'll see, won't we? The forensic scientists are hard at work on that as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........And? What do you propose I did after that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then, while you were in the elevator with the victim's body stuck in the suitcase...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So I put the victim's body into the suitcase, and then? Where was I headed, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's pretty obvious. You were bringing it to First Class where you could safely keep an eye on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're talking about this thing, you know. I'd hardly call it discreet or ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Annoying brat. Well then, you were intending to leave it inside the elevator. But unfortunately for you, a wrench was thrown into your plans, because...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...the plane hit the patch of turbulence, and out flew the body from within the suitcase!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've experienced turbulence on a flight before.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course. Many times. You get used to it after a while.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The patch we hit was especially rough... and I passed out briefly, but only for a second.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Good thing it was only for a sec, sir! It'd been bad if you had really blanked out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y...Yes, indeed. <thought>Unfortunately, blanking out is exactly what got me into this mess in the first place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's enough of your idle chatter. I'm not through with you yet, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">With no way out, you hastily put the suitcase back where you had taken it from...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... If I really were a criminal, do you really think I would be so easily caught?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You are certainly in the middle of being caught right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnaaaaaaargh! <thought>I have to find a contradiction fast, or I won't have much of my own hide left to save!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have to say, you are looking rather caught right now. And I'll tell you exactly what you did after that. You loitered around in the lounge...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...and pretended to be the "discoverer" of the body.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I didn't pretend to be anything! I really was the first to discover the victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I suppose that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? So then...you are yielding to my statements?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't be foolish! I still insist that you are the killer, but... ...in that sense, you really were the first to "discover the body to be dead."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...No matter what I say, she seems dead set on making me out to be the killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her logic is reasonably sound... ...and the large majority of it reflects the truth... ...but there is one point about it that is not quite right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fact that you took this piece of evidence into account in your testimony... ...is to be commended. Your legal prowess is certainly something to be feared.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Evidence and logic. Essential tools that those who would stand in a courtroom must learn to master.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But what if there was a fake piece of evidence thrown into the mix?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A fake...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This Mr. Ifly piggy bank is just such a fake! It is NOT the real murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The timing of when the bank was taken from the shop is important. And it was taken after the turbulence had occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But then, what about the blood on the bank!? What do you make of that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume it was added after the murder when the killer fabricated this weapon. Looking at it this way, the killer did basically three things after the turbulence. After exiting the elevator... ...the killer brought the suitcase to the shop and left it there. Then, the killer proceeded to pick the bank up from off the floor... ...and took it to fabricate a fake murder weapon by hitting the victim on the head. Finally, the victim's wallet was planted on my personage, in my pocket to be precise. Everything was done so that I would be framed for the murder of Mr. Akbey Hicks!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You there!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Other than this piggy bank, was anything else resembling a murder weapon found?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">We didn't find anything in the lounge or in the shop that could be used as one, ma'am! Most of the items that could have been used were broken during the turbulence. And the remaining items all tested negative for any trace of blood!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">........I see. Well, Miles Edgeworth, it appears your stall tactics are at an end.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it's possible that it's just hidden somewhere, sir! Eeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If the criminal had wanted to hide the weapon in a safer place... ...I'd think the weapon would have been hidden in the same place as the bloody cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly what I was thinking. Because the cloth was hidden inside that suitcase, it signals to me that the killer... ...had not prepared a more secure place to hide the evidence. Which means that the real murder weapon is either still on the murderer's personage... ...or is still at the real crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There is one more possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that would be?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That the piggy bank is in fact the real weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But didn't we just...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Let me finish! The killer took the bank out from the display case before the turbulence... ...by opening the lock on the display case door. And it was at that time that the glass pane in the door was broken. I'd say that's a perfectly reasonable line of reasoning, wouldn't you? Let's see... so that means that the killer had the key to the display case...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... The person you're talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Not so fast, I'm not finished! The person I'm talking about also committed another sin. She tricked the captain... ...and granted you permission to conduct the investigation. Yes, it is the sin of lying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Speaking of which, I recall that you also wished to speak with her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Very well, permission granted. But only if I can sit in on your interrogation. Do we understand each other?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no intention of interrogating her. But you are welcome to accompany me if you so wish.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ms. Teneiro is in the flight attendants' room. Let's move.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Way to show her who's boss, Mr. Edgeworth! Not even Ms. von Karma's whip is a match for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You give me too much credit. She simply didn't have all the information. To be sure, the fights will become tougher and tougher as this investigation progresses.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's alright, Mr. Edgeworth! You've got me watching your back! I'll make sure to keep on supporting you any way I can! You just say the word, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Really...? Then how about standing out in front and absorbing whip lashes for me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">I've been told by Ms. von Karma that you can now enter the flight attendants' room. Please feel free to look around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you. <thought>Now to unravel Ms. Teneiro's true intentions!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You! Hurry and solve your murder! If you do not, how am I supposed to have my cargo returned to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could please be patient just a little longer, Mr. Lablanc...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hurry and solve it! Like a strike of thunder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's "As fast as lightning." And believe me, if I could, I would.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ms. Teneiro is in the flight attendants' room. Let's move.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That blue door over there leads to the flight attendants' room, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. Let's go see what Ms. Teneiro has to say for herself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, a movie poster! So what's it for, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"License to Love, Laugh, Maim, and Murder", apparently, though I don't know what it's about.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oh, that movie is the in-flight special! I can't recommend it enough!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aaah! When you talk like that, you sound just like Ms. Rhoda! And you know how I hate that.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean for it to come out like that, Cammy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man really needs a solid crack of Franziska's whip.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I many have a word with you, Ms. Meele...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">No, you may not have a word with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I want to assure you that the lady is a fellow prosecutor. Her name is Franziska von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I don't care who she is, she's talking with mon capitaine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense Ms. Meele is the type who considers every other woman to be a threat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm so sorry for the late introduction. I am Miles Edgeworth, prosecutor. I believe one of the attendants asked you in my stead for permission to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Captain">Ah, yes... You must be the prosecutor Camm... I mean, Ms. Meele was telling me about. I remember telling her you could investigate the in-flight shop, or something of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Then I guess it's true; Ms. Teneiro didn't ask him for permission on my behalf.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Captain">Oh, sorry, I forgot to introduce myself. I'm the captain of...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you for your help. <thought>I think this is about all the information I'm going to get from this man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So you're the one that poked around inside this plane without the captain's permission!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Deviating from the flight attendant's manual is very unbecoming, you know. What were you hoping to accomplish by doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">...I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah! Mr. Edgeworth! You're here, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you please help us and shed some light on why you did what you did?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">......Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you doing, and why are you fidgeting?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... I've never been on a plane before. And I've never been in an attendants' room...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, even on a normal flight, one would rarely ever need to enter one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't know when I'll ever get to be on a plane again, so I wanna soak it all in now, sir! Let's see... A box full of crowns, and a yellow suitcase, and, oh... what a great trip!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pagind Detective Gumshoe. Kindly return to the situation at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Isn't there something that should be doing right now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. I should be asking Ms. Teneiro for her side of the story.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's right. And how does that have anything to do with what's over there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nothing really.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you already knew that, then why don't you hurry up with the interrogation already?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">This door leads to the cargo hold. But I can't let you through without Ms. von Karma's express permission.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not a bad way to handle this situation if it was any old case, but this isn't.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So between you and Ms. von Karma, who's better at their job?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, there is no comparison to be made, Detective. None.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is all this junk inside these boxes? There's no rhyme or reason to any of it.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That's our lost and found, Ms. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gold crowns, and swords, and necklaces... It's like a treasure trove in here, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The fact that these were left on the plane implies they were carried onto it to begin with... Something tells me it's time for iFly to send its metal detectors out for repairs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is sure to be a clue of some sort in this trash can. Detective Gumshoe, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! You just leave the rummaging to me!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Scruffy! How dare you go through a woman's trash without her permission!? Have you no sense of honor!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeeeeek! I'm sorry! I-I'm just doing what Mr. Edgeworth told me to doooooooowww!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Forgive me, Detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's pretty easy to tell who sleeps in which bunk just by looking. I am almost certain that the well-kept one up top belongs to Ms. Teneiro.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ewww... This bottom one is a giant mess.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......You sloven, squalid, scoundrel of a man... You dare to scrutinize a woman's bed and invade her privacy!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeeeeoooww!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* There are some things in life best kept to yourself, Detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, go on. Let's hear out troublesome attendant out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In due time. I do have one thing I'd like to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you plan to continue using that whip for the foreseeable future?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course! I've wrangled many a testimony out of people thanks to it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and probably a whole ton of yelps, toooooooooowwww!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I'm willing to bet that the majority of them came from you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what are inside these boxes?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, those are some souvenirs I bought in Borginia.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's so many! There's even a second box!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, yes. I find that folk art from around the world does great things for my creativity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those suitcases certainly could have done with a whole lot less of your "creativity"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What exactly is this panel for?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah, that's the emergency control panel for the elevator. We used it to stop the elevator on the first floor and to keep its doors open.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you lie about receiving the captain's permission like that?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.................. Because I didn't think I would be able to get his permission.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The captain... He only has ears for Cammy...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I spoke with the captain a little earlier myself. He definitely seems to be rather taken with Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes... and on top of that... ...I had mistakenly accused Mr. Edgeworth of being the killer. I wanted to make amends.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, please allow me to thank you for what you did. Thanks to you, I was able to clear myself of all charges.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Really!? You were able to prove your innocence? Oh, thank goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ms. Teneiro, is it? There is one more thing I'd like to ask you. You were in the in-flight shop just before the turbulence, weren't you? Please answer honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, I was.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And why were you there?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? Why the sudden hesitation? Franziska seems to have struck a nerve...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">All I did was go check up on the shop like I always do.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're saying it was for work then?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. I'm in charge of the shop, so I have to keep an eye on it. I don't have any reason to go there otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After your visit to the shop, you paid a visit to this room, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. I came back to freshen up and adjust my make-up. I'm sorry, but there isn't much else to tell...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Ms. Teneiro claims to have no reason other than duty to go to the shop. But is that all there is to it? Maybe I should ask her about that thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could please take a look at this for me, Ms. Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, that suitcase...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, about this suitcase, you are the one who designed it, correct? And I think I figured something else out about it. This suitcase is the reason you went to the shop, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........There's nothing you won't find out eventually, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Won't you please tell me more about this suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, um, I... Well, I... ...I was interested in seeing how the suitcases I had designed were selling! I... I know that as a service professional, I'm not supposed to care... ...but I really wanted to know! And I was glad to see that it was the last one there...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! <thought>"The last one there"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'm sorry, Mr. Edgeworth... I don't know how to answer you. As a professional flight attendant, I'm a failure...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She must be worn out from the long question session she just went through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So these are the attendants' lockers, huh? Let's hurry up and examine them, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Why must men always be so rude? Besides, who exactly gave you permission to search through the attendants' lockers?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, Detective! It would be uncouth of us to look in a woman's locker without her permission.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I guess so. Plus, I feel this murderous draft and I can sense a whip not far behind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's one of those suitcases designed by Ms. Teneiro. You can tell it's hardly ever been used by the lack of even a single scratch on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying, Ms. Teneiro, that the suitcase in question was the last one?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. They're just so popular, they're practically flying off the shelves!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's not exactly the impression I got...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The one in the shop is most definitely the last one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, we're currently looking at that suitcase. I didn't say anything about buying it!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Then say you'll buy it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I'm sorry, but I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">B...But why? I think it'd go great with your complexion, Mr. Edgeworth! It really suits you! I guarantee it personally as a service professional!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um... Well... That is... How should I put this... ...It's hideous.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Maybe that was a bit too direct.</thought> Moving on... My issue with the suitcases isn't the design, it's the number of them remaining.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">R-Remaining...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were two suitcases in the in-flight shop when I investigated it.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Two...? But that's... impossible! I'm sure there was only one...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Looks like her story has generated quite the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">When I left the shop... ...I'm positive there was only one suitcase left!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something is amiss here. What could be the meaning of this inconsistency?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm?</thought> By the way, Ms. Teneiro... What is one of those suitcases doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought you said there was only one left...?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Th-That one is, um... It's mine. I've used it for a very long time now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's used it for a long time...? I think not.</thought> Ms. Teneiro, I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't lie to me.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Excuse me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't believe for even one second that you've sued this "for a very long time"! <thought>What proves that this hasn't been used for nearly as long as Ms. Teneiro says?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's hardly any dirt or grime on this suitcase! If this has been used for as long as you claim, then there should be some sign of that.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth, in case you haven't noticed, I love to clean.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That suitcase, the floor, and almost everything else in here sparkles. The only thing that isn't is the gray matter in your head!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Urngh... There must be evidence that this suitcase hasn't been used before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Simply by looking here, you can tell!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Tell what by looking where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please... A simple glance won't do. Look harder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...I don't get it either, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah... Then I suppose I have no choice but to explain it to you once again.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. I suggest you take your own advice: a simple glance won't do, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nrghk! <thought>She just had to figure it out... There must be something that proves this suitcase is brand new. Yes, that's exactly what I need to do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me, Ms. Teneiro, is it also your habit to keep the price tag pristine on your suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is the meaning of this!? Why would you lie about a suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Despite having faith in her design sense... ...the sales numbers made her cry bitter tears. The truth is becoming increasingly clear to me.</thought> Ms. Teneiro, I think I understand. I know what you are trying to hide. Now then, this suitcase was originally in...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suitcase was originally in this flight attendants' room!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">So now you believe what I said about it being my personal suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, not at all! It was here, but then it was taken to another location, and...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I refuse to stand by while a villainous man vilifies a woman with such vile tactics!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nnngh! She's making me out to be some sort of super-villain! I need to rethink this... I have to figure out where this suitcase came from!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was originally in First Class as part of a sales campaign! But the passengers were so engrossed in the movie that you brought it back... here...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...And? What does that have to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should try to find that out. Isn't it our job to investigate these kinds of connections?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then investigate it by yourself on your own time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrgh! I should probably rethink this... I have to figure out where this suitcase came from!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Seeing as how the price tag is still on this suitcase... ...one can only assume it was out on the floor for sale in the shop. And the person who brought this suitcase was...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele has a Mr. Ifly stuffed animal that she likes to carry around. If she is that much of a fan, it's only natural that it was she who bought this suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">She does like that doll a lot. So much so that I've had to speak with her about it... ...but she has also laughed at me on many occasions that my suitcase's design is strange.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Come to think of it, Ms. Meele did say something to that effect in the shop...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you're done chatting, ladies, let's return to the topic at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ladies!? Well, I never! Alright, I'll rethink things, but there really is only one point I have to focus on.</thought> The suitcase was on sale at the in-flight shop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the person who bought the suitcase!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Sorry, but I don't understand your line of logic at all. Care to explain why you chose to finger that person?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. If that's how you're going to play this, then I'll admit that I was wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Instead of basking in your "great" admission, perhaps you should spend time thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnnn......! Alright, I'll rethink things, but there really is only one point I have to focus on.</thought> The suitcase was on sale at the in-flight shop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was you, wasn't it, Ms. Teneiro? I hate to say this, but this suitcase that you designed... ...it hasn't sold very well, has it?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw how poorly this design that you poured your heart into was selling... ...and were deeply hurt. That's why you wanted to make it look like it was selling by buying it yourself. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then... the reason you went to the shop and came back here was...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I-I'm sorry! A-All I really have is my job... I... I was overjoyed when my design was chosen... I thought that maybe... maybe I had finally accomplished something...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the suitcases didn't sell.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">It's because of the design, isn't it? All because it's as you put it, "hideous".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't say they chose a great place in which to sell them, either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">We weren't selling a single one, and they were just sitting there collecting dust. I felt so bad seeing them there, day in and day out. So I decided to buy one for every flight I worked.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You buy one every single time you work a flight!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see. So in order to keep your resolution, you went and bought one today as well.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes. And here is my receipt for that purchase.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... This receipt is clearly time stamped 5:40 AM.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The truth is, there's still a bunch of them left unsold. They're planning to scrap the remaining ones at the end of this flight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just as Ms. Teneiro said, the timestamp says she bought the suitcase at 5:40 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro, where are these other suitcases?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">They should all be down in the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then the suitcase the killer used...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Could very well have come from the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Um, Mr. Edgeworth... You don't think that the killer used one of my suitcases to...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I do. The killer used one of your beloved suitcases... ...to move the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaaah! How could they!? Those suitcases were meant to be faithful partners to our passengers on their trips. That's all I ever wished for them to be!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro, is there any other way to get to the cargo hold other than the elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The only other way is just through that door there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what about security?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">That door has no special lock installed, because... ...just to enter this room... ...you need a special keycard that only crew members have access to.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means that the culprit is someone who can enter this room... ...eliminating the passengers, and leaving only crew members as potential suspects.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I-I can't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Going on these wild goose-chases... You're a disgrace to the Von Karma name!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The suitcase came from the cargo hold. That fact alone tells the whole story.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, which is why I said the culprit must be a crew member who used their keycard...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! You're proposing that the killer rode the elevator from the cargo hold, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that's the only realistic possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The other attendant... Ms. Meele... I asked her earlier, and she had this to say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Franziska got information out of Ms. Meele?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In order to make the elevator go down to the cargo hold... ...a different keycard is required.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A different one?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, and the only person who holds that particular card... ...is you, Ms. Rhoda Teneiro, and only you!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? Is this true, Ms. Teneiro!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Y-Yes... I keep that keycard in my locker at all times.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please show us that card right now?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Y-Yes, hold on...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Aaaaah! I... I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">The keycard... It's... It's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ha ha ha. Very clever. Pretending that your card was stolen, when in fact, you're just trying to hide it from us... You've really thought this through.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">W-Wait! I-It's not like that!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You can tell us all about what it's like down at the station. Officer! Arrest this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">M-Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What's wrong? There's disbelief written all over your face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I know that you are the lead investigator on this case, however...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> Don't even think about wasting any more of my time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You know the rules as well as I do. Evidence speaks louder than words. Even if this isn't a courtroom, that basic tenet still applies.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I intend to investigate the cargo hold now. What will you do, Miles Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I intend to do likewise.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a contradiction between this piece of evidence and your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't want to go against the word of a professional prosecutor, but... ...I don't think there's a problem at all. I swear it as a professional flight attendant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrrrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a good look at this, for it will prove my innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............W-Well!? Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah! I'm sorry! Yes, well, I gave it a good look, but... ...no matter what angle I look at it from, I don't see how it will prove you didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrrgh...! <thought>I must've presented the wrong item...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro... What do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">What do I think about it...? ...Oh! I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">? Why are you apologizing?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I was being unprofessional. As a pro, I should've listened to your question with a smile. And I must also answer all questions with a smile.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... Just say what you mean, that you have no answer to my question!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your testimony just now and this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Ah! I cannot believe how much time I have spent here! Yo will pay for this time with your piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? No, stop! This is an invaluable piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">If you do not know how to use it, then give it to me! I will try to use it for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngnnrgh... I know how to use it just fine, thank you! I... I simply made a tiny error.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, could you please take a look at this piece for me?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmm... In American dollars... I say it is worth around... $9.99.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What are YOU talking about? Were you not intending to sell it to me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It's not for sale! <thought>I think I need to present something a bit more case-making to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, your testimony just now contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Ah, yes, from the old word "contradictus"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? Oh, you are correct. But what does that have to do with our present situation?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">The word comprised of the parts "against" and "speak". I dare say I don't deal in such double talk. My are dealings are clean!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's all well and good, however, about this piece of evide...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">There is no value in that! I am not interested in buying that from you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrrrgh! <thought>There's plenty of value in it, even just superficially!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence perfectly exposes the flaw in your logic!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? Well then, why don't you show me how it does just that? Go on!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I bet it's this part, right? This conflicts with something, right, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You have no idea what you're talking about, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Don't speak up when you don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch... I was just trying to follow your head, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That you would allow a subordinate to take over... You're a disgrace!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnnnnnrrrrk! <thought>I guess that wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. It would seem that your logic is not as perfect as you think it is.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence should show you exactly what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Oh, yes. It clearly shows what you're thinking. That you're attempting to buy yourself time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh! <thought>I knew I shouldn't have tried to pull a fast one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I believe your testimony just now conflicts with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And I believe that when you use the phrase "I believe", you are anything but certain. Which means that showing me that piece of evidence is just a way to waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaaaaaah! <thought>She even managed to whip the evidence at the some time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owwww!! Why did you whip me, too, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's one more victim besides myself and the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth, I think it's about time you just admitted your guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no reason to admit to a crime I did not commit, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Ah, but the well-traveled attendant inside of me knows that you're guilty. Guilty of ruining the other passengers' fun! That is a most serious crime, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A s-serious crime!? Surely not...!?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">We've already contacted the authorities, and they will pick you up upon our arrival. And as for the rest of the passengers, I ask that you please remain seated.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was... handed over to the police, just as Ms. Teneiro said... Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You continue to say you can prove you are not the criminal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc... If you could spare me a little more time...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I think I have been plentiful with my patience! Any more spent time would be wasteful! You have had your chances! Even the angels have but two cheeks to strike upon!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I'm very sorry, but I'm afraid it's my duty to report to the captain, Mr. Edgeworth... ...that you don't seem to be making very much progress in your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk! <thought>Time's up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Good! And I want to see you are handed to the police right away after the landing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was... handed over to the police, just as Mr. Lablanc wished... Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaawn* Look, Mr. Edgeworth... You're not really finding out much... ...so I'm going to go ask the captain for his permission to stop your investigation, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">J-Just a little more time, I beg you.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Un huh... Don't make me upset and be a good Mr. Edgeworth, OK? Come along now and let's get you back in your seat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-There is no need to push!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth. Stop squirming and start acting like an honorable man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nmph... But there are still so many things I have yet to prove!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You should know better than that, especially as a disciple of Manfred von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph! So a "low-life criminal" like me is not worth hearing out, is that it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But! But Mr. Edgeworth isn't the killer...OWWWWWWWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I will not allow you to cover for such low-life scum, Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was arrested by the police on the spot... Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's enough, Miles Edgeworth. I think we've heard plenty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How so...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Rhoda Teneiro! I'm finding quite a few points in your story a bit hard to swallow. Why not come back to the precinct with me and let's talk it over again nice and slow.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I...! No! Help me, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk... Ms. Teneiro...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro was taken into custody under the pretense of a "valuable witness". Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>