<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was a close one, huh, Mia?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? Too bad, I'm sorry I missed it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">? M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think I've got a pretty good idea who did it. Now all I need is a motive... and proof.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Good going, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Under the "initial trial" system, tomorrow is the last day we have.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Initial trial"...? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the new court system they introduced two or three years ago. They had so many cases in the system, they decided to speed the whole process up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, under that system, trials have to end in three days?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, pretty much. Well, we've no time to waste!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't get it, Maya. Why would Mr. Hammer steal the Steel Samurai costume?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? You mean Mr. Hammer was wearing the costume!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but Mr. Hammer was the victim, Nick! Why would he go through the trouble of stealing it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what we have to find out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What happened with the director's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's pretty clear that the producer and the director were both in the trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means that the killer has to be one of them!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because the real scene of the crime was Studio Two... where that trailer is!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... was Maya always this excitable?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, have you noticed anything that might help us?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't see what's going on when Mia is here... So, no. I haven't noticed anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we should go talk to WP?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>WP... Powers... right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who would have thought that it was Jack Hammer inside! But why did he steal it? That's what I have to figure out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish I had my own Samurai Spear! Just think, I could poke you as much as I wanted!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me!? Why me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this? It's that fanboy's prized possession.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Impressive! ... It's a little different from the Steel Samurai on TV...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are mostly taken at those PR shows they do at stores and fairs... I'm pretty sure it's not even Will Powers inside that suit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No true fan would be satisfied with anything less than the real thing! He's still a child, I suppose... I guess it takes an adult to appreciate the real deal. Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yeah, whatever you say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Cody's--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! A digital camera! I'm impressed a kid like him would have something this expensive. Kids these days!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't imagine spirit mediums-in-training get a lot of toys...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">Mr. Wright! You did very well again today... thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... thanks. Um, could you not look like you're about to burst into tears...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, Nick! You must have really wowed 'em in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could stop looking so... vulnerable, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, WP! Only one day left! Let's make it count!</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes... Though there's not really anything I can do to help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hah hah hah! I'm not really sure what I can do, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please... this is no laughing matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's that picture again.</line>
<line speaker="Will">I-is that really Jack Hammer inside that suit?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's the only one who it could have been.</line>
<line speaker="Will">But why would he...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're the medium! Why don't you summon up Mr. Hammer's spirit and ask him yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sigh* Gimme about three more years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Look at us, the two novices.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you seen this, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Will">W-what's that!? I've never seen these Steel Samurais in my life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the Steel Samurais that appear at live shows. A fanboy collected all these pictures himself.</line>
<line speaker="Will">... Seeing things like this really makes me think... I mean so much to these kids, you know? *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Will">E-excuse me. Thank you for showing me that, whatever it is. I wish I could think of some way for me to help you... S-sorry. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The old windbag sure is quiet today.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, this place is really... peaceful, like this.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick? I think her guard's down...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet we could even eat those donuts in the guard station... if we wanted.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... You eat, you die.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whew! She's alive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I was wondering about Dee Vasquez, the producer.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, the studio bigwigs LOVE her. So she always gets her way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems bitter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you... not like the producer?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Look, the studio people don't want me talking about her, so, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you about Sal Manella, the director?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Sal? He's soft--a pushover. Does whatever Vasquez tells him to. She treats him like dirt, but I think he likes it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Why would anyone like being treated like dirt? That doesn't make any sense, does it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... No, no it doesn't, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Mr. Hammer...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Arrgh! I heard about what you said today! Cheeky whippersnapper! Poor old Hammer! You'd drag his star down from the sky and stomp on it! Calling him a criminal! A thief! I-I-I-I... I won't forget this!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, she's really pissed this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You listen to me, whippersnapper! My poor old Hammer would never do such a thing! Why would he steal Powers's costume so he could sneak by me? He would never stoop so low! It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? Get that filth out of my sight! And you're claiming that's poor old Hammer in there!? And I thought you were such an innocent youth... Bah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Ms. Oldbag? What do you think of this?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Think? I'm not in the mood for thinking, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Think back, Nick, to the day of the murder... Mr. Hammer put on the Steel Samurai costume. Then he left from here to go to Studio Two...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But why? I wonder if someone called him...? Like the director, or the producer...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Studio Two is down that way. Studio Two... the real scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick, how did you figure that out again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... ... Actually, it's a long story, I'll tell you another time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The mascot of Global Studios. Apparently its name is "Mr. Monkey."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This security camera takes photos of everyone who comes through the gate. It doesn't seem to be switched on today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The entrance to Studio One. This is the studio where they found Jack Hammer's body. I don't have that cardkey anymore, so I can't go in there today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It says "Welcome."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They let people in here when they're not filming, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Let's come here some day! Whaddya say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, if Ms. Oldbag lets us in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick... It's Ms. Vasquez! Hello?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-E-L-L-O!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H!E!L!L!O!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! You should at least try to be polite...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... I'm watching the clouds. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's all she had to say, apparently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where Sal Manella and Dee Vasquez ate. There's nothing left on the plates.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, so they ate t-bone steaks too. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know... I'm getting this funny feeling. Something about this just feels... odd, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can't say that I do...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a big "2" painted here. So this is the number in Cody's photograph. And to think, if he hadn't brought that photograph in...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't get all teary eyed yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There're some flowers here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, so pretty! They're taking good care of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't get too close. That fence looks dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trailer door. It's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, excuse me? Mr. Hammer came here on the day of the murder, and...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Shh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Perhaps you didn't hear me. I'm watching the clouds. I'm not interested in talking to you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do something, Nick! She's really ticking me off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Mr. Powers wasn't the killer! You don't have to cancel the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I think I'm tired of the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You... you did it! Nick! She did it! She's the killer! My Fey blood speaks to me! I know it! I know it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I was wondering if you could tell me about Mr. Manella?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... If you must talk about that man... Perhaps you could talk about it in the trailer? By yourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, oh dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not even looking.</thought> Okay. Hey, you look.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-why are you showing that to me, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Wasn't the assistant cleaning up yesterday? Funny, it still seems pretty messy in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess she was still on a high from getting that rare card she needed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster. "'The Singing Samurai' starring Jack Hammer." What the hell do samurai sing about? Chopping off heads?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. My. God. That movie was the best! It's about a samurai who sings his way to fame and fortune! Mr. Hammer was a very accomplished singer, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Singing samurai stars... What's next? Ninja ballet?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess they're not filming today, either. I did want to see them filming... just one time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This trial will be over and done by tomorrow. You can come see them film later.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess... This is where you found that bottle of sleeping pills, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh huh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if there're any other clues lying around.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaarh! No no no! No touchin'!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, sorry, pal. Didn't mean to frighten you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">D-didn't mean...? I almost had a heart attack!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Heh heh. I guess I can be a little dramatique at times... I suppose it's the actor in me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Dramatique" indeed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ahem. Anyway, I'm here to examine the plate on that table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, are you looking for sleeping pills?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal. Traces thereof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That grate's still lying here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, they've seen wisdom at last! They know if they fixed it I'd just kick it off again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That poor assistant...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The remains of the employees' lunch are scattered around. Everyone was probably too shocked to clean up. There's a t-bone on one of the plates, minus the steak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door to the dressing room. It's not locked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... cola, candy, chips, gum... Huh. It's so... normal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you're looking for traces of the sleeping pills... how?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">For a thorough examination I gotta take the plate back to the precinct. But I have the capabilities to make a cursory examination right here! Our science guy gave me some testing solution. This reacts to sleeping pills, see? If there're traces it'll change color.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Neat! Well, Detective Gumshoe? What are you waiting for?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now, now, everything in due time, pal. ... ... ... Well, the testing solution on the plate changed color alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So there were sleeping pills on the plate!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How goes your investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">To tell the truth, it's a real mess, pal. Some people think we should pursue the case we already have against Powers... And some people think we should switch suspects!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal, I hate to admit it... But I'm not sure I buy the case against Mr. Powers any more. I feel kind of bad for Mr. Edgeworth, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How is Edgeworth doing, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Edgeworth is out of control! He was in the waiting room and he crushed this paper cup with hot, hot coffee in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Talk about burns, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! The fury of Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, crushing paper cups... <thought>Cups... bottles...?</thought> Say, what ever happened with that empty bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, the bottle of sleeping pills? Well, I got some good news for you about that. They found the victim, Jack Hammer's prints on the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that means...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep, it sounds like the one who put Powers to sleep was none other than... the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I was right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's looking like Will Powers was drugged... I'm going to go back to the precinct to do some more detailed tests.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're being very... free with your information today, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... don't go telling anyone this, pal. But I was kind of impressed at today's trial, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Most lawyers would've given up after that director's testimony. I think if it'd been anyone but you up there, Powers would be done for by now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective, about that bottle...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that? Talk about embarrassing, pal! I can't believe I missed that on my first sweep for evidence. Don't know how I can apologize to Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It must be tough being a detective, with all that responsibility...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, heh heh. *blush*</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm guessing I know as much about that as you do, pal, i.e. nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Empty dressing rooms like this are kinda lonely, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure Mr. Powers will be back soon. He'll be fine...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's an array of cosmetics here. This is the wig used in "Samurai Boogey-Woogey."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! You remembered, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks to you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are some regular suits in among the costumes here. Those must be his own clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like someone was sleeping here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we can be pretty sure WP did take a nap here, like he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure being drugged counts as taking a "nap"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They always have mirrors like this in dressing rooms. I always check my hairdo when I look in a mirror. Hmm... not quite as spiky as usual, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers's bag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I hope WP can come pick it up himself, soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Soon, soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a box for snacks on the table. They must give these to the employees. Hmm. It's completely empty. ... I can feel Maya's eyes burning into the back of my neck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me more about Ms. Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh... the producer? She's well respected in the industry. They say she's a genius.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A genius...?</line>
<line speaker="Will">She's been at Global Studios for five years now. Right or wrong, nobody dares tell her different these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Ever since she came on board, we've had nothing but hits. Global Studios was on its knees, but she picked it up and made it shine. Oh, and...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... what?</line>
<line speaker="Will">N-nothing. Forget it. I... I've only heard rumors, anyhow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me anything about Mr. Manella?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh, he used to be a minor straight-to-video director. But something in his work caught Vasquez's eye. She brought the Steel Samurai idea to him. Now everyone knows the name Sal Manella. I hear he's pretty much at her beck and call, though. Whenever she says "jump!" he asks "how high?" and all that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can imagine him being at her beck and call... though I can't imagine him jumping.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was wondering about Mr. Hammer... He was a big star back in the day, right? But then he just dropped off the face of the Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh... Yes, you're right. In fact, he was my role model when I started in this business. But he just stopped taking on big roles. That's when he began appearing in little productions at Global...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How could he do that!? I was really looking forward to a sequel to "Samurai Summer."</line>
<line speaker="Will">He just gave up being a star five years ago. Actually, now that I think about it... That was right when Ms. Vasquez came to Global.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Five years ago...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh! Hello!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh... I was just cleaning up the dressing room. I guess WP won't be using it anymore, so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wha!? What!? Why!? But WP's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, and I'm really grateful for all you've done. But... This week is the last episode of the Steel Samurai...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Nooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like someone was sleeping here.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, sorry. I haven't cleaned up there yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Powers's bag.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I put all of WP's personal belongings in there. He'll be able to come pick them up, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure he'll come, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering if I could ask you about Mr. Hammer...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the murder, he went to Studio Two.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Huh? I thought he went to Studio One?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He stole the Steel Samurai costume, too!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">What!? Why would Mr. Hammer do something like that? ... Oh... I guess the rumor must be true, then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The rumor?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yeah. Mr. Vasquez, that producer, had some kind of hold on Hammer. She had some dirt on him... He'd do anything she said, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Some "dirt"? What dirt!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... Dirt. You know, bad stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Um, I know what dirt means...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">About five years ago, they were filming a movie starring Mr. Hammer. They were using the new studio... Studio Two. Some sort of accident happened during filming. After that, they never used Studio Two again. They left the film set the way it was, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The film set...? Was that trailer part of the film set, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what do you mean, the "last Steel Samurai"!?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I know it's a shock, but nothing can be done to save it now. Whoever really did kill Mr. Hammer, also signed the Steel Samurai's death warrant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No... no!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Also, I hear that Global Studios is going to change its programming. They're not going to make kids' shows anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what!? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I don't know. It's sad, but that's what Global Studios decided.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why aren't they going to make kids' shows anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">The studio bigwigs don't want the Steel Samurai around anymore. They want to forget all this ever happened. They want it quiet, you understand?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-how can they just do that! What about all the kids who love the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">It's okay. I'm sure the kids will be fine. They'll find a new hero to follow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, that can't be true! If the program just ends, they'll be heartbroken for sure! N-Nick! Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... yeah. <thought>I think evidence, rather than words, is called for here.</thought> Here, take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Penny">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is why you can't stop the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I'm sorry... I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Neither do I, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-funny that. I don't either! <thought>Oops. Let's try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">And this is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fan collected all of these photographs. The kids love the Steel Samurai! The show shouldn't be cancelled just so some adults can save face! I would think you would understand that better than anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... ... You're right... Okay! But what can I do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, for starters... You can tell me something. Tell me what it is that Global Studios is so intent on hiding? Tell me about this accident five years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An accident five years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, in Studio Two. That trailer there was part of the film set.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... S-sorry. I don't think I can. They really don't want us to talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell us what happened five years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Well, I can tell you what I've heard. Apparently, five years ago, someone died... and it was Hammer's fault.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-someone died!?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">It was an accident, of course! Anyway... The producer, Ms. Vasquez managed to hush it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's the "dirt" she had on Mr. Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And that's why Mr. Hammer would do anything Ms. Vasquez asked him to do! ... But, it was an accident, right? Why didn't they just make it public?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Well, you know Mr. Hammer was a big star back then. They were afraid about what would happen to his career if word got out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">You know who knows more about this? Ms. Oldbag. She was here at the studios back then, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. We'll try asking her. <thought>If she'll talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">So this photo was Mr. Hammer all along?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems that way.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Why would Mr. Hammer do something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Wow... wow! It must have taken him forever to collect all these.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Kids love the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">They do, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An empty bottle of sleeping pills. With Mr. Hammer's fingerprints on it...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... Now I'm really confused!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I'm sorry... I'm not sure what to make of that.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What, you're still slinking around? If you like the place so much, why don't you take over for me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The old windbag doesn't look so good...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">E-everybody's doing their darnedest to forget Hammer. Who do they think made Global Studios what it is today? Hammer! It's all due to Hammer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's starting to froth at the mouth, Nick... Maybe we should keep a safe distance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I wanted to ask you about five years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">! Who told!? Who did you hear that from!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Nichols!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-nickels?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nichols, Nick. Penny Nichols. That assistant we talked to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-oh, right. Anyway, we heard about the accident. It was during filming with Jack Hammer... He killed a man. Didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wh-whippersnappers! Dredging up dirt on someone's past like that... and the recently departed, no less! I suppose you think this is fun!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, I'm just doing my job to protect Mr. Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And you claim that Hammer stole Powers's costume! You expect me to believe that rubbish!? Or do you have some kind of proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Proof that Hammer stole Powers's costume? Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Proof? Well... no.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! See!? I see how you work! Anything that doesn't fit, you just blame on the dead! Well... well... Just butt out, lawyer-boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She knows something! But how am I going to get her to talk...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry Ms. Oldbag, but I do have proof. I can prove that Mr. Hammer stole Mr. Powers's costume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers ate a t-bone steak for lunch, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-well... yes. So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the plate that he used to eat that steak. There are traces of sleeping pill powder on the plate!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Mmmph? Hah! I-I bet Powers put it in there himself! Even a lightweight like him must have trouble sleeping sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Except, I have proof that Mr. Hammer put the pills in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! What's that supposed to prove!? That means nothing to me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... I'm kinda having trouble figuring that one out too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... wrong evidence? But I know Oldbag knows something! I have to get her to talk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This bottle contained sleeping pills. Mr. Hammer's fingerprints were found on the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's my proof.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? What's a little empty bottle supposed to prove?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a bottle of sleeping pills. With Mr. Hammer's fingerprints on it...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wh-what does that prove? I... I'm sure old Hammer had some sleepless nights! Where's your proof that he used those pills on Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! What's that supposed to prove!? That means nothing to me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... I'm kinda having trouble figuring that one out too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... wrong evidence? But I know Oldbag knows something! I have to get her to talk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers ate a t-bone steak for lunch, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-well... yes. So?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the plate that he used to eat that steak. There are traces of sleeping pill powder on the plate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! What's that supposed to prove!? That means nothing to me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... I'm kinda having trouble figuring that one out too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... wrong evidence? But I know Oldbag knows something! I have to get her to talk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...! ... ... I see. Poor, poor Hammer. You did wrong, Hammer, rest your soul.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms. Oldbag...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Okay. You win. I'll talk. I'm tired, see... Tired of holding it all in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You're right. Five years ago there was an accident... a fatal accident. What's worse, a paparazzi took a photo of it. That photo, well, it caused quite a stir. And guess who made it all better? Vasquez! She has ties to the mafia... She silenced that paparazzi. That was the beginning. After that, she became a force to be reckoned with here at the studio.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But, you have to understand... Poor old Hammer never meant any harm to anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ms. Oldbag...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Poor old Hammer. He was a big star. The biggest. That accident five years ago is what did him in. He wanted to hide it. He didn't want anyone to know. Poor, silly old Hammer. If he had just come out and confessed... Then Vasquez wouldn't have gotten her claws into him!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Sorry... I don't want to think about it anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hold on a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Ms. Oldbag...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Here, take this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? A photograph? W-wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">This is the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is... this the trailer in Studio Two?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hammer was supposed to fight with a bad guy on the top of those stairs, there. He pushed the other actor, and the man fell onto the flowerbox fence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but how did you get this?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It... was a long time ago. I don't feel much like talking about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe must have left by now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's probably thinking about what to do in tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet Edgeworth is pretty angry with him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The assistant must have gone off somewhere. That stuff about Mr. Hammer must have come as a shock to her.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not even looking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Where.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Where did you get that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, well...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Oldbag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Old...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She means the security lady, Ms. Oldbag, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... anyway... Ms. Vasquez. You hid this incident from the press, didn't you? And you used it to control Mr. Hammer!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... The wind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">It's gotten stronger, don't you think? The wind. ... Your conversation interests me. Let's talk about it more inside the trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick. She went inside the trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph. You came. Well then, what was that you were talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...! Why is she so eager to talk all of a sudden?</thought> Ms. Vasquez. You were using that accident! You were blackmailing Mr. Hammer so you could control him, weren't you? That's why he was doing kids' shows for petty change!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph... So I'm a blackmailer now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that's what it was, wasn't it! I mean, sure, it was an accident... But you used it to drag Mr. Hammer down from his rightful place as a star!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Oh...? I haven't pulled anyone down from anywhere. Mr. Hammer's career went sour of its own accord.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but! You were the cause! You pressured him... And to think it was just an accident...!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Excuse me! What is this all about? You keep saying "accident," "accident"... How are you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Must I spell everything out for you? Think: what would it be if it wasn't an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! No... No way! You mean Mr. Hammer did it... on purpose?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">That is what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-where's your proof! Can you prove it!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph! Just think! Would he have let me run his life for five years... over a mere accident? And I ran him hard, believe you me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but, the security lady said it was an accident!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Oh. Well, she was a big fan of Hammer's, you see. She jumped on the reporter who brought that photo into the studio. She wrenched it out of his hands, she did. Gave him a few bruises, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... So that's why she had the photo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">She's an old fool. Of course, all the reporter would need is the negatives. He could have made a copy. But he didn't. The only copy of that photo is the one you hold. Give it to me. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what? This is valuable evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Boys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... U-umm... Who are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Professionals. They're good at erasing... various things. What do you think...? Would you like to be erased?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The trial ends tomorrow? How unfortunate. It's a shame you'll have to miss it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Tell me why. Why do you want this photograph so badly? This is Mr. Hammer's "dirt"... no? Why should Dee Vasquez care about it at all?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... I'm sure you'll have plenty of time to think about that where you're going. So long, friends. Boys, erase away.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hold it right there! I heard everything, pal! Dee Vasquez! You're coming down to the precinct with me, now!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Hmph. Not bad. ... Very well. It appears this contest will be decided tomorrow then. In court. I'll be looking forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-hey, you okay, pal? Sorry I was a little late with my entrance. I don't get many chances to practice that sorta thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe... Thank you thank you thank you! I was really scared...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Don't mention it, pal. Just doing my job. ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, it's just... I've wanted to say that line ever since I became a detective. ... Okay. I've got one more job to do today. I'm sure we'll run into each other again soon!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick. It looks like we're getting close to the bottom of this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And who's at the bottom...? Dee Vasquez!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>