<xml>
<title>Turnabout Succession</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, Phoenix Wright, will be your guide through this game. That terrible trial saw me present forged evidence. ...It ended, half-finished, when the defendant vanished. What became of me after that...? As your investigation proceeds the answer will become clear. ...Oh, and one more thing. There is something I must tell you. As Apollo Justice has his bracelet... ...so, too, do I have my own "weapon" of sorts. ...My Magatama. What does it do, you ask? That I would have you see for yourself. ...Well now. Shall we begin? Touch the arrow to switch between past and present. But let's begin seven years ago... in the past. It is right after my last trial came to an abrupt end. ...Now that you know the game, let's play.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>7 years ago</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Morning, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ah, I'm so glad you came.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You OK, Daddy? They picking on you?</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. I am fine, as always. This old boy is here to help me, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's "young man" to you.</thought> Good morning. That's a cute outfit you have on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks! My first show's today, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Two weeks had passed since then. I called her into my office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy, there's something we need to talk about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been two weeks since your father... disappeared. We need to start thinking about... your future.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, um, did some calling around. This is hard to say, but... ...you have no living</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... ...I was wondering if you wanted to stay with me for a while. Just until your daddy comes home. It won't be long. <thought>...I hope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, of course, it's totally your choice. If you don't like it here, you can go wherever you'd like. I could look up some places you might like to stay at... <thought>This is so weird...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Mr. Attorney. Daddy told me about you. He said I could trust you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, if I stay here... ...does that mean you'll be my family?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Uh... Um... I guess so? <thought>Getting weirder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... Mr. Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er, actually, why don't you call me... Nick. ...Or you can call me "Daddy" if you'd like. It doesn't have to be today, or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK! Say, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was quick.</thought> ...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If I move here, I have to switch schools, right? And I was thinking, I haven't paid for lunches at my last school... for a year. So thanks, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, and this office? It's a little blah. A little color goes a long way, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, and Daddy? You got fired from work, right? Don't you worry one bit! I'll work twice as hard! We'll make it through this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy... how old are you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I'm eight. But don't let appearances deceive you! I'm a young professional! Stick with me and you'll do just fine, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, thanks. <thought>Why does it feel like she's already in charge...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite the collection of law books. My mentor bought all of them. I used to be too busy to read them. Now that I have the time to read them, there's no need. ...But I can't just sell them. Maybe Trucy will want to read them someday?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Nah.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My mentor's favorite plant, Charley. I guess watering Charley's my only real job now. ...... Wait! I have a child now! I can't feed Trucy like this! She probably needs more than the occasional watering, too, I'm guessing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster hangs on the wall. I finally found out the title after not knowing for the longest time. I actually rented the movie the other day. Cried my eyes out. ...... Ack! Just thinking about it makes me tear up... Wait, it's just allergies... Really! ...I should show it to her when she's a little older. ...... <thought>Wait... what was it called again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Not that I have any reason to sit there anymore. I guess Trucy can use it. It's great for studying math, English, geography, magic... ...Ack! I'm not crying. I just got some dust in my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can still see that hotel from the window here. Every time I look out, I think back on those old cases... ...I wonder if the view looks different now that I'm not wearing my old badge...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I really dig the far out view, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Thanks. <thought>She must have learned a lot of words from her parents.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Daddy, you got fired from being a lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could at least kind of look aside or something when you say that. It's... actually kind of hard for me... For Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I'm sorry, Daddy! Wait! Is that "foolish pride"? My other daddy always used to talk about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Actually, that's pretty accurate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, here's my idea. We'll make a new office! "Law" just seems so stiff, doesn't it? And no one will be my friend at school that way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well that won't do, I guess. I just don't know much about anything other than law. <thought>Or even much about law, if you were to ask some people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe the problem is calling it an "office". We should run an "agency" instead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean... like a talent agency? Forgive me for asking, but doesn't that require "talent"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You've got me, don'tcha? I'm a professional!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A professional...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yup! After all, I am directly descended from the famous Zak Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Directly descended... He's your father.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh...! And now I'm directly descended from the famous Phoenix Wright, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think an eight-year-old just massaged my ego.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me a bit more about your daddy... er, Zak Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy? Sure thing, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which Daddy was that again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy's so amazing! The biggest star of Troupe Gramarye! And they're big!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Gramaryes... They were on television a lot. <thought>Haven't seen them on much recently, come to think of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Big magic happens when you put Zak and Valant Gramarye together, you know. Once they made a giant waterfall, right there on the stage! And this giant trout swam up the giant waterfall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me guess, there was a giant fisherman waiting for him at the top?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wish I could have seen more of Daddy's magic...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! I shouldn't have brought it up so soon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what'll happen to me, with Daddy and Mommy both gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mommy...? <thought>Yeah, what about Mommy? I haven't heard anything about Trucy's mother!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But I have my magic! And a great daddy, even if he is unemployed! You know, I think thing's [sic] are going to be OK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if she'll talk about her mother...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Trucy... You're... a "professional"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes! Um... It's like that thing they say! "Baby frogs grow up to be frogs"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They say that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I always thought it was funny, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aren't baby frogs called "tadpoles"...? Maybe they thought it would be easier to understand that way for kids. How stupid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right. So, in conclusion... ...you're a professional magician, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Well? Well? Wanna see a trick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're... going to do a magic trick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, but maybe next time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aw, that's no fun. You only live once, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The tricks can wait. We've got more important things to discuss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't think of anything more important than magic, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Was that... mind reading?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Silly, it was written all over your face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that wasn't a magic trick, I wonder what the real ones are like!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I would like to see your trick. The future of the "agency" depends on it, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the spirit! ...Ready? Here goes! Ta dah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Hey folks, it's Mr. Hat! I gotta say it's good to be seen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeeeeeeeeargh! Whoa... that was... startling.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Amazing Mr. Hat! Isn't he great?</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Your friendly neighborhood Mr. Hat, at your service!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He... certainly makes an impression.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Doesn't he? Ha ha ha! I'm so glad you like him, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Though my routines do get a bit "heady" at times! Hah! Get it? Heady!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...My friendly neighborhood Mr. Hat nearly gave me a heart attack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about your mommy... if it's OK?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mommy was so pretty... She was like an angel up on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On stage... You mean, with your daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yep! She was always there with Zak &amp; Valant, smiling! But then... she went away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Went away?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was a grand illusion... but she made a mistake. She vanished... and I guess she didn't know how to get back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Maybe so.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I cried then, a lot. That's when Daddy gave me this. ...Here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... is your mother? <thought>She's beautiful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Her name's Thalassa. Thalassa Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor girl. I didn't know her mommy had gone missing. And now her daddy's vanished, too, right before her eyes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Daddy? You won't...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. I won't vanish, I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! You can't even do magic! You're like a backup plan! Daddy always said to have a backup plan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I guess all I rate as is a "backup plan".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy, about this locket...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that's Mommy! Isn't Mommy pretty? Wait... you don't want to know more about Mommy, do you, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeek! I better keep an eye on you, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Oh, that's not how I meant it, honest. <thought>She is beautiful, though. And something more... Poise, that's it. She's got poise.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Trucy, see this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm still just training to be a magician. I can't make things disappear yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait one more year! I'll be able to make it disappear then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll be sure to be careful when showing evidence to magicians in the future...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So this is Trucy's mother, Thalassa. She's pretty. I can picture her on stage with Zak. Still, she looks like a down-to-earth type, too. I guess Trucy takes after her.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's OK! After all, we're family! I just hope you're ready! The Wright Talent Agency opens tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? B-But are we... representing anyone?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Me and you... That makes two, Daddy...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you need more than that to make an agency. Besides... ...you may be a magician... but I'm no talent!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I'm sure there's something you're good at!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, when you put it that way...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean you don't have any tricks? No old standbys? This will not do! A boy should always have a trick or two in his pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, OK! I'll think of something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the spirit! See you bright and early tomorrow, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Welcome to the team, Daddy-O!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The team... right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sometimes when magicians vanish, they leave something behind... That's how Trucy became Trucy Wright... my daughter. To be honest, I was pretty lost those first few days. Thinking back on it, it was a pretty dark time in my life. But Trucy... happy, smiling Trucy... she was my light.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Didn't think I'd be back here for a while. I didn't want to have to remember that day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Though I deeply regret having to declare a verdict in this way... This trial is over.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Mr. Zak?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">There is one thing I wish to make clear. Today, in this courtroom... ...you cannot declare me "guilty".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I am talking... about this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Enigmar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defendant's escaped! Find him! Quick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Close all exits from the building! On the double! He must not be allowed to escape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When I came here on that fateful morning, I still had my badge. But now... Like an amputated limb... I can still feel it itching. Where do I start? I don't even have the authority to investigate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you there. Sir! Down on the hands! Floor on your head! Now now now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh-What's the big idea!? My ears...!</line>
<line speaker="???">No unauthorized personnel aren't allowed in here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... But that would mean all unauthorized personnel are allowed.</line>
<line speaker="???">Zoooooooooooooooooooink!? ...I just say it like it is sir! And it's usually wrong. Thrown out of the precinct... lost my friends, my girl and even my wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... We've... met before, haven't we? On a case... two years ago?</line>
<line speaker="???">No recollection of that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">For me, "working on a case" is always in the present progressive tense, sir! There is no past! There is only now! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK, OK! You're... the bailiff, right?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes sir! Court Bailiff Mike Meekins at your service, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I've asked to meet with the bailiff at this court who let the magician escape.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Let me try to make this as absolutely clear as possible for you, sir! It was meeeeeeeeeeeee! Sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... you were a regular police officer once... right?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... Sometimes bad things happen to good people, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me it's a long story. Let's not go there.</thought> So, you were in charge of security at the time of the "vanishing"...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'm. Dying. Over. Here! Oh! Ohh! It's a hard knock life, sir! Thrown out of the precinct... lost my friends, my girl and even my wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I wasn't the only "victim"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess this door was officially a prop in Zak Gramarye's last "show". He passed through that lobby door and vanished... but to where? He choreographed that entire fateful trial according to his grand scenario... ...... I hate magicians.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I actually took a nap on that couch once when I was still practicing law. ...Boy, was that a mistake. I never even sit on the lobby sofas now. I never let my clients sit on them, either. It's bad luck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I think this was the lobby I used for my very first case. This plant has seen me grow from a rookie, to an ace... to a has-been. I hate you, plant. ...Just kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I must have seen that painting a thousand times, but I never really looked at it until now. I guess my head was too stuck in the trials... ...I never had time to stop and appreciate art. I have time now. OK. Let's appreciate. ...... Actually, it's pretty lame.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The last time we met, you were a police officer, right? ...In fact, you're still wearing your uniform.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir I... I wish I didn't have to tell you this... ...but last year, tragedy struck a rising star at the precinct! I lost my case files four times... in three days! They fired me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That takes real talent, actually. They don't know what they're missing.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">So here I am, sir! Forced to start from square one, a lowly bailiff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, your uniform...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...I took it with me as a souvenir the day I was fired!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That can't be legal.</thought> So... you were the one who let the magician get away that day?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I'm. Dying. Over. Here! A star rises among the court bailiffs, full of hope! Then... tragedy strikes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anything you can tell me about it? ...About Zak Gramarye's "disappearance"?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Oh, the humanity!!!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's enough of that.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Why yes, I'd say it was around 2:00 PM when I heard a commotion in court. I opened the door to see what might be amiss. The door slams open! Slam! And some guy's face is right there in front of me! Face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you saw someone suspicious coming your way.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes! And I, being a bailiff of little standing... I gave chase! I chased that silk hat all the way down the hall, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a diagram of the court building here...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Ah ha! There's Courtroom No.7. That's where I was, sir! All by myself! Nary a friend to call my own!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK... And which way did Zak Gramarye run after bursting through the courtroom door?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">He went up, like this, and around the corner, like that! So I, with no delay... ...ran after him with no delay! When I turned the corner... ...I saw that magic man run into the defendant lobby! Swiftly, I ran! Following him, I threw myself boldly into the room! Why, I remember it like it was right here! Because it was! Lobby No. 2, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You ran into this room...? <thought>Hmm. I don't see any place to hide in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Believe it or not, sir, I didn't believe it! Here! In this room! The magician! Gone! Vanished like a puff of smoke! Except there wasn't even any smoke! He was just... gone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... That's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Yes, that! That word! Oh how many times have I said that word! Even the sound of it causes me indescribable pain! ...I'm dying... I'm dying over heeeeeeeeere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK, I won't say it again, promise! But, you have to admit, it's impo... er... difficult to vanish into thin air! Did you search the lobby?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... I searched.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Why the pause...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Th-Th-There was n-n-n-nothing here at all. Sir! That's right! Nothing was here! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How can he talk so loud and still be hiding something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Zak was in this room when he "vanished"...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Absolutely, sir! I saw him with my own eyes! Eyes! That red silk hat, that flowing cape... ...He ran right in here! Right inside this room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Silk hat, cape... That's Zak alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But, sir, look at the room! There's not a single place to hide! Sir, there was nothing I could do but... nothing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... What about now? Have any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I-I-I-Ideas about what, exactly, sir, if you don't mind me asking!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've had quite a bit of time since then. Has nothing occurred to you at all? Do you have any idea what trick he might have used to disappear like that?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Psyche-Locks! I should have known... My Magatama... one of my most prized possessions, which I got during a certain case... It can show me the locks on people's hearts. And if I can unlock their hearts... ...they'll tell me their secrets! The Magatama starts it all. And the Magatama ends it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any thoughts on this, Mr. Meekins?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">This... This is an honor!!! Sir! I've offered my opinions on plenty of things, even things I knew nothing about! But no one's ever asked for my opinion before!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow. There's no need to shout, really. ...So, no opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">None! I know nothing about that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I thought... oh, never mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...OK, Mr. Meekins. What do you know? Spit it out.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...He-He-Hey! Who-Who-Who... What's with the atmosphere in here all of a sudden!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know something, and I'm going to find out what. Zak Gramarye vanished from this room... How'd he do it?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">H-H-How, sir? Well, sir, I can't say as I... sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you so nervous if you aren't hiding something...?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Well, sir, I, you see, at the time, sir, I was here, and... Listen! It was impossible!!! What could such a little girl possibly do, anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...Nyurk! Sir! Did... I just say something, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you screamed it through that megaphone of yours. ...There was someone else in the room, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir! I'm going to have to invoke my right to remain in a state of not talking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's OK, Meekins. You don't have to tell me who Zak's accomplice was.</thought> I know who was here in this room that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... Sir, I don't know what to say, sir. Except maybe I didn't need to worry about not saying anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, it is my distinct pleasure to say, beyond any shadow of a doubt, sir. ...You're wrong! You're wrong! You're wrooooooooooong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I wish he'd invoke his right to remain silent now. Still, his little outburst back there should be enough to go on... "What could such a little girl possibly do", was it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, I, sir, I, sir, I, sir, I siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiurgle. I've never seen that girl until just the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Mr. Meekins. I'm not buying it.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... ...... ...... ...Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, that day. She was here, in the room, sir. But he wasn't!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean... you chased her into this room, not him?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir... In my days as a police officer -- literally days -- I learned a thing or two. OK, just one thing. But it was how not to mistake a girl for a 7-foot-tall magician!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seven feet? Zak isn't that tall, is he?</thought> You have a point... ...I find it hard to imagine that anyone would mistake a little girl for Zak Gramarye. But, you saw something... ...and therein lies the trick. I think you know what it was, Mr. Meekins! Tell me, does this trick look familiar!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...My my my.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your your your what?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I guess ex-attorneys have some tricks up their sleeves, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It hardly qualifies as a "trick".</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">You might be able to fool little girls with that... ...but you'll never fool little Meekins!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I think I put my foot into that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha-Tha- What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That girl's favorite trick, "The Amazing Mr. Hat". She uses it in her show down at the Wonder Bar.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you been to the Wonder Bar?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...... So. It wasn't a waking dream, was it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">That night, on stage, I saw a vision! Except... it wasn't a vision. It was a hat. An Amazing Mr. Hat! He really exists!!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I remember it clearly! Though the details are a little vague. Zak Gramarye exited the courtroom... ...I gave chase and cornered him in the corner room, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Zak Gramarye! Don't even think you can escape Meekins! Down on your hands! Floor on your head!!! ...... H-Hello?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something the matter, mister?</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Er... no. That is... Sir! I'm currently chasing a suspect, sir! Zak Gramarye... Do you know him!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I love Zak Gramarye! His magic is the best! I'm his biggest fan!</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I see... That's why you're wearing that costume you're wearing. Anyway! That very same Zak came into this room!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But no one's been in here except me...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">...B-But he has to be in here somewhere! Under the sofa! In the trash can! Behind the painting! Under the rug!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Trucy was his accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Imagine my astonished surprise when, one week later... ...I just happen to walk into a bar and see... him!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I couldn't believe my own eyes! For a while, I thought it had all been a long dream...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A dream that lasted a week!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">But it wasn't the magician who disappeared... it was Mr. Hat. *sniffle, sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Though it seems complex, what really happened that day was quite simple. You were standing by the door, and out came Zak. ...But that wasn't all. Another person got in on the act... and she was standing in front of Lobby No. 2. Along with Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Ah, and that's the beauty of it, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... ...while you are standing in shock and amazement, the magician rounds the corner... ...and, most likely, runs through the closest door... into Lobby No. 1. This is where you come in. You turn the corner, in rather lukewarm pursuit... ...and at that very moment, Trucy runs into Lobby No. 2! Then, all she has to do is tuck away the Amazing Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Sir, I... ...I only lost sight of him for the briefest of moments! Then, I saw that cape! Zak Gramarye's red cape fluttering like a... cape! ...... ...Astounding, sir! All my days of posing queries and making inquiries and chasing quarries... wasted! It was as if I could see them melting away like... ...an ice cream cone left by the side of the road to die!!! Or the scattered remains of a messily eaten chocolate parfait!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Such sweet sorrows...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It... It's an honor, sir!!! I've apologized to people many, many times! Sometimes more than once! But this is the first time anyone's ever apologized to meeeeeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, about that girl... ...I'm sort of her guardian now.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">Is that so? ...... ...... Sir! You should know that I harbor no ill feelings whatsoever in my harbor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, OK...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">I let the defendant escape, that's the stone cold truth! Just another step on my way from singing the blues to wearing the blues! Someday, sir, I'll be standing side-by-side with the great Detective Guamshoooooooooooe!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Erm, Mr. Meekins. This is a free ticket to the show at the Wonder Bar. If you want...</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">It... It's an honor, sir!!! Sir! I can't count the number of things I've had taken from me, sir! But no one's ever given me anything for freeeeeeee! Right! I'll see you in court next time then, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I look forward to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All eyes were on Zak Gramarye that day in court... until his mysterious disappearance. Now part of the mystery's been revealed... but the magician remained out of sight. It would be seven years before I met him again...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I'll be taking my leave, now. Still have some work to do back at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Then I guess I'll go back to my piano.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">To be honest, it's better when you aren't playing. This frigid culinary dungeon almost feels... comfortable. ...Later, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*... Two hours left on my shift. Wonder if we'll get any "customers" tonight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Ahem. Do you know who I am?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Who I Am"? No... But if you hum it, I can play it! ...Just kidding, I don't do requests.</line>
<line speaker="???">How about a different sort of request? You see... I play cards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... a customer. I was just hoping someone would come in and save me from a night at the keys.</line>
<line speaker="???">...I seek a true competition. I have heard the Borscht Bowl Club is the place for this. Now I see the rumor is true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And this is? A friend of yours?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! Don't mind me! I'm just your friendly neighborhood newsman!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Ah. He will not be playing tonight. When his business is finished, I shall send him home. This competition will be between us. No others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Wright Talent Agency represents two artists. And I'm number two. I play piano... Well, sort of. It's actually just a front for my real talent... ...which is playing poker. Don't ask me how I got started. I don't remember. But I'm good. Real good. It didn't take long for the rumors to get around... "Go to the Borscht Bowl Club if you want a real game. That guy's never lost"... People don't come to hear me tickle the ivory. They come to watch me play cards. Is this a seedy poker club? No. It's a restaurant. We don't play for high stakes. There's no money involved. But real players carry cash... and they're always thirsty. It's a handy source of income for the club owner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, let's compete. I'll take you to the room.</line>
<line speaker="???">The Hydeout, yes. But before we go...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="???">Allow me to introduce myself. My name is Shadi Smith.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh, and I'm Brushel! Spark Brushel! News reporter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. I'm...</line>
<line speaker="???">No, no, Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="???">You must always look a man in the eye when you make your introductions. ...You still do not know who I am?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have we... met? <thought>Ah...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Today, in this courtroom... ...you cannot declare me "guilty".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I am talking... about this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Enigmar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defendant's escaped! Find him! Quick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Close all exits from the building! On the double! He must not be allowed to escape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You can't be... But you're...! ...Zak Gramarye!?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes... The reincarnation act of the century. Pity I have only an audience of one. ...You.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Zak Gramarye!? This must be a bad dream. In a sense, this guy ruined my life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">You there!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...D-Dah?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">We will play soon. Ready the room.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah... I will be preparing the Hydeout for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you really him? The Zak Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Now I am Shadi Smith. Remember this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...How many years has it been now? Six?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">In exactly three days from now, it will be seven. I caused you much... inconvenience, I fear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Is... she well? Trucy, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's fine. I've got her working already. Hope you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I hardly need express my gratitude. But, you have it. ...This is why I have come. That, and to settle a matter of cards.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...By which you mean poker? <thought>Those eyes! He's serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">I despise losing above all else. And so, I have decided that I will win tonight. No matter what it takes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know this guy's type... and they're dangerous. Everything's about the competition. All else is secondary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Perhaps we should take this time to talk, before we play. I know you have much to ask me. ...And I, you.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">This... is grape juice? Is it refreshing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I usually drink too much and it ends up making me thirsty.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Oh, Mr. Wright. There is something inside that bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? It's my business card.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... You aren't surprised at all. Perhaps you don't like magic?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I sure felt surprised. Maybe I had my poker face on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">I must say, it comes as quite a surprise. I never knew you played.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd do anything else if I could, believe me. Oh yeah, there's something you could help me with. Do you think you could make that piano disappear? ...It'd help out in a lot of ways, really.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... Wah ha ha ha ha ha ha! You say the funniest things with the straightest face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...People always tell me that. <thought>Except I wasn't joking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One of the restaurant tables. This one's the closest to the piano. ...Which makes it the hardest to eat at, I hear. ...On days when I'm playing, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">What do you think about the ukulele? The sound is slight, the annoyance, curtailed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A ukulele in a Russian restaurant?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Then, you must go to a Hawaiian restaurant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hawaiian shirts don't go with my complexion.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Wa ha ha ha ha ha ha! ...I give up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We competed that day seven years ago, too.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, yes. ...You must have been surprised. ...Called to the detention center out of the blue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You choose your defense attorneys by playing poker.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Some are hired, others fired. When you compete, you see a man's true nature. You know what I speak of. ...I know that you do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Trucy's "power"?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Trucy? She is in a class of her own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For seven years I've played poker here at the Borscht Bowl Club... And I've never lost once. I'm good... but not that good. I win because whenever there's a big game, I bring in Trucy. ...And she sends me signals.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Daddy, he's got a good hand. ...You might have a chance if you act quick! Better call him soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me what her power is?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Judging a person's thoughts by reading their reactions is a staple of performance magic. But those of Trucy's line possess far greater skill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Her "line"?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Recall, you were the second man to whom I've lost.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Magnifi Gramarye...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">That was the first time I learned of this "power", as you call it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, so you're saying... ...her power is genetic? It's just "in" the Gramarye blood or something?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">"Blood"...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I am sorry, but it is not something told lightly to outsiders. And it is nothing you need to know at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's some kind of Gramarye secret, then? Fine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">She's... fifteen this year?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's still trying her best to follow in your footsteps, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I... see. When I planned my disappearing act, it was the thought of her alone that gave me pause.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, you were planning on vanishing from the get-go?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes, and for that, I must apologize. However... I could not be found guilty that day. Because of this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">A transferal of rights. You see the signature?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A transferal...? That's Magnifi Gramarye's signature, isn't it? "I hereby give all rights to the secrets, staging, and performance of my magic... ...to the recipient named below." And the recipient's name... is you... Zak Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes, it is I.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... This page looks torn.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">You recall the diary, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First... take a close look at this diary. ...Notice that a page has clearly been ripped out! As it just so happens... ...I have here what I believe to be the missing page.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Wait. Let me see that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...How could I forget? That scrap of paper lost me my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">This is the real page that was torn from the book. Magnifi gave it to me that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You could have told me this earlier. Like, seven years earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Once again, I must apologize. It was all I could do to prepare for my escape from that courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">The greatest of Magnifi Gramarye's illusions are true art. As such, they are well protected... by this document. Only its bearer may perform his illusions on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like a pretty important thing to have if you're his disciple.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">As the rightful heir to his art, I, too, wanted a rightful heir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Rightful"...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I'm sure you know who I chose as my successor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">That is why I have risked all to come here tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This person in the photo is Trucy's mother?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...! How did you come by this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy showed it to me. She said her mother was "gone"...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Then, it is so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">She is gone. What more is there to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um... lots?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, I know, I know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! You're still here!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">According to my in-depth research... ..."Trucy's Mother Magnifi Gramarye's Only Daughter!" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? Magnifi's daughter? Is that true, Mr. Zak...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Brushel! You say too much!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Urrrrrrrrrrrrrrng! Eh? Eh? What, why am I the bad guy? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Zak decked him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">In any case, Mr. Wright, this discussion... is over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thalassa Gramarye... She's the most mysterious of the whole lot. I need to gather me some more evidence, clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This woman is Trucy's mother, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She said her mother was "gone".</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...And it is so. What more is there to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thalassa Gramarye... Magnifi Gramarye's only daughter. I need to gather me some more evidence, clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Zak, could you tell me about this?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Mr. Wright. We meet for the first time in seven years, and you offer me this? Please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It... wasn't a present. <thought>This guy's a hard sell. Probably won't get a rise out of him unless I show him something real interesting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Sir! Ah, here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">A letter passing the rights I have inherited to Trucy. I would have you sign here, as a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... I'm not a lawyer anymore. And you need a public notary, besides.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, I may not look it, but I'm a certified notary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">By day, I wear a notary's glasses and hunt for news. Also by day, I wear a reporter's glasses and notarize! When I take off the glasses... I can't see very well.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Your signature, please. This is the first reason I have come here tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... I've finally figured it out. Now I know why you've come out of hiding only now. It's been seven years, you said?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...There's a law that covers your situation. After seven years, missing persons are considered to be legally "deceased". So, if someone was to vanish from the face of the earth seven years ago... ...they would lose all rights as a "living person" after seven years from that day. Not to mention all of their possessions.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Exactly. Which is why I am here. I risk showing my face in public for the sake of this document. ...Before my seven years are up. You might say, I am securing my daughter's inheritance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But do you really need this document? Wouldn't Trucy inherit your estate automatically?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Not in this case, I am afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"This case"...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes, I received the performance rights from Magnifi Gramarye. However, this was done in secret, without witnesses. Before Magnifi died, two potential successors to his repertoire were named. Myself, Zak Gramarye. And Valant Gramarye. ...Not Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. So you do need this document.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I have known Brushel since before I vanished. He is a man I trust. Now, only three know of my "rebirth".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I took the liberty of looking into Trucy's background. And found you had no other close kin.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...It is as you say. ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>OK... I was kind of hoping he'd say something about the mother at this point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know everyone else, but Trucy's mother... is a mystery.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak's signature. I'm sure he's written it many times, being an ex-star and all. Hmm. I bet there's plenty of people out there who'd kill for a Zak Gramarye autograph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Final...? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">As you said, I have come out of hiding today to make this document legally binding. Once that is done, I shall slip once more underground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Without seeing your daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... It would be best if I did not. ...Seven years ago, we played. Seven years ago, I lost. I already lost to Magnifi. I do not care to lose to another. And I have heard that you never lose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's just a rumor.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes... for it is impossible to never lose. Unless one has an ace up one's sleeve.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Zak">As a magician, it causes me no end of irritation. To think a mere lawyer might be out there, pulling the wool over so many eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey... I just signed your document for you. Maybe you could try lightening up?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">That was that. This is this. For my final competition, I will destroy your perfect record, Phoenix Wright. This... will be my final performance. You are warned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy is beyond serious... So much for a fun evening of cards.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Brushel. You may leave.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, but, it's your last game! I mean, what a scoop...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... ...I punch, and I punch. But still, it is not enough.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...... Er, I just remembered a future, er, prior engagement! Toodles, gentlemen! Oh, and nice meeting you, piano man!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Then let us begin. Dealer!</line>
<line speaker="Olga">...Dah?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">You will be witness to our competition.</line>
<line speaker="Olga">Dah. It is honor for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? <thought>Why haven't I seen her around here before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, that reminds me... I saw a familiar face as I entered this restaurant. ...He did not seem to notice me, however.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Gavin... I believe was his name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know him?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">After a fashion. ...Listen, Phoenix Wright. One can learn much from a true competition. ...Remember this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Gramarye "power"... I was close to understanding it, but I needed more. And I knew where to get it. ...Trucy's mother. I'd need to meet that reporter again, that was clear... ...And one other thing. From the moment my "final competition" with Zak began that night... ...a name was running through my head. ...The name of a man now in prison. ...A name Zak Gramarye knew. But how? And why...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Well well, isn't this an unexpected surprise? What errand brings you down to my cramped confines?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Is... this your idea of revenge, Phoenix Wright? Revenge for the events that took away your attorney's badge seven years ago!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My past is like my logic, straight and true. Nothing's changed. All I did was point the finger of justice in the proper direction.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">... Fine. I'm glad we could have this little tte--tte, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...You look well, Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, too... Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's strange, you know? Here I am in solitary, and yet the books keep piling up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you've got more than books up there.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Ah, yes, my "collection". I've a few friends on the prison staff. They show me a little kindness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Just a "little"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's some chair. Just looking at it makes me want to take a seat. You'd probably have to add a whole digit to the price of one of my office chairs.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">In here, a comfortable chair is the most valuable thing in the world. You'd have to add two digits to the price of the standard prison-issue chair for this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Those prison chairs don't look so bad, either. Maybe I should redecorate.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You're thinking, "What self-respecting man would use nail polish?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not really. I know appearances are a big thing with you.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You know what I say? One cannot live a beautiful life without beautiful nails. First rate, in all things. Accept nothing less.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That certainly does look like first rate nail polish. I like the sparkly bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's crystal. If you're so drawn to it, please, have one. It's on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice roses...</thought> You taking care of this one here?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, yes, she's surprisingly delicate, you know. Requires careful tending. But, she is my "best friend", as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Best"...? Come on, now I'm starting to feel bad for you.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh? Of course, she's known to bite if handled roughly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Your rose bites?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... I was speaking of the photo next to the rose. My retriever, Vongole. Cute, but feisty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Every dog has its thorn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That envelope's been bothering me since I came in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It's not nice to peek at other people's mail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You get mail here in jail?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That I do, though they read it first, apparently. Still, I am allowed the pleasure of correspondence. Packages and the like are a different matter, however.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Looks like sneaking a peek is out of the question.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Life has been full of surprises... for both of us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I've no doubt you never expected to lose that attorney's badge of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I'll bet you never expected to wind up here. "Shadi Smith"... was the name of the man you killed. Did you know who he really was?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Who he was...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak Gramarye. You know, the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... I remember him, of course. But you say Smith was Zak? Impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't even try to tell me it was a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...What did I just say? Life is full of surprises. Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After that trial, you were arrested and found guilty. But your motive was never made clear. ...A mistake I plan to remedy.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...You're not an attorney anymore, Phoenix Wright. What possible conclusion do you think this "investigation" of yours can lead to? I killed a man named "Smith" with a bottle because I am an evil human being. ...Isn't that enough?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Not for me, it isn't. I need to know why you did it, Gavin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You recall that case seven years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, yes. The trial where Zak Gramarye pulled his famous vanishing act! My brother won his fair share of praise and adoration for that trial, as I recall. "Genius Prosecutor Reveals Crooked Attorney", was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That was when I met you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Was it now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Bar Association review board voted unanimously for the "strictest punishment". Unanimous... save for one dissenting opinion. Yours.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... It was my brother who was responsible for putting you in that position, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For seven years we've been friends... ...and yet, I still don't understand you.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">But Wright, your "friendship" toward me was never pure. ...You suspected me then as you still do now, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Honestly, right now, I'm not sure what I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't just brain a guy with a juice bottle for no reason. Tell me why you did it.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Persistent, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I came here... because I remembered something. The night of our "game"... ...Zak Gramarye mentioned your name, Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, that reminds me... I saw a familiar face as I entered this restaurant. ...He did not seem to notice me, however.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Gavin... I believe was his name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...After that, he was killed. And I asked you to help me. ...Because I remembered your kindness back when everyone had turned on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have to know. Why did you kill Shadi Smith? No... Zak Gramarye!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-Whoa! I've never seen Psyche-Locks like these! Dark... Cold... Full of despair... Can I even unlock these things...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Something wrong, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No. It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You shouldn't push yourself so hard. Life is to be taken easy, you know. ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...He's doing his nails.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I hardly need remind you that I am not a free man. I care little about the outside world. Save advances in chair technology.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No information forthcoming there, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... "Ariadoney"... I've heard of that brand. And this must be the brand symbol... It's supposed to be some kind of flower. Wait, no, maybe it's a hand. Wait... on second thought. Is that an eagle? ...... Who makes these things up, anyway? You'd think they'd try for a clearer symbol, at least.</line>
<line speaker="???">I... figured you'd come here sooner or later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I decided on sooner. Drew Misham... was it?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...... I... I haven't done anything illegal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And I didn't come here to whine about past events. I wanted to ask you some questions.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...I suppose you have that right. That day... the entire court descended into chaos. Only you stood still, your eyes calmly watching. I admit, it made quite an impression on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm used to finding myself in outrageous situations.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Phoenix Wright, was it? I'll answer what I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>I'm not sure, but... ...it feels like I'm being watched... intensely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, this is my daughter. Vera, say hello.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">Shall we begin, then?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, going home by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, er, no, I was just checking out the door.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good thing I'm far too stubborn to take hints like that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this painting here...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, that's one of mine. It's an illustration for a book. It's not on sale, yet, of course. But I thought it might be a good business. As a father, I'd like to be able to put food on my daughter's table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Not a feeling I know anything about... At least not yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Paints are scattered all around. Probably the ones he's currently using. There's something very artistic about a messy room. Not that this is anything compared to my office. ...... I guess that would make my office a "masterpiece".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You use these gizmos for painting? They're pretty... elaborate.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, those... Those aren't for painting. They're for analyzing. Paint composition, age... every conceivable angle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Tools of the forgery trade, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe I'll just sidle on over here for a closer look...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a pretty bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, don't touch that, please. I'll get in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">It belongs to Vera, you see. She always puts it somewhere she can see it. She looks at it often.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a light pink fluid inside. Nail polish, I'm guessing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is you and Vera?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Yes... Yes. We took that one quite recently. I know, I'm a painter. Why not paint a portrait instead. ...I've never been that good at people, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... right. <thought>Shouldn't you practice?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this red envelope...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah! Don't touch that! That's, er, it's quite important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The painter's face just changed hue. Guess I'd better behave. Though it's tempting to just grab it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an awfully small frame. What's that inside it? A stamp?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, please don't touch that. I'll get in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">That stamp belongs to Vera, you see. She always puts it somewhere she can see it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's "Zak &amp; Valant"... the Gramaryes, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">The post office issued that commemorative stamp last year. When the Gramaryes were at the height of their popularity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not anymore... ...now that one of them has vanished off the face of the Earth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">Vera went to see one of their shows when she was quite small. She's been a dedicated fan ever since. She watched them every time they came on TV... until the end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">That stamp's quite hard to come by, I hear. ...I still wonder how she got her hands on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an awfully small frame. There's a commemorative stamp of the Gramaryes inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Paints and pigments are lined up on the shelves... with some noticeable gaps.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">It's embarrassing, but I can't afford all the paints I want. I insist on buying the ones I use with my own money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see how you'd want to do that, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Perhaps you've heard that you can make any color... ...as long as you have the three primary colors? Well, it's a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Poor guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are some finished paintings stacked here. They don't look all that bad, really.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...I'll sell you one for 50 cents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... That's OK. They look kind of heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe he needs to work on his sales technique a bit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judging from this place... you're a painter?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Not, sadly, a profitable one. I've never sold a painting. It's a source of considerable embarrassment. I would be able to get by, were it only me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your daughter...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Her mother... grew weary of me and left. I don't want her to grow up needy, Mr. Wright. That is why... I began my other occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forgeries...</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Don't look at me with those eyes. I know what it is that I do. More than half of the paintings they bring me are stolen. And who knows what my copies are used for...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... some of your "works" aren't paintings, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">You may not believe me when I tell you this... ...but that was my first work outside painting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...To think it would be used as evidence in a murder trial... I never even imagined the possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why did you take the job!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I was... well paid. Very well paid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think he feels worse about it than I do... The past is hard to escape.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">Honestly, the sooner I can put this behind me, the better. With apologies to you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but it's not going to be quite so easy. <thought>He's trying to forget what he made. Looks like I'll have to remind him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well then. Ready to tell me about this "work" you did?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...It was unlike anything I had attempted before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it would be a little different from paintings.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">That is not what I mean. In all my previous work, it sufficed to create a "copy".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...This wasn't a copy?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...The client gave me two things that day. The first was a sample page, as reference. The second, a printed document I can only surmise was written by my client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you used the real writing as a reference to "reproduce" what the client wrote?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Y-Yes... As I said, it was my first job of that nature.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... ...who was your client?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">A-As I said in court, I do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Really? Even for such a suspicious request? If it was me, I'd want to know as much as I could about the requester.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I... I never met them! N-Not personally, I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah. A Psyche-Lock. Of course.</thought> It seems like you're still hiding something. Something about this "work".</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Unnk... Unnh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "work"... Don't try to pretend you've forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, all you did was make a "copy"... ...but that "copy" might have destroyed the life of an innocent man.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm responsible, too. Which is why I have to know. ...And you have to tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I... knew it would be difficult to escape this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then... let's talk.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "work"... Don't try to pretend you've forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, all you did was make a "copy"... ...but that "copy" might have destroyed the life of an innocent man.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I... knew it would be difficult to escape this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Mr. Misham. Tell me about Magnifi's diary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Misham, I was wondering if you could tell me about this...</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I've... not been in touch with the outside world for some time now. I'm sorry, but that... isn't much of an inspiration to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Oh, so now he's the sensitive artist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's hear it, then. What are you hiding from me, Mr. Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I'm sorry, but I really don't know. I never met the client!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>...True, when I asked the client's name... ...there were no Psyche-Locks in sight.</thought> ...Regardless, you're hiding something! You have to be, otherwise it wouldn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Hrrrm... Why are you doing this to me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I've made my stand. No backing down now. So... what's Misham hiding?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">Yes, there was a reference... Why should I hide that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">After the trial, I submitted everything to the court. My "work", the sample page, everything. I can give you directions to the court, if you'd like...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's fine. I know where the court is. ...Unless you were just trying to get me to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, sorry. I can sometimes be a little blunt.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Like I said, I never met the client. How could I hide someone I do not know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He did say that, didn't he? And with no Psyche-Locks, either. So... he's not lying about that, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ask as many times as you want... My answer's the same. I personally never spoke to the client!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "personally"...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah, er, that is... Ahem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can pretty much piece together what it is from what you've said.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Wh-What is it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You told me what you knew about the client... ...and I couldn't see any Psyche-Locks...</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Psycho locks? Is that some sort of asylum security? Or a new hairstyle, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But then they did show up, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...who was your client?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">A-As I said in court, I do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Really? Even for such a suspicious request? If it was me, I'd want to know as much as I could about the requester.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I... I never met them! N-Not personally, I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Not personally"... Those words triggered the Psyche-Lock!</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Again with the psycho locks! Now I really must know what they are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you didn't meet with the client... ...but someone else did! ...Maybe the real forger behind this "evidence"?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Hrrm... Perhaps I'm hung up on this "lock" business... ...but I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, well, I didn't come here to talk about Psyche-Locks.</thought> ...As long as I come to the right conclusion, it doesn't matter how I got there.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">And your conclusion is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The real forger behind this wasn't you, Mr. Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Drew">P-Poppycock! I don't know what you're talking about. That's my work, I tell you. Made here in my studio! Who else could it have been but me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's the real question, isn't it? If the forger wasn't you... ...then I don't have many other people to choose from. The real forger at Drew Studio is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, Mr. Misham!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...... Sure. Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Feel free to accuse them of being a forger. I'll even tell you how to get to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I know how to get to the court. <thought>OK... now I'm confused. Who's really making the fakes here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The real forger... ...is your daughter, Vera Misham, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ridiculous! My daughter's only twelve years old, Mr. Wright. I've always been more one for landscapes... not surrealism.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice comeback... but you're shaking in your boots. I've got you now!</thought> The only two people with access to the studio are you... and your daughter. The Psyche-Locks tell me you're not the forger. Which makes your daughter the only possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Ahem. I feel very much on the verge of going psycho lock myself!!!</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I... don't know how you knew, but, you're right. The one who made this page... was my daughter, Vera. Not I. She's only twelve... A genius, you might call her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A precocious little girl outshining her father. There's been a lot of that going around recently.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I let her play in the studio, and she watched me... ...She taught herself in that way. The drafting tools and analytical devices I bought when they became necessary. They're my little girl's playthings, now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ah, do I detect a bit of fatherly pride?</thought> So, Vera was the one who made this page. Would she know who the client was, then?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...... Actually, the client came once. Here... to this studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What!? Why didn't you say so sooner!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">But their face was covered, and they did not want to talk to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... they talked to your daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">"I will speak only with the artist," the client told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That little girl might know something about him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>OK, what do I do now...? Maybe I should talk to her father a bit more... Or is it time to turn my attention to Vera?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I suppose there's no sense in rushing things. Let's see if there's any more to get out of Daddy first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Misham, I have a request.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Let me guess. You'd like to speak with my daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Can I?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...My daughter has never been one to talk to strangers. She's quite shy. Extremely so, actually. ...With only one exception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which was...?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Oddly enough, it was that client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Drew">I left the studio while they talked. I returned when they had finished... and she was laughing! It was the first time I'd seen anything of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Please, let me speak with her.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... this could be tough.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vera, was it? I... Would you like to have a friendly chat?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... I'm Phoenix Wright, ex-lawyer... and pianist!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm still looking for the keys that say "do re me". Can't find 'em anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm no good at this. I need something to get through to this girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">I... don't go outside much. I like to paint in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you like the outside?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">There's bad people out there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, true, but there're lots of good people, too.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Actually, I should tell you... ...she was almost kidnapped, once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">K-Kidnapped...!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Since then, she's been... Well, you can see for yourself. She refuses to leave the house.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Wait. But that doesn't make sense. She said she went to the Gramarye Museum... ...with you, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Ah... yes, actually, she was quite insistent on it, much to my surprise. That was the first and last time she expressed such a desire to me.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">That person gave me... a good luck charm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A good luck charm?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">For when I absolutely had to go outside.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Yes, apparently, she received something... a gift. ...From that client, actually. She won't tell me what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Father! I told you to keep that a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>From that client, huh? This I have to hear about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, your father tells me you're good at painting all sorts of things...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I really like painting. A lot. Father is always very happy when I paint them exactly the same.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you did this, too?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh! Yes! That was my first job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your first...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">All I used to do was paint the same thing I saw. ...But this was totally different! The pen slips and the way the writer held the pen, and the pressure on the nib... ...I had to use a microscope and analyze it on the computer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems happy. Odd... Her work was the last nail in the Gramarye coffin. I guess no one told her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">They're the best in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, you mean Troupe Gramarye? Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Father gave it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your father...? But... I asked him about it. He didn't know how you got it.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh... Oh, um, I guess I just took it. Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Took" it...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Father got a letter... from that person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That person? You mean, that letter was from the client?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh, we talked about the Gramaryes forever that day! ...I'm sure that's why I was sent that stamp. I didn't want to just send it back... so I took it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They're a sneaky one, this client. So they were trying to get on her good side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you met the person that asked you to do this job? And... you talked with them?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">.....</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this about a "good luck charm" you received?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... I can't talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">If I do, it won't work anymore! ...That's what I was told.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... but I really, really have to know.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. Time to do some psyche-unlocking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then there's this...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... My stamp...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! She spoke! She can talk!</thought> Yeah, so this stamp... <thought>How can I keep her talking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I have your stamp?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">No way! ...It's my favoritest thing in the whole world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack, sorry, sorry! I won't take it, promise. <thought>Wow, if looks could kill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This stamp... It's got a really nice frame.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... I don't think so. ......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yep, just keep her talking like that. Great job, Wright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't Troupe Gramarye amazing?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I especially like those two, Zak and Valant. I mean they're, uh, just so magical!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Aren't they, aren't they!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! Whenever I go to one of their shows, I'm like... Whoa! Magic! ...You know?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Me, too! Me, too! I love them! They're so cool! It's like... like magic! Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! She's talking! Not saying much... but it's a start!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I went and saw them with Father the other day! The opening ceremony at the Gramarye Museum of Magic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Gramarye M-Museum? They have one of those? <thought>I guess it makes sense now that they have their own commemorative stamp...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... have you been to one of their shows?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Just once, when I was little. With Father. The Gramaryes on stage... It was like a dream! Disappearing, reappearing, cutting apart, putting back together... they do it all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, yeah! Maybe you can keep telling me stuff like this? You know... about Zak and Valant maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh. Oh, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! Better get asking before she changes her mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They look pretty incredible in this stamp. I mean... it's like magic!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I know, I know! I love the Gramaryes! They're just so... um... magical!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's talking up a storm now! Better get what I can out of her before the storm passes over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I think I just made her nervous. I need something to grab her attention... but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to trust this client... Quite a lot, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because they gave you this stamp?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">N-No... that's not why. They listened to me. To my problem...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The problem... that keeps her inside all the time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">"Don't go outside if you don't want to"... That's what they told me. But... when I absolutely have to go out... ...all I had to do... was use a good luck charm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A good luck charm... that your client gave you?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I know what your client might have given you, actually. Is this your good luck charm...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If this doesn't bring good luck, I don't know what would.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... I see. Good luck charms are different for different people, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hmm? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">If you say it's lucky, then it must work for you. That's the beautiful thing about good luck charms...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>See that innocent smile? Everyone has a different way of breaking the news. That's the beautiful thing about being totally wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... was what they gave you, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The same bottle's over there on your desk. Your good luck charm... right?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I heard once... Cosmetics were once thought to ward off evil. This... is a magic bottle. It has the power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah... Of course it does. <thought>I'll just refrain from commenting any more on that one.</thought> I think I know who gave you that bottle, actually. The one who asked you to do this "job". Was this the client?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vera? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I won't tell you. Even if that is the client, I won't.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So you say. But... I know it wasn't the client. I don't see any Psyche-Locks clattering to the floor. *sigh* How could I get that one wrong? The answer is dangling in front of my face!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This man... is a friend of mine. Know him?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name is Kristoph Gavin. ...He's a lawyer, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I... I promised. I promised not to tell!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I'm sorry. I can't talk about the client. I promised. And if I break my promise, the spell won't work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't need a name anymore. I've got my answer...</thought> You're pretty confident in this charm, then?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... I think... they might be the Devil.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Or maybe... an angel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I saw it... Or I think I saw it, when they gave me this. ...I saw the Devil's face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Are you saying the client's face looked like the Devil's?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">No! The client... was gentle... with a gentle smile.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... where'd you see this "Devil" then?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">It was so quick... I don't remember well. But... that's when I knew that person wasn't like other people. That's why I believe in my good luck charm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm not sure what this "Devil" she saw was... ...but it's pretty clear that Kristoph Gavin has her "charmed"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Drew">...I am sorry for what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you want to apologize, try my client, Zak Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Um... Did I... do something bad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Your eyes... they're sad. Very sad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... I'll put on my smile next time I come, promise. ...I hope to see you smile then, too, Vera.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Oh... OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Take care.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thinking back on my first encounter with the young forger... ...I witnessed something of vital importance that day. ...Of course, by the time I realized it... ...it was already too late.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">What strange sight doth mine eyes behold!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Two men on either side of a single transparent pane... ...yet it seems fickle Fate has switched sides, so to speak! The forger of fakes walks freely. While the innocent languishes within these flexiglass confines.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's been no proof that I forged anything.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Nor proof that I took the life of my dear mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet... these chains cannot hold me for long. The stage awaits! And what, may I ask, awaits you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A little piano in a cold little hole-in-the-wall...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">But, since you are here... ...what shall we discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The shooting of Magnifi Gramarye, for one... Who pulled that trigger? Valant? Or his partner Zak? His partner vanished before the answer could be found. If I'm going to get any closer to the truth, this is the place to start.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera. I just had to say it. Old habits die hard. Maybe I should do a few tricks for the viewers at home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That guard keeps stealing glances in this direction. ...And scratching his head. Maybe our resident magician showed him a trick or two.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I have to hand it to my partner. He knows how to make an exit. That's talent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. He made my attorney's badge disappear, and he never even touched it.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Glory's spotlight always leaves someone weeping in the shadows... ...yet his very disappearance is itself a revelation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Revealing what?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Zak Gramarye killed Magnifi. It's as good as a signed confession.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's certainly been public opinion's take on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I grow tired of my cage. And the time of my release is near. I must go and prepare.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Planning on jumping back into the magic right away?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">As long as an audience waits with bated breath, there will be Valant. And also...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Now that my partner has disappeared, Magnifi's repertoire... is mine. Valant Gramarye has a tradition to uphold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that true?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Seen in this light, the trial was quite good to me, verdict or no. And... you can't pay for that kind of publicity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The suspicion on you hasn't lifted entirely, Valant. After all... ...you received one of those letters, too. You were just as obligated to follow Magnifi's instructions as your partner.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...So I was. But only Zak Gramarye followed them. Let us not speak any more of "who shot what". Now that my partner has vanished... the question is moot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm more interested in learning something else, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">What might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to know what Magnifi had up his sleeve. How could he coerce you and your partner to kill him?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The "trick" up his "sleeve"? Ah ha ha ha ha...! Perhaps you do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Know what?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">A great magician never reveals his secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I didn't think it would be that easy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">The audience must remain forever... in the audience. ...Bathing in the reflected glow of the spotlight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Valant, could you look at this for me, please?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Hmm. Yes, I accept your challenge. ...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Challenge? Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You want me to make it float? Disappear? Or shall I simply eat it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... I didn't come here to play games, Mr. Valant. Or watch you do tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm flying by the seat of my pants on this one. There must be a path leading from the evidence to the truth... ...And that's what I'm going to find!</thought> To ask someone to take a life, even one not long for this world... ...that's asking someone to commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. Our mentor was fond of dramatic moves... and dramatic finales.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And he got his wish. His life was taken. What "weakness" could be so powerful as to coerce someone into committing murder? My guess is it was a matter of life... or death.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your troupe lived in a world of showmanship -- the flashier, the better... ...and flashy so often means danger, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Let us make this as painless as possible. If you have proof of this "danger"... then show it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Ah. And this is your idea of "danger".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't agree, Mr. Valant?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">If you want my opinion, I would say there is something far, far more dangerous. ...And that is you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a little early for me to be making mistakes. Think deadly... and what's more deadly than a fatal accident? That could be the source of all the Gramaryes' problems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...! Why, that's one of ours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Specially designed for your show, I gather. A single bullet... One shot...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What are you suggesting!? We are magicians, Mr. Wright. Not murderers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not crying "murder", Mr. Valant. I'm crying something far more tragic... ...An accident.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">"Zak &amp; Valant's Quick-Draw Shootem"... ...How long has it been since those shots were last heard?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was the Shootem cancelled because someone might get hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Of course. What other reason could there be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it could have been cancelled because someone had already been hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...! Fascinating, my Faustian forging friend. But tell me, what can you prove with a single pistol?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, tell me what would have happened if there had been an accident. What if one of your bullets took a life on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The performance of magic is not concerned with "what ifs". It is concerned with precision. Precisely whom do you claim we shot!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I've chosen the right path. Let's just hope he walks it with me.</thought> A life was sacrificed so that the show might go on... and this shows who it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">A word, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Does it excite you to know you stand at a critical moment in your quest...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... it does. Sort of.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Then you'd never make it on stage. You're not fit to be a magician! Give it up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hadn't actually been considering that as a career option.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I'm sure you'll find something else to while away the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like figuring out who that bullet hit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">But... But that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak Gramarye's wife... and Trucy's mother. ...Thalassa, I believe was her name.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah! Allakazaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Bu-But how can you say this? How can you say she was struck by one of our bullets?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Still in denial mode, eh?</thought> Thalassa was at the greatest risk of being shot. And this clearly shows just how much danger she was in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Mr. Wright, I envy you. It appears your chosen profession is far more lenient than mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">For us magicians, a single misstep can be... fatal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...A single mistake can be fatal for an attorney, too.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah, so it can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thalassa's the key, I can see how her name affects him. But just a name isn't enough. I need to recreate that day in his mind. Starting with where she stood!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Troupe Gramarye's performances were very, very popular. So popular, they even made a commemorative stamp at the height of your fame.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">We were not merely the "latest craze"... We were an age. A golden age.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's all here on this stamp. ...There's Thalassa, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy's mother is "missing", I hear. ...What happened to her?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I... I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A part of his memory is still locked up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...There is one thing you're failing to address.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">As you say, our troupe was a world unto itself. If our leader, Magnifi was so inclined, he could hide anything he wished with ease. ...But, Mr. Wright. Then he would have hid a crime... making him an accomplice! ...Not a great foundation for blackmail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>Valant's got a point. If one of the troupe members died in an accident, and Magnifi covered it up... ...his innocence would come into question.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Found the right address, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm so close! There has to be something. About how Thalassa's death could affect Zak and Valant's relationship with Magnifi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I see in your eyes... you still have something to say. How can you possibly prove more than you already have!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll prove why Thalassa's accident tied your hands so completely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...No better proof than the evidence!</thought> The accidental death of Zak's wife tied both your hands... And his evidence proves why Magnifi held so much power over you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Were you, by any chance, trying to threaten me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...You'll never make a good blackmail artist. Never!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not a career choice I'd been considering, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Give up your dreams. Work an honest job. That's my advice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'd better stop dreaming and get to work here, fast. Magnifi used Thalassa's death as a means to control his disciples. How was that possible if he could be implicated in the cover up? ...Do I really have the evidence to prove this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...It's going to take a little knowledge of the players to crack this one.</thought> The accidental death of Zak's wife tied both your hands... And this information proves why Magnifi held so much power over you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Were you, by any chance, trying to threaten me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...You'll never make a good blackmail artist. Never!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not a career choice I'd been considering, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Give up your dreams. Work an honest job. That's my advice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The troupe was a tight-knit unit... it's all about the people involved. Their personalities, their histories. Who was Thalassa, really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It wasn't a question of who shot Thalassa... Thalassa herself was the problem!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">What... do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was Zak Gramarye's wife, Trucy's mother... ...and Magnifi Gramarye's only daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a terrible accident... ...and the two of you killed your mentor's only daughter! If that wasn't the key to Magnifi's power over you, I don't know what was!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">It... It was... It was an accident!!!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...There's no proof, none at all!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Thalassa went missing... ...and your mentor blackmailed both of his disciples. It doesn't take a genius to put one and one together.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... Ours was... a complex family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Troupe Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The master, Magnifi Gramarye, his only daughter... ...and his two disciples.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That does sound like a recipe for disaster, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Do not be tempted into faulty flights of fancy. Yes, there was an accident... ...but that is all it was. An accident. Zak &amp; Valant's tour de force! The guns blaze, the bullets fly... straight toward that beautiful body on stage. And then crash! zing! pow! into everything but her. Now that... is magic. It happened one day when we were practicing. Same trick, with a new twist. And... tragedy. But as for whose bullet stole Thalassa's life... ...we shall never know the answer. Thalassa disappeared from our lives... and Zak was bereft of his wife. Trucy lost her mother... ...and Magnifi, his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And that led to blackmail, I take it.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">It is all part and parcel of the darkness that comes when the curtain falls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did Magnifi Gramarye try to cover up the "accident"...? It was his own daughter who died!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">All I can say is, it was a critical time for Troupe Gramarye. A passing of the torch from Magnifi to Zak &amp; Valant. We all sacrificed so that it might be a success. Thalassa's death... was the greatest sacrifice of all. Yet... ...even when her life was extinguished, her presence was not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">In time, we, myself and Zak, found we could no longer oppose Magnifi's wishes. Magnifi forced us to perform his art, for his benefit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... I guess I can understand. I mean, he did lose his only daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">But do you not find cowardice in his actions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">To decide to hide the truth of your own daughter's death is one thing... ...but then to hang that death as a guillotine above our heads!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Things were dark behind the scenes in Troupe Gramarye, that's for sure.</thought> Does Trucy know...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">She was not told. ...Naturally. Who would want to know that their father might have taken their mother's life?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I had not thought of that accident for a very long time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry to dredge up old memories... but this has helped a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Not to find Magnifi's slayer, I should think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...True.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">After that accident... ...there was one who came sniffing, quite persistently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A reporter?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">He called himself a "newsman" at the time. Often I spied him lurking about the dressing room, doing his "research".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would you happen to remember his name?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">What was his name...? Sorry, I have forgotten. But, in the course of his interviewing, he became quite close to my partner, Zak. I liked him not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">His name... I do not recall. But his scent -- the cloying aroma of mint. ...Yes, whenever he smiled. Which was far too often.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Thanks for your help.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...It does no good to interfere with the past, Mr. Wright. You will not uncover answers. Only wounds.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had begun to notice a dark curtain hanging over Troupe Gramarye... ...and I began to realize what I had to do. I had to protect Trucy from that darkness. The reporter he mentioned... ...the "newsman". I never learned who that was, at the time. ...Though I've got a pretty good idea who it is now. That smile, and the sickly sweet smell of mint. The last floss-thin thread connecting Zak Gramarye to this world. Sooner or later, I'd have to track him down.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Eh? Well well well what do we have here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember me?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course I remember you! "Journalist Meets Ex-Attorney In Bar", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask what you're doing here? Mr. Misham was poisoned, and his daughter's...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh, yes, I know. Oh, how I know! Yes. It's caused me no end of grief, to be honest. "Journalist Wishes He'd Tracked Down Case Just A Little Quicker", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were you on the trail of this case the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Zak Gramarye... was a good friend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak said something to that effect back at the Borscht Bowl Club.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">What a character, what a man! If a little... No, a lot... No, extremely rough around the edges!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think I could ask you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh? You serious? I mean, I'm usually the interviewer, not interviewee! "Journalist Asks Questions, Not Other Way Around", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Fine, shoot, I don't care! People have been asking me all sorts of things lately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...This is where Mr. Misham fell? Never thought our seven-year reunion would be quite like this.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Wait. You knew Mr. Misham!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I met him once. In court. It was a... brief meeting, but one I'll remember for the rest of my life.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Now that's a story right there, that is! I smell a scoop! "Ex-Attorney Now Down-On-His-Luck Pianist Plays Sonata Of Sorrow!" end quote. I'm all ears! Let's have it! Don't hold anything back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Could you at least get rid of the "down-on-his-luck" part?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door outside. Vera might come walking in at any moment... if she wasn't in intensive care. Will she ever come through that door again, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those three paintings...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...All Drew's "works", of course. Which is to say, Vera's "works", really. Or, to be more precise, Vera's forgeries of someone else's works. Of course, if you demand utter and total precision... ...... Actually, there's nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was about to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A drafting table. Probably for making detailed designs for forgeries.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You know what I think about that? I'll tell you! Painting should be done freehand... no rules, no restrictions! You really think a line drawn by a ruler's going to "move" anyone? I smell a letter to the editor! "Could You Write An Article With A Ruler?"... end quote! Unless you wanted a ruler to write the address on your blackmail letter straight! That's what I think. You can quote me on it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>You could drop this guy on a deserted island and he wouldn't get bored.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's an odd assortment of equipment to find in a painter's studio. Of course, it makes more sense when you know they were making forgeries. I guess that's why they never took visitors here. Wouldn't really want people seeing all this.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yes, in fact I was the first human being ever to set foot inside this studio. Er, other than Mr. Misham, of course. Oh, and Vera, too. And, this is assuming that I'm human, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm beginning to have my doubts.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take a closer look at that desk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This envelope's from the client who requested that forgery. Just think, if that had gotten lost in the mail... ...I'd still be wearing my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I just have to do that when I see this pose. I can't believe it's been seven years... ...I have to stop torturing myself with these things! I know! I'll just pretend it's saying something else. "The post office? Why, it's right over there! Good say, sir!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A picture of a young Mr. Misham and a very young Vera. They're smiling. They look happy. Of course, now Mr. Misham's passed away... ...and Vera's on death's doorstep in the hospital. ...Guess I'll just do what I can... and hope it's enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This frame looks even smaller sitting next to that photo. Just the right size for a commemorative stamp, indeed. A commemorative stamp put there by a daughter... that killed her father. Sometimes, life just sucks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all the jars of paints and pigments. Why are there so many jars of the same color?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">My guess is that they're sorted by "age".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Age...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">When you're making a forgery, it's important to match the age of the original, see? Paint composition's changed a lot over the years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... right. Did you learn that in journalism school?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Journalist Relies On Writing Skill And Imagination!" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...As long as you don't do news stories by imagination.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Either that, or they just bought a lot of the same color by mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>I find myself not caring anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was tragic what happened to Drew Misham and his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Forgery is a serious crime, and they paid the price. You know what really did them in though, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. A forged diary page.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The night I "interviewed" him... ...I found out something about Mr. Misham I hadn't known.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You know, he always felt like he was being watched? Every day, for seven years. "Walls Have Ears, Potatoes Have Eyes", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Being watched... you mean, he felt guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">No, no, I'm not talking about "feelings", here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...You know, I felt watched, too. The whole time I've been on this case, no less! "Journalist Gets Tingling Sensation On Back Of Neck, Freaks Out", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because... you felt guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Why would I feel guilty!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You felt like you were being "watched", huh? I wonder what it all means?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Drew Misham felt like he was being "watched"... ...and you along with him. You sure it wasn't just nerves?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Nerves? No, it's nothing so mundane... ...I stopped paying attention to my nerves a long time ago! But I felt it, too! "Journalist Sure He Is Being Watched", end quote. Don't you wonder why Zak Gramarye got rubbed out after seven years... ...right after coming into contact with me!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">He completely vanishes from that courtroom... ...Then, for seven years, he talks to no one. Not a soul! Then, just as the "remaining time" was almost up... ...he contacts me in order to have this made.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then... he dies.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Starting to put the pieces together, are we!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... you were being "watched" this whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Maybe not just me. Maybe you were, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I met Zak through that case, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the shooting of Magnifi Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">No, before that... It's not widely known.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean... the "accident"? During the Quick-Draw Shootem practice?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">My my my, you're well informed! You should've seen me back then. I'd dug up quite the scoop. I wanted it all. Money, fame, women, a little puppy... all for me! I was younger then, and my days and nights smelled of fresher mint than they do now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Valant Gramarye did mention one particularly "nosy reporter".</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">In fact, I was on close speaking terms with Magnifi Gramarye at the time. I knew his daughter, too, of course. Thalassa, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Then Thalassa disappeared. Quite suddenly, at that. And Magnifi wouldn't say a word about it. Yeah... My evil habit got the better of me. "Journalist Catches Scent Of A Scoop, Goes On Feeding Frenzy"... end quote. I set up a one-on-one interview with Thalassa's husband, see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak Gramarye...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Something strange was in the air over at Troupe Gramarye in those days. The whole screwy mentor-controlling-disciples scene'd started by then, I'm guessing. Thalassa, she was part of it all, right? C'mon, you can tell me, off the record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sorry, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Anyway. I kept prying, and eventually became friends with Zak. Sure, he punched me once or twice. Or five times. But over time, he came to see me as his confidant.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">He's been waiting this whole time. Seven years, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Waiting...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">For his big comeback, of course! A big "revival of the Magnifi Miracle"... 'Course it was all a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because of this. ...The performance rights.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">In the absence of any official documents, he was golden. Who's to say the old man didn't give his rights to both Zak and Valant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So Valant waited until Zak "died". Legally, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The time finally comes, and Valant's like a kid on Christmas morning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's getting ready for his show at the Sunshine Coliseum, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">If that document sees the legal light of day... ...it's going to put a bit of a damper on the big show. He's a sorry one, that Valant Gramarye. Lost out to his partner at work... and in love, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Love"...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...It's the same old story, really. Two disciples, and their mentor's only daughter. What has three sides, and all of 'em pointy? ...A love triangle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. That is pretty classic.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">When you're in a performing troupe, that's your world. It's like family. ...One with an entire high school's worth of drama, intrigue, and backstabbing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And in the middle of all this, Thalassa has Trucy. ...And then she dies. <thought>I need to find out more about this Thalassa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">So... Thalassa married Zak and had Trucy, see. It was her second marriage, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean she was divorced...? <thought>I hadn't heard this one before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Not quite. Her late husband was a performer, too. He died in an accident on stage. Tragic, really. They had only been married one year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't know...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Ah, but she was a beauty. I still carry a portrait photo of her around, you know. I've known Trucy since she was a little thing, too. ...She got the better deal, really. She's got you for "family", after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Just reminiscing, you know. "Thalassa Has Another Child Besides Trucy", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? But... But Trucy said she was an only child!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ahh, yes. The one she had with her previous husband.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her previous husband...? Her first husband who died on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yep. They had themselves a kid. Another orphan, now. That's another one who slipped through the cracks. No idea where they are now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thalassa had another child...?</thought> Do you think I could borrow that photo?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Sure. I can be generous on occasion, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I won't need this locket anymore... Better return it to Trucy before I forget.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Brushel? Do you know this person?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Do I know that person? Of course! I was friends with Zak, after all... He hit me a few times. Five times, actually. But still! I'd never forget his wife.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thalassa Gramarye... ...Magnifi Gramarye's only daughter. ...Do you think you could tell me more about her?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...... Well, why the heck not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Brushel, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, I hear you loud and clear! Loud. And. Clear! So... you want me to write an article on that, right? What's the angle!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, no, that's OK. I don't need an article. I was just wondering if you had any thoughts on this.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I hear you. I. Hear. You! You want me to sniff around for a scoop! Well you've come to the right nose, my friend! ... It's odorless.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Th-Thanks. <thought>OK, that was less than informative.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I was too busy wondering about "biggerer" to listen to what you were saying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Sometimes, you just gotta accept that you won't be able to untangle it all, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe so. But still... ...I have to do what I can. And... I have to tell what I find to those who come next.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Next" you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not the one who will close the curtain on this little play. Apparently, that's not my role anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Magnifi...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I was just wondering what Magnifi would think of all this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Haven't you seen it in Trucy? She's got his power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean, how I can't lie to Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It was the same with Magnifi. And with his daughter... Thalassa.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a strange thing. You think it's some Gramarye gene?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Magnifi told me once, back when Zak married Thalassa. He said Zak had good "eyes". But not good like a Gramarye's eyes. Not that good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I wonder if Zak ever played a game of poker with his wife?</thought> Who knows what the "Gramarye Secret" was...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Maybe nobody, now that Zak's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Zak Gramarye...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The plot had finally begun to reveal itself. It sprouted from a warp in the Gramarye fabric, and grew, swallowing everything... ...wrapping itself around the Gramaryes' "power". A power which passed from Magnifi Gramarye to Thalassa ...to the next generation. And I would once again need to meet... ...the one who bridged it all together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to know more about this "power" of Trucy's. It's like she can see right into people's minds...! The first time I saw her do it, it blew mine.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">And after you were done having your mind blown, you took her to play cards with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... Gotta use the resources at hand, I always say.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yet, I myself have no such "power".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Trucy does... ...Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe Trucy got her "power" from her mother? Thalassa Gramarye...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I will not speak of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thalassa is officially "missing", correct? And I think I know why you don't want to talk about her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Zak!?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Let me be frank. It is true I do not wish to talk of her. And now, there is another I could care less about. ...You.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Take care you do not end up "missing" yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For some reason, it's extra scary when magicians threaten me. I'd better rethink my strategy here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The three of you were a team, once. Not that the entire country doesn't already know this. At your peak, you were the biggest stars around. Yet, there's another story behind the fame. One that not many know. Thalassa lost her life during a rehearsal. ...To you and Valant Gramarye's bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">It was an accident! It... It wasn't me! How could I shoot my dear Thalassa!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm sure Valant would say the same thing. Why, it's just like another murder I might mention.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Damn you!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Her eyes... I loved Thalassa's eyes. To think they could read my mind... was frightening. Yet there was a warmth in them that felt... like an embrace. She is dead, and Magnifi Gramarye has joined her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the only one with her "power" left now... ...is Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Zak...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I... do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't need any "power" to see through that one, buddy.</thought> So there's someone else. Someone other than Trucy. Someone who inherited Thalassa's "power".</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Hah... Hah! How would I know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My chances are slim. It would take a miracle to learn the truth. Or maybe... one has already occurred.</thought> There is someone else with the "power". And I know who...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Tell me, what do you think the "meaning" of magic is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">It is simple. To do magic is to make miracles happen. It is not something an amateur can achieve. Or you, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't need to make a miracle if one's already occurred... And I've known it all along. In fact, it would take a "miracle" for me to mess this one up! I know who the other one with the power is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">This... This boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name is... I forget. Something weird.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Who could he be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">A-Attorney!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I noticed him when I went to visit a friend's law offices.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... ...So, what are we to make of this, O Great Ex-Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Zak">You can show me pictures of strange boys all you like. But you could at least say something like "I'm this boy". I could use a laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps you wouldn't laugh if you knew the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This might not be 100% proof, but it's close. There's a link between this boy and Thalassa... Actually, it's more of a "ring".</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...A ring?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps this will refresh your memory. I just so happen to have evidence showing this "missing link"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Wa ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Zak?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">This face is your response, Mr. Ex-Attorney. You did say that I wouldn't laugh if I knew the facts, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Few magicians will tell you they're going to produce a dove, then take off their hat. It's almost more effective to not reveal your hand in advance, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Which I've just done, clearly. The question is, do I have a trump card in here somewhere? Think, Wright, think!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I know something. Your marriage to Thalassa was her second.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">How did you know this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her first husband... He died a year after they were wed, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...... He was a performer. They met when he joined us Gramaryes as a guest in our show. After Thalassa wed him, she left the Troupe for a while. ...... And you say she had a child then...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a photograph of her here. I couldn't help notice what she was wearing when I first saw this. Those bracelets stand out.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">They are a Gramarye family heirloom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This boy... ...wears a bracelet just like the ones in this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">What...!? So... that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why what, Mr. Zak?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I took this photograph of Thalassa before she left us. When she returned... ...she wore only one bracelet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet I know where that other one went.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">She gave it to this boy. ...Her son.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">This strange "power"... I myself do not know from where it comes. Yet, the fact is that it is passed down the Gramarye line. It runs in their veins.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What... is it?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I asked her... Thalassa, once. This is what she told me. Her power responds to "tension" in others.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tension...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">If she were to face a person, and they became tense, even slightly... ...then she would know, no matter how hard they tried to hide it from her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, she could "see" it?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Not quite. This is the strangest part of it all. She wouldn't realize that she was subconsciously detecting this tension... ...without the use of a particular "object", or, in her case, "objects".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Objects...? Wait... were they something she wore?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes. Her bracelets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I admit the first time I saw one of those, I felt there was more to it than just fashion. But what kind of power could a bracelet have...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">...I have made a decision. I will tell you all I know. Consider it a gift.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I hardly need you to tell me at this point, but those two...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Are brother and sister, yes. And the brother, too, has this "power" of theirs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Trucy has an older brother... I wonder what will come of that.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Mr. Wright. Tonight, after our game is done... ...I will return to a life of hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I would not see her live her life without knowing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. I'll tell the two of them when the time is right.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I... am in your debt. Once again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding. What I want to know is how all this got to be so messed up...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Those bracelets are made of a special alloy... ...It is said to expand and shrink, very slightly, in response to body warmth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they're temperature sensitive or something?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes. This is how they can shrink to the exact size of their wearer's wrist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And this has something to do with the "power"?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">What have I told you? The Gramarye "power" reacts to tension in others. When a Gramarye senses tension, they, too, become tense. And this tension translates into minute contractions of the muscles. So minute, they cannot sense it on their own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Their muscles? Oh, so that's what the bracelets are for!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">With a bracelet on, one can sense these contractions. Because the bracelet is always a perfect fit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So when the person they're watching gets tense... ...the bracelet feels tighter on their wrist!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that alone doesn't really count as mind reading.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I believe I understand how the process works from there. It's a simple question of "eyesight".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eyesight...? <thought>I guess that sounds simple enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Have you ever heard of "kinetic vision"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something about the ability to see moving objects with full clarity, right? I've heard of it before. They say athletes can see a moving ball like it was stopped... if they focus.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Oh, but it's not confined to sports alone. It all relies on the ability to "focus". When we focus, we can see many things... ...The faintest twitch of the face... and the meaning that lies behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Therein lies one of the secrets of magic. One must know the mind of a crowd before one may distract it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, basically, what you're saying is... ...the Gramaryes can see really well?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">For them, seeing is more than believing. It is knowing. Their "power" relies on eyesight combined with exceptional focus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Things are starting to come into focus for me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Of course, it is difficult to maintain such levels of focus for any length of time. But, what if someone could tell you when to focus?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or some-"thing"!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wait. Trucy doesn't have any bracelets.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">You are talking about poker, yes? The timing of when to focus is so elementary, she probably does it without thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I doubt Trucy herself has realized this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Mr. Zak.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">If this boy's bracelet is the real thing, then he will use it before long. Thereby awakening his power.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll keep that in mind. Well, shall we play a game?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah... I've said so much. Let me say one more thing. ...I will tell you of that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"That night"...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">The night my mentor, Magnifi Gramarye, passed from this world to the next.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">There were two pistols, and two letters sent. This... was Magnifi's "test".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A test?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">In his last years, Magnifi Gramarye worked us to the bone... No. To the pain. But that night, I could not shoot him. ...So I shot the clown's forehead instead. This, it seems, was the correct "answer".</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">...Take this. I give my art to you, Zak.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">It is thanks for playing along with my "show". You shot well tonight, Zak. Though I would not have minded dying by your hand.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">How could I shoot you? ...You're my mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">Bah! I thought you might say that.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...If I went home without shooting anything... ...what would you have done then?</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">Then, of course, I would have given Valant his chance.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">And if I had shot you in the forehead instead?</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">Then it would be over. If you or Valant were to shoot me in the head... ...then I to the darkness would go, and my art with me. A fitting end, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">Yet this ending, too, gives me no cause for regret. I thank you, Zak. And... I am sorry. I have done much that was wrong in my day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems to me that Magnifi wanted you to be his successor all along. That's why the time he gave you was earlier than Valant's.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Perhaps. But it is not something we will ever know for sure now. I wonder... What is Valant up to these days?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Waiting for you to "die". If seven years pass like this, the performance rights go to him.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Ahh. And now here I am... and his dream is ended.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's worse than that, actually. Public opinion's a fickle thing, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">What...? You don't mean to tell me they've put the blame for our mentor's death on... him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trial ended when you vanished, Mr. Zak. There were even rumors that Valant had helped you pull it off.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">But that's madness! ...... Well. It seems that before I can once again disappear from this world... ...I have one more act to perform.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">...Isn't it odd that sorting out my life should prove so complicated... ...even though I'm "dead"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That night, Zak Gramarye was killed. He died as "Shadi Smith", a mysterious traveler with a secret past. But he left one thing behind before he parted... This. His "confession". ...To use as I saw fit. ...Of course, he'd killed no one. This was his way of tying up loose ends with his old partner, Valant Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Well, this is a blast from the distant past.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Long time no see, Mr. Valant.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Seven years, has it been? Frankly, I didn't think I'd ever see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I came because there's something I want to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I've spoken to the press. I've nothing more to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've spoken to a lot of people myself... and come to some conclusions. But then I realized... ...I needed to hear it from you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A man in a costume is handing out balloons to the kids. ...It's nice to know kids still like balloons, somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">They're a favorite of mine. Balloon-sellers, that is. I would have them join me on the big stage. They could hand out balloons to the children in the audience!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wouldn't all those balloons get in the way of seeing your show?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Bravo. The possibility had not even occurred to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phoenix Wright, Entertainment Consultant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "Sunshine Coliseum", was it? I'm not sure it actually qualifies as a "coliseum", but it's a great forum.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes, it is a favorite of mine. I have always been fond of sunshine. Speaking of which, have you heard what happened here recently?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah, something about something going on during some concert?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Exactamundo! I see no reason to hide the fact that I, too, was involved in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's something. Did you help solve it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Hah! What do you take me for? No, I merely served to deepen the mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's obstruction... of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I'm a magician! It's my sworn duty to create mystery whenever possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think I've ever seen a hot-air balloon so close.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">It's a favorite of mine. I've often thought of how to use it in one of my shows. Perhaps for the climax of "Valant's Quick-Draw Shootem Returns". I stand on stage, I shoot, and the hot-air balloon is pierced! It explodes! ...What do you think? Thrilling, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little, I guess. But no one inside the coliseum would be able to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Bravo. It took me four days of planning to realize that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That sure is a big sign.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes, it's a favorite of mine. Impressive, isn't it? I considered using it for one wall of my house when the show's over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, your house is that big!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Actually, as fate would have it, I currently live in a one-room apartment. But following the wild success of my show, I intend to build a luxurious mansion. I was torn over just how big to make it. Until that sign whispered the answer to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... really beautiful.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I have walked a difficult road these past seven years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because you couldn't perform Magnifi's repertoire?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Do not be deceived! Valant's skill is the "real deal". I do not require my mentor's hand-me-downs. No, it was my partner who slowed me on my way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak Gramarye...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...His rather well-performed disappearing act seven years ago was the end. ...Or so I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Zak Gramarye murdered our mentor, and fled to escape punishment for his crime." You said something to that effect seven years ago, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I remember it as if 'twere only yesterday. Yet, that was not the way of it, in the end. For while he vanished, the suspicions upon my own person never did! "His partner Zak vanished to protect him..." That's what those thieving magpies of a press said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet that very same press comes to me now, feigning interest. They cover the greatest magic show in history as if it were a vaudevillian distraction! And here must I stand, smiling at them all. What am I, if not a player in some fiendish farce!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Might I suggest it's because you never made it clear what happened? Magnifi's death is still a mystery to this day. ...Which is why I came here to get the answer from you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I knew I'd be seeing these sooner or later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">The audience has no business stepping upon the stage. They must be content to sit and stare at the spotlight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That sounds an awful lot like something I heard seven years ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this, Mr. Valant?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Your forgiveness, I beg. Valant has eyes for naught but the preparations for his show! The coliseum, the hot-air balloon, the sign... Oh, and the balloon-seller.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, right. Sorry. <thought>What does the balloon guy have to do with his show?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Ask what you will, you'll get nothing from me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm as much a part of this affair as you are now. I have to know what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">For seven long years, I have endured... ...Now, finally, the curtain lifts on my new golden age! All the miracles of our troupe, within my grasp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry to do this, Valant... But right now, I need answers. I think I'll start... by dropping a bomb. That should shake things up.</thought> Valant... I wouldn't be so sure about those miracles. Not as long as I have this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Let me be frank. ...No one, and I mean no one, can stand in my path. Not even you, with your silly-frilly ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me be frank, too. That's the first time anyone's called me "silly-frilly". <thought>What I need is a bit of magic... something to stop Valant's show in its tracks. ...Now's no time for subtlety.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">And what might that be? I see it bears the Gramarye seal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I should have brought this to your attention sooner. But I didn't imagine you'd be planning your comeback quite so fast.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... What is this...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A document showing the true recipient of the performance rights to Magnifi's miracles.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Wh-What...!? Zak... Gramarye... He wrote this!? What!? He passed everything to his daughter!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy Enigmar... Actually, she's officially my daughter these days.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Preposterous! Zak's... Zak is gone! Vanished into the void!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the genuine article. ...Zak was alive when he wrote this. Both myself and the notary can testify to this.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Unh.................. Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Why... Why does Fate toy with me so!? Why must my life be lived in thrall to the dead!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You're not the only one with that problem.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">But he shot Magnifi! Yes! It was Zak! It was! And then he left... and my career as a magician fell into darkness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you think there might be some way out of it? Say, if you could prove Zak Gramarye shot Magnifi? Was that why you testified?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes! My way out... It should have been my way out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it might not be too late, Mr. Valant. All you need is a way to prove your case. Who really killed Magnifi Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Valant">So this is the evidence that answers the question, "Who killed Magnifi?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The only question that this evidence can answer is, "Who here is an idiot?" And it answers, "You," Mr. Wright. Must I suffer such indignities even now? Ah, the life of a magician is a life of toil.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's one easy way to win over public opinion... By producing a signed confession... even if the confession is a fake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe I have the answer to your prayers right here. Zak Gramarye wrote one more thing before passing on.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">This... But this is a confession!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In which he admits to the killing of Magnifi Gramarye. ...See? All according to your plan.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... I am... a magician by trade. Deception is my life's work. I fool the audience, give them a fleeting dream... ...... Yet, it seems the tables have turned. Now I am the audience, believing in the deceptions I have wrought upon myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak wrote this right in front of me. ...After I explained your situation to him.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Allaka... Allakazooooooooooooomg!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...You do know that this "confession" is nothing but lies?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. It's my opinion that Zak Gramarye killed no one.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Then you must be thinking the truth is a simple matter of elimination. Two received instructions to kill, but if one is innocent? Then the one who remains is guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That would be the logical conclusion, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">So he vanished to protect me, his partner... Ha ha ha ha ha ha!!! A stirring tale, 'tis true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you shoot Magnifi Gramarye in the forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...If I had, and I told you, what would you do? Run to the police, perchance? ...Do as you will. There is nothing left for me now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...It is true, after all. I have little talent. I needed my mentor Magnifi's repertoire. ...It was, as if a little demon grabbed hold of me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it... So Valant Gramarye did kill the Great Magnifi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Heh. Heh heh heh... ...Ha ha ha ha ha!!! So sorry, Mr. Wright. But it was not I who shot my mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? But if it wasn't you, then who was it!? There wasn't another disciple, was there!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Another disciple... Such as...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... "Knack &amp; Talent Gramarye", maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Your wild fancies couldn't be further from the truth! Only Zak and Valant received those threatening letters. But, there was another. One more person could have fired that pistol that night. ...I don't suppose you've figured it out by now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If it wasn't Zak or Valant who shot Magnifi... ...then it had to be the only other person at the scene, which means...</thought> W-Wait... You don't mean...!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Yes. The Great Magnifi Gramarye himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Magnifi Gramarye... committed suicide?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...You find it hard to believe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest, I hadn't even imagined it as a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">When I arrived that night, the old man was still alive. He appeared to be asleep. I... I could not shoot him. But when I turned and made to leave the room... ...the old man called out to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...So you spoke with Magnifi Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. And this is why I knew what he had done. Magnifi transferred the rights to his repertoire to my partner, Zak Gramarye. Not me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Then I guess I owe you an apology. I always thought you were the one who did it.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... You owe me no apology.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">My crime was, in a way, more serious than that of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What!? Your "crime"...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is Valant Gramarye confessing something to me...? What could be more serious than murder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">You see... I knew that two letters had been sent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">There are no secrets between partners. It was easy to find out. ...That was when I understood Magnifi's plan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wanted to die by one of your hands...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Little did I expect it had anything to do with the rights to his repertoire! That was when I heard it... ...the little demon whispering inside my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The demon...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Let me confess: I had intended to shoot Magnifi. And... I planned on framing my partner for the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha... Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">That night, I prepared something before going to Magnifi's hospital room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which was...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">IV fluid, of course. I'd seen it on an earlier visit. If Zak did not shoot, I would do the deed! Then, I would use the IV liquid to place the murder on his hands. That was my plan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... you didn't shoot him.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... I could not. The demon in my heart fled when the moment came. But then Magnifi called me back.</line>
<line speaker="Magnifi">...I am sorry, Valant. ...I am giving my magic to Zak... not you... ...You still lack the draw he has... ...Please, help him, if you can...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I left the room... ...and then I stopped. The shock of what I had just been told consumed me. That is when I heard that fateful gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Magnifi Gramarye... killing himself.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Then, the demon awoke anew within me! ...Zak killed him, he was the one... ...Frame him, and the magic will be yours... I... altered the scene of his suicide. I took the pistol from his hand, wiped off the prints... ...then I used the syringe to add the IV liquid I'd brought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So in the end, things happened pretty much as planned. Magnifi died, and you framed Zak for his murder.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... "As planned", indeed. Of course, the outcome was somewhat different than I had anticipated.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... That was seven years ago. I don't know what to believe. But...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad I heard it from you, Mr. Valant. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...It is I who should be thanking you, Mr. Wright. Only when I had lost everything could I make my decision...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You're going to turn yourself in?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">My partner may have vanished, but not so my guilt. And as my guilt stays, all else begins to leave me. My friends... my performance rights... my magic. I've had enough of vanishing acts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I thought my life was ruled by a dead man... ...but I find I was wrong. For Zak Gramarye was alive...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, not anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...... And now, it occurs to me: What if he was not the only one who survived?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You see, now that I think about it... ...I realize that I, no... we never saw proof of her demise. We never saw her body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, "her"...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...The mind races and the mouth flaps on. My apologies. Forget this matter. I can only hope that the day will come when I again meet my partner, Zak Gramarye. Then... I shall apologize for my terrible mistake. I am glad we had this chance to talk... Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Zak Gramarye... "Shadi Smith". Whichever name you prefer... he is no longer with us. The truth revealed in that trial was only a sliver... ...and the impenetrable darkness that remained has taken another life. I knew what I'd have to do to push back the darkness for good. And it would involve paying that man a visit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Do you know when he'll be finished?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Ah, erm, well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Could you go find out?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Ah... Certainly, sir. Please wait here a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My apologies to the guard... But there's something I need to see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently, Gavin brought everything in here with him when he came. All the things in here are more valuable than what I have in my office. ...I'll admit I'm a bit jealous. But I shouldn't be... I mean it's still a prison.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That chair is just screaming to be sat in. And if I sat... I'd probably fall asleep. ...And have very expensive dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My knowledge of flower names includes sunflowers, tulips, and that's about it. ...Or so I always thought, but now I see I was wrong! I know that this is a rose! ...I think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...There it is. The yellow envelope! And the sender is... Drew Misham! I was right!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">When I arrived at the studio, Mr. Misham was at his desk. He seemed to be writing a letter... but he quickly sealed the envelope. It was a yellow envelope. ...I heard it was left at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If this is the last letter that Drew Misham wrote... ...then there's something I need to do. ...The last thing I need to do, in fact. ...Here goes! Let's see if this atroquinine spray finds anything...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this was Drew Misham's "messenger of death". It was this stamp alright! No mistaking it! And his last letter... was sent to Kristoph Gavin. Gotcha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Finally... decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no mistaking it. This commemorative stamp was the one on the desk at Drew Studio. ...Which makes this the letter he mailed just before he died. Better hold on to this one.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...What's this? A burglar... in jail?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I didn't know you moonlighted in larceny, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gavin... There's something I have to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">"Can I steal your stuff"? The answer is "no". My apologies, but there's not much I care to discuss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Vera Misham hasn't received her verdict yet. ...You follow me, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There are no known survivors of atroquinine poisoning. But it never hurts to hope.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...OK, I'll be leaving now, then.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wright. Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Would you mind leaving that letter? ...It's private.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, sorry. Forgot I had it.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Many thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We've now seen all the clues in this case. Clues I gathered over seven long years. Now, it is time. Every story has an ending. We've come to the final chapter, the final trial. Find the truth. You're the only ones who can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I may not have enough evidence right now to pull this off. Maybe it's time to do a little more legwork.</thought></line>
</xml>