<xml>
<title>Turnabout Airlines</title>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, so this is the cargo hold, huh!? It's so biiiiiiiig!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This plane is a special model. It has both a super-large cargo hold and ultra-luxurious First Class seating.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So is this the real scene of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is certainly a high probability of that, which is why we are here, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! Let's get investigating, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we can safely conclude that these fragments are from a pair of glasses.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And the victim was waering a pair of broken glasses!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly what I was thinking. I'm sure that the shards would match up perfectly with the remnants of his glasses' lenses. Ergo, the victim was here, just as I suspected.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you're saying... ...that the real scene of the crime was here, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't that what I've been saying for a while now!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, is it? I didn't know that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps it's a bit early to draw that conclusion? ...however, I believe that the probability has just skyrocketed considerably. All that's left is to find the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, why would Mr. Hicks have documents profiling Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I know! I bet he's a big fan of Ms. von Karma, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska said that she had come to this airport as part of an Interpol investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! Maybe Mr. Hicks had heard she was coming here and he followed her...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, I think it's more likely that Mr. Hicks was, in actuality, Interpol Agent Hicks. I think Franziska has some explaining to do.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This cargo hold is really big! I can't believe they can fit stuff like that in here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective! What are you going on about!? We're in the middle of an investigation here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whooooa! Stuff's falling on me! Ho ho, I can't get really into my work without something like this happening first. Well, let's get this show on the road! So, which item do you wanna start on!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In this world, there are those who are masochistic, and then there is Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So that flight attendant... Rhoda Teneiro... She's the killer, isn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think we can say for sure yet. But there certainly are a great number of things pointing us in that direction.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean like how she didn't tell us about her buying her own suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, however, in regard to the keycard being stolen... ...I can't seem to find any evidence that she's lying about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I just love pushing the buttons on elevators and crosswalk signals! Here, you should give it a try, sir! Go on, push it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The elevator is currently stopped on the first floor, Detective. It can't move.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah... I guess nothing would happen if you pushed it now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, nothing would happen normally anyway without the special keycard. <thought>Both the door to the attendants' room and the elevator's control panels... ...require a keycard, which makes it impossible for a passenger to come down here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All sorts of boxes are piled up here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This one says "FLAMMABLE", and this one... it says "PHARMACEUTICALS"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...This one says for "FOR EXORCISM USE ONLY"... <thought>Just what kind of operation is this airline running!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you noticed anything strange happening around here?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">No, sir! I haven't noticed a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm not sure that he meant to sound so oblivious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You arrived at the scene of the crime before Detective Gumshoe, correct? And you then immediately began to direct the investigation. It seems to me that you were already here at this airport for something besides this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............Yes, I was.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I've been following a very large and involved govermental-level international crime. But it's much too large for one person to take on alone. So it was decided that I should form a joint investigation with Interpol <thought>Interpol - Franziska came to this airport as an Interpol liaison.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Interpol is involved...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's a top-secret operation, so I really can't tell you any more than I already have.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You came to this airport to rendezvous with the victim, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Nonsense! What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We found a profile detailing information about you in the victim's luggage. I suppose it was prepared for him so that he could recognize you when he landed. Which makes him not Mr. Hicks, but rather, Interpol Agent Hicks. Isn't that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I should've known you'd figure it out, Miles. But it looks like they got to him first.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you really did come here to receive an Interpol agent, then?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes... Agent Hicks was on the trail of a very large international smuggling ring <thought>Smuggling - Agent Hicks was on the trail of an international smuggling ring.</thought>. He went undercover to investigate this crime. And it was I who put him on this case. I was supposed to receive a call from him on his cell phone once he had landed. ...I never expected to receive a call about his murder instead.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's the victim... It's infuriating to see him crumpled on the floor like that, lifeless. I will catch the one who did this to him myself! i swear it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Franziska is really worked up over the victim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you think about this piggy bank, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What do I think? What else is there to think but that it's the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I meant, what do you think about the Mr. Ifly itself?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's a crude rendition of a genus of primates commonly referred to as "slow lorises". "Loris" comes from the Dutch word of "simpleton", which is extremely fitting, because... ...that's exactly what Mr. Ifly represents, the guilty simpleton I'm going to arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't suppose she's capable of giving a more "normal" answer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There's something much more urgent we should be dealing with right now. Don't waste my time or yours.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, what's with the suitcase, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">It's what the victim checked-in, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this suitcase belonged to Mr. Hicks... I don't think he'd mind if we took a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's nothing out of the ordinary in here, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait. A file?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And there's a photo of Ms. von Karma in it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like a profile on Franziska <thought>Profile on Franziska - Why did Mr. Hicks have documents on Franziska in his possession?</thought>... Why would Mr. Hicks have had a file on her...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Holy suitcases, Mr. Edgeworth! It's like an all-you-can-use suitcase fair!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These must be all the left-over ones they couldn't sell. <thought>The ones the company is planning to dispose of after this flight is over...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This paint job is really cool, don't you think!? It practically screams "ARTSY!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Why not purchase one, then? I'm sure it will bring you much happiness.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You think so!? Then maybe I will! Let's see here... ...TWELVE HUNDRED DOLLARS!? .........I think I'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And Ms. Teneiro wonders why they don't sell, You'd need two jobs just to buy one. ...Hmm, it definitely looks like one is missing. Hm? What is this brittle substance I'm stepping on?</thought> It's a bunch of... glass fragments <thought>Glass shards - What are these glass shards from?</thought>...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't know that this plane was capable of carrying such large pieces of cargo. This thing's as tall as two of you on top of each other, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would probably take 20 of you to cover the entire surface of this monstrosity.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What, really!? Hmm... Yeah, I guess that sounds about right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's really no need to take that throwaway estimate seriously, Detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Keeping track of this many pieces of cargo must be very taxing on the cargo crew.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This sure brings back memories of when I worked as a part-time mover, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>By the looks in his eyes, he's waiting for me to ask about the rest of the story... ...but no matter how he pours on the puppy eyes, I have no intention of doing so.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we now have pretty definitive evidence... ...that Agent Hicks came down here to the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But what was he doing down here, sir? There's nothing but luggage! Oh, I get it! Maybe he forgot something in his suitcase, and came down to get it! Owwwww!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Hicks came here for a work-related reason. Of that I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'm sure he was here to investigate the smuggling operation he was observing. Franziska, do you know exactly how he intended to pursue his investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No. Unfortunately, I was going to find out from him after he landed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... But this raises another question. A normal passenger can't access the cargo hold on their own.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Hicks must have identified himself to a member of the crew... ...and entered the cargo hold with that person who let him in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and then he was murdered here... These glass fragments and his broken glasses are a testament to that. And then...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The killer put Agent Hicks into one of the spare suitcases and...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...They entered the elevator, But while they were riding it up... ...the plane hit that patch of turbulence. Because of the intense shaking, the suitcase popped open, and Agent Hicks's body flew out. At the same time, his wallet fell out of his pocket, spilling its contents everywhere. Which explains why there was money scattered all over the elevator floor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I think it's pretty easy to say who the culprit is at this stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Really, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I know what you're thinking, Miles Edgeworth. But the killer can be none other than Ms. Rhoda Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If it was a crew member, any one of them could've shown Agent Hicks to the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know what she's trying to say, but I'm not certain it's as simple as that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If it was a crew member, any one of them could've shown Agent Hicks to the cargo hold.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That might be true, but then, it could be anyone, including Ms. Meele or even the captain.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't be a fool! A plane without a pilot in the cockpit is like... ...a horse without a rider, crop in hand! Much like Scruffy over there!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Heeeeeeeeeigh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't disagree with her on that. Detective Gumshoe does always need a guiding hand.</thought> Very well, then what about the other flight attendant, Ms. Meele?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah, I thought you might ask about her.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But the point to keep in mind is the keycard that allows the elevator to come down here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But it's highly likely that the keycard was stolen from Ms. Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"It's highly likely"...? Is that "possibility" the best you can come up with? And you call yourself a disciple of my father!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnrgh! Yes, well... While I don't have any evidence, I...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Be quiet! You're a disgrace! There's more evidence pointing to Ms. Rhoda Teneiro, you know! It's not just the keycard that gives her away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you talking about the murder weapon, the Mr. Ifly piggy bank?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes! She is also the only person with a key to open that display case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Adds statement">"Further, there is the matter of the key to the display case that held the murderous bank."</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Further, there is the matter of the key to the display case that held the murderous bank.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The only person with such high-level access is Ms. Rhoda Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would such important things, like the keycard, be entrusted to only one person?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">According to Cammy Meele, Rhoda Teneiro is in charge of most of the "important stuff".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then what exactly is Ms. Meele in charge of?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Chatting it up with that foolish captain, apparently. She was being so foolishly foolish that I didn't want to ask what her other duties were!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah! I understand how you feel, but whipping me just now was uncalled for!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In the end, the only one who could've let Agent Hicks into the hold was Rhoda Teneiro.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'd say that's a pretty decisive piece of information, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Decisive...? Do you really think it's that strong?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There is no room for doubt! All of the other evidence points to her as well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No snappy comeback? That's as it should be.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Tch... There's not a single flaw in Franziska's reasoning. However, there must be something I can work with that I can draw out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that is a fake...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Stop right there, Miles Edgeworth! You don't have any proof that this is just a red herring! If you must keep on insisting that it's a fake... ...then what is the real murder weapon and where did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Speechless, I see. That's not a surprise. After all, you know that we've searched the entire cargo hold and came up empty-handed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must be a way... There must be something that can help me rule out the piggy bank as the murder weapon... What should be examined further to help us ascertain the authenticity of the weapon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should examine the bank itself once more to determine if it is the real murder weapon. If this is the real weapon, it should be damaged or perhaps have a dent on it somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We've looked into that already and there is no sign of anything on it. But we can't discount it as the murder weapon on that one fact alone. The piggy bank is, after all, made of a stronger material than human flesh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh... <thought>If I can't prove it through the piggy bank itself, then I must find another way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we should examine the crime scene in more detail. We might turn up the murder weapon if we search all of the cargo and luggage.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Did you think I hadn't thought of that? Even now, we're searching through them. But we haven't found anything that even closely resembles a murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk... Alright then. I suppose we should examine something else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I think you were too quick to jump to your conclusions.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh, was I!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. We don't even have the autopsy results yet. How can I not say that you made a snap judgement when you have yet to even see... ...if the wound on Agent Hicks's head is consistent with the "murder weapon"?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......... Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Contact the medical examiner's office at once! I wish to hear the results of Agent Hicks's autopsy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeek! Yes, siiiiiir!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-We've got a big problem, Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're still doing the autopsy, but they said that they already know this one thing for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Report! Now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The doc said that it's one giant bruise from a beating from his shoulder down to his mid-back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From the victim's shoulder to his mid-back? He was beaten over such a wide area?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'd say maybe it's a sign the killer had a grudge against Agent Hicks! It wasn't just his head; the killer went all out and hit him multiple times, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Scruffy! What is "had a grudge against Agent Hicks" supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... Well, that's... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was the wound on the victim's head consistent with the murder weapon, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, well, they said they were still looking into that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............You're completely useless!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeeooooooooowwwww!!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir, I told you already! You can't go down there!</line>
<line speaker="???">No, you remove yourself from my way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is all that racket?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">My luggage! My cargo! They're mine, and I demand you return them to me!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">We're still investigating the cargo hold! Please understand and have a little patience!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">...I suppose there is no choice...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Finally... I think he gav... Hey! What are you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You have left me no choice but to use strong force! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaarrrrrrrrr!!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Y-You won't get past me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is...! Wait, that's it! So that's what this whole thing has been about!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Further, there is the matter of the key to the display case that held the murderous bank <thought>Mr. Ifly piggy bank - Is there some way for me to prove that this isn't the real murder weapon?</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After all, you know that we've searched the entire cargo hold and came up empty-handed <thought>Weapon couldn't be found - Nobody could find anything that could be considered the real weapon in the hold.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The doc said that it's one giant bruise from a beating from his shoulder down to his mid-back <thought>Cause of death - Extensive bruising from back of head down to mid-back, as if severely beaten.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Already, the killer struck the victim many times over... ...which is why there is extensive bruising over such a wide area. ...But is that really the correct conclusion to draw from the evidence? The bruise from his shoulder to the middle of his back is one continuous mark... ...which is more suggestive of a single blow to the back. If that's the case, then the piggy back is much too small to have caused that. Therefore, the murder weapon must be something far bigger (A sizable weapon - The unusually large area of bruising suggests that a very large weapon was used!</thought>!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If we're looking for a rather large weapon, you'd think it would stick out... But so far, we haven't found anything that resembles a weapon of any sort. Perhaps... Just perhaps, it's something we all overlooked from the very beginning. ...because normally, it's too impossibly big to be taken into consideration!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What was that all about!? Was he trying to jump his way down here!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What!? What do you want!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I found it, Franziska... I found the real murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Y-You did!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He... He really jumped!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We didn't realize it until now, but... ...the answer has been right in front of us this whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He might be hurt! We should go check up on him, sirs!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There's that pompous attitude of yours again. You should learn to drop that habit.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This coming from a prosecutor with a habit of whipping everyone she comes across...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Anyway, if you really are a prosecutor, then you'll back yourself up with evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...You two aren't listening at all, are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Come on then, show me this "real murder weapon" you speak of!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the real murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As we have thought all along, the real murder weapon is probably this piggy bank.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How easily you flip-flop on your own opinions. Perhaps you should flip-flop with Scruffy there and trade jobs. I'm sure he'd like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......You must be joking! <thought>I can't believe I showed her the fake murder weapon!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real weapon is... this suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">When you say it with such confidence, I suppose you must have some evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. Agent Hicks was placed into this suitcase alive. And it was while he was in here that he was beaten in the head and ba...aaackngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder if you would die if I whipped you from head to toe right now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What are you thinking, woman!? Of course I would!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have concluded... that this is the real weapon, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What is that supposed to mean, you fool!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That... was practice just now for when I would show you the real murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Why don't we add "practice whippings" to your routine as well?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaaargnnn!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I need to think about the circumstances of the victim's death in a different way. There's a wide bruise running from the victim's shoulder down to his mid-back. Maybe I should be focusing on what could cause such a large bruise in one strike...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I don't have any evidence to show you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Foolish reasoning for a foolish fool from a foolishly foolish fool meant to fool me... What do you mean by "I don't have any evidence to show"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps I should've phrased it as "that which caused Agent Hicks's death is incorporeal". Forgive me, but I do believe I have figured out what was the real cause of death!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim suffered from a lack of oxygen in the elevator and suffocated!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-And... ...the bruising on his back and his broken neck was caused by his sudden fall to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...You are like a fly buzzing in my ear. Be gone!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaargn!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aw, that wasn't such a bad guess, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Without a shred of proof, did he just accuse me of making a good "guess"...? Wait... But he did imply I was on the right track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim was strangled to death inside the elevator! But there are no marks on his neck because... the killer found a way to hide them somehow. A-And... ...the bruising on his back and his broken neck was caused by his sudden fall to the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Care to explain how the killer magically erased strangulation marks from around his neck!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.................. In that case, please allow me to demonstrate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's going to leave a mark!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aw, that wasn't such a bad guess, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Without a shred of proof, did he just accuse me of making a good "guess"...? Wait... But he did imply I was on the right track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim fell from a great height and subsequently died as a result. In other words, the real cause of death is free-falling to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He f...f...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Fell to his death!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes... This is the only plausible possibility!</thought> The victim has extensive bruising on the back of his head and his back. And the only rational explanation for these injuries is that he fell to his death!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">B-But the murder happened inside this plane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you claiming that there is someplace in this plane from which he could've fallen from!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I said earlier, the answer has been right in front of us the entire time!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You... You can't mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I do. The victim fell from the top of the stairs of this very cargo hold!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaaat!? Then... Then... W-We're in trouble! We may have a second death on our hands, sirs! Hey, you! Tell me you aren't dead, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Quiet! Why are you screaming!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">! He's alive!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And there you have it, Miles Edgeworth! It's not possible that Agent Hicks fell over the railing to his death. That man is living proof of that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I suppose it's true that it's not possible... given the current circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The "current" circumstances? What is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Suppose that large piece of cargo wasn't there at the time. What would've happened then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He would've been a Borginian pancake for sure, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose that man over there wouldn't still be breathing... But the reality is that the cargo box is there! So there is no point in entertaining your wild hypothetical scenarios!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It may be there now... but there is no proof that it was always there!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah! As if there could've been a window of time when that giant box was not there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but there was.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What can I use to show her that it's possible the box was not always where it is now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doesn't this show sufficient probability to you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-Why are you asking me!? I was the one asking you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I think there's some possibility in that, siiiiiiiiiiiir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No one was asking for opinions from the instant noodle crowd, Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose this is where the phrase "to be whipped by one's opponent" came from.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't act as though you have nothing to do with this! Now answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose she's right. But first, I should reconsider all of the information I have.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You refueled in the Republic of Zheng Fa...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this flight had a short layover in Zheng Fa in order to refuel. But that wasn't the only reason for the layover. We also transferred some cargo. What if the box in question was only transferred onto the plane at that time? To further prove my point, let's take a look at what's next to the box in question.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! It's labeled "Zheng Fa Express"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. Meaning it was loaded onto the plane in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, what if the box in question was also loaded on at the same time?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It would mean that the box... ...was not here in the cargo hold during the Europe - Zheng Fa leg of the flight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Making a clear drop from which Agent Hicks could've fallen to his death entirely possible!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ah, but your theory is still very far-fetched.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then allow me a chance to prove how very likely my scenario is. <thought>My first order of business will be to examine that piece of cargo in more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Man... I can't believe Mr. Hicks fell to his death. I never would have guessed in a million years!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is still only a hypothesis, however, the investigation should prove it to be true.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Speaking of falling, I'm glad that art guy's OK! He took quite the spill!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he was lucky to have landed on top of that piece of cargo.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I can just see it now. "Passenger Pays Price for Police Foul Up! Did Prosecutor Edgeworth add fuel to the fire of the first murder with a second death!?" Yup, I'm willing to bet that it'd make the front page!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........! <thought>That's not funny, Detective!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you spot anything off, you come and tell me right away, OK, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Roger, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's rather unusual for Gumshoe to be so directing. He must outrank this officer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you run into any trouble, you just leave it up to me, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, sir...! Ah! Watch out, Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owwwwwwwwwww!!!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Scruffy! I think your ego is in need of some deflating.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I was following in your footsteps, sir... I wanna try patronizing my subordinates.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Cruel and unforgiving to the Detective, even in front of his own subordinate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I may have a word with you, Franziska...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't think you have the time for idle chatter. You still need to prove to me that your hypothetical situation is, in fact, really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So Mr. Hicks was actually an Interpol agent...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That is so cool! I can't believe he was from Interpol! The adventure! The glamour! And the miraculous big escape when you get caught by the enemy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Except, in this case, there was no big escape.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...And no miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The left-over suitcases sit here, lined up in two pretty, neat rows. Too bad for Ms. Teneiro, but this design is unmarketable.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd buy one if it was cheaper, sir! Do you think they'd sell it to me at a discount? Oh! Or! Why don't they sell them in the airport and have a bargain basement sale!? "Buy one get one free! If you win the raffle, you get one more for free!" How about those ideas, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think if they did that, everyone would lose.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Borginise speaking! Borginise speaking! Borginise speaking?!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">You can rant at me in Borginian all you want, but no still means no, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What!? You cheap man! You are only waiting for me to give you money, yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This guy is really pushy... I wonder if he really makes any sales this way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As long as I never have to face him in court, he can be as pushy as he wants.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... This is a rather large piece of cargo.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a tag on it, sir... Let's see... "Alif Red Statue"...? Never heard of it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nor I, but all I care about is if we can prove it wasn't here at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then let's get investigating, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Borginise speaking! Borginise speaking! Look here! Do not go about touching my possessions without my permission!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaack! D-Don't rush up on me like that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this belongs to Mr. Lablanc, does it? I should see what else I can find out from him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If Mr. Lablanc has something to do with the smuggling ring... ...then it's possible this fake statue was brought onboard in Zheng Fa! I think I need to question him a bit further.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What exactly is an "extremely valuable piece of art", sir? It is like the stiff you see at country fairs?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Somehow, I get the impression that it's worth a lot more than you can comprehend.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So this thing is worth more than I can imagine, huh. Whoooooooooop! It kinda makes me wanna try collection expensive art!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Collecting expensive art...? Hmm... Interesting. It seems there are people out there besides Mr. Lablanc who know the true value of art.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? ...Are you talking about me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course not! Where did you get an idea like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phoo-whee! I thought something smelled fishy in here! Turns out it's a smuggling ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If a smuggling ring is involved in this case... ...then their target would most definitely be the most valuable piece of art.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And that'd be the two statues on either side of the elevator, right, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I doubt those ghastly things are worth anything to anyone other than the person depicted.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good job, officer. Mr. Lablanc is certainly not an easy person to hold back.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">No thanks necessary, sir! It's all part of the job... even if he did eventually get by...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I have a few things to ask him anyway, so it worked out in your favor this time.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Thank you very much, sir! Next time, I'll be sure to not let anyone through... ...even if it takes my life in the process, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I appreciate the sentiment, however, we can't have people getting hurt on the job either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I take it that this large piece of cargo belongs to you, Mr. Lablanc?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Of course it is mine! I shipped this fine piece of art from Europe! This "Alif Red Statue" is worth 10 million cents! No! Maybe much, much more!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Mr. Lablanc's reason for choosing this plane must've been the large cargo hold.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ten million cents...? </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suggest you stop trying to calculate how many packets of noodles that makes, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Darn... How did you do that!? I feel like you getting better and better at seeing right through me every year!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Though I grow with each revolution of the planet around the sun... ...I have the distinct impression he continues to madly spin in place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth... So that 10 million cents... Is that in Euros or in Dollars?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Does it really make a difference to our case!? Mr. Lablanc, there is a chance that your cargo is related to our murder case. I was wondering if you would allow us to examine it a bit closer.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">It is a very valuable piece of art <thought>Valuable piece of art - Mr. Lablanc claims to have brought a piece of art from Europe, but...</thought>! So, no! There will be no touching!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What a waste! How horrible to see a priceless piece of cloth soiled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I assure you it wasn't me! I believe it to be the work of the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I will teach that killer a lesson! You can be sure I will! It will be the "Lablanc Revolution"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think he meant the "Lablanc Retribution", but either way, it sounds intimidating.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Why do you show me something of no value!? "Show me the bread" first and maybe we will talk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait, he wants me to pay him before he'll comment on this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Look here! Do not go about touching my possessions without my permission!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose I have to first appease Mr. Lablanc if I want to examine this in more detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About your statue, Mr. Lablanc... ...I wonder if it might be a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Wh-What!? How dare you say my art is fake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspect that your statue... might be the target of an international smuggling ring.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Don't say such fantasical things! Those thieves would not dare! I have the certification of my cargo right here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do you mean the Cargo Certification document? Mr. Zinc Lablanc! Why didn't you say so earlier!? Please show it to us at once! ......... I can't read this! What does it say!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">It says as plain as day "the cargo was put onto the plane in Europe"!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And there you have it, Miles Edgeworth. Too bad for you... ...this statue was brought onboard in Europe, just as it states in this certificate.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Which means that there never was a window of time in which the statue wasn't sitting there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ I respectfully disagree. We can't discount the theory until I see the statue for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmph! Then you can have your wish! Look at it yourself and see I am right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This...! I know I've seen this somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the "Alif Red"!? It gives off such a feeling of ART! I can practically smell it!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">This statue has a high amount of historic value! After it was unveiled at a museum in Europe... ...I brought it to this country to exhibit it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I believe a closer look is warranted here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">I grant you permission to look, but if you make tiny, single fingerprint... ...I will make you pay 10 million cents!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't that the value of the statue itself!?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Of course! It is the price of my very valuable time and the loaning of my statue! Now you wasted another minute! That will make your bill 11 million cents now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ack! I'm going to have to conduct this examination with even greater haste!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What have we here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It says "Zheng Fa Express" on the cloth, sir! I'm gonna take a guess and say that this delivery company is based in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, then we can assume this was loaded onto the plane in Zheng Fa. <thought>Something is tugging on the corner of my mind... as though something is out of place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this is the Alif Red statue... I swear I've seen this somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No wonder this thing is worth 10 million cents! Look at how it sparkles, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wouldn't call it "sparkling", Detective... Maybe more along the lines of... "dully shining".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this Alif Red is a fake...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That art dealer isn't looking too happy about it either, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I will get to the bottom of this, for his sake as well as mine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this statue was brought onboard in Zheng Fa...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Which means it's a fake, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and there is still one last contradiction to resolve here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As unobservant as ever, I see. Take a good look at the evidence and it'll come to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are these eyes made of some sort of gem...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's a real nice shade of orange! For a sec, I couldn't even tell they were jewels! Oh, but they kinda remind me of the eyes of this stray cat that lives near my house!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Are the eyes supposed to be this color...? Is it possible this statue... is a fake...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe you were able to tell this was a fake from a single glance, sir! You knew right away that its eyes were a different color than the ones in the photo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, unlike a certain Detective who needs to try a little harder... <thought>The fact that this is a fake means it was swapped with the real one at some point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These eyes are awfully orange, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, and pretty! They remind me of sunsets when I was in grade school, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I don't think you see what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, I do. But it's really like the color of the sun when it's setting, sir! Ah, the memories... I remember standing out in that field, spinning with my arms out until I felt ill...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't care about sunsets! Focus, Detective! What color are the eyes in this photo!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Huh!? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Sir! They're red!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I thought... This statue is a fake. Mr. Lablanc.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What do you want!? Do you not know I am a busy man!? I allow you two seconds for your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Alif Red... I suppose this is your pride and joy, is it not?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">It is the biggest trophy on this European trip! Do you know why I wanted to possess this statue? The trigger started 17 years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Better grab a chair, sir. Sounds like this is gonna be a long story...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Lablanc, I regret to inform you, and you have my heartfelt sympathy, but...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">What is that? Sympathy? For what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You'll see. I'd like you to compare the eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">...That large fellow there has very bright and pretty eyes compared to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wasn't talking about the two of us! I meant the eyes of the statue in front of us and the one in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Why the sudden yelling!? Now then... Ohhh! It is a photo of the statue on display at the museum in Europe! ............Nnwwwhaaaaaaah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now do you see, Mr. Lablanc? The statue before us is a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">A...A faaaaaaaaaaaaaaaake!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that even further examination will be required... ...now that we have confirmed that this is indeed a fake. There must be some sort of proof that this was brought onboard in Zheng Fa. And I will present to you evidence that will resolve the remaining contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not entirely confident that there is a contradiction here... What do you think, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I think it's really suspicious-looking, sir! My well-trained gut tells me so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............I see. Well then, I must be mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How come when I answer confidently, you take that to mean we're off course, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The statue looks like it's stepping all over its neighbor's cloth cover. It kinda resembles its owner's attitude in a sense, ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You! What did you said now!? Further, my clothing's hem is not being stepped on by anyone! It is too expensive for me to allow that to happen!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please forgive the trespasses of my subordinate.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Why should I forgive if the dress passes!? Unless it is an expensive dress, you keep it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe you could spot a contradiction from a piece of cloth getting stuck!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">You two! Why do you continue talking about the hem of my clothing being stuck!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The fact that this was brought onboard in Zheng Fa... ...is going to bring many a tears to Mr. Lablanc's eyes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is clearly a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you going on about? It's just a simple case of a cargo getting stuck under another piece of cargo. ............ Ah! That's not possible...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But it is... It shouldn't be this way, but the statue is on top of the cloth. Supposing that the neighboring piece of cargo was brought onboard in Zheng Fa... ...there is no way that any part of it should wind up under something from Europe. Which means that this fake statue was smuggled onboard in Zheng Fa!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But then what about the cargo certificate!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me ask in return, what about Agent Hicks? Why did he come down here in the middle of the flight?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is only one reason why: to secure proof of smuggling activity aboard this flight.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So you say, but I don't believe he had to do that mid-flight. We could've just as easily inspected all of the cargo after the plane landed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That must be true, however, you have it backwards, Franziska. Sure, Agent Hicks could have waited until after the plane had landed... ...but he had a reason for coming down to the cargo hold. Suppose he had found the fake at the airport. It would've been after the swap had occurred. At that time, the suspicion would naturally fall onto the statue's owner... ...who would have no way to prove that the statue was switched without his knowledge. Which means there is someone involved who is forging or modifying cargo certificates.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that even further examination will be required... ...now that we have confirmed that this was brought onboard in Zheng Fa. There must be some sort of proof that this statue is indeed a fake. And I will present to you evidence that will resolve the remaining contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not entirely confident that there is a contradiction here... What do you think, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I think it's really suspicious-looking, sir! My well-trained gut tells me so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............I see. Well then, I must be mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How come when I answer confidently, you take that to mean we're off course, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What have we here...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It says "Zheng Fa Express" on the cloth, sir! I'm gonna take a guess and say that this delivery company is based in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, then we can assume this was loaded onto the plane in Zheng Fa. <thought>Something is tugging on the corner of my mind... as though something is out of place...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This statue's eyes look like they're made of a jewel-like stone.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Those gems sure are pretty! And look at that fiery orange color, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, according to Mr. Lablanc, this whole thing is worth a pretty penny.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I just got a really great idea! I can probably find some rocks down by the river I can polish up to look like real jewels! I think I'll try that out and give one to Maggey as a present next time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if he's serious... and I wonder if I should try to stop him if he is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The jewels in the eye sockets... They were made to look just like real gems.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you mean... these aren't real?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think the forgers would waste that kind of money on a replica?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess not... Ooh! I just got a really great idea! I can probably find some rocks down by the river I can polish up to look like real jewels! I think I'll try that out and give one to Maggey as a present next time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if he's serious... and I wonder if I should try to stop him if he is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess the victim knew the real version of this was gonna get nabbed, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. While this photo could be seen as nothing more than a simple souvenir... ...it was in fact taken to be used as a reference document later on. Next, Agent Hicks had to secure proof that the smuggling had taken place. He came down here to take a picture of the cargo hold... ...a rather empty one at that, right before the fake statue could be loaded onboard.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A photo of the hold missing a valuable piece of cargo would have been proof enough. After that, all he had to do was hold the Zheng Fa cargo crew and arrest the smuggler.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. This only goes to prove my theory. If the statue was not in the cargo hold during the Europe - Zheng Fa leg of the trip... ...there would've been enough height from which Agent Hicks could've fallen to his death!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Officer! Move this statue immediately! I want a thorough examination of the floor underneath. Now!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Ms. von Karma! I'm ready to report my findings.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">After moving the Alif Red statue out of the way... ...we tested the area under it with Luminol, and there was a reaction!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see, there was a reaction to Luminol... An indication that there was blood in that spot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nngh... Can we stop looking at it now, sirs...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would seem that my deductions were correct after all.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I suppose it would appear that way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The culprit cleaned the blood up well.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And how do you think the killer did that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How did the killer clean up all the blood?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would suppose that... perhaps the culprit used this... to clean up the blood.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There is no need for you to waste your breath if you're just going to waste my time. After all, I hate to waste my energy on wasteful whipping.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If it's that wasteful, then I'd rather that you didn't whip me at all! For the killer to clean up the blood, they would've needed something to soak it up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer used the bloody cloth I found inside the suitcase to clean up the mess.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see. They had a need to clean up all the blood before the plane landed in Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, because otherwise, the cargo crew would've discovered it during the layover.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So you guys are saying... ...that the murder happened before the plane landed in Zheng Fa!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is no other conceivable timeline for the events of the murder. But if that is true, then that throws a certain person's testimony into doubt!</thought> If the murder occurred before we landed in Zheng Fa, then this becomes highly suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro's testimony... is not particularly suspect, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, that's all well and good. Glad we agree.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............ No, that is not all well and good, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrgnnnh! <thought>I suppose there's no fooling her. The point to focus on is the fact that the crime occurred before we landed in Zheng Fa.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The times referenced by Mr. Lablanc in his testimony are inaccurate. However, I believe the actual body of his testimony is fairly reliable...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you sputtering on about over there!? Hurry up with your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-Hold on! I'm still collecting my thoughts! <thought>The point to focus on is the fact that the crime occurred before we landed in Zheng Fa.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Recall Ms. Meele's testimony about Agent Hicks in regard to when we departed Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I saw Mr. Hicks sitting in his seat at 5 AM, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She claims Agent Hicks was alive at the time of the service calls, but...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That totally contradicts the facts, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But why would she lie about something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think the only person who can answer that is Meele herself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you recall what you said earlier... ...about when you answered some service calls as we were departing from Zheng Fa?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said that Mr. Hicks was sitting in his seat at that time. However... that is simply not possible! Because Mr. Hicks was dead long before we ever touched down in Zheng Fa!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Cammy Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">......... Um... Maybe I didn't see what I thought I did?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No one could make a mistake so large, Ms. Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ummmmmm... But I make that kind of boo-boo all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This is going nowhere. There must be a better way of resolving this contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Ms. Meele, if you please, tell me about your alibi during the time span... ...from just before we were to land at 3 AM and 6 AM when the body was found.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.........Are you telling me I'm a suspect, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.....................Mnngh. Oh, um... yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How is a man supposed to react to a testimony like that...?</thought> Ms. Meele! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ah! ...............zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* She fell asleep again. It looks like the only way I'm going to be able to wake her up is by pressing her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">.....................Mnngh. Oh, um... yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yawn* I'm awake, I'm awake. ..................zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I demand that you do something about this flight attendant this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why ask me to wake her when you can finally put that whip to an appropiate use?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">From 3 to 4, I was, um... in the flight attendant's room all by my lonesome self.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I remember correctly, food was being served in First Class and the Lounge... ...between the hours of 3 and 4 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, but that kind of stuff's run by Ms. Rhoda.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then what were you doing in the attendants' room at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Eating, and then having a most delicious dream!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean you were neglecting your duties!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">No way! Sleeping's part of our job, too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.....................Mnngh. Oh, um... yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! How many times do I have to repeat myself!? Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yawn* I'm awake, I'm awake. ..................zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeowch!! Wh-What did you whip me for, siiir!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ooh, what did I miss?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A poor detective being on the receiving end of a lash in your stead.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Really? Heh, sorry 'bout that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can make amends for that by continuing with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">And from 5 to 6, I was, um... in the flight attendant's room all by my lonesome self.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were alone the entire time, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, no one else even popped their head in to say, "Hi!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Oh? Well, I think a contradiction just popped in to say, "Hi!" What should I do? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe not yet. She hasn't exactly given me much to object to, yet, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaawn* What did I miss?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! There is a clear contradiction embedded in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not possible that you were alone in the attendants' room the whole time from 5 to 6 AM!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now take a look at this eye-opening piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...............zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! I need you to wake up and take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Enough of your foolishness! Now hurry up and show us the real evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! I guess this wasn't as eye-opening as I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................Mnngh. Oh! Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Finally awake, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">What do you mean? I've been awake this whole time...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, it's alright if you were sleeping, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Pay no mind to the scruffy detective beside you, and wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaw! Hurry up and wake up, Ms. Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Enough with the clowning around. This is my show and I will resolve the contradictions as I see fit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if you would be so kind as to take a look at this receipt, Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? A receipt? For what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's for the suitcase Ms. Teneiro bought. Now, if I may direct your attention to the timestamp. As you can see, it clearly says 5:40 AM. Ms. Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? Why is the "killer" here? I thought you'd have her locked up by now...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I requested that she be present as a witness so that we may straighten out your complex lie.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Ms. Teneiro. Between the hours of 5 AM and 6 AM... ...you took a trip from First Class down to the first floor in-flight shop, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Yes, I went to the shop to buy a suitcase... ...after which, I went straight to the attendants' room to drop it off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And did you see Ms. Meele there at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">...Um, no.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, Ms. Meele, where were you really between the hours of 5 and 6 AM?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Cammy Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh!? Ah, um... The bathroom?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be the one to ask the questions here!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, maybe that's it. I probably just missed her. Nature calls, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you take me for a fool? That's a little too convenient to be true.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um... but it's the truth! Cross my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I don't have enough conclusive proof to counter-argue her at this stage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">You don't believe me, do you? But please, won't you give me a chance and hear me out?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Look, I know you're suspecting me 'cause I'm one of the crew.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please leave Ms. Teneiro out of the conversation. Only you are under suspicion for now.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I don't get it. Why are you covering for Ms. Rhoda all of a sudden? Oh! Now I get it! Maybe you've "got your eye" on Ms. Rhoda...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I'm keeping an eye on her! I can't very well let her escape, can I?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Never mind... But you wanna know something? Ms. Rhoda actually kinda li...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I have absolutely no interest in people who can't appreciate my sense of design!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>Now's not the time for this sort of talk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Look, I know you're suspecting me 'cause I'm one of the crew.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it's not the only reason I have for suspecting you. Your statements regarding Mr. Hicks also turned out to be a bunch of lies.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ah, but say I wasn't an attendant. You wouldn't suspect me then, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, yes... I suppose that's true enough.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">But you'd think then maybe you should suspect Ms. Rhoda, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She is already being detained for further questioning, or have you already forgotten?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, Yeah, guess I just forgot.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Cammy... Don't tell me you suspect me, too...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Sorry, can't help it. I mean, other than you, there's no one else who could've done it.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I can't believe you would think that! I mean, me! A killer...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele, what did you mean just now by "no one else who could've done it"?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">She's the one in charge of the elevator keycard and the shop, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what are you in charge of, Ms. Meele?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um... I take care of the attendants' room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That doesn't count!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aww, but I spend so much time in there, it might as well be my responsibility.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth, Cammy is very talented in languages... ...so she assists passengers who may not speak English. Especially those who speak Borginian. She is the only one on this flight who is fluent.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh! You mean that kind of "what am I in charge of"! Why didn't you say so in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What else could I have meant!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, so I'm really good at Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's fluent in Borginian...?</thought> Then I suppose you're in charge of processing documents in Borginian?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah, I take care of anything that has to do with Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Very interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Adds statement">"All I'm in charge of are the attendants' room and some Borginian stuff."</line>
<line speaker="Meele">If you ask me, that makes her super-suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, your on-the-job behavior makes you "super-suspicious" in my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Huh? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While Ms. Teneiro is busy with the passengers and all of her other duties... ...you have a lot of free time on your hands. Thus providing you with ample time to commit the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I demand that you cease and desist in this line of conjectural questioning. I won't allow you to bluff your way through this like a certain defense lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... But I do not honestly believe Ms. Meele does any actual work aboard this flight.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, that's not true, Mr. Edgeworth. Although... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">All I'm in charge of are the attendants' room and some Borginian stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what exactly do you do as the one in charge of "some Borginian stuff"?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Um, I do stuff like translate things from and into Borginian.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Cammy is the only member of the crew who understands Borginian, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele, I take it then that it is your job to process all the Borginian paperwork?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yeah. See, I toootally pull my weight around here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So it would appear. <thought>Perhaps I should ask her for a few more details about her work. And...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele, it's very unladylike to push suspicion onto someone else.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">That's not what I'm doing at all! I'm just saying that Ms. Rhoda is very sus...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There you go, pushing everything onto her again!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Umm.. I don't get what you're saying... It must be a really abstract concept, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. The only thing abstract here is the landscape inside your head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you are the only one in this flight crew that speaks Borginian... Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">............Oh! Yeah, I guess so. I studied abroad in Borginia for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that is the case, then the signature on this document... ...belongs to you, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a falsified piece of documentation with only one purpose. To lead anyone who read it to believe that Mr. Lablanc's statue was loaded in Europe. The only person who could've either prepared or processed this document in Borginian... ...is you, Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Without your participation, the smuggling of the Alif Red could not have occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't sleep while I'm pointing my finger at you!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh, I wouldn't dream of falling asleep on you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">It is exactly as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you confessing to having participated in the smuggling?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">No, far from it. It's true that I was the one who signed off on that document. But you can't use that fact alone to make your allegation of smuggling stick. There is no direct correlation, after all. All you have is my signature on a piece of paper.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really? All you did was sign it?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I neglected to check if the cargo had been loaded onto the plane properly. So, sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>It seems that she's finally woken up. This is going to be one tough fight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Suppose... And this is just a supposition... Even if I was involved in the smuggling... ...you can't throw the charge of murder on me just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you were involved in the smuggling, you would have a strong motive to kill! Agent Hicks was in the middle of an investigation regarding a smuggling ring. And just when he was about to close in, he's killed by a member of that ring...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Well, did you ever stop to think that maybe Rhoda is the smuggling ring member? After all, unlike me, Rhoda has access to many things on this plane for "work" purposes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. So perhaps there is some element of a set-up at play in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry, I wasn't talking about you. I meant the killer. First, it was myself, and now it's Ms. Teneiro who is under the microscope. Seems to me that our killer is going to great lengths to pin this crime on anyone they can.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You have no proof that Rhoda is being set-up, or that she isn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I believe that she was indeed the intended target from the very beginning. I believe that the plan was to push all of the blame for the crime onto her. And this evidence will prove my suspicions! This proves that the killer was out to frame Ms. Teneiro from the very beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence will answer all of our questions.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Are you sleep-presenting or something, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, as you can plainly see, I am wide awake.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ha ha ha, then I'm afraid you failed. You were making so little sense that I thought maybe you were asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argnh! Talk about a Dr. Sleepy/Mrs. Hyde-esque transformation! Is this it? But wasn't there a piece of evidence that's still unaccounted for...? I need to stay calm, think carefully, and then present the condemning evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer could have hidden the body anywhere, and yet they chose the suitcase. Why is that? Perhaps it was to move the body up from the lower deck to the first floor. However, why go through the trouble to do so?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only way all of these actions make sense... ...is if the killer had wanted to frame Ms. Teneiro for the murder. Ms. Teneiro buys a suitcase on every flight she works without fail. But, should her suitcase be switched with the one containing the victim's body... ...that would put her in a very tight spot. Unfortunately, for the killer, the turbulence put an end to that plan.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There wasn't enough time to put the body back into the suitcase. Ergo, they made due with whoever was at hand, adapted their plan... ...and tried to frame me, as I lay unconscious on the floor from the turbulence. The killer then went to hide the suitcase in the in-flight shop... ...and brought the piggy bank back to the elevator in order to fabricate a false weapon. A lot of work for a fruitless endeavor, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Sounds like the killer had a tough time, too, huh. I mean, why did the killer need to frame someone that badly anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is because of the special circumstances surrounding this particular case. <thought>What special circumstance dictated the need for the killer to frame someone?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder took place before the movie was scheduled to go on. Around that time, almost all of the passengers had returned to their seats. Therefore, the killer had to choose someone who was not at their seat to frame...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Isn't that an explanation for how the killer chose who, and not why they had to?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I thought it best to start from there.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">If you're going to talk about completely unrelated matters, do you mind if I take a nap?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-Hold on! I'm just getting to the meat of my argument!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer was at a loss of what to do with Agent Hicks's body. But, as it just so happened, there were a bunch of empty suitcases nearby. Being a skinny man, the killer thought to put his body in the suitcase and hand it off...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">You mean that the whole plan to frame someone was an elaborate coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, that's not what I said. You've wrongly deduced my meaning, Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The one with the wrong deductions is you! Think before you speak again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Patience, Franziska! I was about to reveal the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The special circumstance is simply that the murder took place on a plane mid-flight. No matter which country, customs is quite strict in this day and age... ...so no matter what you do, the chances that the body will be found is very high. Therefore, there was no choice but to frame either Ms. Teneiro or myself. In other words, the only one who fits within the boundaries of the criminal's movements... ...is not Ms. Teneiro or myself... ...but you, Ms. Cammy Meele! Only you and you alone could be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaawn*... And?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Are you done already? I was about to fall asleep again. Anyway, let's be honest here. You don't have anything on me other than a whole lot of circumstantial evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Nnnghk! <thought>I can see the outline of how the murder occurred, but I have no definitive evidence... And isn't there a piece of evidence that's still unaccounted for...? Something that I still can't quite fit into the big picture?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence will answer all of our questions.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Are you sleep-presenting or something, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, as you can plainly see, I am wide awake.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ha ha ha, then I'm afraid you failed. You were making so little sense that I thought maybe you were asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argnh! Talk about a Dr. Sleepy/Mrs. Hyde-esque transformation! Is this it? But wasn't there a piece of evidence that's still unaccounted for...? I need to stay calm, think carefully, and then present the condemning evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have any actual evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I thought not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that's because it went missing, and still is.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Missing...? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In the complex puzzle that is this case, there was one piece I kept getting stuck on. And that is the victim's cell phone. Franziska. You were waiting at the airport for a phone call from Agent Hicks's cell phone. Or at least, that's what you told me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But Agent Hicks's cell phone could not be found at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You mean, the killer took the phone with them!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. I suspect that if we were to find that phone, it would lead us to the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ha ha ha. Come on. Get serious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">If the victim fell to his death from that height, wouldn't his phone break as well?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We won't know that until we try a little experiment, will we? Franziska, I'd like to ask for your assistance. You know the victim's phone number, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course I do.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Agent Hicks's phone! It's ringing from somewhere, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I hear it, Detective. Now, where is it coming from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! It sounds like the cell phone's in the flight attendants' room, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. We should move to retrieve it at once!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>We've determind that the real crime scene is here. All that's left is to catch the killer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">......zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...Sorry, Mr. Edgeworth. I got sleepy all of a sudden because it sounds like a lullaby I used to love as a child.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nnrgh...! I'd better find that cell phone fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry, Ms. Teneiro. I will get to the bottom of this and find the truth. So please, wait here until I return.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Alright... Thank you for all you're doing, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It sounds like it's coming from the flight attendants' room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree. Please don't hang up just yet. Let me find it first.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's fine, but let's get one thing straight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't you dare answer his phone when you find it, understand?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I understand that you don't want to pay for the call...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The elevator is inoperable right now. The ringing is coming from the attendants' room. I'll have to use the stairs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like the phone is up in the flight attendants' room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We'd better hurry to the flight attendants' room, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The ringing's coming from somewhere in here, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Leave no stone unturned, Detective Gumshoe! We must find it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't seem like the phone got mixed in with the items in this lost and found pile.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it's not like the victim would've just dropped it somewhere, right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't seem to be over here...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then let's look somewhere else, sir!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the emergency control panel for the elevator. The switches are currently set to "1F Open". ...which means that right now, it's stopped on the first floor with its doors wide open.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The ringing is coming from somewhere around here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it's not here, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why do I have such a bad feeling about where we're going to find the phone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if it might be inside this suitcase...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't hear any sounds coming from inside, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't suppose the culprit would have been so dumb as to try the same trick twice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The ringing's coming from in here, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What...? No, it can't be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This has gotta be the victim's cell phone! Just whose locker is this, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's Ms. Teneiro's.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">So Mr. Edgeworth, how did it go? Where did you find the phone?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I found it in the flight attendants' room... In Ms. Teneiro's locker...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Wh-What!? But...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Rhoda Teneiro!</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I don't know anything about the phone! It wasn't me! It wasn't me...</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Ms. von Karma, is it? I suggest you arrest Ms. Rhoda Teneiro right away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! I have a theory! This is related to the incident with the keycard! When the killer went to steal the keycard... ...they conveniently stashed the cell phone in Ms. Teneiro's locker at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This is related to the keycard alright. In the same way that we have zero proof that the killer did just that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The only voice that sings the truth is evidence. That is the one bird we cannot ignore.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do? Franziska's right. I can't offer baseless conjectures at this point! Alright then, why did the culprit take the cell phone from Agent Hicks? It must have something very incriminating on or in it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What now, Miles Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not over yet! We have yet to figure out why the killer took the phone!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Inside this phone lies the final piece of incriminating evidence that will point us to our killer. <thought>We need to examine this phone in more detail!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The LCD is broken. Without a screen, you can't even place a call with this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This must be the switch that opens the phone... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! When did they start putting keyboards like these into cell phones?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! This is one of those "computer cell phones" that they started selling recently!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..."Computer cell phones"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! It's got a computer in it, AND it's a cell phone! Neat, huh, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...All you need in a phone is the phone part. Nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... I'm guessing yours can't even send out e-mail... Talk about inconvenient.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Do you have a problem with what I do and do not care for, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! No... No, sir! As they say, "Simple is best!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah! It's camera lens! Come to think of it... ...I wonder... How exactly was Agent Hicks planning to preserve the crime scene of a smuggling? Franziska! I need you to confirm something... This cell phone... Can it take pictures?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I can't believe you don't know about this kind of basic stuff, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This looks like a very similar model to my own. And mine can take photos just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you think Agent Hicks could've taken some pictures with this? In particular, pictures as evidence for his smuggling case? If so, I'd say there may be some very inconvenient photos in here for our killer-smuggler!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But the phone's all busted up, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Even a super-prosecutor can't repair a broken phone.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrgk! I'll find a way, don't you worry about that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaawn* May I go back to sleep now?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The LCD screens on the inside and outside are broken, that's for sure. But that's also reason enough to believe that the killer wasn't able to erase the data.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by that, Franziska!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like our killer isn't very familiar with electronics. This phone still rang when I called it, meaning that only the LCD screens are broken. It's possible that the photos are still there inside, waiting to be accessed. All we need to do is transfer the data to my phone!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska! Your phone, if you please!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Very well... It's transferring... Alright, displaying it now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! This is...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Hicks was most certainly trying to obtain some evidence for his smuggling case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! The Alif Red's nowhere in this pic, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">But this has no meaning as a piece of evidence in this murder case, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch, she's right. There's not much we can find out from this about Agent Hicks's killer, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Is this it? ...Is this the end...? Is there really nothing in this photo that we can use...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fact that all of the suitcases are here in this photo is odd!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Hicks was still alive at this time. So what exactly is so odd about suitcases that haven't been used yet bring there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well, I was only pointing out things that are different between now and then.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Your off-topic ramblings have put this attendant to sleep yet again, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">...Gnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr... I'll give sleepyhead here a rude awakening: a deafening objection and a contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Boxes of bedsheets... These are still in the cargo hold. <thought>There's nothing unusual about them in particular, but I can't shake the feeling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meele">*yaaaaawn*... If you're just playing around, mind if I go home?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I mind! <thought>I need to focus on what's different now from back then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The guard rail.. It looks exactly the same as it does now.</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">That rail is entirely too low! I even almost fell to my death! However! I was saved in a miracle-like maner! Perhaps that is what "to run away from death by the skin of one's gum" means!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Try "to narrowly escape death by skin of one's teeth", Shakespeare. Now then, there must be something in this photo...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's all this...?</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hm? Oh! They are cargo shipped from Borginia to Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the reason they aren't here now is that they were dropped off in Zheng Fa...</thought> Mr. Lablanc, can you tell me the contents of the boxes? Unfortunately, there is no English written on them anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Hmm... One cluster of boxes is written in Borginian. It says "Borginian Speaking". It is "cloth" in English.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Cloth...? <thought>Could it be...!? Is this where the killer...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Wh-What!? What for is that scary face!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that Agent Hicks was no ordinary investigator.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He left us with a piece of evidence after all. A striking piece that will point out who his killer is!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Hah! Maybe you shouldn't force your mistaken reading of a simple picture, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Borginian cargo and this piece of evidence will point us straight to the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Meele">Would you care to fill me in on what you are trying to prove with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's quite simple. It shows that I will be re-presenting my evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">I'm not laughing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It wasn't meant to be a laughing matter!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">And what is that supposed to prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer used this piece of cloth to wipe up the blood they had split. But there was one thing that bothered me this whole time: "Where did it come from?" And now, I have finally found my answer in this very photo! The cargo that was unloaded in Zheng Fa had "cloth" written on it. In Borginian, that is. And this is where the killer grabbed a piece from to clean up the blood with!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. The killer was someone who could read and understand Borginian. And the only crew member that fits that description is you, Ms. Cammy Meele!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Hah! That's pretty flimsy! The killer probably searched through all the boxes looking for something to use. When you're frantic, you don't care if the box is in English or Borginian!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but I cannot agree with your assessment of the killer's indiscriminate nature.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was no need for the killer to tear through boxes at random at all. And if the killer supposedly could not comprehend Borginian... Well then... Logically, the killer would have opened this box first!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This proves that the killer knew how to read Borginian!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't fool me! Don't pretend as though you don't see what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I don't understand either.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't get it at all, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Alright then, I will show it to you all once again in a more understandable fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You don't fool me! Don't pretend as though you know what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I probably should have known better than to play pretend.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, it says "Bedsheets" in English right on the box, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. And bedsheets would be perfect for cleaning up blood, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">So what are you trying to say!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That if I were the criminal... ...this box of bedsheets would have been what I would have spotted first.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">However, the killer chose to use some Borginian cloth... Do you have an explanation for that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer didn't want anyone to know that the real scene of the crime was this cargo hold. So they were afraid to leave signs that the box for the sheets had been opened. However, the Borginian cloth... Well, that's a horse of a different color!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Because the killer knew that it was going to be unloaded in the Republic of Zheng Fa!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. That is why the Borginian cloth was used. And the only Borginian-reader onboard who could make such a calculated decision... ...is you, Cammy Meele! You and you alone!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Unnnnnngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would be very easy for us to confirm if any of the boxes were re-sealed. All we would have to do is contact the Zheng Fa authorities in time. We may even find other evidence to incriminate our killer within those boxes.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Grrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what do you say, Ms. Meele? Why not confess to your crime here and now? Or would you rather wait and see what we find out from our investigation in Zheng Fa!?</line>
<line speaker="Meele">.............................. Oooooo......oooooo...... Oooooo......oooooo...... Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo! He... He was Interpol... I couldn't stop it... I brought him here... He started taking pictures... I... I couldn't be found out... I... was scared... I... was in trouble... I... I... I I I I I I I I I I I I I I...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We've finished making all the arrangements to take the suspect in, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good, Detective. What about the smuggling route? Did she say anything about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">They're taking her down to the precinct now. Hopefully, we can get more out of her there. Whenever we even approached the topic, she just started foaming at the mouth. It was scary, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She probably wasn't prepared to commit a murder all of a sudden. One thing is for sure, the ring behind this whole mess means serious business. It looks like there's a lot more to this case than meets the eye...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Mr. Edgeworth! I just wanted to say how much I appreciate everything you did. Thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was nothing. In fact, I should be the one thanking you for your cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">But truly, if it wasn't for you, I... I might not be here right now. Instead, I can continue to serve our passengers as a flight attendant! Um... I hope that... Well, please accept this as a token of my appreciation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I see... You don't have to take it if you don't want it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No... I mean, I would never turn down a lady's generous offer.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Oh, thank you! I'm sure it will serve you well! And remeber, we here at iFly Airlines are always ready to serve, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, I'll keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">Now I must bid you farewell. May all your skies be blue, no matter where you go!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe we wound up investigating the whole day, sir, but boy was it fun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Speak for yourself! My day was filled with earthquakes, elevators, and false charges!</thought> By the way, where's Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, she's filling out some customs paperwork for her departure.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Departure...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, Ms. von Karma's always really busy, sir. She's been flying from country to country to chase down some leads regarding her case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Detective. Can you cancel the car I had you reserve earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I thought I told you when you first landed. I have no time for idle chatter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no intention of wasting your time, however, it has been a while since we last met.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I also have no time for such familiar reminiscences. Just who do you think I am!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are Franziska von Karma, a very proud prosecutor deserving of much respect.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Until only a little while ago, I was but a retched mutt who was always losing to you. A dancing pierrot living her life on the name and fame her invincible father built!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">True, your father, Manfred von Karma, didn't lose a single case for 40 years as a prosecutor. However, I wouldn't say he was invincible.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The group I'm on the trail of is a little more troublesome than most. The smuggling route we found this time is only one sliver of the big picture.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sounds like a dangerous assignment.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You really don't have to worry. I can take care of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I suppose you can.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Plus, there is another agent on this case with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Another agent?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He's a star among Interpol agents, and has the highest successful arrest rate. Who knows, you may even run into him one day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? I was simply caught up in this one case... I hardly see why we would cross paths.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose. But I doubt he would say the same.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not following you...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You'll understand soon enough. The fight has only just begun, Miles Edgeworth. I'll be back in this country soon enough. And when I am, you can be sure I'll pay you back... in full!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And just like that, she's gone, huh, sir? Thank goodness! I can finally rest easy knowing I won't have to watch out for her whip!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, I want to thank you for all your help and cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, it was nothing, sir! I was just happy to be able to work with you again, ho ho! I think I'm gonna celebrate by adding a little extra salt to my instant noodles tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* Just how much did you cut his salary by, Franziska...?</thought> Detective, I was wondering if you might give me a ride down to the Prosecutor's Office!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, sir! I'll even fly down the road in the patrol car if you want!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't make me remind you, Detective. "Safety first"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Thus, I solved the first case upon my arrival home. Franziska von Karma... The smuggling route she was after... The leaders of that ring had already put their trump card into play. And the players on the other side of this war... ...they would begin to make themselves known through the next incident...</thought> Hm...? Edgeworth speaking.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, finally. I called who knows how many times earlier but I couldn't get through.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, have you forgotten my voice, Miles, my boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. M-Mr. Amano!? Ernest Amano, correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Ernest">Ah! So you do remember me! ...I know it's rather sudden, but I can't ask this of anyone else. ...There's been an incident, Miles. ...My son... He's been kidnapped...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence perfectly exposes the flaw in your logic!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? Well then, why don't you show me how it does just that? Go on!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I bet it's this part, right? This conflicts with something, right, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You have no idea what you're talking about, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Don't speak up when you don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch... I was just trying to follow your head, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That you would allow a subordinate to take over... You're a disgrace!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnnnnnrrrrk! <thought>I guess that wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. It would seem that your logic is not as perfect as you think it is.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence should show you exactly what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Oh, yes. It clearly shows what you're thinking. That you're attempting to buy yourself time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh! <thought>I knew I shouldn't have tried to pull a fast one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I believe your testimony just now conflicts with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And I believe that when you use the phrase "I believe", you are anything but certain. Which means that showing me that piece of evidence is just a way to waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaaaaaah! <thought>She even managed to whip the evidence at the some time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owwww!! Why did you whip me, too, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's one more victim besides myself and the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah, I've got you now. Your testimony contradicts this piece of evidence...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, really!? Can you explain it to me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Certainly. It's quite... ......Gnnrnk!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! How can you ignore a witness like this!? Because of you, shes's fallen fast asleep, yet again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I...I'm sorry, Franziska! Ms. Meele! Please wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Cammy">*yaaawn* Good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnnnnnrrrrk! <thought>I guess that wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe your testimony contradicts this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Cammy">Really? You think so? I don't really get these kinds of things so... you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Then in that case, I might be wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Your brain is about as awake as that flight attendant! Here, allow me help you wake up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ooooooooongh! I didn't need a second lashing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Meele. Your testimony stands on clear contradiction to this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Cammy">............zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wake up! This is a very critical point we're discussing here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We seem to be in need of an alarm clock here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... If you please.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Sure, to wake the one who gave such a sleepy objection... Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaarrrrgnnnn! I-I guess that wasn't it...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's as far as you go, Miles Edgeworth. I've known the truth now for quite some time, and I won't allow you to dawdle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? But we haven't completed the investigation yet!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's obvious that the culprit is Ms. Rhoda Teneiro! There's no one else it could've been!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh! <thought>It can't end like this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Teneiro was kept in custody under the pretense of a "valuable witness". Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Aren't you out of patience yet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah... Unfortunately for you, I am overflowing with patience and my will is strong. I can keep on investigating you for as long as it takes!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Oh? Well, unfortunately for you, I've got a flight to catch and attend to, Bye-bye!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!? No...!</line>
<line speaker="Meele">Hee hee.. Now if you'll excuse me, I must be going.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Cammy Meele was never seen nor heard from again... Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>