
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reclaimed</title>
<line speaker="Buckler">WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?! The ship's doctor and Azura were romantically involved?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's my theory, but I don't actually know if it's really true.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Azura would never get involved with that cod-awful ship's doctor! But I do admit... they were friends... But would Azura send Dr. Crab videos, I wonder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Videos? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Azura used to send her boyfriend videos of herself teaching the orca tricks. I used to help Azura take the videos on her TV phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. This is an interesting bit of information...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So TV phones can shoot videos, too, huh? My dumb phone sure can't. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">These TV phones are amazing! They can even record sounds you and I can't hear! All the equipment we use at Shipshape Aquarium is high-tech. The ship's doctor sends away for all kinds of electronics.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So all the high-tech stuff is Dr. Crab's doing, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Anyway, I still highly trout Azura's boyfriend was the ship's doctor. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Dr. Crab found a charm yesterday, and he was really shaken by it.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Charm...? Hey! Leave that alone! That belonged to Azura! What was Azura's charm doing in Rifle's stomach...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That charm looked just like your keepsake of Azura.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, well... She did say she and her boyfriend had matching charms... Was the ship's doctor and Azura really a couple...? I-I can't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think Dr. Crab will be called as a witness today. There are still so many unanswered questions... ...but I hope to solve them all in today's trial. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I believe in you two! I know you can do it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we WILL, Sasha! We promise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready-- AAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Ready.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Now I'm completely thrown off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. It appears both the prosecution and the defense are ready. Yesterday, it was proven that the orca was not guilty and that the victim fell to his death. Prosecutor Blackquill, did your investigation of the orca pool area turn up anything?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. It did. We found a bloodstain from the victim at the bottom of the pool. ...On this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my. What a frightening-looking rock. And you say it has a bloodstain on it? Hmm. Just looking at it gives me the willies. So can we assume that there was no water in the pool at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Very good. What a clever little deduction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! Well, it's nice to get a compliment from the prosecution for a change. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Blackquill has completely tamed the judge with his carrot-and-stick approach.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I guess I should've brought a few carrots of my own.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Right. Moving along. I have prepared a witness. Buckler was the only one who entered that room when there was no water in the pool. The witness will prove that. ............Come to the stand, witness. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Name and occupation. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Dr. Herman Cr--</line>
<line speaker="Sniper">Peep!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Sniper! Stay in there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who is that cute little creature?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Such a restless bird. Quite unlike Taka.</line>
<line speaker="Taka">Graaaaaw!</line>
<line speaker="Sniper">Peep!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... Chalk one up for Taka... He shut Sniper up with a single sound.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun... Dr. Herman Crab, Shipshape Aquarium's veterinarian.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And could you tell us the name of your cute little friend there, as well?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, please focus on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But it's important to learn all we can about the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">This is Sniper. </line>
<line speaker="Sniper">*peep!* *peep, peeeeep!* *peep, peep, peep, peep!*</line>
<line speaker="Crab">She's the offspring of a penguin named Rifle. Sniper lives in my hair. She might cause a commotion now and then, but please try to ignore her. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I was originally going to call the animal keeper to the stand... ...but he refused to testify, so I settled on the veterinarian. ............Now tell us. Why was the defendant in the orca pool room when the water was drained?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. And your claim is that the victim was made to fall to his death during the cleaning? </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. Only Buckler and the owner had the security card necessary to enter the orca pool room. And we already know from the security company's record of card usage... ...that the defendant was in the orca pool room during the time of cleaning. The witness's testimony and the record of security card usage are conclusive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So no one beside the defendant was at the scene, and the water in the pool was drained.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh-oh... The judge already seems to be leaning toward the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We have to strike fast... Your Honor, we're ready for our cross-examination now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Yes, of course... Please proceed, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The power of youth comes in handy at times like these.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Our aquarium is open every day of the year, without break. So of course the cleaning has to be done at night when there are no visitors. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... No days off, is that it? I can relate to that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess prisoners don't get to take days off...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Things SURE are different around OUR office, huh, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have to rub it in quite so enthusiastically. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, was the defendant cleaning alone?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I don't know anything about that. All I know is what was on the schedule. Maybe they changed plans. They probably felt awkward with each other after their fight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, there's no proof the victim entered the orca pool room during cleaning!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gah... <thought>Do you have to be so violent...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Proof or none, the victim must have entered the pool room during cleaning. Witness, tell him why.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Jack must have entered the orca pool room. The reason I think so is because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No, only Sasha's. But they must have gone in together. Jack's body was found in that room, so that's the only logical explanation. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We talked about this just yesterday. What purpose does that brain of yours serve?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gak!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">You're even more birdbrained than Rifle.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I get disparaged either way. Great.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hmph. Bird lover, huh? I guess we're not destined to become best friends.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That is fine. All I need is for you to talk about the state of the scene during cleaning.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">All right. Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, I don't know. I think the two of them were made for each other...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. They use the hoist there to lower themselves to the bottom of the pool. They can do regular cleaning with water in the pool, but this was an intensive session. I never clean my own lab, however...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't you think it might be due, then...? <thought>I guess I can't talk, though...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, Sasha and Marlon come in and clean it for me on occasion. But I'm too busy, myself. I have animals to look after. Like this one, for example. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such an adorable little creature! It lends cheer to this bleak courtroom. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Your reaction to Taka was very different, as I recall...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh, T-Taka is a fine bird, too, of course! ...Please continue, Dr. Crab. Quickly, now. </line>
<line speaker="Crab">As I was saying, Sasha was cleaning the orca pool room...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, it wouldn't do to get her covered in cleanser, would it? Of course she was moved! You don't take a bath while you're cleaning the tub, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Excellent point. I usually clean the tub after I take a bath, myself. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... I was assigned to clean the shower stalls yesterday. They were cleaner than an Edo bathhouse by the time I was done. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess Prosecutor Blackquill is the fastidious type... </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I polished it so well, I bet the inmates are slipping and sliding all over right about now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hmm. Maybe he's not so much the fastidious type as the prankster type...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Somehow, I don't think that's it, either...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Anyway, cleaning the orca pool is just like cleaning the tub.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">None. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. Shot down with a single word...</thought> Why are you so certain?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Think about it. If the pool water were drained, what would happen to the orca?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-The poor thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whose side are you on, Athena?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Exactly, young lady. Without water, Orla would be all right for a short period of time. But anything longer than that would pose serious risks. She could even die. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the fact that Orla is alive and well is proof the water wasn't drained on her?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. The orca pool and the show stage pool are next door to each other. A hoist runs between the two to move the orca and equipment back and forth. When intensive cleaning is done, the orca is moved to the show stage pool first... ...so the water is only drained while the pool is being cleaned.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Please add that information to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun... Then why did you harp on it so?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defense loves to make a fuss over nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">You do like to stir up trouble, don't you, Mr. Lawyer. Just like this one...</line>
<line speaker="Sniper">*peep, peeeeep!*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How rude! Don't compare Mr. Wright to Sniper! Granted, his suit may make him LOOK a little like a penguin...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Athena... <thought>Is that what she really thinks of me?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Crab">Gaaah! I wish Sniper and Miss Baby Chick would both stop all the peeping and cheeping!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Miss Baby Chick...?! How dare you-- No, wait. That actually sounds pretty cute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. He just got away with calling a young woman a "chick" in court.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. I don't see a single hole in Dr. Crab's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He leaves himself wide open to Rifle's attacks, though! I guess all we can do is keep pressing him for more information!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Somehow, we have to show that the water could've been drained at some other time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we don't, Sasha will be the only one under suspicion! There must be a hint somewhere. I'd better look through the evidence again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to find out how the water could've been drained while Orla was there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the water in the pool is drained, you say the orca could die. But is that necessarily true?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a way to let the water out without harming the orca, isn't there? Your Honor, please allow me to submit this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Oh! This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, there is no water around the skull rock area. With the pool in this state, the victim could have been made to fall to his death. However, there IS water on the other side of the partition... ...and Orla looks just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Son of a gun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, if the partition is set up at the bottom of the pool... ...the water can be drained without doing Orla any harm!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you implying the water could have been drained at a time other than during cleaning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, there is that possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dr. Crab is shaking... Looks like he has something to hide. Could it have something to do with the calendar note about meeting with the victim? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It might. I'll submit to the judge. Your Honor! Please take a look at this calendar.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you waved that around in court yesterday. No need to drag out your souvenir today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I would like you to make note of the entry for the day of the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me see, here... "Meet the captain at the orca pool at 7 am." This note is about a meeting planned with the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense would like to argue that, at the time of that meeting... ...the pool may have been drained of its water!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whose calendar is that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............It belongs to Dr. Herman Crab. Isn't that right, Dr. Crab?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Son of a gun... SO you suspect me, do you?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this calendar entry, Dr. Crab? Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Fine. I was supposed to meet Jack at the orca pool at that time. But... I ended up not going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're saying you simply broke your promise? You can't get out of it that easily. I believe you have some explaining to do.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>The calendar alone isn't good enough, huh? I have to prove the victim could have fallen to his death at that 7 AM meeting time!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's put our heads together, Boss! The victim could've fallen during cleaning, when the pool was completely drained... ...or, using the partition, it could've been at 7 AM, with the water partially drained. What would be the major difference in circumstance between these two possibilities?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... What circumstance was different...? The answer could really tell us something... What circumstance was different between the two possibilities of cleaning and 7 AM?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the murder was at a time other than during cleaning, the pool must've been half filled!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I suppose there's half a possibility the pool was only half filled... ...but if you wish to make that claim, let me see your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Proof...? I... don't have any proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, there's much more than half a possibility that I will assign you a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better rethink that. There must be some other circumstance that was different...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder must have been at a different time of day than the cleaning time!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono... If you wish to claim the murder was at a different time of day, show me your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Proof...? I... don't have any proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, it's the time of day for me to assign you a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better rethink that. There must be some other circumstance that was different...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the murder occurred at a time other than during cleaning, the orca must've been there! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, you're right! And that would mean... ...Orla witnessed the murder! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's this? You're sheathing your sword so soon? Stop yammering to each other and show me how you wield your sword!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, then. My sword is poised and ready. If the murder was committed at a time other than during cleaning time... ...then Orla must have been present at the scene. If I can prove that the murder happened right in front of Orla... ...then I can prove that Ms. Buckler is not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court...! Mr. Wright! Are you implying that the orca was a witness to the crime?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is exactly what I'm implying!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. And...? How do you intend to prove the orca witnessed the murder...? What are you going to do, put the orca on the stand and cross-examine her?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is a critical point. I'd better think about it carefully...</thought> The defense will...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I asked Orla if she witnessed the murder, I'm sure she would tell me everything!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Really? How interesting... And how do you propose to communicate with the orca?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I... I'd have to think about that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unlike some birds, an orca is incapable of human speech. No, I'm afraid I cannot allow you to cross-examine a creature that cannot speak. Unless the defense has some other way of communicating with the orca...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... I'm afraid I don't, Your Honor. <thought>I guess that was a silly idea...</thought> Please let me try again, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll continue my cross-examination of Dr. Crab!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Hmph. That's fine with me, but I've already said everything I have to say. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You still haven't told the court why you broke your promise to meet with the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Balderdash"...? Is that some sort of shot at me...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That seems to be quite a sensitive subject with the judge...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Maybe I'd better come up with something that isn't "balderdash"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense will present evidence, evidence that will prove Orla witnessed the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're going to... present evidence? Knowing the defense, I thought surely you would try to cross-examine the orca... I must say I'm a little disappointed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, sorry to get your hopes up, Your Honor...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's see this evidence, then. What evidence shows that the murder took place right in front of the orca? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. I thought maybe if I presented it with confidence, it would all work out somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nothing to say for yourself, is that it, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I must have some evidence here somewhere that shows Orla witnessed the murder!</thought> Your Honor! Please allow me to present a different piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's see this evidence, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This photo indicates where we discovered luminol reactions yesterday. By accident, we got some of the luminol testing fluid on Orla. We were then very surprised to see... ...luminol reactions on Orla's body!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that cloud of blood Ms. DePlume saw... ...was from Orla head-butting the skull rock, was it?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Those luminol reactions you saw on the orca are most likely from her head-butting. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then where did the blood come from...? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my firm belief that it's the victim's blood. The victim was killed right in front of Orla... ...and the victim's blood splattered onto Orla's body!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gaaaaaaaaagh! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now it finally all makes sense! Orla was a witness to the murder...! So THAT'S why...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla? Boss! Something's wrong with Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You're right! She's listless... and she's sinking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one more fact that indicates Orla was a witness to the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's more?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The culprit was afraid Orla could somehow reveal what she witnessed... ...and that's why they did what they did. It's the only thing that makes sense! I have to present that evidence...! ...That evidence that proves the culprit thought Orla was a dangerous witness!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Evidence, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What I'm asking you is, what does that evidence have to do with anything?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! You don't even have an answer for me?! Your silence will be rewarded with a penalty. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The culprit was afraid Orla could somehow reveal what she witnessed... ...and that's why they did what they did. I have to present evidence to prove that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense would like to submit this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? It looks like some sort of medicine...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a sleeping drug, Your Honor, a very powerful one. The sleeping drug was discovered in Orla's stomach yesterday. The culprit tried to drown Orla by putting her into a deep sleep!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tried to drown the orca?! B-But... why? </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono... are you trying to tell this court... ...that the perpetrator tried to kill the orca off to prevent a witness from talking?! Do you really expect to defeat me with that feeble attack?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My sword has been drawn. I'm not about to sheathe my evidence now. Orcas have an enormous potential for intelligence. The possibility that Orla could somehow manage to reveal the truth can't be denied. The culprit believed in this possibility... and that's why they tried to kill her! ............Dr. Herman Crab. You purchased this sleeping drug, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?! Does this mean the veterinarian tried to do away with the orca?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who but a veterinarian would better know how to disguise an orca's death? He could even prevent the police from examining Orla's body!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Why, you... Are you actually accusing me of trying to murder the orca?! HOW DARE YOU?! HOW DARE YOU slander the noble profession of VETERINARIAN?! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>E-Eeek...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">My goodness! One could cut the tension in this courtroom with a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">YES! I admit to purchasing that sleeping drug! However............ it was subsequently stolen from my lab.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's such a flimsy excuse!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">It's the truth. What else can I say? Any one of the crew members could have entered my lab. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that weakens my evidence quite a bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">...Besides, think about it for a minute. Who was it that treated Orla after she swallowed the drug? It was I! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But as I recall, it took you quite a while to give that treatment. You didn't even come on your own. We had to go get you.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Son of a gun. You just remember all sorts of little details, don't you, Mr. Lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca pool and the lab are far apart. It's little wonder he didn't know Orla's condition.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Crab:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk... No, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What happened to your fire now, Mr. Wright? Let me rekindle it... with a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter how far away Dr. Crab may have been, there's one piece of evidence... ...that should have allowed him to realize Orla's condition!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The TORPEDO...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Gah! You just had to bring that up, didn't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With this advanced data system, surely you would have known Orla's condition! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dr. Crab! How dare you bring a weapon of mass destruction into my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The TORPEDO, or "TeleObservation Realtime PErtinent Data Organizer," is a data system. Until yesterday, only Dr. Crab and Mr. Shipley knew about the TORPEDO. It isn't legally approved in this country, so it was kept secret from the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It's illegal?! Dr. Crab! I demand an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Son of a gun! You and your big mouth, Mr. Lawyer! Yes, it's true... I'm using an illegal system to monitor the creatures at the aquarium. The system uses sensors like these, and, yes, there's one in the orca pool, too. These sensors send sound waves through the water to gather data on the creatures. If it finds abnormalities in their condition, the TORPEDO alerts me with a sound.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my goodness! How very high-tech! But if it's illegal, I will not turn a blind eye. This matter will be appropriately dealt with at a separate time. Now then, Mr. Wright. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With the TORPEDO, I'm sure Dr. Crab noticed the danger Orla was in... ...but he made no attempt to come to her aid on his own! And the reason for that is... that Dr. Crab wanted Orla dead!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............The TORPEDO didn't give me a warning message. That's why I didn't know there was anything wrong with Orla. The sensor in the orca pool wasn't working during the police's investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What's with him?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess this is all so high-tech for Prosecutor Blackquill that it's making him a little "funny." </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Funny"...? Yes, I find this all very "funny." Witness, those "sensors" send sound waves through the water, correct? But what if there isn't any water?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Then they wouldn't work. They would automatically switch off.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I see... And where is the sensor in the orca pool located? </line>
<line speaker="Crab">I don't know. Jack is the one who attached it for me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You don't know? Then I will tell you. The police found a sensor just like the one you just showed us. They found it attached to the table at the bottom of the pool. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Table...? Do you mean the table in this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That's right. ............Don't you get it yet, Wright-dono? The table is on the skull rock side of the partition. It's affixed to the bottom of the pool, and can't be moved. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! And so if the water was drained from the skull rock side of the pool...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Precisely. Without water, the TORPEDO sensor would not work. Witness, when did that sensor automatically switch off?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Hang on. I'll look it up. The only times lately were during cleaning two days ago and the investigation yesterday. Of course I knew the pool would be drained while they cleaned it... ...but I had no idea they drained it for the investigation. No one let me know. That's why I didn't know about Orla's condition yesterday. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Dr. Crab really did want to save Orla...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh heh. Did you hear that, Wright-dono? Yes, the water can be drained without harm to the orca if the partition is used. But if the water is drained from the skull rock side, the sensor turns itself off. If the sensor was always on except for during the cleaning and the investigation... ...it means there must have been water in the pool at all other times. It was never drained. In other words... no one but the defendant could have committed the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! This completely shatters the defense's argument!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ggg... B-B-But... The fact still remains that Orla was nearly killed with Dr. Crab's sleeping drug!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You're right. That hasn't been discussed yet, has it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca pool is the scene of the murder. The police were there all day yesterday. The only way to give the drug to the orca undetected is to put it in her food. Yesterday, someone gave the orca food during the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Someone did? I'm afraid I don't remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You don't remember? You're not THAT old yet, are you? ............It was the defendant, Sasha Buckler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So that is the orca that stands accused, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aw. She's waving her flipper at us. Maybe she's cheering us on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla, wish Phoenix and Athena luck!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So your argument is that Ms. Buckler is the one who gave the orca the drug?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The prosecution's argument hasn't changed. Buckler made the victim fall to his death and then manipulated the orca to pin it on her. Still not satisfied, she further planned to kill the orca with the sleeping drug!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. I didn't hear any reports of Dr. Crab feeding Orla... Maybe he didn't have a hand in Orla's attempted murder after all... But is there anybody else who could've fed Orla, besides Sasha?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If it's true the defendant is the one who fed the sleeping drug to the orca... ...then that places even more suspicion on her than ever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, well. You still haven't admitted defeat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill. I don't appreciate the way you only mention the parts that are convenient for you.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The prosecutor failed to mention that Ms. Buckler wasn't the only one who fed Orla! As you will all recall, there was another person who gave Orla food.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh! You mean, that person...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Athena remembers now, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Congrats, Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="???">This is to celebrate! Eat it all up!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Mr. Wright! No...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't want to believe it, either, but we can't ignore the truth... The other person who fed Orla during the trial was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............That's what I've been saying all along! After the orca was falsely accused, the defendant planned to kill the orca. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, wait a minute...! I, uh... Huh? I was just trying to, er... confirm... that the defendant ALSO fed the orca...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was already clearly established, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... It was just a simple attempt at confirmation, Your Honor... <thought>But there WAS another person who fed Orla during the trial...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oops. Uh, my finger slipped.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You'll receive a penalty for that, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But, other than Sasha... ...there was one other person who fed Orla during the trial...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please recall when Orla was found not guilty yesterday. ...Marlon Rimes gave the orca a large quantity of food. If the sleeping drug was mixed in with that food... ...it could be given to the orca without arousing police suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now that you mention it, I do remember that flip-flopper feeding the orca!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............Mr. Lawyer. Both Miss Orca Lover and Marlon Rimes are important members of our crew. I don't want to suspect either of them, but I'm ready to accept whatever truth you find. Here. Take this. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! That charm...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's the charm that matches the one Azura Summers had, isn't it? So you and Ms. Summers WERE romantically involved, weren't you, Dr. Crab? </line>
<line speaker="Crab">What? No, of course not. Sorry to disappoint you, but this doesn't belong to me. At the time, I thought it was Azura's, so I grabbed it... ...But it wasn't hers. Now it's up to you, Mr. Lawyer, to figure out whose charm it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I will. Thank you, Dr. Crab.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">After all, I'm interested in the outcome of this trial, too...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then. Please summon Marlon Rimes to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Wh-What's going on? What's everybody makin' that face for? I haven't been watchin' the trial and nobody's told me anythin'.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Marlon Rimes. You are under suspicion for the attempted murder of the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ I see... Well, if it's already out... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Rimes...? <thought>Is he really going to admit it?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Fine. I'll tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sasha is lyin' to protect that orca.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now we're back to the orca again?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............ I did not see THAT testimony coming...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now wait just one minute! Yesterday, Orla was proven innocent! Besides, you said Orla was in the show pool during the cleaning!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I didn't wanna sell Sasha out... That's I didn't tell the truth... But the fact is, all three of us--Sasha, the captain and me--were cleanin' the pool room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Dr. Crab and Ms. Buckler both said you were at the show stage...!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Well, the only thing Dr. Crab knew about the cleanin' was what I told him. I didn't give him a whole lot of details, either. Maybe he misunderstood. And Sasha is lyin' to protect the orca. She can't tell the truth. Sasha put blood on the skull rock herself to make a fake bloodstain. I think it's pretty brave of her to let herself get arrested to protect the orca. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Rimes! How can you lie like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">It's the truth! Besides, wouldn't it be better for you if I wasn't lyin'? If the orca did it, you win your case!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ This is all very hard to believe... ...but if Mr. Rimes's story is true... ...Ms. Buckler would be innocent, and the orca would be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! <thought>Meaning, if we turned our backs on Orla... ...we could save Sasha...?!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Having a witness lie to save your own client? What a dirty, underhanded tactic, Wright-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What are ya sayin', Mr. Wright?! All ya gotta do is admit the orca did it, and Sasha goes free! Isn't a lawyer supposed to act in his client's best interest?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that wouldn't be acting in her interest. Ms. Buckler believes Orla is innocent. And we, of course, believe that Ms. Buckler herself is innocent, too. Acting in the client's best interest is an important part of our job as lawyers. Using dirty means to win a verdict would destroy our client's faith in us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! We believe in both Ms. Buckler's AND Orla's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Huh?! I just don't understand how ya can treat a human and an orca equally. Sasha or the orca? You can only save one of them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. I don't know about that. I think I can save them both. All I have to do is disprove your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Oh, yeah? Then go ahead and try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will do just that. <thought>If I can't tear down his testimony, I won't be able to save both of them. I have to find a weak spot and start tearing!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sasha put that bloodstain on the skull rock and stuff herself, as false evidence. She left fake traces to try and save the orca! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense supports the prosecution's idea!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">But, Mr. Wright! My testimony helps your client! You oughta be happy... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to save both Orla and Ms. Buckler. I won't accept anything less. Now that that's understood, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">It was before the pool was drained for cleanin', so it was full.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went into the orca pool room and saw this yourself? Dr. Crab said that you were at the show stage. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Taka">Graaaaaw!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'd better be careful how we press the witness. Taka is watching us like a hawk...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Witness. Continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, I guess so. The captain, Sasha and I were gonna do the cleanin' together. It's much more efficient than tryin' to have just one person do it alone. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In the defense's case, however, more lawyers means simply... more lawyers. Nothing more. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! You're one to talk! All you have on your side is a cantankerous bird!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What about me?! I'm up here all alone!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Are you people done?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You need the witness to keep you focused? For shame, Wright-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I was the only one who kept my mouth shut!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Anyway, the incident happened in the orca pool before the cleanin' got started.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yup. Of course. I've seen orcas bashin' seals 60 feet into the air. So, naturally, Orla could do that to the captain, too. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a frightening thought! And you mention it so casually, Mr. Rimes...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, what else can I say? It's the truth. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Rimes is claiming that Orla killed the victim by sending him flying into the air... ...but would something like that even be possible in the orca pool room? There's something about that statement that bothers me...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so you witnessed the moment the victim was killed by the orca, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ahoy! Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo! Sasha could be found guilty if we let her be! But if the orca died, Sasha could go free! I thought if the orca was already dead, Sasha might tell the truth and free herself. It might seem cruel, but a man-killin' animal has to be put down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The culprit must have tried to do away with Orla because she was a witness to the crime. But if Mr. Rimes is the culprit... why would he try to protect Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I'm sensing some very complex emotions from Mr. Rimes... I need more information before I can do a proper analysis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I'm going to tear down his testimony, then I guess I have to present evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course we don't believe Mr. Rimes's testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But he's suggesting the murder took place in the orca pool... Unless we can disprove that, we won't be able to save both Orla and Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When lies are piled on top of each other, contradictions start to emerge. ............This time is no different.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Are ya sayin' there's some kind of inconsistency in my testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly what I'm saying. You claimed that the victim was sent flying about 30 feet into the air. But the autopsy report states the cause of death was thought to be from a 65-foot fall.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Additionally, in your testimony a moment ago... ...you said, "At 3:30 AM on the 20th, there was still water in the orca pool." The pool is about 65 feet deep and there's about 30 feet between the water and ceiling. If the pool was full of water as you claimed... ...it would be impossible for the victim to fall about 65 feet, as the autopsy states.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Aaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Rimes claimed he was in the orca pool room so he could make these statements. But the truth must be he was at the show stage, just as Dr. Crab and Sasha testified!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe that brings us back around to "the orca didn't do it."</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............I didn't believe the witness's testimony from the outset. I am grateful to you, Wright-dono, for shutting the witness up. As I thought, the only person who could have killed the victim is Sasha Buckler. That fact still remains, whether the witness was the one who tried to kill the orca or not.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Son of a...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Rimes was right about one thing. His testimony WAS advantageous to our case. But pointing out the contradiction in his statement will only drive us into a corner...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As Prosecutor Blackquill said, suspicion against Ms. Buckler is now deepened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh! If I don't do something fast, the judge is going to find Sasha guilty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Wright! Isn't there anything we can do? There has to be a way to prove Sasha is innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>At a time like this............ the thing to do is turn my thinking around! Instead of trying to prove that Sasha couldn't have done it... ...I have to think about what made it possible for somebody else to have done it. As long as the crime scene is the orca pool room... ...then Sasha is the only one who could have committed the crime.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............No need for pity, Your Baldness. Just finish him off with a swift verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears the defense has no objections. Very well. I will give my verdict--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But you were so quiet, Mr. Wright. Do you have something to say now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has a counterargument!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You do?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Pitiful. Such desperation. You look pale. Are you sure you're prepared to make this counterargument?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"A lawyer is someone who smiles no matter how bad it gets..." I'll never forget those words, no matter how many years go by. Even though it's probably just a bluff, I'll give it to them with a smile!</thought> ...What if the scene of the crime was somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Somewhere else...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What? You're finding fault with the police investigation now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I understand, the prosecution's argument is as follows. The scene of the crime was the orca pool room. Only the defendant and victim entered that room when there was no water in the pool. Therefore, only the defendant could have committed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But of the scene of the crime was NOT the orca pool room... ...then somebody other than the defendant could have committed the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Are you sure you know where you're going with this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I might not be too sure, but I can't back down now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... I hope that I'm wrong, but this isn't one of your bluffs, by any chance...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha! Of course not! <thought>...The judge knows me far too well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And do you have a theory on where the actual scene of the crime was?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, of course! <thought>Think, Phoenix! Think! Think of a place--other than the orca pool room--where one could fall to one's death!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, by all means, please share your theory with the court! Where was the real scene of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really? Do you actually believe the victim was killed there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, when you put it like that... my response would have to be... a definite "maybe."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case... you will definitely be getting a penalty. No "maybe" about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack...! This time, I promise to point out the true scene of the murder, Your Honor! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">You sound very sure of yourself for a man who just received a penalty. I hope you are right this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The show stage pool might have been drained of water at some point as well! And, if so, it would be just as possible to fall to one's death there as the orca pool!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Wright-dono. What you're doing is a disgrace to your profession. I sincerely hope you have some basis for what you're suggesting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course I do! <thought>I will... as soon as I think of something...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The victim's body was found in the orca pool! How do you explain that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"How about if..." What kind of presentation of your argument is that?! You had better have a reasonable explanation of how the body was moved! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no turning back now! I have to think of a way the body could've been moved! Was there something at the scene that could've been used to move the body?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How could anyone move a body with that?! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please make it a habit to think before you speak!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even though the two pools aren't all that far apart... ...it would still be pretty hard to carry a body all that distance. So the culprit must've used some kind of tool to move the body.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The hoist runs between the orca pool room and the show stage. The stretcher can be hung from the hoist to move things like Orla or the skull rock. The stretcher could also have been used to move the dead body! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Yes, if the stretcher can move the orca or the skull rock... ...it seems likely it could also move a dead body as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow! Somehow, that worked! I just might be able to pull this off!</thought> If the show pool was the scene of the crime, somebody else could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Not again?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You don't have the soul of a warrior. You don't deserve to be on the battlefield! And even your fabrication is half-baked. It's a disgrace! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean, "half-baked"?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The hoist can be operated from the orca pool room only.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gah... </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And the only person who entered the orca pool room was the defendant. So even if the body was moved... ...the only one who could have moved it was the defendant herself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order...! So it comes back to the defendant, no matter which pool it was?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Meaning... I can't clear Sasha either way...? Sasha said she moved Orla and the skull rock... ...and I believe her. So could it be possible that she moved the body herself without being aware of it?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Do you have an objection to Prosecutor Blackquill's claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have an objection to the claim that the defendant moved the body?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has an objection!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. All right, fine. Let's hear this "objection," then. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... well... My objection is... <thought>I can't admit I hadn't thought of one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you just FELT like saying you had an objection, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I just FEEL like giving you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The hoist could only be operated from the orca pool room. Furthermore, the defendant is the only one who entered the orca pool room. Therefore, the defendant is the only one who could have moved the body. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There are no inconsistencies in Prosecutor Blackquill's claim itself. But the only things Sasha moved are Orla and the skull rock. So that must mean... Sasha moved the body without realizing it...</thought> ...I admit, I don't see any problems with Prosecutor Blackquill's claim per se... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have............ no objections.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Buckler must have been the one who moved the body...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Are you admitting the defendant committed the murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No. I'm simply conceding that she was the only one who could have moved the body. However, I contend Ms. Buckler was not aware that is what she was doing. The culprit made her move it, unbeknownst to her!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant moved a dead body without recognizing that it was a dead body? How could that be possible?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The body was found in the orca pool. It must have been moved there somehow. I might find some kind of hint in the things she moved with the stretcher!</thought> The culprit made Ms. Buckler move the body along with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It might seem surprising, but it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. It's not "surprising." It's "absurd," which is no surprise, coming from you. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I have to agree. Indeed, there's nothing else to call it but "absurd."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. Looks like I got it wrong. The only two things Sasha moved are Orla and the skull rock. Why was Orla ramming the skull rock? There must be an answer that explains everything!</thought> Your Honor! Please let me give that another try!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The skull rock...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Buckler told me yesterday that she moved the skull rock when she was cleaning. The only two things Ms. Buckler moved to the orca pool are Orla and the skull rock. I would like to suggest that the victim's body may have been inside the skull rock!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hidden inside the rock, the body could have been moved to the orca pool with the hoist. At the show stage, Marlon Rimes loaded up the skull rock, with the body inside... ...and then he used the walkie-talkie to let Ms. Buckler know the rock was loaded. Ms. Buckler operated the hoist from the orca pool room and moved the stretcher! She moved the rock without knowing the body was inside!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you really think there's enough space inside the skull rock to place a body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Swashbuckler flyer indicates it could be possible. Please focus on the question at the bottom left.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! It says, "Who will obtain the gold coins hidden in the skull rock?!" Hmm. In that case, I suppose the rock is most likely hollow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's more, if the body was inside the skull rock... ...it explains the remaining unanswered questions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such as...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at the security footage of the scene Ms. DePlume witnessed. Where did the body that Ms. DePlume saw come from? Please recall... What was Orla doing to the skull rock at this time? She was head-butting it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Orla's ramming released the body from the skull rock! The body had been placed inside the skull rock and moved there from the show stage. I assert that the real murder scene was, in fact, the show stage pool!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! What rubbish is this now? You don't have a single scrap of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! Wright-dono...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Th-That was incredible! You turned things completely around! And to think! It all started with that half-baked bluff, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew! That was a close one! <thought>Did you really have to add that last bit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the murder took place at the show stage, then who is the perpetrator?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is, naturally, the person who was at the show stage.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes... Weren't you the one who loaded the skull rock onto the stretcher at the show stage?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">........................ ............Heh heh. Wow, Mr. Wright. That was some pretty smart brain work ya did there. To be honest, I never thought you could figure it out... I tried to protect myself, but I guess it came back to bite me...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you confessing you gave false testimony before, Mr. Rimes?! That's perjury!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah... What Mr. Wright says is true. The body WAS inside the skull rock. And it's true the captain was killed in the show pool, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What? He's admitting it that easily?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">This time, I'm gonna tell ya the whole truth about what happened that day!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">In the show pool, the orca shot the captain up into the air!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So now we're back to the orca again, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you were going to give testimony like that, why did I bother putting you on the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">All I'm doin' is tellin' the truth! That day, Sasha wanted to do the old version of the Swashbuckler Spectacular. So I suggested she hide the body in the skull rock and move it to the orca pool. I was gonna figure out what to do with the body after the show was over. The orca is the one that killed the captain! It wasn't me, and it wasn't Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it was Mr. Rimes's idea to hide the body in the skull rock? But if Mr. Rimes is the culprit, why would he protect Sasha? False charges against Sasha would mean he himself would escape suspicion. So why...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, how about if you leave this to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena! Do you mean... you heard something?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup, noise! Discord in Mr. Rimes's heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that means, somewhere in his testimony, there's an inconsistency in his emotions... All right, Athena! Give him a good counseling session!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it, Boss! Huh? What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you getting, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Hmm... This testimony is pretty complex. Feelings of deep sadness and intense anger are being called up. Those two emotions appear to be running out of control!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out-of-control emotions...? Is that going to be a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll have to probe their cause if we want to get to his true emotions and testimony. There might even be odd or unnatural spots in his testimony he isn't even aware of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's probe the cause of his out-of-control emotions, then!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll explain how to probe. Let's find the root cause together. When you see something off in a statement, tap the Probe button! Next, point to what's causing Mr. Rimes's out-of-control emotions. Finally, tap Probe to complete the process! When emotions are out of control, memories can be recalled incorrectly. If you still haven't found anything after all the statements and images, I'll help.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Great! All right. I'll get started comparing the statements with the images.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">In the show pool, the orca shot the captain up into the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, you're angry with Orla, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Angry? At an orca? Why would I be? If ya think I have some reason to be mad, then show me some proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have proof that Mr. Rimes has a reason to be mad...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got your proof right here! Uh, somewhere... I'm just not sure where at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">You're accusin' me without any proof? That's low, man. If ya wanna fight with just words, why not settle this with a rap battle? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no, thanks. Maybe some other time... <thought>Well, THIS isn't working... If I can't uncover the reason for his anger, I'd better think of a new approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid I don't have any proof. <thought>I'd better think of a different approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Then the captain came down and slammed into the water!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I can still remember the spectators' screams clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">All Sasha did was move the body! She was tryin' to protect the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">When Ms. DePlume witnessed the orca findin' the body, I freaked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, you're angry with Orla, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Angry? At an orca? Why would I be? If ya think I have some reason to be mad, then show me some proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have proof that Mr. Rimes has a reason to be mad...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got your proof right here! Uh, somewhere... I'm just not sure where at the moment...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">You're accusin' me without any proof? That's low, man. If ya wanna fight with just words, why not settle this with a rap battle? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no, thanks. Maybe some other time... <thought>Well, THIS isn't working... If I can't uncover the reason for his anger, I'd better think of a new approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid I don't have any proof. <thought>I'd better think of a different approach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What could be the cause of his out-of-control sadness and anger?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It'd be hard to find them both at the same time. Let's concentrate on probing just one. He did make one odd statement I was wondering about... I highly doubt there were any spectators at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, good point! That just doesn't fit. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just to be sure, I'll explain how to probe one more time. Tap the Probe button at the statement that seems off! Next, point to what you think is causing his out-of-control emotions, the spectators. Finally, tap Probe again to complete the process!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I doubt there were any spectators there at the show stage when the owner died. If there had been, those witnesses would've told us the true crime scene right away!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! ...Oh, right. Of course. I just made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay. That made the sadness subside. So maybe the "spectators" part was what was making him sad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder why he would make that mistake, saying spectators were there? How strange.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The only thing I can think of... is that he was mixing up one memory with another. Like... he was in a similar situation before, and it was deeply imprinted on his heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A situation where an orca killed somebody and there were spectators there...? Hey! I think I know why he's mixing up his memories... The reason why Mr. Rimes mixed up his memories is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I don't think that piece of evidence would make him mix up his memories. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No? <thought>Ouch. She dismissed that pretty fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's look for something that shows he suffered intense emotional pain in the past. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When it comes to psychology, I can really count on Athena! Hmm. An orca attacking somebody in front of spectators... Hey! I think I've got it now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, I think I know what happened. Could you have been mixing up what happened a year ago with this incident? Maybe that's why you slipped and said the owner was killed in front of spectators?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! How did you...?! You're right... I did see the orca kill somebody a year ago... But what about it? I was just one of the spectators.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Just another spectator? There must a reason why you feel great sadness about that incident last year.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Stop this nonsensical scrutiny of feelings! Just present evidence to prove your point!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeep! B-Boss, do we have any kind of evidence that would back us up here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. There IS one piece that comes to mind that might explain his sadness...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well?! I'm waiting! Let's see this "evidence" that has to do with Marlon Rimes's sadness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The only thing that piece of evidence made clear is my feeling toward you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what feeling might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A feeling of complete disgust that you have presented such ridiculous evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I feel disgust and sadness, too. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gak! <thought>Looks like I made a mistake there... I have to find some evidence that connects Mr. Rimes to the incident a year ago!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Azura Summers died an accidental death one year ago. This is her boyfriend's charm.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">H-Hey...! What are ya doin' with that charm?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was found in Rifle's stomach yesterday. Judging by your reaction, I believe this charm belongs to you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I need to push him just a little harder to make him admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When Mr. Rimes said the word "charm," he was very rattled. We'd better examine this charm a little more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. Let's look inside it. ...Huh? What's this? A photograph...? H-Hey, this is... ...Azura Summers and Marlon Rimes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Rimes, you and Azura Summers... were a couple, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Nghhh! So what if we were a couple?! It doesn't have anything to do with the captain's case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You believe you saw the orca kill your girlfriend. That's the cause of your sadness. Isn't that emotion of yours connected to the current case? </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The only thing you revealed was the witness's relationship with the victim a year ago. What does the witness's past have to do with the case at hand?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know yet...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But we managed to pinpoint the source of his sadness! Now let's delve into who Mr. Rimes is angry at!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">In the show pool, the orca shot the captain up into the air!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Then the captain came down and slammed into the water!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I can still remember the captain's dead body clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">All Sasha did was move the body! She was tryin' to protect the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">When Ms. DePlume witnessed the orca findin' the body, I freaked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now that his out-of-control sadness has subsided, the situation is a little different. Let's think about why he was so intensely angry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, you're angry with Orla, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Angry? At an orca? Why would I be? If ya think I have some reason to be mad, then show me some proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have proof that Mr. Rimes has a reason to be mad...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Maybe you don't have a reason to be angry at Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">That's right! I like orcas.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I heard discord in Mr. Rimes's heart. Does he really like Orla...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better take a look at the evidence again and see if anything is connected to Rimes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet that evidence we just took a look at would come in handy here.</thought> This charm indicates that you were Azura Summers's boyfriend. I'm sure you believe Orla killed your girlfriend a year ago. You lost your girlfriend, and so you've been angry at Orla! </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ngh............ All right. I'll admit it. I'll never forgive that orca. Azura is dead, and that orca is still swimmin' around, happy as a clam. I became an animal keeper just so I could prove that orca is a killer. You're right! I want that orca to pay! There! Do ya feel good, draggin' up a person's past?! But it still doesn't change anythin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>He's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I disagree. It DOES change things! His out-of-control emotion quieted down. Now we should be able to find out the truth behind that emotion!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">In the show pool, the orca shot the captain up into the air!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Then the captain came down and slammed into the water!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I can still remember it clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">All Sasha did was move the body! She was tryin' to protect the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">When Ms. DePlume witnessed the orca findin' the body, I freaked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">According to my analysis, Mr. Rimes is usually a very calm person. Let's see if we can find any inconsistencies between his words and his emotions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Ms. DePlume witnessed the orca finding the body, you "freaked"? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ What are ya gettin' at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With Ms. DePlume as a witness, Orla was guaranteed to be accused of the murder. Didn't it work out exactly as you'd hoped? In order to have Orla put down, you made sure Ms. DePlume witnessed that scene!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............So ya figured all that out, did ya?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Rimes? Are you admitting it?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I didn't really wanna have to fight anybody but the orca... ...but ya leave me no choice! GRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! Now it's time to get serious! AHOY! WHAT WHAT! YO! YO! YO HO HOOOOOO! AHOY ME MEAT BROTHAS REPRESENT! AVAST YE GRASS EATERS STAY FREE! TAKE ME WORDS N' POP N' IN YO MOUTH! SCURVY GRASS EATERS KNEEL TO ME BEAT! YO! YO! YO HO HOOOOOO! BRO I'M READY FOR THE SHOWDOWN!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh-What is going on?! Where did this pirate fellow come from?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-He looks like a completely different person!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! If we don't have order, Prosecutor Blackquill will yell at us!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Prosecutor Blackquill is at a loss for words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">So I planned to have that wench be a witness? Heh heh. Arr! Ye caught me out. It be true I thought that orca's murderous ways should be found out! That be why I schemed to have DePlume see the body!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you admit it? You deliberately framed Orla?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............Arr! It be true! But what skin be that off of anybody's nose? That orca be a murderin' scurvy dog! I may have a grudge against that orca, but I always felt grateful toward the cap'n. The orca murdered Azura and the cap'n, so o' course she should walk the plank!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gah! <thought>I-I don't have a response to that...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I agree it wouldn't make any sense for him to kill the owner. Why would he? But his hatred for Orla on the other hand comes through loud and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>............Wait a minute... If killing Mr. Shipley doesn't make sense, who would it make sense for Rimes to kill? Maybe... my theory has been all wrong...</thought> Your Honor! I think I just became aware of a new fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that we know about Mr. Rimes's intense hatred of Orla... ...it turns the premise we've been arguing under on its ear!</thought> I will now reveal the identity of the individual Mr. Rimes meant to kill from the start!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-Really?! ...But why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, because... Hmm. One can only wonder. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! How dare you roll the dice when you accuse someone of intent to murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I apologize, Your Honor... I'll do better next time. <thought>Who did Mr. Rimes bear a grudge against? There's only one answer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaaaaaaaat?! So the witness's intent was to kill the orca?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. The witness's intended victim was not Jack Shipley. From the start, it was all a scheme to kill Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca was his true target? But Jack Shipley is the one who died! The orca is alive and quite well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>Hmm. He's right... He wanted to kill the orca, and yet it was Jack Shipley who fell to his death. How did that happen? ...Wait a minute...! What if...? What if Mr. Rimes wanting to kill Orla was somehow connected to Mr. Shipley's death?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... At a loss for words, are you? What happened to your bravado of a moment ago? Enough of these reckless words, without any basis in fact!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's my contention that two incidents happened at the show pool. The attempted murder of the orca, and the victim falling to his death. First of all, in order to kill the orca, Mr. Rimes removed something from the scene. And, by so doing, he made it possible for Mr. Shipley to fall to his death.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did he remove?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. That remark was as salty as sea water... But wait a minute... Orla is a creature of the sea... And how would one kill a sea creature...? So THAT'S the answer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">So what be yer answer? Smartly now, Mr. Lawyer! How did I try to kill the orca?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't tell me you're trying to claim he tried to kill the orca by draining the pool water?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly what I'm claiming. To help the defendant with the cleaning, Marlon Rimes took charge of Orla... ...with the plan to kill Orla in the show pool! And because the pool water was drained... ...it made it possible for Jack Shipley to fall to his death in the show pool!</line>
<line speaker="???">Rimes:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">How would ye know such a thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know because of Orla's record here in the TORPEDO data system. This system continuously records data on the subjects it monitors. From Orla's record, we can tell exactly when she ate... or didn't eat.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sink me! Nobody ever told me 'bout that dastardly contraption!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only a few of the Shipshape Aquarium staff know about this system. According to Orla's record, she never ate in those early morning hours of the 20th. You planned to kill Orla, and that's why you didn't feed her!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You're wasting time. What proof do you have of that? Perhaps the orca simply wasn't hungry?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack, he's right. I don't have any proof...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If Orla simply didn't eat, then that would create an inconsistency. Where did her fish go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her fish? Good question. Where did it disappear to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fish? What does it matter? What relevance does it have to the case? Cease this stalling by asking inconsequential questions! Stop delving into the depths of the orca's stomach and delve into the case instead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you driving at, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How could the fish disappear? Somebody must have eaten it... So who came to the show stage and ate Orla's fish? I think I might have a pretty good idea...</thought> I believe there must have been a visitor to the show stage that Mr. Rimes didn't notice.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Visitor? Are you trying to introduce yet another suspect at this eleventh hour? If you utter more of your careless remarks, Taka won't look favorably upon it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't plan to utter any "careless" remarks. <thought>Whether my remarks will actually be related to the case or not, I don't yet know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Boss. If Taka comes this way, I'll fend him off! But do try to keep your remarks "careful"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow, Orla's fish disappeared... Somebody must've visited the show stage, but who?</thought> This was the visitor to the show stage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe that Sasha Buckler visited the show stage!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defendant...? What basis do you have for that claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that Orla's fish disappeared. Ms. Buckler must have eaten up all of the fish meant for Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Is this some kind of jest? Do you actually believe the defendant ate the orca's fish?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe it could be a possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...No. No, I don't believe it could.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did Orla's fish disappear? I'd better think about it a little more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe Dr. Crab visited the show stage!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...The witness from before? Do you have any basis for that claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that Orla's fish disappeared. He most likely decided to feed Orla some fresher fish... ...and took the old fish away somewhere. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Somewhere"? Where? And where is this "fresher fish" he was going to give her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where...? Yes. Hmm. Good question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, there is no "question" about "where" this penalty is going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did Orla's fish disappear? I'd better think about it a little more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe Rifle the penguin visited the show stage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">First an orca, now a penguin?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Why would ye be sayin' such a thing, Mr. Lawyer? I didn't see Rifle durin' the wee early mornin' hours! Do ye have any proof Rifle visited the show stage? If ye be a lawyer of any salt, show me yer evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bottom of Rifle's feet were pink for some reason... That fact is a clue that Rifle was indeed at the show stage. I have to present that piece of evidence that connects Rifle to the show stage!</thought> Now to prove I'm a lawyer worth my salt! This is the proof that Rifle visited the show stage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rimes:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. I quite agree. That evidence doesn't support your claim, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, shiver me timbers, Your Honor! Ye have a fair sense of rap music!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bottom of Rifle's feet were pink for some reason... That fact is a clue that Rifle was indeed at the show stage. I have to present that evidence that connects Rifle to the show stage!</thought> ...I promise to present some much more credible evidence this time, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! What a cute little sign. Look at all of those adorable stars!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These stars are actually starfish. Ms. Buckler painted this sign. In the early morning hours of the 20th, she left this sign at the show stage to dry. Mr. Rimes kept an eye on the sign for Ms. Buckler while the paint was drying.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Aye, that be true! But what be yer point?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On this sign... ...is proof that Rifle visited the show stage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proof of the penguin's visit? I'm afraid I don't see it... Where is this proof that the penguin visited the show stage? Please point it out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It might prove it, but then, on the other hand, it might not. No one can say for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I can say for sure that you are getting a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ungh... Do you really think this sign proves Rifle was at the show stage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do. If you take a good look, you'll see the marks of her passage. And if you check out Rifle's data in the court record, you'll get another clue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I expect a better answer out of you this time, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A couple of the pink starfish are shaped a little differently from the others.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you're right! They look almost like little leaves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rifle had pink paint on the bottom of her feet. These little leaf-like shapes on this sign are actually Rifle's footprints. Rifle made these footprints by walking on the sign before it was dry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! What cute little penguin prints!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So there are footprints... What of them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Marlon Rimes was watching over this sign at the show stage while the paint dried. And during that time, the penguin paid a visit. According to the TORPEDO data system... ...we know that Rifle ate something that morning of the 20th. Most likely, Rifle ate the fish meant for Orla that was at the show stage. Orla's snack was a small quantity of fish. Even a penguin could have eaten it all.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Begad! Rifle ate Orla's fish...? Who be ye to say Rifle ate Orla's fish? She could have picked up food anywhere! But that doesn't change the fact that I really WAS at the show stage. After all, I had to help move the skull rock. It couldn't have been moved without me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The witness claims he never saw the penguin. How do you explain this contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Both Mr. Rimes and Rifle were at the show stage, but Mr. Rimes didn't see her. So where could Mr. Rimes have been at the time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono, if you aren't up to the task... ...I could disprove this witness's testimony for you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I leave it to Prosecutor Blackquill, Sasha will be declared guilty. I can't let him interrupt this line of reasoning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Let's try to figure out how things looked when Rifle came to the show stage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes was at the show stage, keeping an eye on Orla and the sign.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we know it must be true, because he helped move the skull rock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then Rifle came in and walked over the sign...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But wouldn't Mr. Rimes notice Rifle if he was right there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, let's think about where Mr. Rimes could have been... Is there a place in the show stage area from which Rifle couldn't have been seen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Now that you mention it, maybe you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, Mr. Wright! We're all counting on you, here! Try to imagine yourself as a high-powered attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, I'll do my best. <thought>Um, what's with the "imagine" part?</thought> Okay, let me try to figure out where Mr. Rimes must have been.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Inside the pool? But, you're right. If he was inside the pool, he wouldn't have noticed Rifle. So are you saying Mr. Rimes was underwater the whole time Rifle was eating?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, not underwater. <thought>When I think about what he was trying to do, the answer is clear. Now I'm finally starting to get the whole picture!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Just like yesterday... Must you two always be whispering to each other? Why don't you admit that resorting to a penguin will get you nowhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The penguin is a "key point"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The show stage pool is very deep. If Rifle came to visit while Mr. Rimes was at the bottom of this pool... ...he would have never noticed Rifle!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Arrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orcas can be out of the water for a short time without sustaining damage. But if they're out of the water for a long time, they weaken and eventually die. In order to kill Orla, Mr. Rimes had to drain the pool. And while the pool was drained of water, Mr. Shipley fell to his death. The show stage pool is about 65 feet deep, just like the orca pool. Without water in the pool, a person could be made to fall 65 feet.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes probably wondered what to do. If he continued with his plan to kill Orla, how would he dispose of Mr. Shipley's body? So he devised a plan to kill two birds with one stone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? How...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes went down to the bottom of the pool and put the victim's body in the rock. He then had Ms. Buckler move the rock and the body together.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And the witness made the defendant do this somehow without arousing her suspicion?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Mr. Shipley told Ms. Buckler that she couldn't perform in the new show. Ms. Buckler became upset, and wanted to switch back to the old version of the show. So Mr. Rimes conveniently suggested that she take and hide a prop for the new show. Mr. Rimes then manipulated Orla, using her singing and lifesaver tricks. He schemed to have Orla find the body while Ms. DePlume would be standing witness. He saddled Orla with the false charge of murder so that Orla would be put down!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arrrrr............! Raaaaarrr! GRAAAAAAAAARRR!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the fact that the witness didn't see the penguin...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Shows that when Rifle visited the show stage, Rimes was putting the body in the rock. At the bottom of the pool, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who would have thought the presence of a penguin could prove the witness's actions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's working! Just a little further now and Sasha will be proven not guilty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you think you've won this battle, you are sorely mistaken. Your theory is based on the notion that the witness could manipulate the orca. Witness, can you control the orca's actions?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............! Of course not. What kind of bilge be that? I be but a simple animal keeper!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If my memory serves... ...wasn't Ms. Buckler the only one who could issue commands to the orca?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. The judge's blade is sharper than the lawyer's. If you wish to do battle with a witness, you'll need a honed blade. Where is your sword of evidence that Marlon Rimes could manipulate the orca?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>Rimes had to have manipulated Orla in order for his plan to work. But how can I prove it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it appears this line of reasoning has become unsustainable...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've analyzed the hearts of all kinds of people. I have enough experience to see when I look into your heart that you haven't given up. So that objection was my way of speaking up for your heart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............! <thought>She's right. Why would I become a lawyer again, only to give up? I have to keep fighting!</thought> Athena, thank you. With your help, I've remembered the old "Wright way."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The "Wright way"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I'm not finished with presenting my argument!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Do you have anything else to ask this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You've cross-examined all the witnesses and presented all your evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The central figure...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The one involved in not only the case a year ago, but this current case, too... I've never called her as a witness, but it's time to do so now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Who are you talking about? I demand you tell the court immediately! Who is this "central figure" in both cases?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have the final say over the verdict. Just as I have final say over assigning penalties.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gah...! But there's no way I can give up now! There's one figure at the heart of both the case a year ago and this recent case... Even if this individual can't speak, she can still help me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Mr. Wright. Please give us a proper answer this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense calls the central figure in both cases... Orla the orca!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You intend to cross-examine an orca?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! Cross-examine an orca? Ye must be addled! It be impossible, says I!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This absurdity is beyond the pale. How do you expect to question an orca, a creature incapable of speech?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Very well! Do what you will, then! But if you fail to garner anything from this little exercise with the orca... ...I hope you realize the reward for your efforts will be the defendant's guilty verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............I'm ready and confident.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So... Cross-examining Orla, huh? That was a bold move, Boss. Now all we have to do is figure out how Mr. Rimes manipulated Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Now it's Orla's turn to help us save Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An orca defendant yesterday, an orca witness today! This is truly unprecedented. But even though this is highly unusual, I'm prepared to allow it. Bailiff! Ready the witness telecast! We'll have a ten-minute recess while the telecast is being set up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leave it to you to think of something like calling Orla, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she's the only one who knows all the answers, after all. I just talked to Pearls, and she said Orla seems to be feeling fine. Now we have to try and figure out how Mr. Rimes manipulated Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If we put Mr. Rimes and Orla together, maybe we can get some kind of clue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And I can't forget about that strange set of prints of Rimes's, either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I r-EEL-y appreciate your trying to save both Orla and me. I had no idea Marlon hated Orla like that... I feel like I've been shocked by a torpedo ray.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Of course he would hate the killer whale that murdered his girlfriend right in front of him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! Ms. DePlume! You've been watching the trial?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh, yes! I came to make a declaration of war!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A d-declaration of war...?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">No matter what the results of today's trial, I will report the truth in my new book. Even if that truth goes against what I wrote in "The Killer Killer Whale."</line>
<line speaker="Crab">I don't know what the truth is... Not even about what happened a year ago...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Crab...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Azura died right in front of my eyes, in the middle of a pirate show... She suddenly fell from the orca's back and began to thrash around in pain. The orca was singing a song, and then started head-butting Azura over and over. Finally, the orca took Azura in her mouth and brought her to the side of the pool. Just before she died, Azura was holding her chest, in obvious pain...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She was holding her chest...? Wait a minute... Could it be...?</thought> ...I don't think Orla was to blame for the incident a year ago, either.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think the cause of Ms. Summers's death might have been... ...her heart condition.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Heart condition? What heart condition?! I never heard anything about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Summers had a prescription with Hickfield Clinic for a heart condition. The orca didn't kill her. I think it's possible her heart condition did!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">What?! Azura had a heart condition, too?! I guess she hid it from everybody, just like I did...</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............! So that means... ...the orca was innocent a year ago, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a theory, but... I think the orca head-butted Azura to check on her... ...and then did the lifesaver trick to rescue her.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">............So there was no need to put the orca down after all...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you really did intend to put Orla down...?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">...No. Jack and I... ...were against such a thing from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But you said you were going to "euthanize the orca"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... I've been wondering about that...</thought> Dr. Crab... About this capsule... It's not a poison, but a sleeping drug, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That's right. Even if Orla attacks someone... ...or even if the Center for Dangerous Animal Control demands she be put down... ...I never had any intention of killing her. I would use sleeping pills to make it look like she was dead, and then set her free. That's why I purchased so many sleeping capsules.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! THAT'S why?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">............! I never considered the possibility that that poor woman's death was illness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems pretty disturbed to be wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">............I simply want to know the truth. That is why I will tell you who my client is. The day I witnessed the owner's death, I was there at the request of the animal keeper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Marlon Rimes...?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That is correct. That day, my client called me to ask me to investigate the orca pool.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-he must have wanted you to witness what Orla was going to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Why did you decide to tell us this?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">My desire to protect my client was standing in the way of the truth. I couldn't allow that. I will be watching to see how this all unfolds. Good luck to you, blue and yellow duo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that was quite a bombshell she just dropped, and so casually, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That woman really is a free spirit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">Do you remember what you said yesterday, Mr. Lawyer? That you'd expose any secret if it would help save Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I remember. It's my duty as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Well, I just wanted you to know that I don't blame you for exposing the aquarium's secret. It may put me in hot water, but if it helps save the orca... Let me clue you in on another secret. Focus on the orca's song.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The orca's song, huh...? <thought>What could he be hinting at?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Mr. Wright! Looks like it's time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's go back in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You've got it, Boss! We're gonna go in there and save Sasha and Orla--together!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene. Is the witness, Ora Shipley, commonly known as "Orla," ready?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, the orca is present, but I highly doubt she understands what's going on.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet? Fweeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! Just as adorable as yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I distinctly remember you being afraid of her on several occasions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Wright. How do you propose to cross-examine the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I intend to have the young lady there with Orla help me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hello, everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That young lady... Didn't I meet her once before, a long time ago?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's Pearl Fey, my old friend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, well. Didn't she grow up to be a lovely young lady! Aaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I have no interest in this chit-chat. On with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! This is all your fault! Why are you dawdling?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How is this my fault?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now hear the testimony of Ora Shipley!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet... Fwe fweet. Fwe fwe fweet fwe fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">........................ ............Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Do you seriously intend to cross-examine this orca?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she is a key witness for the defense, after all, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Every time you come to my courtroom, you open my eyes to a new way of thinking. It appears this will be another one of those times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes! He's given me the go-ahead.</thought> I'd now like to put the witness and Mr. Rimes together to see how he manipulated the orca. <thought>Hopefully, Orla will have some kind of reaction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! Fine by me! But naught will happen, I tell ye!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet? Fwe fwe fweeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Mr. Rimes was right. Nothing happened...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I shouldn't have expected it to be easy... Hmm. How DID he manipulate her...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono, I hope you realize... ...that if you can't prove how Rimes manipulated the orca with this cross-exam... ...your defendant will be declared guilty immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Yes. I realize that. <thought>This is my last chance. I have to figure out how Rimes commanded Orla to do her tricks!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please begin your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix: </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. This is your plan of action? If you are incapable of interpreting orca speech, this entire exercise is folly!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe? Fwe fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ Oh, Orla! You're so cuuuuute!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Wright-dono. Surely you don't intend to continue this farce...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I do. Ms. Shipley, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix: </line>
<line speaker="Orla">*whoosh*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm getting a strong reading of happiness. Maybe she thinks she's doing a show?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I demand serious witness testimony! This is no time for fun and games! If you continue this mockery, I will subject you to forty lashes with a wet fish.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Not a wet noodle? That just sounds... fishy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, speaking from experience, anything is better than forty lashes from a whip...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will please caution its witness to conduct herself with propriety.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix: </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Orla won't do what you want unless you give her the proper signal. ...Ooh, doesn't Orla sing beautifully?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Taka's singing voice is much more melodic and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Meh. Neither one should quit their day job.</thought> Please continue your testimony, Ms. Shipley.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix: </line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Perhaps she's hungry? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Fey, could you give Ms. Shipley a snack?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Certainly! One moment...</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a heartwarming scene. It reminds me of my granddaughter with her pet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wow. Your granddaughter must have a pretty large pet...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Stop all this pet prattle and get on with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I could actually communicate with Orla, this case would be solved in an instant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even if we can't understand what she's saying, at least we can understand her heart! If we can just figure out how Mr. Rimes commanded her, I'm sure Orla will confirm it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did Mr. Rimes make Orla do those tricks...? We have to find the answer somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet fweet fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But she's such an adorable creature! I never get tired of looking at her!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I, on the other hand, have had more than my fill of this tomfoolery! Enough is enough!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sounds like Prosecutor Blackquill is about to blow his top... What should I do? Should I continue the cross-examination?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm not finished with my cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... You have just about exhausted my patience, Wright-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! Please finish as quickly as you can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor... But I'm not really sure how to continue, to tell the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Rimes had to have commanded Orla somehow! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Do we have anything in evidence he could've used...? <thought>With Orla, it's not like I can present evidence that contradicts a particular statement... Guess it doesn't matter which statement... Hmm. What could be used to command Orla?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm done playing games! I will now explain how Orla was manipulated by Mr. Rimes! <thought>In order to respond to a command, Orla needs to hear the sound of a whistle. But Mr. Rimes isn't a trainer. I doubt he'd know how to give the signals himself. So that means... he must've had help! So how did Mr. Rimes issue commands to Orla...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I agree that evidence seems patently wrong. I enjoyed the comedy of errors, myself, but I must give you a penalty, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. No verdict yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rimes isn't a trainer. I doubt he'd know how to give Orla signals with a whistle himself. So that means... he must've had help! I'd better rethink this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sasha told me an interesting story about Ms. Summers...</thought>  </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Azura used to send her boyfriend videos of herself teaching the orca tricks. I used to help Azura take the videos on her TV phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Most likely, Mr. Rimes still has these videos of Ms. Summers.</thought> ...Ms. Fey, could I ask for your help?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of course, Mr. Nick. What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're using Mr. Rimes's TV phone, correct? I'd like you to examine it for me. Please look for videos of Azura Summers issuing whistle commands to Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... videos...? I'm not too sure how to do that, but I'll give it a try... My apologies to Marlon...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono... what are you up to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll see in a moment. <thought>If Pearls can find those videos for me!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! I found them! I found some videos like you described. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did? Thank you, Ms. Fey! <thought>Just as I suspected!</thought> How did Marlon Rimes get Orla to do those tricks? I will now show you... ...with Mr. Rimes's cell phone! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">His cell phone?! Are you implying he used an app?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Fey, see if you can issue Orla a command.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Me? Can I do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You might be able to, if you play a video with a whistle signal in it. If there's a video of the lifesaver trick, please play that. Before you do, though, please put the practice dummy in the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">The practice dummy? All right... In it goes! ...There. It sank to the bottom. Now I'll play a video.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Orla is diving down, heading straight for the dummy!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee! What a smart girl you are, Orla! The lifesaver trick was a complete success, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Ms. Fey. You were a big help. <thought>Now I have proof!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Unbelievable! You actually pulled it off...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was... the lifesaver trick we saw yesterday! Is Ms. Fey an orca trainer now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor. I'll explain after we try one more trick. Now let's see if we can command Orla to do the singing trick. ...Ms. Fey. If there's a video of the singing trick, please play that. </line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Certainly! ...Let's see. Is it this video? </line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh my! Isn't she wonderful! That was the Swashbuckler Spectacular song!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho. What a lovely singing voice!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ It wasn't bad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way, how did Ms. Fey give the orca those commands?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Marlon Rimes has something on his phone that his girlfriend, Azura Summers, sent him. They're videos of Ms. Summers issuing commands to Orla with a whistle. If they have Orla listen to the sounds of the signals, anyone at all could command Orla! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! Anyone at all?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I believe so, Your Honor. All they would have to do is play those videos. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Please submit those videos as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm getting the sneaking suspicion the judge just wants to try it out for himself...</thought> Ms. Fey, could you send those videos to the TV phone here?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">All right. Certainly!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Got them! All right, I'll try playing one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this was a training session a year ago, huh? But wait a minute... There's something about that song that bothers me...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the orca can be commanded using videos on a cell phone... ...then that means that Marlon Rimes could have manipulated the creature! </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes! You can't talk your way out of it now!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ I have to commend you. That was very good proof. I concede Marlon Rimes could have manipulated the orca. But isn't it true that the defendant could have done it as well? All she would have to do is use the whistle, the whistle she knows how to use so well. And she wouldn't have had to use those videos... Surely you admit it's a possibility? She could have easily had Norma DePlume witness the singing and the lifesaver trick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's trying to argue it was equally possible for Sasha as it was for Rimes, is he? But is that true? Let me think about that for a minute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That's right! Those weren't just simple cries. It was singing! As I approached the pool, the killer whale suddenly started singing! It kept head-butting while it sang the Swashbuckler Spectacular song!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The culprit made sure Ms. DePlume heard the song and saw the lifesaver trick. Could Sasha have shown these two tricks to the witness?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As Prosecutor Blackquill said... Ms. Buckler could have shown these tricks as well.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Just as I claimed! And isn't it much more natural to assume that it was the defendant who did it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Huh? </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. It does appear that way to me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...W-Wait! Can I take that back?! Please let me have a do-over!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Take it back"?! "Do-over"?! Mr. Wright, are you trying to make a mockery of my court? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...But hold on. Could Sasha really have created those exact same conditions?</thought> But, come to think of it, I doubt Ms. Buckler could have produced those exact conditions. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And on what basis do you make that claim?! Show your sword if you want to challenge me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I don't think Ms. Buckler could have created the same conditions as the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You challenge me to a battle? I hope your sword is sharpened... Let me see those sword skills of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't you worry... My sword is drawn and ready! My sword is... evidence that the two tricks couldn't have been shown at the same time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Maybe if I just don't say anything, it'll all work out somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Are you giving us your best imitation of Prosecutor Blackquill?! Speak up and give the court your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. Silence, is it? Then I will reward your silence with a penalty. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I guess it didn't "all work out somehow"... Ms. DePlume said she saw these two tricks at the same time. But didn't I have a piece of evidence that contradicts that possibility? I think my sword is finally ready now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume said in her testimony that she witnessed these two tricks at the same time. However, that fact is inconsistent with how Orla performs tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How Orla performs tricks? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla can't perform two tricks at once. She performs only one trick per whistle signal. That's how she's been trained.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. In other words, it would be just like, with a dog... ...if you tell him to both "sit" and "shake," he won't do them at the same time. Am I understanding it correctly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's the idea, Your Honor. <thought>I wonder if the judge has a dog?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh... Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! What a farce! So are you saying that the witness somehow managed to produce an impossible scenario? </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! If the creature's own trainer couldn't do it, how could I?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Yes, it's a mystery, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defense is claiming that Marlon Rimes manipulated the orca... ...but if you cannot explain fully how this was done, your argument doesn't hold water! If you can't straighten out your own theory, would you like me to straighten you out?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... no, thank you! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm. So Orla can't do two tricks at a time, but Ms. DePlume saw her do it... This logical inconsistency means there's a flaw somewhere. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was Ms. DePlume lying...? Or is it not true that Orla can't do two tricks at a time..?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Ms. DePlume had no reason to lie about such a thing. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If it really is impossible for Orla to perform two tricks at once... ...then maybe either the lifesaver trick or the singing trick was... faked?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Faked"...? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Maybe Orla only performed one of the tricks... ...but it was made to look like she performed two! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Maybe"?! How do you expect to conduct a sword battle with conjecture?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like I'd better present some evidence here, and fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Although I am concerned about your profuse sweating, Mr. Wright, allow me to ask you... Which of the two was faked, the lifesaver trick, or the singing trick? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The lifesaver trick was faked!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The security footage plainly shows the orca performing the lifesaver trick. Norma DePlume also stated in her testimony that the orca was singing. There's no indication that either one of these tricks was "faked"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Gah. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense appears to be at a loss for words. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But Sasha said that Orla couldn't perform two tricks at once. If the lifesaver trick is clearly shown on the security footage... ...then that means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Allow me to ask you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Surprisingly enough, they were BOTH faked!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If that's true... then what was the orca doing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What? Oh, um, she was performing some other trick!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The singing trick was faked. The lifesaver trick was faked. Are your qualifications as a lawyer also faked?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I'm beginning to wonder about that point, myself. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Orla was obviously performing some kind of trick. But which of the two was faked, the lifesaver trick, or the singing trick?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Allow me to ask you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense wishes to argue that the singing trick was faked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And on what grounds do you base your assertion that the singing trick was faked?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor. This piece of evidence will not prove that. In other words... this piece of evidence is... a fake-out! And if this evidence is a fake-out, then the singing trick was a fake-out as well!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss, I don't think that makes any sense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Momentum is key at times like these. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can hear every word you're saying, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm still confident it was the singing trick that was faked. Wasn't somebody looking at something and saying the songs were different...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I ask you once again, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a recording of a recent Swashbuckler Spectacular. In this recording, Orla sings the same song she sang for Ms. Fey earlier. But Ms. DePlume said this song is different from the one sang a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The song is different...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please listen to the song in the video from a year ago, sent to this cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwe fweet! Fwe fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. It sounds quite different from the song Orla sang for Ms. Fey earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet, this is the same video Ms. Fey used to issue the command to Orla to sing. By having Ms. DePlume listen to the song recorded in the cell phone video... ...the true culprit made Ms. DePlume think Orla was singing the song from a year ago! Only Marlon Rimes, the owner of the cell phone videos, could have done this!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But Ms. DePlume said she heard the orca singing right in front of her! How do you claim he made her think that? How was the song recording played?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I intend to explain that, too, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The answer lies somewhere in the orca pool visitor's corridor. Marlon Rimes played the song recording by using this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... he could have used it with some kind of... thing, and played it... somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That "somehow" is what I'm asking you to explain!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your ambiguous answer has earned you a very unambiguous penalty, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So where DID he play the song recording from...? There's only one answer...</thought> Prosecutor Blackquill! This time, I'll explain how the song recording was played properly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume heard the song while she was in the orca pool visitor's corridor. There's a speaker in that corridor, so that visitors can hear the orca's sounds.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And you claim the song was played from that speaker? How?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Here's how Rimes played the song over the speaker in the visitor's corridor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do I really have to explain? This piece of evidence is actually a microphone. Testing! One, two, three... Testing!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I guess the test failed... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Although you test my patience, I will not fail in my duty to assign you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, Phoenix! You can do this! What do I have in evidence that could play a song over a speaker...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes could broadcast the song in the video to the speaker by using a walkie-talkie! And he could get Orla to do a trick by letting her hear Ms. Summers's whistle signal, too. He played the singing through the speaker, and he made Orla do the lifesaver trick. All of this was the doing of the true culprit--Marlon Rimes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gaaaaaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what you did, isn't it... Mr. Rimes?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Ngh............ ARRRRRRRRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it! Now we can save both Sasha and Orla! Just leave it to Cap'n Wright's Swashbucklin' Lawyers to win any case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't remember agreeing to that name...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So it actually WAS possible for Mr. Rimes to manipulate the orca! I'm stunned. I see we will need to hear more from this witness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes. The time has come for you to tell the court the truth!</line>
<line speaker="???">Rimes:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What do you mean, "impossible"?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I shall sing ye a li'l shanty dissin' yer scurvy theory! Hark ye well, now!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">YO! WALKIE-TALKIE BE BROKE 4 REAL! MR. LAWYER'S FREESTYLE GOT NO APPEAL!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Here we go with that "flip-flop" music...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Broken...? Of all the flimsy excuses! <thought>"Bilge-suckin'"? That was uncalled for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You probably broke it on purpose after the fact!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arrrrr! That be untrue, li'l lassie! ...Although I can't prove when it really was... Lucky be it for me, ye lawyers be the ones who have the provin' to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... After everything we've uncovered, he still won't admit it! Somehow, I have to prove that he still could have done it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">YO! WALKIE-TALKIE BE BROKE 4 REAL! MR. LAWYER'S FREESTYLE GOT NO APPEAL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Of course I be sure! Although... it doesn't have me name written on it or anythin'... But ye can't prove it be not me walkie-talkie, now, can ye?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll never save Sasha this way... I have to figure out how he got a command to Orla!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If Rimes couldn't get a command to the orca, your theory crumbles. Everything you've done will all go up in smoke!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I be not on the prosecution's side, neither, mind ye. The defendant be innocent, says I! But, either way, me walkie-talkie was broken, and that be the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! If ye be accusin' me of thievery, let me see yer proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right. This evidence tells who you stole the walkie-talkie from! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr... Har har har! *chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp* AHOY! YO! YO! YO HO HOOOOOOO! YO ME BUCKO, YOU BE TRIPPIN'!? AIN'T WORTH GOING ALL IN! Ye say the walkie-talkie be not mine? The "proof" ye just presented doesn't prove aught!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............I guess you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. That piece of evidence doesn't tell us anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wasn't there somebody involved in the case who lost their walkie-talkie...? I'd better take a look at the evidence again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Our aquarium may look like a band of pirates, but thievery...? Arr!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">BROKE B4 DEPLUME ON DA SCENE! BROKE B4 WRIGHT COULD EVA DREAM!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The burden of proof is on you! If you can't do that, then we can end this cross-examination right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">AHOY! YO! YO! YO HO HOOOOO! PROOF THAT IT BROKE? BRO YOU A JOKE! LAG EVEN A SECOND &amp; YOU GON' CHOKE! WRIGHT WANNA PRESS ON EVERY WORD? NOPE! JUDGE GON' JUDGE UNDETERRED! YOU GON' FRONT? THEN BRING THE PAIN! OR STOP AND WALK AWAY IN SHAME!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, he makes me so mad! We gotta come up with our own freestyle, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let's get him back with evidence instead, shall we? No singing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please continue your testimony about the walkie-talkie.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">LEGIT GOOFED DURING CLEANING TIME AYE. BUT BILGE-SUCKING LAWYER SPITTIN' LIES!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">After I helped Sasha with the cleanin', I dropped it by accident and broke it. Ye wish to see it? I still have it with me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does indeed appear to be broken.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Heh heh. With me walkie-talkie broken, there be no way I could have done what ye said! I couldn't have given the orca any commands!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, your walkie-talkie broke! Isn't that just SO convenient?! Mr. Rimes, I think you broke it on purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Miss Lawyer, none o' yer false accusations, if ye please! I broke it on purpose? Where be yer proof?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ungh... I-I don't have any proof...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If his walkie-talkie was broken, it throws a monkey wrench into my whole theory. When he let Pearls borrow his cell phone so casually yesterday... ...he must've already been confident I wouldn't be able to prove anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Har har! Ye'll ne'er get me to agree that that poxed orca be innocent! If somethin' be not done about her, she'll get Sasha one day, too! The orca killed the cap'n! It weren't me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ So you intend to continue to claim that the defendant is innocent, do you? But I won't stand for that... Now, then, Wright-dono, what's your next move?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I would like to examine that walkie-talkie, if you don't mind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly. Here you are.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see if there's any way to tell when the walkie-talkie was broken.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If he gave Orla that command, then it couldn't have been broken at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">[Tap and slide on the bottom screen to rotate the evidence. / Slide the screen to rotate the evidence.] Tap again if you notice anything of interest.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can also zoom in and out to get a better look. Now, let's check every last inch of it for anything "off"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A walkie-talkie shaped like a sword... Pretty clever. But I don't see anything odd. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, a sword walkie-talkie in and of itself is pretty odd, I guess. But let's keep checking it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Darn. It IS broken. It doesn't seem to work... ...Wonder what would happen if I thump it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Hey, it's not an old TV, you know! Please don't break it any further! Let's keep looking!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Look at these. They look like... tooth marks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. A bite this big... I wonder if it was Orla?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... A walkie-talkie... with tooth marks...? Didn't we hear a story like that just yesterday?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It was the walkie-talkie Azura used right up until her death. In the middle of the show, the orca brought Azura up to the surface in her mouth. She left tooth marks in Azura's walkie-talkie... The captain said he always kept that walkie-talkie with him so he'd never forget...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rimes said this walkie talkie was his... but could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Heh heh. Naught odd about it, don't ye agree? Arr! Time to give it up, Mr. Lawyer! Forget the orca! Just save Sasha, says I!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I can't do that. Now that I'm finally a lawyer again... ...how could I hold my head up if I made my client so miserable?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! A stubborn one, ye be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">After I helped Sasha with the cleanin', I dropped it by accident and broke it. Heh heh. With me walkie-talkie broken, I couldn't have given the orca any commands! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">This walkie-talkie has Orla's tooth marks on it. Does that give us any kind of lead...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think these tooth marks change the meaning of another piece of evidence... <thought>I won't stop until I find the clue I need to save both Sasha and Orla! I have to uncover the truth about this walkie-talkie!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">DAT ORCA YO DON'T LISTEN TO ME, 'KAY? KILL THE CAPT? YO YOU SO CRAY-CRAY!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes... The orca could have received a signal from the defendant's whistle... Is this the point you're trying to concede?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">ROTTEN LAWYER! BLACK-EYED SAMURAI! TIME FOR A FREESTYLE DRIVE-BY! SASHA IS LEGIT. THAT THE TRUTH. ORCA IS GUILTY. YOU GOTTA ADMIT. I tell ye, it be all the orca's doin'! If ye don't belay all this bilge, I shall dis [sic] ye with some rap!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh... I believe you've already been doing that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not even sure where to start with testimony like this... I mean, how can we possibly prove when his walkie-talkie broke?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it's all pretty convenient for him, I have to say. All we can do is stay calm and keep pressing him for as much as we can. Maybe we'll find a place we can break through somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm, we tried pressing him, but it didn't change anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I don't know about that... His statements might not have changed, but the meaning of one of them may have...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! You caught something?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And that one statement just might be the breakthrough we need!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the defendant's statement... ...Mr. Shipley talked to her on his walkie-talkie before his death. However, no walkie-talkie was found near the victim's body. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr! Methinks the police just didn't look hard enough. Besides, the cap'n's walkie-talkie wasn't broken, be that not right? So his walkie-talkie has naught to do with mine! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm not so sure that's true. The victim fell to his death. It's quite possible his walkie-talkie broke in the fall. You stole the walkie-talkie after the victim's death, didn't you, Mr. Rimes?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I will not allow such leading questions, Wright-dono. If you claim the walkie-talkie belonged to the victim, show me your evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Certainly, I plan on doing just that. Please look at these tooth marks here on the walkie-talkie. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tooth marks? Ah, yes. I see them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's walkie-talkie... ...was a keepsake that used to belong to Azura Summers, who died a year ago. These tooth marks were left by Orla when she carried Ms. Summers in her mouth. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. If this is Mr. Shipley's walkie-talkie... ...then Mr. Rimes's walkie-talkie is still unaccounted for! Which means he could have used it to command the orca after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's not all, Your Honor. The only one who could have taken the victim's walkie-talkie is the culprit himself!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arr............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that Marlon Rimes had the victim's walkie-talkie... ...is proof that he murdered Jack Shipley!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Sink me............ ARRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR! ............Not so fast, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What?! He still won't admit defeat?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">This walkie-talkie be mine, says I! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then how do you explain the tooth marks on it?! </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I've had many the run-in with that orca meself! Arr! She bit me more than once, and me walkie-talkie, too! Evidence of our fights are carved here into me body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My goodness! I can clearly see the tooth-mark scars in your skin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...?! Are those really scars from being bitten by Orla?!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">AHOY! YO! YO HO HOOOOOO! YOU WANT ANSWERS? I GOT SOME MATE! THESE SCARS FROM ORLA? THAT'S RIGHT. DEM GIRL CAN PUT UP A NASTY FIGHT! DAT ORCA BIT ME AND LEFT ME SCARRED. HAD A REP TO PROTECT, SO I WENT IN HARD! SO MR. LAWYER, I WIN, JUS BEIN' FRANK! AND ORLA? HEH, YOU GET DA PLANK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't let him run this show! I have to find a way to prove the walkie-talkie belonged to the victim!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">And ye can forget about fingerprints! I always keep me walkie-talkie clean 'n' polished! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This man had everything worked out before he even took the stand! But I won't give up. There has to be a way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I found something interesting. The tooth marks on the walkie-talkie... Notice anything funny about them? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Funny? Funny, how?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something is different about them, compared to the other tooth marks we've seen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. The only other ones I remember are the ones on the practice dummy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's just a tiny difference. It might not even mean anything...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right now, we need to consider every possibility we can, no matter how small. <thought>If I can figure out what's different about the bite marks... ...maybe I can somehow prove Rimes's walkie-talkie actually belonged to the victim. Think, Phoenix! You can turn everything around, right here and now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Time to review the facts we have so far. With the intent of killing Orla, Rimes drained the show stage pool. But Rimes failed to kill Orla, and, instead, he tried to pin Shipley's murder on Orla. In order to manipulate Orla, Rimes must have used a cell phone and a walkie-talkie. But the walkie-talkie Rimes has is broken. I think it's the victim's walkie-talkie, the one he kept as a memento of Azura Summers. I have to find a way to prove that it is indeed the victim's walkie-talkie! Which piece of evidence left on the walkie-talkie could prove it belongs to the victim? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... Rimes said he wiped away any prints on the walkie-talkie... I doubt I'd find as much as a tiny fish scale on that thing. But I think the scales are starting to fall from my eyes, though! I think I'll give it another try.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have two pieces of evidence with tooth marks: the walkie-talkie and the dummy. What's striking about these two pieces of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They both have a similar yellow color... but I doubt that has anything to do with the case. Hmm. Maybe I'm starting to notice yellow more because of Athena...? I'd better refocus my attention.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I look closely, I see two different bite mark patterns... Hmm. Two variations, huh? Wasn't there a trick of Orla's that had two different variations as well?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... I don't think that's right. I think there was only one lifesaver trick... At this point, I kind of wish Orla knew a trick that could save me... But enough whining. Time to get back to work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A year ago, the orca's song and teeth marks were different from what they are now. What could be the cause of these two inconsistencies? What's behind the fact that the orca's tooth marks and song were different from a year ago?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if new teeth grew in, that still wouldn't explain why the song was different. That would be like my voice changing the second I lost my baby teeth... I'd better go back to the drawing board. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. If she learned a new song, that would go against the basis for my whole theory. Orla can only sing one song. I can't start second-guessing everything now. I guess I need to think about this some more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm beginning to think... there are two different orcas: the one a year ago, and Orla now. And if the orca a year ago wasn't Orla... ...it means the bite mark on the walkie-talkie isn't Orla's, like Rimes said it was. Now I can finally prove the walkie-talkie belongs to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you appear to be lost in thought there. Is everything all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I just realized something... astonishing, Your Honor... </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Your face is what's astonishing, Wright-dono.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Your rudeness is what's astonishing Prosecutor Blackquill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is this astonishing thing you realized?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Until just now, I thought the orca at Shipshape Aquarium a year ago, and Orla... ...were the same orca. However, two inconsistencies led me to a new fact. And that fact is... that there might be two Ora Shipleys! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Two different orcas?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">B-But that's impossible! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Explain yourself! What is the basis for this preposterous claim?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The orca's show song a year ago and the one now are different. I believe it's because the orca a year ago was a different orca. Two different orcas; two different songs. It explains the show song contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Wh-What be this bilge-water talk?! I don't understand! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm talking about the truth--truth that will finally catch you out in your lies. You claimed that the tooth marks on the walkie-talkie were Orla's but that's not true. The two different bite mark patterns on the walkie-talkie and on the dummy proves this.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! Two different patterns, ye say...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...While I will concede there is a possibility that two different orcas exist... ...bite mark patterns alone are not proof enough. I want more conclusive evidence! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...All right. I will show you conclusive evidence, then. <thought>So he wants to see evidence other than the bite mark patterns, does he? The orca a year ago and Orla have different songs and different teeth. Don't I have two videos on hand that can be used to compare those differences...?</thought> I will now submit two videos with which the different songs and teeth can be compared! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course they won't. That's because... I submitted the wrong evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you don't have to be so smug about it. Please try to show proper remorse!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to show evidence other than the bite marks to prove they're two different orcas!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please compare these two videos, one from a year ago, and one recent. As discussed, the two orcas are singing two different songs. Please also pay special attention to the appearance of the two orcas' teeth! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly do you claim their teeth are different? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's look for shots in the two videos where the orcas' teeth are shown. This is Orla in the recent video of the Swashbuckler Spectacular pirate show. As you can see, she has all of her teeth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What a healthy smile she has! I'm a bit envious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Next, let's take a look at the TV phone video from a year ago. <thought>Just as I thought! Their teeth are different!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I believe this smile looks a little different from the one we saw a moment ago. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, the orca from a year ago has one tooth that's broken off.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh............ If the teeth are different, then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. If the teeth are different, they of course leave different bite mark patterns! On the practice dummy, you can see Orla's uniform pattern, with all teeth intact. And on the walkie-talkie, you can see that one tooth is missing from the pattern. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see it! Just like the smile of the orca in last year's video!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The tooth marks on the walkie-talkie were not made by the orca we know as Orla! They were made a year ago by a different orca! </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">T-Two different orcas...? I-I can't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The statement that the tooth marks on the walkie-talkie were from Orla was a lie. The truth is... this walkie-talkie was stolen from the victim, Jack Shipley! And the only person who could have stolen it is... the true culprit, Marlon Rimes!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">No... Ye got it all wrong............ It be all............ the fault of that orca... Woah............ Huh............? Arr............! Ye got it all wrong! Blimey! It be the orca's fault! This can't be............ ARRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... it would appear... ...we should hear more from the defendant about Ora Shipley. ...Sasha Buckler.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Y-Yes, Cap'n Judge?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is what Mr. Wright claims true? Are there two different orcas?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I............ I, uh............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The secret that Shipshape Aquarium was hiding was about Orla, wasn't it? Dr. Crab told me to focus on the orca's song. He hinted it would be a clue.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">............Phoenix is right. The one we call "Orla" is the second "Ora Shipley." There actually used to be two orcas at Shipshape Aquarium. I used to call the first Ora Shipley just "Ora" for short. Ora and Orla are sisters. The captain rescued them both when they got beached on the shore. But Orla was in bad shape, and the ship's doctor had to look after her for a long time. Both orcas loved the captain, so we decided to keep them on at Shipshape Aquarium.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Why didn't you say anything about there being two orcas?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Well, because... ...after the accident a year ago, Ora was put down.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Ora is dead?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, the Center for Dangerous Animal Control demanded it... Apparently, the captain and the ship's doctor begged them... ..."We put the first one down, so please leave the second one alone," they said. Anyway, after the accident a year ago... ...the captain told us he was gonna put Orla in the pirate show as "Ora Shipley." He asked us to keep quiet about Ora's death until the time was right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What a surprising and complex tale... Did all Shipshape Aquarium employees know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">No, just a select few of us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Rimes, did you know about it?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Of course not... How would I...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me, Mr. Rimes. Did you plan on killing Orla from the start?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Yeah. I planned to do it durin' the cleanin', so I drained the pool. I figured if I didn't do somethin' about that beast, Sasha's life was in danger... Sasha trusted that orca... just as much as Azura did... I wanted to protect her! I couldn't help Azura... so I felt like protectin' Sasha was the least I could do... My duty... I built up my strength so I'd be ready to kill the orca. I even fought with sharks! But the captain realized my plan, and tried to save the orca...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And that is why...you killed Jack Shipley? Ah... Now the report from the crime lab finally makes sense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Report from the crime lab?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In court yesterday, you will recall I showed a photo of the victim lying on his back? According to the lab, the bruise on the victim's right wrist was Rimes's handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His... handprint?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I didn't know how it fit in the case until I heard Rimes's story just now. But now we can imagine the reason for it being there. Rimes must have made the handprint when he fought with the victim over the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A handprint made during a struggle...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...I don't care what happens to me anymore. I deserve the death penalty. I'm the one that killed the captain. Please give Sasha her "not guilty" verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. You accept your defeat well, I see. Let me be your guide... to hell. Get on with the verdict, Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It seems this unprecedented trial that began with an orca as the defendant... ...has finally come to a close.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sasha is saved! Orla is going to be so happy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sasha's "not guilty" verdict is coming... Why do I still have this nagging feeling? Rimes's handprint on the victim's right wrist... Was it really the result of a deadly struggle over the orca? I can't shake the feeling... that handprint has some other, hidden meaning... Is this trial going to end without revealing the whole truth...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. This court finds the defendant, Sasha Buckler...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! What is the meaning of this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to further explore this new evidence the prosecution just submitted!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...But what complaint could you have? You are about to get your "not guilty" verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see no need to further prolong this trial, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, we still don't know the entire truth of this case! This unnatural handprint Mr. Rimes left on the victim's right wrist... ...I don't think it was a result of a fight between the two men.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not the result of a fight?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Then what do you suggest it was?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Boss! What are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you remember that evidence we found at the show stage?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Evidence? What evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That mysterious mark might be the key to understanding the whole case. Your Honor! The defense would like to submit evidence that will expose the truth of this case! A mysterious piece of evidence that pairs with Mr. Rimes's unnatural handprint!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Pardon me, Your Honor. In my excitement, I'm afraid I made a mistake. <thought>Rimes left an unnatural handprint on the victim's right wrist... ...and I have another piece of "unnatural" evidence that has to do with Rimes!</thought> This time, I promise I will submit evidence that will expose the truth of this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Marlon Rimes left behind a very unusual set of fingerprints at the show stage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In what way were they unusual?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They were right-hand prints on the left side of the ladder. If one were to grasp the ladder in the same way as the prints, it would look like this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It looks like the ladder is being grasped from above.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor. And the handprint on the victim's right wrist shows it was held by a powerful grip. Marlon Rimes grasped the show stage ladder in an unnatural pose. If he was gripping the victim's wrist in this position...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gripping the victim's wrist...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Th-Then he must have been...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...It means Mr. Rimes was actually...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right. If we couple the unnatural handprint with the mysterious fingerprints... ...we see that Marlon Rimes was trying to save the victim's life!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">B-But that can't be...! It's... impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't we ask Mr. Rimes himself?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah............ I............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, we want to hear the truth directly from you.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Heh... I gotta hand it to ya, Mr. Lawyer... You got skills... Why...? Why did ya have to figure it out? It doesn't matter what happens to me anymore... I'm ready to die...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So is what the defense is claiming... true?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">The captain... He found out I drained the show stage pool... He rushed to the side of the pool, frantic to put some water in for the orca. And then... he slipped...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Captain! Gimme your left hand!</line>
<line speaker="Shipley">No, Marlon! You'll fall, too! Forgive me, Marlon... I didn't realize what deep pain you were in... But, please... Please don't blame Orla. It's nobody's fault... Not Orla's... and not yours............</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Hey............!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So............ Jack Shipley's death was accidental... Why didn't you tell us that you didn't kill the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Because... I have no right to live anymore. I'm ready to get the death penalty... The captain died because of me! And then, on top of it all, I used his body to frame Orla... I was gonna kill Orla, and she wasn't even to blame. She didn't do anything wrong... The only thing I can do now... is pay for it all with my life... I can't do anythin'... ...I couldn't save the captain... I couldn't avenge Azura's death...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Rimes, you have the wrong idea about Ms. Summers' death. Not even the first Ora Shipley was responsible for her dying. Ora--of her own accord--was trying to save Ms. Summers's life.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What............? What are you talkin' about...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Azura Summers suffered from a heart condition. But she didn't tell anyone, and she performed in the pirate show anyway. She had a heart attack and died before anyone could save her. I'm sure she didn't think Ora attacked her. There's nothing to "avenge."</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">No way... A heart condition...? She never said a word about it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe she didn't want you to worry about her...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">So I wanted to get revenge all this time... for nothin'...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So neither case was murder--not a year ago, and not this time, either. ...Your responsibility in this matter is great, but I believe you can be rehabilitated...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Marlon, you better come back to Shipshape Aquarium when you're done, ya hear? Orla and I and everybody will be waiting for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You still have a lot to offer, Mr. Rimes. Live your life and never give up... for the sake of those who are gone, as well!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I... I promise to make up for what I've done... even if it takes me my whole life! Mr. Wright... Sasha...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! I have seen countless trials, but never one that ended like this. I don't know how, Mr. Wright, but you always seem to manage to turn things around. ...I think all this excitement has taken a few years off of my life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is that praise... or a diss...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then! This court finds the defendant, Sasha Buckler...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Congratulations on your win!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for all your help today, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. All I did was have fun with Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! Fweet fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla, I'm back! Oh, I missed you, girl!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I'm so happy for you and Orla, Sasha! Everything turned out great!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Phoenix! Athena! I r-EEL-y want to thank you, from the bottom of my heart! Orla and I are both r-EEL-y grateful! I will now act out me gratitude with a li'l performance! Arr!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Miss Orca Lover! Don't you think you'd better take care of your health first?!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">A-all right, fine... I promise. No more shows until I'm better. I don't want anybody to worry about me, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Good! I'm glad that's settled. ...Hey, buddy. Mr. Lawyer... You just had to blab every single one of the aquarium's secrets, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Dr. Crab.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Nah, that's all right. I'm glad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was kind of hard to tell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">Although, thanks to you, they now know we're using the illegal TORPEDO system... ...but I think we'll be able to wiggle out of serious repercussions somehow. That writer lady is advocating for us, saying the law itself is to blame. She said she's going to look into getting the law changed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. Go, Ms. DePlume. <thought>She sure is a powerhouse.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Crab">There's one thing you didn't figure out, by the way. Keep this to yourself, will you? We don't want it getting out publicly. Remember that appointment I had written down in my calendar?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you mean, "Meet the captain at the orca pool at 7 am"?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">That note meant the orca pool of the Supermarine Aquarium, not Shipshape's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Why were you supposed to meet there?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Jack and I... ...We visited the Supermarine Aquarium once a month. Any idea why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, to get dolphin therapy treatment...?</line>
<line speaker="Crab">No, silly! Remember I told you? Jack and I were against putting the orca down from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">We just pretended to put the first Ora Shipley down. The Supermarine Aquarium is harboring her for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?! Oh! So that talk about large amounts of money you were paying them...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Once a month, the owner and the vet disappear from this aquarium. And I came to find out that, each time, a large amount of money was being paid out!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">We were paying for Ora's care. You wouldn't believe how much fish orcas eat! Now that it's been proven she was innocent all along, I think we can bring her back soon. Until then, keep it under you hat, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? What was he telling you about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, nothing much.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By the way... Orla wants you to give her a little celebratory prize!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! Fweet... fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla specifically requested that you give it to her, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. All right. Fine. <thought>Let's see... What can I give her?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I don't think she liked it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! What did you do? Orla's heart is overflowing with sadness! I think THIS is what she wants!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! Fweet! Fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh! She wants a snack, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Orla, it's coming a day late... but congratulations on your verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">*Fweet fweet!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, my! Hee hee! Aren't you lucky!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Ha ha! That's Orla's best trick! The "thank-you kiss" trick!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet! Fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Orla! I want to be next!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so the curtain fell on my first trial in years... I'm looking forward to the comeback of Sasha and Orla's Swashbuckler Spectacular. After all, I made a comeback of my own... as a lawyer. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been a while since I visited Shipshape Aquarium. Now that Sasha has recovered from her illness, she's performing today. There's still some time before the show starts... Think I'll wander around a bit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Hi, Phoenix! Hope you enjoy the show today! The orcas are excited and ready to go! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sure I'll enjoy-- Wait a minute... Did you say "orcas," as in, plural?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yup! Let me show you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Two Orlas? Don't tell me...! </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yup! You cod it right! Ora Shipley the First has returned to Shipshape Aquarium! We be the Three Pirate Sisters! Arr! We be out to stop the evil Scalawag League, led by Redstache and the giant octopus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Well, I don't want to get in the way of their rehearsal... Guess I'd better go.</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, if it isn't blue boy! Did you come for my book signing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Ms. DePlume. There's a book signing?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes, my new book is just out. It's called "Shipshape Aquarium: Don't Pull the Plug." The book signing will be held here in this room. After all, the vet owes me a favor.</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Yes, she got them to approve the use of the TORPEDO. I'm grateful... ...but why does she keep coming to my lab to bother me every single day?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">My next work will be entitled "Sniper: The Penguin Leaves the Nest." </line>
<line speaker="Rifle">Kree! Kree!</line>
<line speaker="Crab">Gaaaaaah! Stop this cacophony! Why am I surrounded by carping females?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee, Dr. Crab gets all the ladies... I guess I'll leave him to it... Oops. It's almost time for the show.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Where have you been, Daddy?! Polly and Athena already went in!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">While we were waiting, I bought some souvenirs to take back to the village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to keep you waiting... I bet they'll love your souvenirs back home, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">By the way, I hear a certain someone is going to be in today's show!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A certain someone? <thought>I wonder who it could be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! It's almost time! The show's just about to start! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's go to the show stage, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I saved you all seats, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I can't believe I get to see the show again! I'm so happy, I want to dive in the pool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd better not. I think they'd call security.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You're welcome in the pool anytime, Athena! But Redstache is the best swimmer of all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Who have you got playing Redstache's role?</line>
<line speaker="???">Sasha! Ora and Orla are ready to go! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I know that voice!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yup! You min-now it! Marlon is back, and he's playing the role of Redstache! It be the new Swashbuckler Spectacular! Hope ye enjoy it, me buckos!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so, our pirates set sail for bluer seas under a sunnier sky. As for me... I set foot into the world of law once more as a full-time lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? In what way...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It does indeed expose something... the defense's boneheadedness. There is nothing untoward about that evidence, no matter how you bluster.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. There is nothing compelling in that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm definitely losing the judge's confidence in me here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My opinion? My opinion is that there is nothing wrong with it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... This is my first trial in eight years. It looks like I made a little mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is no excuse, Mr. Wright. I should give you eight years' worth of penalties! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been eight years. Can't he go easy on me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I hope you don't think waving your finger about aimlessly... ...is going to help you win this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I agree. I see nothing inconsistent with that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I must have the wrong evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I think I have something here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sensed something wrong with the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Let me show you which statement I thought was strange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. That would be a big help! <thought>Then I'll just have to compare the evidence with the statement she shows me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I don't see any inconsistencies in the testimony. This might be a good time to--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Press for more information? I think you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just can't help but feel that there's more to this statement than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll put my faith in Athena and press on that statement, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm. That doesn't appear to be the cause of his out-of-control emotions...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What could be the cause of his out-of-control sadness and anger?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It'd be hard to find them both at the same time. Let's concentrate on probing just one. He did make one odd statement I was wondering about... I highly doubt there were any spectators at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, good point! That just doesn't fit. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just to be sure, I'll explain how to probe one more time. Tap the Probe button at the statement that seems off! Next, point to what you think is causing his out-of-control emotions, the spectators. Finally, tap Probe again to complete the process!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's the cause of Mr. Rimes's intense anger?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't think it was directed at that... Let's think about who he was really angry at, and why!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we view your emotions alongside your testimony, we find the unexpected emotion-- <thought>Wait a minute... There really isn't anything strange here.</thought>    </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but I think maybe we made a mistake, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I think maybe you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's take another look! There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing of particular interest here. Guess I'll check out another spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Sasha Buckler...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. And I require no further time to deliberate on the defendant's verdict. This case is very clear. There is no room for doubt! This court finds the defendant, Sasha Buckler, not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sasha won her "not guilty" verdict... ...but Orla was taken away by Dangerous Animal Control and never seen again.</line>
</xml>