<xml>
<title>Turnabout Serenade</title>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for... how do I say that?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Machi Tobaye", Your Honor. The Pixie of the Arpeggio.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right, his trial. Court is in session!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The prosecution is A-OK, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, my opening statement, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no, actually... There was something else I wanted to ask you about.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...? Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Say you're going to visit someone in the hospital with an incurable disease... What do you say to them?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I mean, you wouldn't say "get well soon", right? You'd only be kicking them when they're down...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem, actually I'm going to visit someone who is terminally ill. ...Right after this trial. The Chief Justice's son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Chief Justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His son is afflicted with a most terrible disease... He doesn't have long, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So I thought I'd go pay him a visit. I thought saying something moving might be the order of the day.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why don't grown-ups ever just say what's on their mind instead of pretending?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's looking at me with something like... disgust.</thought> ...Hey! What are you looking at me like that for!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case... I'm a bit busy today, so let's wrap this up quickly. Prosecutor Gavin, your opening statement, briefly!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You're in luck, Herr Judge... I believe you'll be going on your hospital visit sooner than you think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">First, to review the victim in this case. Romein LeTouse, age 35. The global manager for diva songstress, Lamiroir. The cause of death: blood loss due to being shot by a large caliber revolver. This report has all the details.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">45-caliber... That's quite large, isn't it? A direct hit from that could knock a man off his feet.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">However, the bullet struck him in his shoulder. The damage to his body was slight... death was not immediate. Sadly, his blood loss was such that he could not be saved.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose the victim's condition could have been much worse, considering.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Two shots were fired. One shot missed, the other penetrated and passed through the victim's shoulder. Both bullets were found in the wall at the scene. Observe the diagram... ...This is where the bullets hit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... The court accepts this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If we're talking about a 45-caliber revolver... ...we must assume that the killer was adept at the weapon's use.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, apparently, weapons that size have a powerful kickback. If, say, the judge tried to fire one, it'd break every bone in his body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will take more care in choosing examples!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...As I was saying, the victim was shot backstage, in a dressing room. This dressing room has only one entrance: this door.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That does seem to be the case, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">However, there were witnesses who heard the gunshots.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's talking about you and Ema, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet when the witnesses entered the room... ...it was empty, save for the victim's body, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's... That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Exactly. This murder was impossible. ...For all but one person.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One person?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That is, of course... ...the defendant, Machi Tobaye.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only this defendant could have committed the crime? But how?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's quite simple. The circumstances of the crime scene make it clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I assume you have testimony to back up this claim. Let the witness please take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your name and profession, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ema Skye, I'm a detective for the police department. I was on security detail at the concert forum that night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ema seems... tired, somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Security at the concert, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Some security I was. Couldn't even stop a murder... ......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, don't blame yourself! Things like this happen! I've made even bigger mistakes in my career, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm sure that makes her feel much better.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I want to hear about these bigger mistakes!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In any case... Because you were on security detail, the crime was quickly discovered. And, we were able to identify the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You may give the court your testimony, if you would. Describe the circumstances of that day, and your discovery of the crime, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The night of the murder, I was on security backstage, at Prosecutor Gavin's request.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It was lucky that a detective was the first on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But that door was the only way out of the room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, pretty much.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then I don't get it. How can they say that Machi did it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like we need a bit more information.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, the defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The night of the murder, I was on security backstage, at Prosecutor Gavin's request.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The night of the murder was the night of the concert, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was a detective doing on security detail, might I ask? ...If it was only a concert?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">My thoughts exactly. But, orders are orders. Even when they come from rock gods.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, allow me to explain. I smelled something that day, you might say. The stench... of conspiracy. That day, at the concert hall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Conspiracy...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, isn't it obvious!? My keys! That whole morning, no, the whole day was ruined! And it's all because someone stole my keys! I couldn't ride my hog to the show, I couldn't open my guitar case...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There he goes again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't it possible he simply misplaced them?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Misplaced them!? Misplaced items don't just wander into a murder victim's hand on their own!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this!? Prosecutor Gavin, if your keys were in the victim's hand... That makes you a prime suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">..."Love, slow-acting and new. Atroquinine... is waiting for you..."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's singing something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does everything with this guy have to be so over-the-top?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The killing happened in the middle of my concert. I was... like a sailor, adrift on a sea of sound. Anyway, I didn't want anything else stolen. So I put the detective with the most time on their hands on the task.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. I can accept that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well I can't! What do you mean "time on their hands"!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Only people involved with the concert in some way were allowed backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...We were let in, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I didn't know about that! I certainly didn't invite you.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I gave the Fräulein special permission to be there. ...I wanted to see her again.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh boy! Did you hear that? We're officially involved now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gee, great.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Some other hangers-on tried to get backstage, but I drove them off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So no other "outsiders" were there, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">And then...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">At the beginning of the third set... I heard shots.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe we were having a chat when we heard the shots.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You were the one chatting. I was eating Snackoos.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! Hey! No snacking in court!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And you're sure the shots came from Lamiroir's room?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, absolutely.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, I'm the one being cross-examined here! Here, this'll keep you quiet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, thanks. So...MUNCH...how about it ...MUNCH...Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We were right...MUNCH...there. Hard to be mistaken about that...MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, either talk, or eat. Not both at the same time!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... *gulp* Right, so after that... ...me and Mr. Lawyer there opened the dressing room door.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I went into the room, filled with blaring rock music, and found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Rock?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Blaring, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When you say "rock", are you referring, perhaps... ...to this "rock 'n' roll" music that's so popular these days?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right, when we went into the dressing room... ...music was blaring over the speaker on the wall.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">They pipe sound from the stage into the backstage through speakers. That way people in the back can hear when they're supposed to be on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did it have to be so loud?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You don't listen to the Gavinners with your ears. You feel it with your entire body and soul! I always have the backstage monitors at full volume.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">When we walked in the room... ...the band was playing "Guilty Love", I believe. Making it easy to determine the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If you could hear that music playing...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Then everyone on stage for that song has an alibi. Including myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Anyway, I closed off the scene and started my investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I examined the scene and determined that only the defendant could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How could you know something like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">As I said, it was clear from the circumstances. Listen... We know there was only one exit from the room: that door. The small window only opened a tiny crack. And I was standing in front of that door. So, how could the killer have fled the scene? There's only one possibility: the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But that air vent was too small! Who could possibly...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's certainly no way you could get through. Nor me. The only one who could fit through... was a child.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A child...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Remember, access to those rooms was limited. Only those involved with the concert were allowed.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And of all the people involved with the concert... ...only one is small enough to be considered a "child".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The... The defendant!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The pixie of the arpeggio flitted up toward the sky... ...and disappeared from the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But that's just conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? There was no other way out of that room. You were there. You should know, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And... there is another vital piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence...? What!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Marks were found on the air vent grill. Traces that it had recently been opened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what...!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And something else was found, quite clearly. The defendant, Machi Tobaye's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That air vent was the only way out of the room! The defendant's fingerprints were found on the grill! ...Well, Herr Forehead? What fairy tale does this suggest to you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Only one could pass through that vent, that "doorway to heaven"... ...and that one is our pixie.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why are you looking at me, Apollo? Hey! I was out whooping it up in the audience!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this was his decisive evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Quite decisive, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know the circumstances under which the body was found... I was there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">An examination of the crime scene was enough to nail down the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure they have a good reason. <thought>They must have had a good reason to arrest Machi... ...And I'm going to find out what it was!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution has a rather convincing case. The only way in and out of the crime scene was watched. Making the defendant the only one who could possibly leave the scene. Simple, and decisive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we've heard enough to determine our verdict. Even if I wasn't in a hurry to make a hospital visit.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm sure the Chief Justice will appreciate the gesture. Unfortunately, we have no direct witnesses. Fortunately, the criminal left decisive evidence for us. That will have to be enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! It can't be over already!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I believe this trial is finished. If the defense has no contradicting evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The prosecution has presented our proof, clear and plain. If you have contradicting evidence... ...it'd better be clear and plain.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack, Apollo! They've got us on the ropes already! We'd better come up with something quick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know! I know! <thought>Think! What can get us out of this!? We need evidence, or a witness, that can prove Machi is innocent beyond a doubt. Without that... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice? Do you have contradicting proof that can overturn the prosecution's case? If you do, you'd better tell us about it now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it... and so soon! If I mess this one up, it's all over...!</thought> The court wants contradicting proof?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is prepared to show contradicting evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This should be interesting! What sort of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, what sort of evidence, Mr. Justice? Show us evidence contradicting the prosecution's claims!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence does more than contradict, it flips the whole case on its head!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Thank you for presenting evidence that is both clear and plain, as requested.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... Clearly and plainly wrong! I'm afraid the only thing flipped on its head here was you as a child, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My claim is clear: the only person who could have fled the scene was the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And there were no witnesses, either.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I fear the defense's options are limited, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr! There's only one way out of this... Evidence, or a witness, that can prove Machi's innocence beyond a doubt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's ask the defense once again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... don't have contradicting proof, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Too bad. Very well, this court finds the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">W-Waaait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What for?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We have, uh, what was it called? Contradictual proof? Anyway, whatever it is, we've got it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course it's true! Show 'em, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the heck are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, we give up now, Machi's really done for!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's right... If we give up here, we're finished. I need proof or a witness... I must have something...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, we'll give you another chance, then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin, you claim that there were no witnesses to this crime. Are you absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Absolutely. I'd swear it on my career as a prosecutor... And on my million-seller hit song "Atroquinine, My Love".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...There he goes again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's too bad, because there was a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho! Really now? But how did you come to possess knowledge the prosecution clearly does not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because I am the only one in the world who knows this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...What's going on? I just talked to him, and now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">......Nnnh......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>He... He's alive!</thought> Mr. LeTouse! Can you hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Cold... so cold... Witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're cold? D-Don't worry, you're going to be fine! Help is on the way!</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Can't s...see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hang in there, Mr. LeTouse! Tell me, who was the witness?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaat!? The victim said this before he died!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps he did... and perhaps he did not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All we know is what Herr Forehead says he said. It's no testimony, especially since it comes from the defense attorney himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But it's the truth! He said it! I even told you about it! But apparently, you ignored me completely.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's my policy to fully investigate everything I deem relevant. Clearly this rookie lawyer thinks he can tell me how to do my job.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That's enough! Mr. Justice, we need clear contradictory proof from you. This witness of yours, unknown to the prosecution... ...I hope you're right. Failure carries a stiff penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps... A stiffer penalty than usual is called for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Urk! There's no backing out now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear the name of your witness, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you claim that they witnessed the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is a bit unexpected. And you have proof?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, actually... <thought>Uh oh. I can't think of anything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know that look, Mr. Justice. It's the look of a man who's about to be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I doubted there was a witness in the first place. No one had time! They were far too busy rocking to our wild sounds!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My heart was handcuffed to the stage, I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I felt nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It's sad but true. Some people will never appreciate true art.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why's he pointing at me!? Think, how can I get him to accept there was a witness? I need some kind of proof...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's start over, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall Mr. LeTouse's last words.</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The siren... Ah ha! He meant the "Siren"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. The "Siren of the Ballad"... Lamiroir! Lamiroir was only on stage for the second set... ...and she had access to the backstage area. She could have been a witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My claim still stands. There were no witnesses to this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! Let's hear it from the horse's mouth then, shall we? We will now take a break from Detective Ema Skye's cross-examination. ...Please show Lamiroir to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir would say nothing the night of the murder... Not today, though. Today we'll drag that story out of her no matter what it is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is my distinct honor to welcome the Siren of the Ballad to our courtroom...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">You are too kind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, y-you can speak English?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... Yes I can. Though I am not very good. ...There is much I do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You speak so well! Have you spent time here before?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Actually, I do not know how I came by my knowledge of your language. Nor where I studied it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...? <thought>What does she mean, she doesn't know...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I, too, thought to call her as a witness. But I did not. I had a reason, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir... suffers from amnesia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Amnesia...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Lamiroir... is not my true name. Yet I remember nothing of the time before I was given it. ...Nothing of the time before I started singing on stage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa! She's even more mysterious than I thought!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As lauded singer Lamiroir, she lives a good life. There are little difficulties for her, thanks to her success. Yet... I did not wish to subject her to unnecessary stress.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. I care surprisingly little about people's pasts. You have nothing to fear in this court, Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Thank you. Yet there is something I do not understand. I am being called as a witness? What might I say? No one will tell me anything of what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir, let me be frank. I did not want to ask you up here to testify. Yet, that young gentleman with the wide forehead over there was adamant that you stand.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Congratulations, Apollo. You're the bad guy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, now that you're here, please give us your testimony. ...If nothing else, the sound of your voice is welcome. Tell us what you saw the night of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As for what I saw... I saw nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I must say, you sound wonderful just testifying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I hope he was too distracted to hear what she was actually saying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There you have it. She saw nothing that night. Now we can only pray that the defense has the sense to admit defeat. ...And refrain from detaining her here longer than need be.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, you just got badder, Apollo! Way to go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. Keep it short and sweet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir wouldn't talk to me the night of the crime. She must know something, and I've got to find out what!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As for what I saw... I saw nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you must have seen something! Mr. LeTouse named you!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. LeTouse... ...How can I tell you what I don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir! He said you were a witness with his dying words!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I do not know what he meant to say, but that night...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That night, I was invited to sing on stage, and this I did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It... It was a great concert.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">You heard me sing? Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was hoping to get an autograph later, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! This is a cross-examination! You're out of line! ...If anyone deserves an autograph here, it's me. One on my gavel would be nice.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's my autograph. Now keep this trial moving.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my grandchild will be so happy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Apparently his grandson is a big fan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let us continue, shall we? If you would, Lamiroir... ...Tell us what you did after your stellar performance.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I did not return backstage after the second set.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You did not return backstage once? Where were you then? What were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was cleaning up on stage. There are many things I must do for a performance other than simply sing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And was Machi with you at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Unfortunately, I do not know where he was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So much for an alibi for Machi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry Lamiroir, but I'm having trouble believing you.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You remember this brooch, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why that's Lamiroir's. She was wearing it for her song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Care to add that to the testimony, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This brooch was found after the murder took place. ...At the very scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Lamiroir. How did your brooch get backstage if you did not go there yourself? And, as Prosecutor Gavin has just told us... ...you had been wearing it during your performance that night!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this? Lamiroir, please explain!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">............ [Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...She says, "English is quite difficult."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That trick's not going to work here!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Your forehead may be large, but you are a lawyer, truly. But... you have missed one important fact."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What now?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"In fact, at the time of the incident... ...I went backstage, but only for a moment."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Think back to the moment of the crime. You know whereof I speak."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is she really saying all that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's she talking about, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right when the incident occurred... Ah! <thought>Is she talking about that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Watch this room for me. I have to call for backup!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right, understood. You want me to make sure no one comes in, right? Mr. LeTouse! Can you hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Cold...so cold... Witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're cold? D-Don't worry, you're going to be fine! Help is on the way!</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>..."Siren"? How can a siren witness anything...?</thought> Yipes! Ema!? <thought>What was that!?</thought> Wh-Who's there!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema! Did you see anyone just now!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? No...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I could have sworn I heard a door close...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... looked into the room. Just a glance, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So this was when your brooch dropped? That explains that.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It does. There was no other time I could have dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's ridiculous! You only looked in for an instant, but you dropped your brooch?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She has raised a possibility. The only thing that can counter that... is evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So she looked in at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Actually, I intended to go into the dressing room. I knew nothing of what had happened, of course. But the moment I opened the door, I heard a horrible voice.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead shouting, "Who's there!" no doubt. A horrible voice indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I closed the door immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that explains the brooch. Let's return to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's too convenient... She's hiding something!</thought> Lamiroir! You did look into the room though, right?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Testify as to what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Very well. Though it was only the briefest of glimpses...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">When my performance was finished, I went backstage for just a moment...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did you see in that brief glimpse?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I had only opened the door slightly when I heard that horrible voice...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And shut the door.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I have always wondered, Herr Forehead. Does that voice of yours lack a volume knob?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's my Chords of Steel, man. Just back off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I saw nothing. The late Mr. LeTouse's body was behind a wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A wall...? Was there a wall there?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"[Borginese speaking]" is what in English?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A "division" or "partition", I believe. It was a large dressing room, divided into two halves.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And the murder took place in the inside half. I guess that partition might have hidden the body...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"The late Mr. LeTouse's body", you say?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know something more about Mr. LeTouse's death than you are saying.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could see you trying not to remember... But the effort made you swallow! ...You can't fool my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">! ...It is true. It was so terrible, after all. Why did Mr. LeTouse have to be shot?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One moment, Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was that you just said? "Why did Mr. LeTouse have to be shot?"</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She was hiding something, I knew it!</thought> Lamiroir, I'm afraid you haven't realized it, but... ...your words just now contradict your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Eh? How could that be!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Take this! Lamiroir contradicted her own testimony, and I have the evidence to prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">If I do not misunderstand the meaning of "contradiction"... ...it is you who contradict, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Your evidence... is meaningless.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! Wrong evidence! Gotta think this over... What did she say again? "Why did Mr. LeTouse have to be shot"? That's right... That totally contradicts her testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell me, Lamiroir... How did you know he had been shot?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Eh. Well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Immediately following the incident, a gag order was placed on the scene. This is the document proving that. In your testimony, you told the court... "No one told me anything about the incident."</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Furthermore, you testified that you had "seen nothing".</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet you knew that Mr. LeTouse had been shot! How could you have known!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...! Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeoooooooowrk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Lamiroir! You aren't hiding something from this court, I hope!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That sweet song of hers was sounding a little too sweet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, now I remember. Please... allow me to add to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Of course. All we want to know... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She looks kind of pale, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She saw something, I know it. Even the victim said so!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I saw bullet holes in the wall, and knew Mr. LeTouse had been shot...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only a glimpse, yet you knew they were bullet holes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. I recognized them immediately. I have seen bullet holes before, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You have traveled the world as a singer... You must have sung in places far more dangerous than our country.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I go wherever my voice is needed. Those places... are many, these days.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's really cool! I hope I get to travel like Lamiroir some day.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I plan on recording my next album overseas. Their studios have a different sound, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. Maybe I should go on a Chords of Steel tour, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Then I was led by the police to Mr. Gavin's dressing room, and told to wait there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With Machi, correct? How was he then?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He seemed as he always does. Though I believe he was shocked by the news of Mr. LeTouse's death. Yet... He is not the type to show much emotion.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. He's given the police no end of headaches. He answers most questions with silence... and those glinting frames speak nothing. The questioning hasn't gotten very far.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">We sat there, waiting...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That was where I learned that something had happened... But I wasn't told the details.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How was the incident explained to you?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was told nothing in detail. Only that Mr. LeTouse died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course, investigations require some security.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But Mr. LeTouse was my manager! I wanted to know more. I should have been told. Both Machi and I were beside ourselves with concern.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Allow me to apologize. But please understand... ...keeping you in the dark was as painful for me as it was for you.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Think, what doesn't ring true about her testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...It's hard to imagine Lamiroir lying...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She might not be lying, but she's hiding something... <thought>What wouldn't she tell me the night of the murder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir. They call you the Siren of the Ballad... ...but lies are hardly becoming of such a creature.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A put-down worthy of our prosecutor, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Such put-downs are hardly becoming of you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Stop polishing your forehead and start polishing your character, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, can't I be cool for once!?</thought> Observe the diagram! Lamiroir, you looked in from the door for just a moment. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Y-Yes, that is so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There were bullet holes in the room, yes. But they were in the wall the door is on!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You see? Assuming you merely glanced into the room... ...you couldn't have seen those bullet holes!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeooowrk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid the defense has raised a good point. It appears you have been holding back something.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...And I must tell you? I must tell you what it is that I saw?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. The happenings in this trial are being recorded. And I'm certain it will be on the news in Borginia. You understand your reputation is at stake. It falls to you to avoid tarnishing it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Personally speaking... I still believe that cross-examining her will yield us absolutely nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But she knew how Mr. LeTouse died! And he named her as a witness! You must have seen something, Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Lamiroir... Please continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">... Very well, I shall.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you did witness the crime! And the killer was... a grown person, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ach. This is my first time hearing this, I assure you. Nice play, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Herr... er, Mr. Justice. You may begin your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Great going, Apollo! You were right about Lamiroir. ...What's wrong? You don't look too happy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This whole thing smells fishy... That's what's wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you were heading toward the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this is a little before she opened the dressing room door and dropped her brooch. ...About the same time Ema and I heard those shots.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way back...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There was something like a little window there... That's how I saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what exactly is something like a little window?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, well... "Window" is the best word I know in English. I think this is how it is said, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You need not worry, Lamiroir. Your choice of words is impeccable. There is a small window in the dressing room in question. Perhaps the defense remembers this detail?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That little window on the wall...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I, er, saw the crime from there.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There were two shots... I couldn't do anything to stop it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You are certain you heard two shots fired?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, quite certain. I was on my way to the backstage exit. This was when I heard a faint sound... like a gunshot. Wondering what it had been, I peered through the window. That is when I heard the second gunshot, much closer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And there were two bullet holes at the scene... no contradictions so far.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...It all happened on the other side of that window. There was nothing I could do.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But it wasn't Machi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It wasn't Machi who shot... Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, quite certain.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha... It amuses me that you would question her testimony. It is testimony in your favor! Isn't it my job to object?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, Apollo, what were you thinking!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy... Let's just listen to what Lamiroir has to say. Can you tell me how you were so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, of course. You see...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was a grown person! ...I know it was!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You can't ask for a better testimony than that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not so sure it's all that simple, Trucy. <thought>There's a critical flaw in this testimony... And I have to point it out, even if it isn't good for our case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A "grown person"... That's a little vague.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am sorry. My skill with your language is... lacking, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly you could at least see whether the shooter was male or female?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... It was a man. A young man.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you're sure of that?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, his voice was quite clear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Voice...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Looking at this diagram, it seems the dressing room was quite cluttered. It does seem likely that you wouldn't have had a clear view of the shooter.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As a singer, I rely more on my ears than my eyes. When I hear a voice, I do not forget it. That voice... was the voice of a man.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So you heard a voice. But wait... ...Couldn't that have been the victim, Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Absolutely not. Did I not just say that I do not forget a voice? If it was Mr. LeTouse who spoke, I would have known.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed. So you were at the window, and you heard the shooter's voice, the voice of a young man.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! This is a good testimony! That proves it wasn't Machi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... If this turns out to be true, it would cast this case in a considerably different light. What is the defense's opinion of this testimony...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well, I'd have to say it's pretty good. Vital, even. This shows that the shooter wasn't Machi...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Surely you can't be serious, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Why not!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Though it pains me to say this... ...There's something about Lamiroir's testimony that rings false.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Heh. Bravo, Herr Forehead. You're colder than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm sure you remember what the problem is as well as I do, Gavin.</thought> As has been established... No grown man could pass through that air vent. He couldn't have fled the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But that means Lamiroir has to be lying!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, and I know it's bad for our case, but I can't shut my eyes to this. <thought>Believe me, the idea was tempting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is as Herr Forehead says. Yet, this is not the only contradiction within her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What next!? <thought>What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir. I understand why you would want to protect Machi. Yet remember, you are the Siren of the Ballad... ...And lies do not become such a creature.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What does the prosecution mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! What's he talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How come no one bats an eye when he says stuff like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I recall the state of the crime scene quite well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The state of the room...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, and when the murder took place... ...that window was closed. I find it hard to believe you could hear a voice through it.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What!? B-But I... I'm sure...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Lamiroir. I have nothing but the highest regard for your musical sense. ...But my opinion of you as a witness is somewhat lesser.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But she's the only eye-witness we have!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So you say. And the victim named her, the "Siren" as the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right! That's what Mr. LeTouse...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We heard your claim. We even entertained the possibility. And it brought us to this. Herr Judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The prosecution requests that the witness... be excused. Please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I must honor the prosecution's request. There is indeed a question of the witness's credibility.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But if Lamiroir can't testify...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then we don't have a chance of proving Machi's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This cross-examination is over! ...Prosecutor Gavin. You may continue making your case.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Danke. Now where were we? Ah yes, I would like to hear from Fräulein Detective again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! Let me hear Lamiroir's testimony one last time...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the cross-examination is already over. Until such a time as a need arises... ...this witness may leave the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... I'm sorry I could not be of more assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">At last, back to the real trial. Ready, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... I hope I didn't just miss my only chance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fräulein Detective, how far had we gotten until we were so rudely interrupted?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I dislike saying the same thing twice. And I never repeat a song for an encore.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...If you would, Ms. Skye.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Hmph. I believe I was saying that the only way Mr. LeTouse's killer could have escaped... ...was through that air vent on the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes, there was only one door in the room. And a witness, you, was standing in front of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That air vent isn't very big, see. Kind of limits the people who could possibly get through.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I certainly would have a difficult time.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You sure would. Not that you would have been there in the first place, though. Remember, the whole backstage area was off-limits to people not involved with the concert. The only one who meets the conditions for our killer... is the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A virtuoso performance! I couldn't have put it better myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. She does state a clear case. Though, reading the report, something caught my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The circumstances of the defendant's arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The circumstances...? <thought>Again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, that's right, Apollo! Remember when we found Machi? That was bizarre!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's right... Why did Mr. LeTouse's body disappear from the room... ...and end up on top of that stage tower? ...Holding a guitar, no less.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A perceptive observation, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, er, thanks! It was kind of an accident, really. But you work in this job long enough... ...you get a nose for things. Eh he he.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The judge sure seems pleased with himself!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Very good, Fräulein Detective. Perhaps you can tie it all together for us. Why was the body moved? And how does that lead us to the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe Machi stole the body because of some lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir's... song?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes... "The Guitar's Serenade". You noticed its "code" too, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Its "code"...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All the events that day followed the lyrics to our song. First, the keys my "heart" held on to so tightly were stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then Prosecutor Gavin's guitar burst into flames on stage. Mr. LeTouse's life was taken by a bullet...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The rest hardly needs explanation... "Guitar, Guitar... Up together to the sky."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's mad! It's like a story out of some fairy tale!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I admit, I'd forgotten about the song... But there it is now, waiting for me... the grand finale, as it were.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! You know I was the one who first noticed that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've heard of jumping rope to songs, and counting to songs... ...But killing!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's a wild world out there, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! We've heard one song and dance, let's get on to the next: the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not so sure I'm going to be doing much singing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I believe Machi stole the body because of some lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who would steal a body just to match some lyrics!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I didn't believe it myself. But it can't just be a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is as Fräulein Detective says. Let us begin with the first verse. If you would, Fräulein Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? You want me to sing it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You are the witness, ja? Or did you want me to sing? I warn you, my fee as vocalist is not trivial.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Fine, fine! Er, ahem. Let's look at the first part of the lyrics, shall we? "When you stole away the keys my heart held on to so tight."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Indeed, my favorite heart-shaped key ring was stolen that morning.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Next, we go to the right page of the lyrics sheet. Where we find... "Burning on in my heart. Fire. Burn my love away. All away." As we know, Prosecutor Gavin's guitar burst into flame. "Like a bullet of love. Fire. Take my life away. All away." Mr. LeTouse's life was taken by a bullet.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Bravo, Fräulein Detective. Your singing... it's not bad. Now, for the finale! "Guitar, Guitar... Up together to the sky." As it says in the lyrics, Mr. LeTouse... ...was found with a guitar, high in the "sky" over the stage. No series of coincidences could be so well conceived!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's right. ...Scientifically speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What would Wocky have said? ..."That concert was wack."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's hard to argue when she pours her heart into it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, er, ahem! Anyway, the shooter...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He moved the body to match Lamiroir's song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does the prosecution have any idea why he'd do all this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You want my scientific opinion? "No clue." But, he clearly had a reason to go through all that trouble. Some deep reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A deep reason?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not only did he steal my keys, he torched my guitar! ...Unforgivable acts even if he had a reason... and worse if he had none!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The diva's complaints aside, I can't imagine someone doing this on "just a whim".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fräulein Detective! I take offense at that description...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, it does seem too well rehearsed, shall we say.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. This crime was planned for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No one in this country had a motive to kill the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... Mr. LeTouse spoke English! He may have come to this country before!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I looked into that, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...It was his first time in the country, it seems. Apparently, he learned English on his own.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You see? No one here had a motive to kill him, and certainly not in such an elaborate fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does seem difficult to imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Unless our famous prosecutor did it as a publicity stunt.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Wh-What did you say!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin! You did this to promote your song!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Of course not, and I am quite dismayed by the ludicrous nature of her claim. Why would I need promotion? Everyone already listens to my music.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They're even in my textbook at school.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And I'd never heard of them. What does that say about me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was just kidding! Don't get all worked up, glimmer-boy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And, Machi practically left his signature at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean by his "signature"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The bullet holes in the wall, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The bullet holes...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The revolver was fired twice. One shot missed, and left a hole in the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that means what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That dressing room isn't exactly spacious. Picture the shooter facing off with the victim in there. They can't have been more than five feet apart. It would be difficult, almost impossible to miss at that range.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Difficult to miss, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Very. Assuming the shooter could properly aim.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! Y-You can't be serious...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Machi! He can't see... ...That's why he missed?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's the only explanation that makes sense. He used sound and other senses to fire the gun... ...poorly.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That reminds me, the monitor in that room was blaring at the time, ja? Hardly ideal conditions for tracking by sound.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A blind shooter...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No wonder he missed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I knew those bullet holes would come back to haunt me. Think Justice, what do I do now!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, there were bullet holes left in the wall... ...but that doesn't prove the shooter couldn't see!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, there could have been a struggle with the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, that's certainly possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And... it might have been the revolver's fault.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The revolver...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The revolver was a very large caliber, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the shooter wasn't used to firing such a large weapon... Why, it could dislocate their shoulder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly. The defendant, Machi Tobaye, is, as you can see, tiny. It's not so hard to picture him firing the gun and missing entirely! The kickback alone would throw off his aim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A convincing argument, to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ha ha! Take that, smug prosecution!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That bit about Machi being tiny... ...and the gun throwing off his aim? Um, aren't you kind of, um... ...admitting that he did it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It does not matter why he missed. What matters is that the shooter was, without a doubt, the defendant. Even the defense seems to agree on that point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yurk! Uhh... <thought>Cripes! I really put my foot in it this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But, let's get the facts of the matter on the record. If you would, Fräulein Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will add this to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Adds statement">"From the state of the crime scene, I conclude the shooter was blind."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He couldn't see, so the first shot missed... ...As explanations go, it's airtight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears the shooter did leave his signature. I'm afraid this is looking bad for our young defendant. The witness may continue with her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You got it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "signature", you mean the bullet holes in the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. Allow me to explain it... scientifically. The murder weapon was fired twice. The shot that missed left a hole in the wall. Furthermore, there was no more than five feet between shooter and victim. Hard to miss at that distance.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, Machi can't see...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He would have had to use sound and other senses to aim... ...and miss.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And our music was blaring over the room monitor. Not the best circumstances for aiming by sound.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Which makes it very likely that the shooter was blind.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Thus the prosecution's position.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ahh! Nothing like a scientific explanation to get the blood pumping!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why's mine frozen in my veins, then...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">All of the evidence clearly points to the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, but you can't say that for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Please, none of those non-scientific objections. They're bad for my complexion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's so scientific about a murder to lyrics!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lyrics can be explained scientifically! ...Never underestimate the power of science!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Put that bottle of finger-printing powder down before you hurt someone, like me!</thought> OK, then explain it! Scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... I require more data.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hah! Likely story...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">From the state of the crime scene, I conclude the shooter was blind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can't say he was blind just because of those bullet holes in the wall! I think I've proven that!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I wouldn't call it "proof", per se.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You've merely raised a "possibility".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fräulein Detective has made a most logical conjecture based upon the evidence. Of course, there is more evidence than just bullet holes. The defendant was the only one who could have escaped through the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But wait! If he was blind... ...how would he know about the air vent in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ah, a very good point. Well, Fräulein Detective? If you would care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He certainly seems sure of himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Recall the crime scene, if you would. There was a stepladder below the air vent. As it happens, maintenance was scheduled for that day. Custodial staff went around checking all the air vents.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't believe it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Everyone backstage was told about the maintenance. ...Including Machi Tobaye. He would have known that there would be a way out at the top of that stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's... Why is this the first time I'm hearing about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You could have figured it out for yourself. You only needed to consider what that stepladder was doing there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Looks like the defense's objection has been squished by a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, Herr Forehead? Out of ammunition, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've never seen Prosecutor Gavin so... so aggressive! Maybe he's caught the scent of blood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Don't you have something? Anything? You know what we need... We need something to prove the killer could see! That'll put him in his place!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Proving the shooter was sighted would do it. That would take down one of their central points... Do I have any evidence that can prove that though...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine... I accept the prosecution's challenge.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As I knew you would, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What exactly am I up against here...? The prosecution is saying the shooter missed because he or she couldn't see... Therefore, Machi, who's blind, did it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will please present their evidence. ...Evidence that overturns the prosecution's claim that the shooter couldn't see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm not sure that overturns anything, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. Wrong evidence, I'm guessing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently both love... and Justice are blind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I have to think! There must be something... anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't think of anything that proves the shooter could see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your face does not exactly project... confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe you should just accept it and move on?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Grow a backbone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I couldn't even get a word in edgewise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The prosecution holds that the "shooter couldn't see".</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A scientific conclusion based on a thorough examination of the crime scene, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently not thorough enough. I have a certain piece of evidence that completely overturns your claim!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This doesn't look so good, does it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it doesn't.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... What do we do!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>First, we don't panic. Even though Machi's case is leaking water by the gallon. Gavin's on a roll, and it's up to me to stop him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is that evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The photograph of the crime scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't care much for the smirk on Prosecutor Gavin's face... But this is no time to think twice... Time to press on!</thought> Yes, Your Honor, the crime scene. There is something in here that decisively contradicts the prosecution's point!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then perhaps you'd best show us this "something". Get your finger out of the breeze and put it to good use, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, show us what you're talking about, Mr. Justice! The contradiction at the scene of the crime is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look! The contradiction's right there! Plain as day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Your finger has a force of weight... ...that I'm afraid your argument lacks, Mr. Justice. I see nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... What a time to mess up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe all he has added to our understanding of this photo... is his fingerprint. I would hope you could refrain from soiling the evidence, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps Mr. Justice would care to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The contradiction is right here!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The smeared blood stains...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I thought it was just my blurry vision. But it really was blurry! The way the victim's hand is raised above his head... ...Much like a gesture I have seen many times in this court.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's almost as if he wrote something...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah ha! I get it! At least, I think I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Get what, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When Mr. LeTouse was shot, he tried to write something! And what would he write but the shooter's name? And what would he write it in but his own blood? Pretty good, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Thanks for making my point for me...</thought> Yes, in fact, that's what I think happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does seem to be a distinct possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim wrote the killer's name... ...It's certainly a logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Drat! I just wish it wasn't all rubbed out like that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course it's rubbed out. Why, if I were a killer... ...I certainly wouldn't want to leave my own name behind!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Neither would I.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... No one has anything else to say?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...About what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the prosecution accepts this? You agree this was the victim making an attempt to record the name of the killer? ...And that the killer tried to rub the name out?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's your point?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's my point!? Let me ask you this: How did the killer know the victim was writing their name?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, Mr. LeTouse was writing something in blood. Once the killer saw what it was... ...Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once he "saw" what it was...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what did you just testify about the shooter?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I said... they were blind. Ack!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet the crime scene itself contradicts that! The killer had to have been able to see! Why would they rub out the name in blood otherwise?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah... ahh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">May I remind the court that the defendant, Machi Tobaye, is blind! He couldn't have been the shooter!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Urk... Immmmmmmmposssssibbleee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! P-Prosecutor Gavin! Please explain to me what all this means!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I mean, looking at this photo... It seems quite clear that the shooter could see! Yet, up until now...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It seems I owe the court an apology.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The Gavinners are a band with law enforcement ties, yet a murder occurred... ...during our concert! Apparently, this caused some confusion over jurisdiction. As a result, some reports were not filed in an entirely timely manner.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I... I'm not sure I like the vibe I'm getting here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey Apollo, look at him. Why is Prosecutor Gavin all relaxed and smiling like that? Like he knows something we don't... and he's about to tell us.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Heh heh heh. I've got an idea... Let's rock! ...With these documents. But before that. I have a question for the Fräulein Detective. If I may?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Tell me... Why do you think that Machi Tobaye is blind?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What did he say?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What are you saying? Of course he's blind!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">H-He's the blind pianist, right? So... So he's... Doesn't Lamiroir lead him around by the hand all the time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I have a report here on the defendant, Machi Tobaye. According to this, Machi Tobaye... ...can see perfectly well.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">His blindness was merely a publicity ploy by those clever Borginians. He can see quite well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But you said...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...What did I say, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead, not once in the course of this trial... ...have I claimed the defendant was blind. The only one who did was Fräulein Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bu-But that's...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A significant fact, yes! Consider: Machi Tobaye sees. And he was the only one who could have fled through the air vent. I see no problems with this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But what about the bullet holes in the wall?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, the bullet holes. I believe Herr Forehead neatly explained those for us. He didn't miss because he couldn't see. It was the kickback from the 45-caliber revolver. A simple accident, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How's that? I'm afraid your "objection" has just flown off for brighter skies...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is where the real fun begins, Herr Forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeeeeaaaaaaaarrrrrrrrrggh!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I knew you didn't have what it took.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You... You jerk! Just what was I in here for? Comic relief!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! Apologize!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha. Oh, sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's no way to apologize!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's angered the Trucy now. Look out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. If we can please end the bickering. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whatever! I'm not leaving! I can't leave like this. I'll come up with some clue to solving this case if it kills me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But your testimony has already given us enough to convict the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh, don't say that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah! Ah ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Ah ha" what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This blood stain... The criminal tried to wipe it off, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That seems to be what happened, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We might be able to find out what was really written here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Really...? You can do that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right, with this! It's called Luminol! Maybe you know of it? It's a chemical that reacts to blood.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah yes, have we done those tests yet...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hah! As if I'm going to tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The blood stains covered a section of the carpet. In order to perform blood tests, that section was removed and submitted. Perhaps we should request it here in court now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right! Go for it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I have to do the test?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You just have to spray the luminol on it! Simple!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A chemical that reacts to blood... I've heard of this somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes, I believe an analysis is called for. Have at it!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right, ready? It's easy as pie! Just touch the screen to spray an area. Here! Give it a try!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...The eyes of the entire court are focused on me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Your hand's shaking!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... Grrrah! Let's do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow... it really works!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This must be... this must be the power of science!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It says... "IPXX314206"... ...Is that the killer's name?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Maybe it is... if the killer was a robot!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah hah! I have it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I thought those letters "IPXX" looked familiar. This is an Interpol ID number.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I-Interpol? You mean the international police agency?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. Most are undercover agents working to solve international crimes. But why would he write that number...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would Mr. LeTouse even know a number like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good show, Fräulein Detective. Rock on.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your Honor! We can verify this number immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Daryan, are you there? Come up to the witness stand! Daryan... you heard what we need. Go check into this Interpol ID number.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Sure thing. Gimme 30 minutes. No... Gimme 27.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm not sure what to think of all this. The prosecution's case is airtight, or so it seems. Yet if this number is really that of an Interpol agent...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, wait, I know... What if Machi Tobaye's really an undercover Interpol agent?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That would be a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A possibility, yes. And one that would mark him as the killer for certain.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why did LeTouse know an Interpol ID number...? That's what I want to know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, we have some time while we await Daryan's report. Let's work on unraveling another mystery, shall we? A curious mystery concerning Machi Tobaye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fräulein Detective, please accept my apologies. I received word that the defendant could, in fact, see, just before the trial began. It seemed too much of a bother to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...You had me until that last bit.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Does this not raise a rather straightforward question?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, sure... Why did Machi pretend he couldn't see?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Exactly... It makes little sense. What do you think, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Machi Tobaye pretended he was blind... ...Do you know why?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How could he know!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait... Prosecutor Gavin knows why, doesn't he...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's known from the start of the trial. He's been leading us on the whole time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hmm? Something wrong? Do you think, perhaps, this is all some kind of game? Know that the moment I heard that report... ...I knew why.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose people who have sold over a million records really are something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What does that have to do with anything!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There was a reason why Machi Tobaye pretended to be blind. But it wasn't for his own sake. ...Getting the picture now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It wasn't for himself...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Can you present evidence that shows us why the defendant had to feign blindness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi had no reason to pretend he couldn't see... Which means... No. It couldn't be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Good show, Herr Forehead. It seems you've thought of something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... Why can't I figure these things out on my own? I hate having to take my cues from this guy.</thought> ...Very well. Look at this. This is why he was pretending he couldn't see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is... Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir and Machi Tobaye. Recall their relationship. In particular, their unique arrangement over the years before visiting our country.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lamiroir and her pianist... They would always walk together, she leading him by the hand. Even when they got on stage, she would lead him to the piano. She would walk all the way over there with him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. Because he was "blind". She led him at all times, never letting him go.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All times... Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet, we have just learned something that makes their arrangement peculiar indeed. Machi could see! Why did they have to keep up this act the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, wasn't it part of their, er, performance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think there's a simpler explanation. Machi did not need to be led by the hand at all. That can only mean one thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah! Aaaaaaaaaaa... Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really. It was all the other way around. The one who needed to be led by the hand... ...was Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this...? S-So you mean to say that Lamiroir is... she's...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. Lamiroir is blind.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! This is crazy, Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please... Please shed some sanity on this madness! The defense has made an outrageous claim...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The only thing outrageous I see about the defense is his vast forehead... ...Yet I see it is not vast in vain. This time. He's quite correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that makes no sense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What... is that supposed to mean? I don't see how it relates to the defendant's vision or lack thereof.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, see, it... <thought>...is the wrong piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I do see how your lack of an answer relates to this penalty, however!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha. Herr Forehead, I'm disappointed in you. Unless you're merely "feigning" stupidity? Ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Keep it up wise guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Recall the relationship of Lamiroir and Machi Tobaye. In particular, their arrangement over the years before visiting our country.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lamiroir and her pianist... They would always walk together, she leading him by the hand. Even when they got on stage, she would lead him to the piano. She would walk all the way over there with him!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. Because he was "blind". Or so we thought... She led him at all times. All times.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All times... Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet we now know that Machi could see perfectly well. Why keep up the charade?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, wasn't it part of their, er, performance?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There is a simpler explanation, Herr Judge. Machi did not need to be led by the hand at all. Which means...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaah! You don't mean---!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I do. It was the other way around! The one who needed to be led by the hand... ...was Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So you mean to say that Lamiroir is... she's...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Blind as a bat, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! This is crazy, Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I have no idea!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha. Herr Forehead, I'm disappointed in you. Unless you're merely "feigning" stupidity? Ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Keep it up wise guy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Recall the relationship of Lamiroir and Machi Tobaye. In particular, their arrangement over the years before visiting our country.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lamiroir and her pianist... They would always walk together, she leading him by the hand. Even when they got on stage, she would lead him to the piano. She would walk all the way over there with him!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. Because he was "blind". Or so we thought... She led him at all times. All times.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All times... Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet we now know that Machi could see perfectly well. Why keep up the charade?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, wasn't it part of their, er, performance?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There is a simpler explanation, Herr Judge. Machi did not need to be led by the hand at all. Which means...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaah! You don't mean---!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I do. It was the other way around! The one who needed to be led by the hand... ...was Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-So you mean to say that Lamiroir is... she's...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Blind as a bat, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! This is crazy, Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah! Wasn't she supposed to be the "landscape painter in sound" or something?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, since we have her here...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Why not ask Lamiroir herself? I believe she is still in the witness waiting room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo, what does this mean for our case!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't ask me! I had no idea she couldn't see... I hadn't even imagined it until now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Bring in Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Lamiroir. It pains me deeply to call you before us again in this way. And yet I must.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Please, do not be concerned on my behalf.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Those eyes... She really can't see? Really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... It is true.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">How funny it is that a tiny lie born in the Borginian countryside... ...would one day grow to entangle the entire world.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... So you are...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. As I mentioned before... ...I have no memory of the time before I became Lamiroir. Know too that my memories begin in darkness. The word "light" has no meaning for Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You may recall me saying something toward the beginning of this trial, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe I said it was unfortunate this crime had no "direct" witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now, Lamiroir, I must ask you to stand once more. Will you testify to the court about your eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Of course. It was never my intent to deceive any of you. May I begin, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh, yes, yes of course... Though I admit, I'm a little lost here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we're all a bit lost here, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I have no memory of the "light".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... this is a murder trial!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I apologize. It was part of my contract, you see. I was to keep my blindness a secret, no matter what. Music is everything for me. I never imagined something like this would...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She told us the truth in the beginning. When she said she "saw nothing".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Does the defense have anything to add?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... I'd like to cross-examine.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, what is there left to ask!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There was one thing in her testimony that bothered me.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps it is best we let you get it out of your system. Someday you'll come to understand... ...the importance of thinking for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defense may proceed. However... Be aware this court will not tolerate any questions deemed too stressful to the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...OK. <thought>There was only one part that bothered me... Just let me ask about that and I'll be happy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I have no memory of the "light".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you don't know why you went blind?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I do not. I may have been born this way, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It's fruitless to attempt to pry into her past. And, I might add, it's a delicate subject.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure we can reasonably expect Mr. Justice to do anything delicately.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! Why I oughta... take a deep breath and calm down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What I am now is all that I have. It is enough, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I debuted in a world of darkness and sound...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Weren't you nervous to hit the stage in your condition?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">No, not at all, surprisingly. It felt natural, singing in front of everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's not something just anyone can do.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She has talent, that much is quite clear. You might even say she is beloved by the gods of music.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Even without light, I live perfectly happy in my world of sound. If that is a talent, as you say, then I thank the gods responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about your PR motto?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">My producer came up with my PR line before he knew this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Perhaps your music reminded him of the Borginian scenery?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah ha ha. No, it was quite the opposite.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The opposite?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">According to my producer... ...my music has a certain "global" quality.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Global?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Multicultural, if you will. Hard to pin to one region. When people listen to it, they picture the country closest to their hearts. Which is why my music has reached so many.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a lovely story!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It sounds like this producer might have known what he was doing after all.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">My songs are nothing more than a white canvas. To me, the real landscape painter [sic] are the listeners. When I think of that, I do not mind how I am represented to the world so much. Yet, one thing quickly led to another...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">So, silly as it may sound, I had to pretend I could see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was that to protect your image as the "landscape painter in sound"?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That does not matter so much to me, really. But the label is quite concerned about it, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A landscape painter who can't see... that's like a pianist who can't play, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure you can compare your father to Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The world of commercial music is filled with these little white lies. Nothing is sacred when it comes to publicity...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Everyone on my staff knew, of course, but no others.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I suppose that's her confession, of sorts. There's just one part that bothers me... ...And I'm going to get to the bottom of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you say your staff, do you include Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Of course. He was my manager.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he knew... and that's what's been bugging me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something the matter, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe I know what is bothering our young defense attorney. ...You are thinking of when you discovered the body, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is he right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, I was.</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">......Nnnh......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>He... He's alive!</thought> Mr. LeTouse! Can you hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Cold... so cold... Witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're cold? D-Don't worry, you're going to be fine! Help is on the way!</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Can't s...see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hang in there, Mr. LeTouse! Tell me, who was the witness?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. LeTouse told me to ask the witness, and he named you.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would he do that? He knew you were blind!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... I don't know...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Tsk, tsk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What did I just say? You need to learn to think for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Meaning what...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There is no mystery here if you recall everything he said. Think of his last words once more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"The witness... siren"? We've heard them many times. Along with a little play-acting by our defense.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I remember them well myself, but that statement is not to what I refer. I mean what he said before that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Before? <thought>What came before that...?</thought> Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...That's right. He tried to tell you. When he said "can't see" he wasn't talking about himself. He was talking about the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Too bad the defense did not. Well, Herr Forehead? Try relaxing and "looking" at the facts first next time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Recall Lamiroir's earlier testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit. There were two shots... I couldn't do anything to stop it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But she couldn't have heard those gunshots! I thought we proved that...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That is not the most important point here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The moment he was shot, Mr. LeTouse "witnessed" her through that window. ...Why else would he have named her as the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But I really did hear them! Two gunshots... and the man's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Unfortunately, such a thing was impossible. The window was closed. We have already run a simulation, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But it was so clear... If I heard that voice again, I would know it in an instant...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">...Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Bailiff? Can't you see we're in session here!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">We have the results back from the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The investigation...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, the Interpol number that Mr. LeTouse left us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! Well let's hear it! ...We will continue this cross-examination afterward. Detective Crescend! Your report please!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I asked Interpol about that number. I'm sure you'll find their answer intriguing.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Quick work as always, Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, tell us about the number! Is the defendant a secret agent!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">"IPXX314206"... The agent registered under that number... ...was Romein LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Our undercover Interpol agent was Mr. LeTouse himself! He was apparently in the middle of an operation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, when he wrote those letters...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...He was trying to tell us his own identity. And a cautious killer tried to wipe them away.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. LeTouse was an undercover Interpol agent... So him being Lamiroir's manager...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Was just a cover, most likely.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">There's one other important detail I found.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, out with it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">It concerns that 45-caliber revolver, the murder weapon. Apparently, it belonged to Romein LeTouse. He had an Interpol permit to carry firearms. ...And the registration number on the revolver matched.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So the victim was killed with his own weapon, which makes sense. It's hard to imagine someone who wasn't an Interpol agent with such a large revolver.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the victim was an Interpol agent on an undercover op... I wonder how that ties into everything.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's got to tie in somehow, you'd think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thanks for looking into that for us, Detective Crescend. It's a great help.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, no problem at all, Your Honor. ...I'll be heading out...</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">La-Lamiroir! Is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That voice just now...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Daryan?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. Daryan, is it...? ............ It was him. I am sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was "him"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Y-You aren't saying--!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That voice I heard, talking to Mr. LeTouse... when I heard the gunshots fired. It was him! It was Mr. Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is this some kind of a joke!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...No way...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The courtroom fell into such a chaotic state, the trial had to be suspended temporarily. I'd never seen that happen before. Of course, it's not every day that you get an accusation like that one. Lamiroir, fingering Daryan Crescend. Not only is he a guitarist, he's a detective! Could it really have been his voice Lamiroir heard? Things were changing fast, and frankly, I wasn't sure I could keep up with it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! No wimping out now, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You may have seen the world, but I've seen your heart. You were flustered during your testimony just now!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... I do not understand what it is you are saying. Perhaps this is a joke, in your culture?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She doesn't seem very flustered to me, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. Maybe I got that one wrong. I have to look harder! I'll find that weak spot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Machi Tobaye...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>