<xml>
<title>Turnabout Big Top</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I've got a confession to make... I'm terrible at figuring out magic tricks...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Magic tricks?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep. Magic tricks are by their very definition tricks, right? But I can never figure out the tricks when I see them. I'm just not good at it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because the tricks are performed by pros. They do it so you can't guess the trick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But but... The trick Pearly showed me was incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls did a magic trick? Hmm... What kind of trick was it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's see. It looked like she pulled the end of her own thumb off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">First she put her right thumb next to her left hand, and then it just separated! She could move it up and down and everything! It was incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Was it kinda like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAT!? WOW! HOW'D YOU DO THAT!? Nick, you're like a real magician! See this is why I just can't figure out magic... I'm no good at it... Especially hard tricks like flying away from the scene of a murder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll take all the fun out of magic if you keep trying to figure it out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I'm reading that one! You know I'm studying the law now, right!? I put that bookmark on the page I was reading... Don't you dare move it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? You're reading!? THESE!? A bookmark, huh... Hmm... You mean this thing? It was only on the second page.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you have to start somewhere right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You do realize that you have 1000 pages to go right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Maybe you really should sell all these books, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you've been watering the plant everyday, right? I've been thinking about watering it too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, we don't want to drown poor Charley.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But he'd get bigger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does she want the office to look like a tropical rain forest or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... It's covered with dust. Maybe you should use your desk every now and again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of the newest member of the "Steel Samurai" universe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know about the new "Steel Samurai" movie they are making, don't you Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I heard that they're making a movie starring the new cast.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's already out! Critics say, "Time to commit 'hara-kiri' if you miss this action epic!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't say...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I bet the star will win this year's Hero of Heroes Grand Prix!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*yawn* Uh huh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright already... I'll go see the movie!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Let's hurry and wrap this case up so we can see it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lately they've been holding huge events at the Gatewater. It seems they've really become a top-class hotel. I wonder if that bellboy would remember us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any way out of this. We're stuck between a rock and a hard place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's no way we can solve the mystery of a criminal flying by tomorrow... I was thinking... Do you really think the criminal flew through the air? The only one who thinks that is Moe, right? He says that he saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true... Moe looked awfully serious when he said that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think he might be trying to frame Max?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that was it, he would have simply said "I saw Max". That would have been enough. There's no reason why anyone would believe "he flew".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... What if the criminal really did fly? There's only one person who could do that... Max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're really not helping my confidence here, Maya...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everyone seems to hate Max. Ben, Trilo, Moe... They all have nothing nice to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That magician does seem rather full of himself, doesn't he? Especially when he says things like customers only go to the circus to see him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He even hit Ben over the head with a bottle. But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But that doesn't seem enough to frame another person for murder!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it was proven that neither Ben nor Moe lied on the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe Ben saw the Ringmaster wearing Max's costume, but Moe clearly said that he saw Max himself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yeah... The picture of the scene. I wonder what that wooden box is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was probably left at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe there was only a bottle of pepper in that thing. It must be related to the crime somehow... This is fun, isn't it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not really... It may be fun to solve mysteries, but don't forget this is a murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awww... You're right. I should take things more seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No matter how you look at it, this is definitely Max's silk hat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's even a feather stuck in it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's something wrong with this hat though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe's testimony, right? "He left the scene wearing that dumb silk hat!" That's what he said, but the hat was found on the ground at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... This really is a mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa. Max used a broken bottle to crack Ben over the head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no... It broke because Max cracked Ben over the head with it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He must have really hit him hard then... I guess I should give it a try... For research purposes. Come here... I've got a nice bottle right here for you Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">YEOW!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's weird. It didn't break.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course it didn't!! You hit me with a plastic bottle!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you believe this cost three months of pay? Three months!! Trilo doesn't skimp when it comes to Regina. He's really in love.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a real glass stone. Its brilliance is amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet Money would love to get his hands on this again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll have to give this back to Trilo sometime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Twenty pounds, huh? That's pretty heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Especially since the only thing inside was a small bottle of pepper.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The more you think about it the more it starts to make your head hurt. But compared to tomorrow this will all be a happy memory.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tomorrow!? Don't get ahead of yourself Maya... Let's concentrate on today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You wanna know something Nick? I love to put pepper on my hamburgers. But I also like to put pepper on peanut butter and jelly sandwiches. Do you think I'm weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't seem to be in a very good mood today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I'm not... I have to find a criminal who has discovered the ability to fly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. I guess that would put you in a bad mood.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If Moe says that he saw a flying criminal, that means it must have been...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter with you!? You know that people can't just up and fly!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Max... He is a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without their bag of tricks, magicians are incapable of magic. Besides, what's the likelihood someone set up a flying device at the crime scene? Near zero.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What if they set something up so they could trick Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Maybe. But I get the feeling that would have been pointless...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Yeah... Sorry. I got nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must have been trying to think up a joke or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh! My sweeties!! You mind hurrying up and getting me out of this place!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're doing our best, Max. Just hang in there.</line>
<line speaker="Max">A little while ago, some people from a local TV station came by... They said that, since I'm a famed magician, "Let's make your very own TV special!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? What kind of TV special?</line>
<line speaker="Max">"Maximillion Galactica: The Great Prison Escape" It would be aired live.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! That sounds like it would be an awesome special!</line>
<line speaker="Max">But if I do the special before I'm acquitted, they'll never let me out of here for real.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it would surely be an unnecessary addition to your troubles with the law.</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's what I was thinking... But the production staff is already working on the show! If you don't get me out quick, I'll have no choice but to stage a real prison break.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem awfully calm about that possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'd have no choice. It would be a contractual obligation... That's show business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm. The night of the crime... You didn't happen to fly off into the sky, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Here is how everything went down, sweetie. At the time of the murder, I was sitting in the Ringmaster's room. Not to mention... Flying off into the sky is not just something I can do at will. I don't care what the stoogey clown says, it wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max! Max! Do you mind teaching me the trick behind flying?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Hmm... You'll have to forgive me, sweetie. The difference between me and cheap imitation magicians is that I keep my mouth shut. I don't teach people tricks, but I will say this much. It's much harder than you think.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was thinking about this in court today... I've got a favor to ask of you.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Anything for you, sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Be friends with the other performers in the circus!</line>
<line speaker="Max">FABULOUS! A great joke!! Why would I be friends with a bunch of hacks like that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...!</line>
<line speaker="Max">I've won on the world stage! I won the International Grand Prix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">International Grand Prix?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Performers should always look to perform on the world stage! But the performers at this circus are completely and utterly devoid of ambition! That is something that I can simply not tolerate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ambition, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something about what Max just said rings true to my ears...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh my! My sweeties want to hear all about the Grand Prix, don't they? To be honest though, I've told this story like 100 times already, so it's a bit boring.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're sorry to make you tell it again.</line>
<line speaker="Max">You must not have heard me... I am really sick of telling this story. But what can you do? I'm Maximillion Galactica. I suppose I can tell it again. ... Voila! Here, take a look at this! I just happen to have a picture from the Grand Prix with me. Just look at that fabulous stage!! That is the first stage that I ever flew on. I flew right over the audience! The crowd erupted into applause! At that time, I thought to myself that I could die right then and die a happy man. I'll never forget how I felt that night. The emotions... The acclaim...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow.</line>
<line speaker="Max">*ahem* By the way... I think everyone who is a performer should get to experience that feeling. I just wish I could explain that to the other people in the circus!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's incredible Max... I want a trophy too! Hey Nick! How about you buy me a trophy!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not how you earn a trophy Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Max">My sweeties, you can have this picture of my triumph... Just make sure you show it to all the other members of the circus. "Watch and learn!" That's what you should tell them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Learn how to get thrown in jail?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">This is definitely my silk hat. I don't suppose I'm allowed to wear it anymore am I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Max, this one of your uppi... I mean, excellent symbols, right?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's right. Honestly though, I only like it because of the feather in the brim.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max! How could you!? How could you hit poor Ben over the head with this!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I've been thinking about that lately... But he did call me a "no-good talentless hack of a fast food magician"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean Trilo said that? Not Ben, right?</line>
<line speaker="Max">There is no Trilo or Ben. There is only one Benjamin Woodman.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'm normally fabulous, but in this picture, I'm the king of the world! I even got a fabulous trophy and a super fabulous bust.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's really cool! I wouldn't mind seeing your trophy some day.</line>
<line speaker="Max">If you want to see one of my awards, you should just go to the cafeteria.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The cafeteria? You mean the one inside the circus tent?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Of course. The trophy isn't there, but the bust that I won is!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's in the cafeteria? We were just there yesterday. Nick, did you see a bust anywhere inside the cafeteria?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You hear that? It sounds like two people arguing...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Alright, let's do it. Are you ready?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Y-Yes... A-Ah... Wait...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Quit your whining! Let's just give this a shot already! Alright! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Row-row-row-your-boat!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Row-row-row-your-boat!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What are you doing!? Gently-down-the-stream! C'mon, you know that!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I'm trying my best, but... Trilo, this just isn't going to work...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Do you enjoy saying dumb things? You're going to have to be on your own someday! If you can't handle something as simple as this, was are you going to do then!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hello Ben. Hello to you too, Trilo.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What are you doing here!? Can't you see we're on a secret crash training course!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Secret crash training! Whoa.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Yes. Trilo wouldn't give up until I said we'd try out his idea for a new routine. So... We were trying to sing in a round for our new ventriloquism act.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In a round!? You can really do that!? That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">See! See! Even they are surprised by the idea!! I told you!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">They're not the only ones!! You even surprised me with your idea!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Once we've got a grip on the basics, then it's just a matter of practice!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Y-Y-You t-t-think so?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I almost forgot! I wanted to give this back to you.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Ahh! There it is!! Now that I've got this ring back, it's time to take one more shot at Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The murder took place right over there..</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You never really get used to the feeling of being where someone's life was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know... The Ringmaster seems like he was such a good man. It * <thought>[sic]</thought> so sad... For everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... I know that you already testified in court today...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You want to talk about what we saw, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Well, at first we thought it was the old man... Just looking at his walk and how he acted. Right Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Huh!? Oh, oh yeah. That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">But then we said hello and didn't even get a reply. Not to mention he was draped in those gaudy symbols.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What would you have thought if he wasn't wearing those symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hmm... What do you think Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">What!? Oh... Umm... I would have thought it was the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Something just isn't adding up here. I wonder who they really saw?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was hoping I could ask you about Regina...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I'm completely serious about her! That's why I'm waiting for her even now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? That's so sweet... But if you really wanted to see Regina, shouldn't you check out the tent?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hah! You haven't got a clue about things, do you sweetheart?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Waiting like this is part of being in love.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">If you had a clue, you would know that waiting is such sweet, wonderful torture. When your body aches for your partner's love... That's one of the best parts!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Y-Yeah... I-I knew that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Maya... She's so red she looks like a vine ripe tomato!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So how is this new routine working out?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Will you two just take a chill pill already!? Our routines are secret!! We're going to take the ventriloquism world by storm! It'll be a real revolution!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That sounds incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">But let me make one thing clear... We're not going to take on the world just because that stupid jerk said we should...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Max Galactica. "Performers should aim for the world!" Who does he think he is!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trilo, you seem to really be fired up about all this!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">He needs to realize that he isn't the only one who can conquer the world stage!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Mark my words... I, Trilo Quist, will win the Grand Prix!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're the man now, doll!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">"Row-row-row-your-boat!" will be the key to a glorious victory!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Not to rain on your parade, but wouldn't a more mature song be best?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hey... You've got to start somewhere right?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't screw this up! You've gotta be a part of this too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Um... Umm... Uh... I-I-I-I... Umm... That... U-U-U-Uhh... I-I-I-I-It's...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I guess we won't need you to look at this after all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Where's Regina?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno... But if she's with that tiger, I don't want to find out!! Let's hurry up and get out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe... Nick. You're kinda a chicken, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no no no... I'm just... Umm... Allergic to wild tigers!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max and the Ringmaster had their talk in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That could have been when the Ringmaster put on Max's costume and went outside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why'd he do that? Maybe it was cold or something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They still haven't cleaned this place up yet. If Pearly got one look at the state of this place... She'd slap whoever was in charge across the face!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Remind me to never invite her to my office.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, it's you two.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You look like you just got hit by a truck. Shouldn't you get some rest?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nah... I'm taking a rest right now, pal. I've been listening to come crazy clown's life story. Ms. von Karma told me to come down here and do this for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Being bossed around by a woman... I know how you feel.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let me tell you something, pal. Listening to that old clown sucks all your energy. Every time he's done talkin' he looks at you like you should be doing something...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I think he's waiting for you to laugh at his jokes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know that, pal. Do you have any idea how much your face hurts if you fake laughing that much?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Franziska really set you up bad this time, didn't she? If you ask me, she should be listening to Moe herself...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way, pal. You're not gonna get me to backbite a woman with a whip. No way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why are you defending her?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Prosecutor von Karma's always got her eyes on us. And every time you definitely don't want her to show up... *poof* There she is!! Don't show up... Don't show up... Don't show up... Don't show up... Don't show up...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like she's wound him pretty tight...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's directly above us as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? How's that possible?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">According to the clown, the criminal jumped from here and disappeared into the sky. If that's what happened, it means the killer passed right by this window, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I see... Who lives in that room behind the window up there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The acrobat's got his room up on the third floor, it seems. Pretty soon, Ms. von Karma's gonna start her investigation up there. So don't get any ideas of going up to the acrobat's room, got it pal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*shivers* V-Von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Once she's done with her investigation, I think I'll go up there and check it out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe's not here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If he was here, you would have been able to tell even before you stepped into his room. I'm sure you would've heard him laughing away... "Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think he is laughing at when he's all by himself?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I always thought he was just thinking up new jokes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He must really love his work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe's got an excellent pair of pajamas... Laid on his bed in an excellent manner.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They're not actually pajamas. They're actually costumes. Uh huh... I guess you could say that they're professional sleepwear.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You've really gotta give it to Moe... Slipping on a banana 100 times a day. That's incredible. Maybe I should try giving it a shot myself. I guess I'll start out by juggling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe you should start with spirit channeling... Just a thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is where Moe witnessed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well this is where Moe witnessed some craziness... <thought>I mean, c'mon... A flying criminal... Jeez... If we had a normal judge, he'd never believe something like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">These carrots like like they are the pick of the crop, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I still don't get why he went with carrots...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... What do you think about this theory? A long time ago, the circus was down on its luck. Moe was so hungry that he had to steal the horses food to survive. But he got addicted to their orangey goodness... Ha ha ha ha ha. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd laugh, but I think Maya might not be too far from the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tee hee... Clown equipment is so funny looking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's got a balancing ball, a unicycle... He's even got a trampoline!! ... But they're all broken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you've got to give them all a shot. Trying is the most important thing!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He sure seems to have tried them all... But were any of them useful?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ah! Wright!! Welcome to the wonderful, the fabulous, the cafeteria!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes... He's in an awfully good mood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Alright! You know what time it is!! Riddle time!! Why does everyone cry when they eat Mexican pizza?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">C'mon! You can answer this! It's easy!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Because cafeteria Mexican pizza is possibly a weapon of bowel destruction?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">*BUZZ* Wrong! Try again! OK! What do you think, girlie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Ahh! I got it!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">OK!! What is your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because they are in the Café Teary Eye!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly!! It's an incredibly sad place, that café. Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I did it!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's going on? He's being too nice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The kitchen is over here.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh yeah! Oh yeah! I wrote a new joke about the kitchen... Let's see... How did that joke go... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lemme guess... "What did the chef say to the chicken before dinner? Knife to meet ya!" It's gotta be something dumb like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">What did the chef say to the chicken before dinner? Knife to meet ya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a great one Moe. I would have never thought of that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Keep Our Cafeteria Clean!"</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Take a good look at that sign girlie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? It says... "Keep Our Cafeteria Clean!?"</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I added a question mark on there... I'm thinking that might be why the cafeteria is so dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are dirty dishes all over the place... It must have been too hectic that night to clean up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know I can't stand a mess Nick! I think you and I should clean this place up for them!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yay! You two are going to help us restore order to this cafeteria!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about? You're gonna help too!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Clowns can't clean!! We're here to throw pies, not clean them up! I'm a bust-a-gut boy, not a bus boy! Get it... It was two jokes in one! I'm fat and funny! Get it!? Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Moe. We got it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like they've left it exactly as it was on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I was in charge of the cooking that day. It was going to be a special menu.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? What were you going to cook?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Moe Moo Burgers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are those?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">A beefy burger filled with laughs and a sauce that tastes like my jokes. They're outstanding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So those burgers leave just as bad of a taste in your mouth as his jokes then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chair's been knocked over.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what it looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Looking at all this brings back lots of memories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I proposed here... To a girl on horseback. Of course, I was much younger back then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what happened? What was her answer?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Let's just say that my love was put out to pasture.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Today's been a really crazy day, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're telling me! I didn't think it was going to be so tough.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tough?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yeah. It was a tough crowd. That's what you call a crowd that refuses to laugh. For instance, it was such a tough crowd last night I had to smash watermelons.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I told them all a great story and even greater jokes, but no one busted out laughing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You even used the famed "No shoes, no shirt, no service" joke!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly! How can you not laugh at stunning comedy like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you 100% sure about your testimony today?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I saw that I saw! I swear! That creep just...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Flew through the air?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It wasn't exactly flying per say... It was more like floating. The silhouette of his face made me positive it was Max!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't see a Psyche-Lock... He must be telling the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Max's bust should be on that small table over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing over there.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Really? ... Oh yeah. Hmm... When was it...? I'd say about five days ago, all of a sudden... The bust disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">If you want to see it, there's a photo on the bulletin board over there. Max just had to put the picture up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Hey! This thing is really cool! Nick! Nick! I want someone to make a bust of me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, as long as I'm not paying for it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is there anything else that's changed about this place?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Nope. Nothing's changed that I can see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if he's actually thinking about this, or if he is setting up for a bad joke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Nope nope... I'm drawing a blank here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A quiet Moe is a good Moe in my book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess there really aren't any other things that have changed, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... There is this one tinsy tiny thing that does seem different.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell us! Tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... On the morning of the crime, over on that bulletin board... This piece of paper was posted front and center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Piece of paper?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's torn, so I don't know what it said, but I could see it's* <thought>[sic]</thought> title.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes! It says, "To The Murderer!!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-M-M-Murderer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... When did you find this?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The morning before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Before the murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes. The Ringmaster was killed the night after this paper was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who in the world posted this thing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I think this is a very important clue!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I can't stand Max and his attitude sometimes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But lately...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's just... Lately I've started to understand what he is always going on about.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is is then?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Umm... I'm not sure if I can explain it all that well just yet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just when you think it's impossible, Moe flashes a glimpse of maturity...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ahh! Not this picture!! He showed it to you guys too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You've seen it as well?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well, you know what they say about Maximillion Galactica... He really gets around. Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh yeah... He didn't just show me the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He showed me his bust too. Let me tell you, that this is enormous! It's in the picture, I think. He'd make us worship it... Everyday. He made us bow to his greatness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's got a... Big... Bust? I wouldn't mind hearing more about Max's bust... Not that I'm into that sorta thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">The morning of the murder, this was posted up on the bulletin board. That's when Max clonked Ben over the head. Sorry I hadn't remembered it until now. It was torn down before anyone really paid any attention to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you don't know what was written on it, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Unfortunately I don't. But I betcha they would know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who are "they"?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Max and Ben. They were at the cafeteria earlier than I was that morning.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Sorry, but I don't know anything about that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">After all, I'm just a clown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I concede Moe's a clown, but I get the feeling he's not your average clown...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know anything about this note?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The morning of the murder, it was posted on the wall in the cafeteria...</line>
<line speaker="Max">I do know all about that note. When I read it, my heart certainly skipped a beat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your heart skipped a beat?</line>
<line speaker="Max">While I was enjoying my morning tea, the Ringmaster and company entered the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And company...?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I guess it wasn't really a company... It was just the Ringmaster and my sweetie pie. When the Ringmaster read the note, he turned an incredible bright red. All of a sudden he tore it off the wall and shoved it into the pocket of his tailcoat!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? Out of curiosity, what in the world was written on that thing?</line>
<line speaker="Max">... Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-huh...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh I don't want to steal the fun from my sweeties! Go and find out on your own! I'm sure you can find it somewhere. You might also want to ask my sweetie pie princess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, do you see that? There's a scrap of paper shoved into the pocket of the tailcoat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... I've got a feeling I know what that is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet that's the other half of the note that Moe gave us. Then let's hurry up and check this thing out, Nick! I knew it! It fits perfectly with the other piece.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does it say? What does it say? "To The Murderer! I have conclusive evidence of what took place. Meet at 10:00 PM tonight at the lodging house plaza."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tonight at 10:00 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's when the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now we need to find out who called out the Ringmaster!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Ringmaster's tailcoat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's been expertly cleaned and pressed. It's got one perfect crease.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Ringmaster must have liked things neat and tidy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is kinda pointless isn't it? There's no way this beats Moe's room. Now that's cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I can hear in my head right now is "Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wha...? Moe's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a message on the bulletin board. "I'm hungry so I'm off to get some hamburgers! Love, Moe."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmmm... Hammburrgeerrrr... Just thinking about it is making me hungry! All of a sudden I need a burger bad!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All of a sudden, I need a new partner... BAD!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Detective Gumshoe! I'm sure you did a good job as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I am done with the investigation of the acrobat. Finally. But with Ms. von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, what is that? That beeping sound?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Every time I hear that sound, she's usually not very far behind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some sort of pager or something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you don't mind pal, I'm gonna go ahead and get outta here... Quick. See ya, pal!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't know that Gumshoe could run that fast! So much for being a flatfoot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Never seen a grown man so afraid of a girl still in her teens!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, let's go inside... It's freezing out here! Uh oh... The whi... OWWWW!! That whip could cut right through me...!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Von... Von... Von... Karma!! <thought>She really did appear!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you have to jump out and scare us like that? What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the story of my defeat at your hands making the national news?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she might be overestimating the importance of a win by just a smudge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Von Karma... It appears you got your hands onto something, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Anyone could. You couldn't hide that look of victory with ten paper bags on your head!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"A conclusive witness"... You must mean the acrobat, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it already, you want to beat and destroy me. I can't worry about her. I've got to try and find out more information myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why do you keep giving Nick the evil eye!? It doesn't matter if you prove the defendant guilty tomorrow... Nothing will be able to bring your dad back!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! Your dad! I know you miss him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Him"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Edgeworth!? Mr... EDGEWORTH!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-M-Mi-Miles E-Ed-Edg-Edgeworth!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That means that Edgeworth was...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Little brother? Edgeworth and Nick are the same age...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth... The man who inspired me to become an attorney. I fought against him in a few cases... But after "that" case was over... He "vanished"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">HUH!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What does she mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was one year ago. It was right after you left to go back home.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Edgeworth... He's dead?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What about this? OWWW!! She hit me again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you should hold off on the wild goose chases.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-N-Nick! Umm... About Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, I already told you this once. Don't make me do it again. Don't bring up his name in front of me again, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know if you are god's gift to prosecutors or not, but I've had about enough of you!! Him too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wha... What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go. We need to talk with the performer on the third floor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry I brought it up, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="???">You must be Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes.</line>
<line speaker="???">Pleased to meet you. I'm Ken Dingling.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">But here at the circus, everyone just calls me Acro.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr... Acro.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ummm... How do you know my name?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">The detective told me. He said you'd definitely show up here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Acro, you're a member of this circus as well?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">That's right. I mainly perform on the tightrope or the flying trapeze. But nowadays... All I perform in is my wheelchair.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eww... It's a huge pile of trash!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One man's trash is another monkey's treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess you're right. Look! They're all shiny things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's even got a motorcycle exhaust. What do they call this thing? Oh... A tuba right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course it's a tuba, silly! You didn't know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey... It's a picture of Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, she is a shining beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No objections here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe... It's a monkey calendar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro must really love monkeys.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro, why did you join the circus?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">When I was a kid, my parents failed miserably at business. Then one night, they decided to run away from it all... Without me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!!</line>
<line speaker="Acro">The only person who was willing to take my parent's* <thought>[sic]</thought> place was the Ringmaster. The Ringmaster took such incredible care of me. He was truly a lifesaver.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It seems like the Ringmaster was truly a saint.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">He was... That's why I decided to do something very important. I decided that I would devote my entire life to finding a way to repay him... And now... Look how someone repaid him for all the good in his life!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's such a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Sometimes I think that he was almost too kind... Perhaps he was too kind to his performers... Perhaps he was too kind to his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I wonder if he spoiled Regina?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina is so cute!! She's truly a princess.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Truly a princess? Are you sure that's a good thing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Do I detect a hint of a grudge against Regina...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... I'm sorry to ask, but why are you in a wheel chair?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">The nerves in my legs were badly damaged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you can't walk now?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I can't even stand now. And since I live on the third floor, I can't even leave this building by myself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's awful...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The accident happened during an acrobatics session, right?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A Psyche-Lock! It doesn't seem like Acro's injuries were acrobatic in nature...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">What's on your mind, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... Exactly when were you injured?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">It's almost been six months since I was hurt. I injured my legs during practice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Six months ago... What in the world went on at this circus then!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">I'm still undergoing rehabilitation for my injuries. I still can't stand, but the doctor's* <thought>[sic]</thought> say that I'll be able to recover and walk again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Out of curiosity, what kind of accident was it again?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I don't really have much more to add beyond that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Acro's hiding what really caused his "accident". Maybe it's related to what happened to the Ringmaster?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I stopped by yesterday and noticed that you weren't in your room.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I was at the hospital all day yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh... You went there for rehabilitation? What about the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Of course I knew about it... I spoke with the police before they allowed me to go to the hospital. Before I got the call from the prosecutor, I was convinced that it was all a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I just couldn't believe it. When I saw what I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"What you saw"...? <thought>Jeez, that sounded really ominous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you see, Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">That night... I was in bed sleeping when I heard a huge sound coming from below my window.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... The scene of the crime was right below your window.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">That's when I looked out the window...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">He was flying straight up into the air...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-He?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Maximillion Galactica.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaatttt!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's what I thought he'd say...</thought> Your absolutely positive that it was Max you saw flying?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I am absolutely sure. There's no doubt in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro, please take a look at this photo for us...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">No problem... Ahh... This is how it ended for him... Such a shame...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He seems awfully calm... But his eyes have a look of sorrow and profound pain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">If my legs weren't like this... I would have been able to prevent this from happening! That's an absolute certainty!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Acro...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Maximillion Galactica, right? You'll have to forgive me, but I try not to think about him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Acro won't even look at it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like something is really weighing on him.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Heh... Money is a great friend to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That pile of "treasure" over there is his collection, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">It is indeed. Money will bring anything back with him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... That's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Yeah, I'm not great with the ladies... But I seem to be pretty popular with the animals.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Hmm... What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what we want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was posted in the cafeteria the morning before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">In the... Cafeteria?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-What happened? He suddenly looks incredibly serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">... If it's got something to do with her, then you should go straight to the source.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Regina. Ask her about it.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">You want to know about Max? Well, his colleagues in the circus all seem to hate him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about you, Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I've got my issues with him as well. But he just also happens to have a diamond shining in his soul.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A diamond shining in his soul?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I guess you could say it is his pride as a performer. We didn't have that pride in ourselves before Max arrived. Honestly, I think he brought something wonderful to this circus when he came.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Acro...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy is really different from the other members of the circus...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was hoping you could shed some light on Ben...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Well, he'll always be here. And as long as he's here, he really can only continue to be a ventriloquist. Whether that's a good thing for him or not... I'm afraid I can't really say.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Mr. Wright. I just realized who you remind me of... You're just like this prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-W-W-W-WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">You and the prosecutor have the same glint in your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're joking, right!? You think I'm like that whip carrying demon!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Whoa... No need to get so hostile about it. You two may view things from very different perspectives... for now. But you both see the world through the same color-tinted glasses. I know because when I look at people, their eyes are the only things I can believe in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Nick and Von Karma, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Regina...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's cool, isn't she? And can you believe such a cute girl is an animal tamer!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">It seems animals are not the only thing* <thought>[sic]</thought> she tames.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Max, the Ringmaster, Ben... She's got them all under her thumb.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-Whaddya mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Hmm... Maybe I went a bit overboard. It's just Regina's innocence. She was incredibly sheltered as a child.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'd say it seems that way.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">That's why she can be so cruel.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Regina is just like the animals she claims to tame. She's innocent, thus she can be cruel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what happened between Acro and Regina...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">The Ringmaster... He was even more than a father to me. When he took me in, the circus was in bad shape. It was obvious that he had no real way of supporting us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who does he mean by us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that why you started with acrobatics?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Back then, I was only nine years old. I begged the Ringmaster to let me try, and he finally gave in. Having a kid in the circus was probably the last thing in the world that he wanted... I just wanted to be helpful. So I could help the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's such a nice story.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">The Ringmaster really believed in Moe. One-hundred percent. What will happen to the circus now that the Ringmaster's gone...? The beginning of the Lawrence Curls era I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if it's really alright to let Moe run the show...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">Mr. Wright, you don't know much about Moe, I suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see right through me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww Nick! You can't let him get to you like that! You're an attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I can't believe what happened to the Ringmaster... Such a wonderful man... What a pity. I have no clue what to do with my life now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">This circus meant everything to me. But don't worry about me... There are still things that I have left to do in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I'm sorry, but in my present physical condition... I don't really know much about what goes on outside of this room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... We're sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Don't worry about it. No need to apologize.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Lately, I've been confined to this room, so I don't have a clue what's going on with the circus.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not really important is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Must you always be so blunt?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">YAAAH!! NICK!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wonderful... Today's special must be Filet O'Phoenix!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">STAY! STAY! HEEL! Oh! Maya! Nick! It's you guys! I'm sorry... I guess I made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A m-m-mistake!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah. A little one. I was thinking of teaching whatever primate was out there a lesson... But I was expecting more of a monkey than a human...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A monkey?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a pity about what happened to the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Dad?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everyone loved him, didn't they? He must have been quite a man.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">He was!! I love my dad sooo much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hate to say it, but she doesn't seem all that broken up about her father...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">That's why I feel so lonely. Now that I won't be able to see him for a while...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">For a while?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah. When Léon died, I talked with my dad, and he told me that... "When someone dies, they just become a star in the heavens."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A s-star?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">That means that my dad is looking down on me from the sky. That's why I love the night so much. I can see everyone who's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"When someone dies, they just become a star in the heavens." That's kinda sweet... But I bet you there's no way that Maya believes that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean "there's no way I believe that"!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Do you think that one day... I'll be a star too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">You really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... You will. I think...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I've got a feeling that everyone is doing great up there in the sky!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if everything's alright with Regina...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just to go back up and clear something up... Why'd you want to teach Money a lesson?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Because he's a meanie! He's got something that means a lot to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something that means a lot to you? It must be something shiny right?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Umm... Actually... It's a stage costume. It's got lots of spangles... It's really beautiful, you should see it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are spangles?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">When the costume gets hit by the spotlight, it dazzles. Hey Mr. Attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">If you saw that monkey, you'd get my dress back for me, wouldn't you? It's really important to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Leave it all up to us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no way I could tun down that request...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yay! You're really gonna do it!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">There's no denying it... Max is cool. I wanna try flying someday! With Max!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's already flown off into her own little world...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I wanna try flying too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... OK. I'll think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">He just loves to cause nothing but trouble... That cute little monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But don't you think using a tiger to scare him is a bit much?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Huh? Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you really have to ask that!? It's dangerous to use a tiger for that kinda thing!!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">It's not dangerous at all. Regent's just a little kitten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've seen plenty of kittens... And that's no kitten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">That's pepper, isn't it? From the cafeteria...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? It's from the cafeteria?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">It's not? I remember seeing it there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So this was the cafeteria's pepper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">You know, I'm not a big fan of pepper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regina, have you ever seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Uhh... I know what this is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Well, it was in my pocket for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It was in your pocket!? This piece of paper... Was in your pocket!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hmm... I guess I noticed it was in there around breakfast time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Breakfast time?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah. I always take Acro his breakfast in the morning. That's when I also take out the trash in his room. Then I'd go to the cafeteria and eat my own breakfast...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's when you realized the piece of paper was in your pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yep. But since I'm not a murderer, I just figured it belonged in someone else's pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then what...?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I wondered if the person who lost it was in trouble, so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You didn't put it on the bulletin board in the cafeteria, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I did! I stuck it up there. How'd you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... <thought>So it was Regina who put it up there!</thought> When did this happen?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Umm... The morning of the murder. I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That explains a lot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">I wonder who wrote this...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I wonder what they mean by murderer... It's like some sort of soap opera. It's kinda strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Strange is probably too nice of a word...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hey Maya, do you know if Max is doing OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Umm... I don't think I'd go so far as to say he was OK...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Aww... I hope he comes back here real soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sure he's going to come back here... Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">There's no way he will lose with you helping him... Right, Mr. Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... *gulp* Of course. If I'm Wright, you're right!!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I might not be able to see my Dad for a while, but... I know I can wait until I see him again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the spirit. Even though he won't be coming home...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Don't do that Maya. Please don't look at me that way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'm s-s-sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Regina's so cheerful... It kinda makes you wonder if all the lights are on... Especially when she says she won't be able to see her dad "for a while"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">He's been a good friend to my dad for a really long time now. My dad always said... "When it comes to who I can entrust the circus to, it's definitely Moe."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Yep! That clown is one lovable stooge. Don't you think so, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... No comment...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Ahh, it's Acro. Is he in his room today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, he is. We just came back from meeting with him.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I hope his legs get better soon. Acro's so incredible! Especially on the trapeze!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The trapeze is that enormous swing hanging from the top of the tent, right?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yep, that's it! I really want to see him up there again... Acro the Acrobat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's strange... Acro doesn't seem to have very many nice things to say about Regina... But Regina seems to like Acro just fine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Something smells fantastic! So we know it can't be Moe... Wait! I know what it is!! It's burgers!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hello hello hello! Welcome to the Bistro du Cirque aka the cafeteria!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm... It smells so good in here... Those burgers look great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's drooling like she' some sort of crazed burger monster!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">My burgers are the best!! Juicy meat... Toasted buns... Special sauce... They are absolutely irresistible to anyone with a hankering for a burger! One bite will send you into hamburger heaven!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet! I can tell by the smell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa... I'm getting hungry too! Those burgers must have some kind of special power!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that the Ringmaster is gone, what are you going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's all I've thought about the past two days... Everyone loved Russell... You've heard Acro's story haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like how he was adopted when he was younger?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's calmed down a bit now, but when the murder happened he was livid. Acro was so upset that he said he couldn't go on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was that upset?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes he was... Anyways, I gave it some thought. Maybe I should give up on trying to be a half-baked clown... I've been thinking of trying on the Ringmaster's shoes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Max would still be an issue though...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He may be a bit mean and hard to work with, but it's hard to argue his importance. He's probably the reason the circus is still around... A lot of what he says is right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Moe...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">All that's left is to see if everyone would get over the tragedy... You know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The tragedy? You know? What is he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Get over" what tragedy, Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Huh!? Don't worry about it... It's nothing. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He must mean the tragic death of the Ringmaster, right?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes Yes! That's it! You're right, girlie! Dang! Dang! Dang! Correct-o-mundo!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Doesn't he mean "ding"?</thought> Moe... I mean no disrespect here, but... Are you lying to us?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Egghhh... No! Not at all! What makes you think that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just the way you said "if everyone would get over it" seemed a bit strange. It sounded like you were talking about something from a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Eek eek eek eek eek.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe! I'm right!! Aren't I!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So now we're getting closer to the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">It was about six months ago... It was just a little accident... Give me a break... Us old men have accidents. I wear big pants for a reason!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Six months ago, eh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C'mon Moe. Tell us what happened six months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I'm kinda busy right now. Look... I'm eating a burger as we speak!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm... That looks so tasty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just wish we could do something about Moe chewing with his mouth open...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Let's see here. "To The Murderer!"... That's far from polite. Where did you find the rest of this note anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe it'd be best if I didn't tell Moe where we found it...</thought> Don't worry, about it, Moe.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">If I didn't need to worry about it, you shouldn't have shown it to me!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's always been a very private guy. When he came here, he was only about 10 years old. We had just started the Berry Big Circus around the time that Russell took him in. These are really hard memories to bring up...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Acro was so happy to have joined the circus...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was especially grateful to the Ringmaster... And I'm sure he is grateful to you too.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Huh? He's grateful to me too? Aww... Shucks. You guys are exaggerating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's fidgeting around so much, you can tell that he's embarrassed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... They must have taken Max in for questioning again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There really isn't anything that we need to ask him right now anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right, I guess... Alright, let's go then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Moe's not here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that!? I hear something...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Stop it, Nick... You're scaring me!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oooo-Ooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!! It's Money!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That monkey's gotten his hands on something again...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's it! That's the thing "that means a lot" to Regina, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright! Time to take on this monkey, attorney-style!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Give it back, monkey-brain!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oooo-Ooooo-Ooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That means a lot to Regina!! A real man wouldn't make a little girl cry!!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oo-Oo-Oo-Oo-Oooh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WAAHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I tried to have a man-to-man talk with him... I really did.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know... Man-to-man isn't really accurate. It was more like man-to-monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stay! Money! Stay!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oo-Ooooh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, it's working!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... It sounded like he was confused at the end of that "Ooooh".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stay... AHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oooooo-Oo-Oooh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WAAHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I knew that acting like Regina would do the trick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oooh-Oooh-Oh-Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oo-Ooooh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wa-Oooh-Oooh!!</line>
<line speaker="Money">Oooooo-Oo-Oooh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yikes!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WAAHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I tried to have a monkey-to-monkey talk with him... I really did.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I swiped it while Money was distracted...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? You're really on the ball today, Nick! Lemme see it... Lemme see it!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You can see it fine from where you are.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know what I mean... I really want to try on Regina's costume...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe then they'll take you in at the circus and I can get some peace and quiet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't fit me at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh well, guess it's time for you to lay off the burgers! Not to mention it doesn't look like something any girl I know would actually wear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Léon... He was killed, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">That's right. My dad killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Well... Léon did something really bad during practice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During practice?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Léon was sitting down, and then he opened his mouth. You know... GAAAWWW...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh huh. Uh huh.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Usually when he did that, I would put my head into his mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh huh. Uh huh... Wait... You put your HEAD into a lion's MOUTH!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I sure did. The people in the crowd always loved seeing me do that! They'd always start screaming!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You sure they were screaming because they loved seeing you do that!?</thought> Anyways... What was the "bad thing"?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Oh yeah. Léon bit someone during that practice.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-R-Regina!! Everything was alright though right?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">No, it wasn't alright... That was the problem. My dad was incredibly angry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's then Léon...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah. That's when he became a star in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Poor thing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Here you go Regina!!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">YAY! THANK YOU!! YOU REALLY GOT IT BACK FOR ME!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I love you, Mr. Attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*blush* It's... Nothing... <thought>No wonder guys melt to mush in front of this girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Regina. That costume is yours right? I tried it on, but it didn't fit me...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Huh? This costume? This isn't mine. It was Léon's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Léon's?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know... The lion she told us about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ohh... The one that someone killed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">You wouldn't know it but I was responsible for naming all the animals at the circus.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You named Money the Monkey? And Regent, Regina's tiger?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Guilty as charged. But Léon got his name from the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He always said "keep names simple and easy to associate".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick's name is simple and easy to associate, right Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I always told Russell "If that's what you think, then call him Lyin' the Lion!" I's a great name, don't you think? Imagine if he could talk... "Im Lyin'!" Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lyin'...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But that's when Russell said, "Don't lie to yourself. That name is awful."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe, please tell us what happened six months ago. What in the world went on at this circus?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">OK OK... There's no need to look so scary when you ask me. Hey! Look over there! Some juicy burgers! Let's eat instead!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, I'm more of a grilled chicken sandwich man myself.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I've kinda got an idea of what happened back then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe, you said something about an accident? This wouldn't happen to be the cause of that accident, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Look tasty!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You know!! The burgers!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like I shot a blank on that attempt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Whaddya say? Another burger sound alright to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard a little bit about it from Regina? Léon made a mistake during a performance, right?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Whattttttt!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... I told them so many times... "You shouldn't be doing dangerous performances like that!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Putting their head inside of Léon's mouth was part of a act!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But Regina believed in Léon. She believed so strongly that the Ringmaster went along... He could never say no to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of curiosity, who was bitten?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on Moe! Don't clam up on me now. Who did Léon bite on the head?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Umm... I promised I wouldn't say anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You promised?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's involved in this too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's "involved" huh? Moe must be talking about...</thought> Moe. Is this the person that you promised you wouldn't say anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oooowoooahhhh!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">There's a lot of spice on this Cajun burger!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... What about the person who you promised to keep silent?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must have been Acro, right?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">H-H-H-How... How'd you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry about that, Moe. Getting to the bottom of this accident may help solve what happened to the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">No... No way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need to know the truth about what happened to Russell. Please tell me what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... I'm sorry, Acro...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's just like you said. You know... The accident.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did someone... die?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">No, but it would have probably been better if he had.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? How would that have been better!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's still alive... But when he got bit, he suffered massive brain damage. He'll never recover from the coma that he's in...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Coma...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">All he does now is lay in his bed at the hospital. And that's all he's ever going to be able to do...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How is he related to Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's his brother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The person who got bit was Acro's brother.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-Brother?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">They were an acrobat team of brothers, Acro and Bat. Cute nicknames, I thought... Anyways, they were an incredible team... Cut down at the same time...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Who is Acro's younger brother?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Sean Dingling... But everyone always called him Bat. He fell in love with Regina. Trying to win her love was his downfall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Everyone seems to fall in love with Regina...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Six months ago... While we were practicing... All of a sudden Bat blurts out, "Let me perform with Léon!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why'd he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I don't know. But that's what caused the accident. I'll never forget that moment... It was so strange... Léon had the weirdest look on his face. He was... Smiling.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He? You mean Léon?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes. Léon. When he bit down, he was smiling. Some sick grin...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No way!! That's impossible!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A smirking lion... A flying murderer... Why does it seem that it's always Moe who catches all of these incredible events?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick? Can lions smile?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">We never told the police about the incident. The circus would have shut down if we had. The next morning, the Ringmaster took Léon out and shot him with a rifle.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's what really happened...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... You guys were so serious! What was I supposed to do!? I had to tell you! But all this truthfulness has put me in the mood for a burger! Here... You two have some pepper! *shaka shaka shaka shaka*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There he goes again, acting like his normal lazy self...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh... Ahh... Ahh... *Achoo!* *Achoo!*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Nice! What a wonderful sneeze!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You think so?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You sneeze with pepper and slip on a banana... That's basic clownsmanship. Girlie, I know you "Gotti" understand that!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I think I'd make a good clown!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Other than Regina, I've never seen a cuter sneezer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh! Does Regina sneeze with pepper too?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">She does! Bat would always tease her with pepper!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-Bat?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">From my point of view, those two always looked so perfect together...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They looked perfect together, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Ahh... Mr. Wright. Back again I see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, he did say, "I'll be back." Wait... or was that someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We're back because Acro's hiding why his legs were injured! He was hurt in the accident six months ago! It would seem that he knows that we know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">Well well... It seems you've got things you want to talk about, so fire away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to ask you, how were you injured?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I'm sorry, I thought we talked about this? It was an accident that happened during practice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An accident during practice?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Yes. Unfortunately acrobats are prone to all sorts of injuries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's lying... If that were the real cause, he'd have no reason to keep it a secret.</thought> Acro, are you really telling me that a practice accident was the cause of your injury?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright Acro... Just tell me the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Do you mind if I ask you a question first?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Do you really think I could get an injury like this from something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! It seems I'm off-track with this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">If that's how you handle yourself, I suggest a net if you ever try the tightrope.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right. I slipped up just now... I've got to rethink things.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">Léon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Six months ago, you were attacked by the lion. That's when you were injured.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know I'm on the right track. I just need to keep going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">You're saying that I was attacked? By a lion!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I'm sorry Mr. Wright, but I'm an acrobat. I'm no animal tamer... If a lion was coming for me, I'd be running for the exit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure if "attack" is the best word to be using. You must have... battled the lion.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">You seem to enjoy telling jokes... Why would I decide to battle a lion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because you had to fight it. You had to fight it to save someone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So how about it, Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">You mind if I ask one question first?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go ahead. What do you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Why would I possibly battle the king of the jungle for something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>I must be going in the wrong direction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">Mr. Wright, I assure you that it would take more than that to get me to go after a lion.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Bat...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a shame what happened to your brother six months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You tried to save him, didn't you? And that's how you got that terrible injury.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Moe... He must have told you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, we learned about Bat from Moe. But he didn't mention anything about you in regards to the accident. I suppose it was just a slip of the tongue on his part. That's how I figured it out.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">A slip of the tongue?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Anyways, they were an incredible team... Cut down at the same time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Cut down at the same time..." That was where he slipped, and that's how I figured it out. You two ended up wrapped up in the same accident together, like always.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I see... But an accident is an accident. It wasn't anyone's fault...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I still haven't broken Acro's Psyche-Lock... He must have an incredibly deep seeded secret...</thought> "It wasn't anyone's fault..." Do you care to explain more?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro, I know you are still hiding something from me... Maybe something you don't seem to like much is the reason you're being evasive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this, Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Are you aware how strange you seem sometimes? You seem to think you know what will happen before you do... But you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">It's clear you haven't come to grips with what's going on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! There's no way I can back pedal away from this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">R-Regina...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You always seem calm and collected, until you start talking about her. Saying things like she is "cruel"...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Well done, Mr. Attorney. You've got quite the set of eagle eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... Her tiger tried to attack me...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Regent tried to attack you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Twice.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Hah hah hah... He wasn't serious I'm sure... You're not trying to insinuate that I believe she spurred on Léon to attack Bat, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Léon was never taught a command to attack people. Regina isn't capable of doing anything like that. Besides, Regina had no reason to want to hurt my little brother. Regina and Bat were such good friends back then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you still hate Regina! I've got proof of it!</line>
<line speaker="Acro">What!? What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Doh! Maybe I overdid it again... But if I can hand something over to Acro, maybe it'll...</thought> Here's proof that you had it out for Regina all along!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Acro">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">You know, I think I hate you more than I ever hated her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">How could what you just showed me possibly prove that I hate Regina?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhhh... <thought>It looks like I picked the wrong piece of evidence... But there's gotta be something that works... I know it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Acro">T-This... Where'd you get it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regina posted it on the bulletin board in the cafeteria. Before that, it was in her pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hmm... I guess I noticed it was in there around breakfast time. I always take Acro his breakfast in the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wrote this, and then you put it in her pocket... That's right, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">... That's right. Well done Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">My legs were injured by Léon. Six months ago. My younger brother, Bat, had a dare with Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A dare?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">An absurd dare. "If I can put my head inside of Léon's mouth like you do... You have to go to the movies with me on a date."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's insane!! Didn't he know how dangerous that is!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">We all thought he was being stupid too... But that lion was very old to begin with, and age brought with it countless experience in doing that very trick. Unfortunately, this particular time, I guess Léon wasn't ready or willing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when the accident happened?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">He just wanted to take her out... To the movies...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Bat...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">When Léon chomped down, I jumped towards him. Then Léon attacked me and that's how I ended up...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What about Bat?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">He's still in a coma. I went to the hospital yesterday to visit him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">I'm still waiting for him to open his eyes again... And that's the reason why I keep going.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Bat and Regina... They were such great friends. Oh yeah... I wanted you to take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">This is the scarf my brother was wearing when Léon attacked him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gross... It's covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Acro">This scarf... Was a present from Regina to my brother on the day of the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Acro">When he did it, he looked like he was smiling...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Léon, obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">When he bit down on Bat's head... The expression on Léon's face looked like a grin.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know!! Moe said the same thing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think it all means?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll be taking that scarf if you don't mind...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But the scarf is evidence in the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Preparations?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Acro... A witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Acro">Yes, ma'am.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now what do we do, Nick? How are we going to handle tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry about it. I'll figure something out...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at you all full of confidence!! You must have found something you can use!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is all beginning to come together now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>