<xml>
<title>Turnabout Serenade</title>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, this is it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Today's the day it all goes down. <thought>And then there was yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">This meeting is over. ...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just give us five more minutes. We can call them back after that.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Sorry, no go. C'mon, piano-boy. We're leaving.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daryan! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...I never liked you. Either of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Darn it! We were so close! He was about to tell us! Hey, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He didn't want us to hear what Machi had to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...And I think I know why. Time to bring down a little Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What was that!?</line>
<line speaker="???">He is heard but unseen...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Who's that talking...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Valant Gramarye! <thought>...Using the door like an average muggle, no less.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You... aren't the witness today, are you, Uncle Valant?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha ha! A preposterous proposition. How could I stand to stand upon the stand? Why, my secrets would be free for the plucking! ...I might even have to sign autographs! That is why I intend to remain hidden for the entire day.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, with vanishing magic!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed! I will jump upon an express train, and express myself to the next town over! But before I go... a word of warning.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Warning...? What?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">A grand Gramarye glamour resides at the root of all that has happened. Do not forget this truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... glamour?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">A spell, a sorcery... a great illusion! ...Miss Trucy, though it pains me to part so... ...I need to get in line for a ticket. Farewell!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And there he goes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He sure seemed happy about that illusion thing...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, big illusions are the bread and butter of a magician! You can't pull off a show without one! The big illusion is always a spectacle to remember! Usually, it involves cutting up things, like people or elephants... ...or the Eiffel Tower. Anything, really!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he was talking about what we saw at the concert.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir's disappearing act.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And Prosecutor Gavin's exploding guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what he meant by it being at "the root of all that has happened"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's about time. Shall we go?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Ah, excuse me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The scheduled starting time for the trial has been changed. The trial will not be commencing until 10:30 AM. Sorry for the inconvenience.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Did something happen? This is a first...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">It was by the judge's request. Some urgent personal business.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great. I bet he stayed up too late last night, watching courtroom dramas.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Apparently, he's visiting the hospital again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The hospital?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">I believe it was mentioned that the Chief Justice's son is unwell. Apparently his condition worsened considerably this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Chief Justice's son...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that's right... Remember yesterday morning? The judge said he had to go visit him after the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">There's an article about it in the newspaper. If you care to read about it yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Incuritis"...? Where have I heard that before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll let you read that article for us, Apollo! Just leave the TV guide page to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Try not to lose the page with the funnies if you can.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. My apologies for the delay. Court is now in session for the trial of... erm, how do you say this name again?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Machi Tobaye... our suspect fortissimo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Right. It's his trial, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is prepared, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The prosecution... is ready to rock.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Is something wrong, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No. Well, yes... It's just, I've been friends with the Chief Justice since we were students. It pains me to see him going through such a difficult time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Incuritis", was it? That article said there is no known cure!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Judge, let me say, with all honesty, I feel your pain. But, now is not the time for tears. Now is the time... for law.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Indeed. We left off at quite the juncture yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I asked Interpol about that number. "IPXX314206"... The agent registered under this number... ...was Romein LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thanks for looking into that for us, Detective Crescend. It's a great help.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, no problem at all, Your Honor. ...I'll be heading out...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wait! That voice just now... ............ It was him. I am sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was "him"?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That voice I heard, talking to Mr. LeTouse... when I heard the gunshots fired. It was him! It was Mr. Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...No way...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Quite a sensational ending. Who would have thought Daryan would guest star in the season cliff-hanger... as a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I asked the prosecution to look into this matter. ...Please tell the court your findings.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Daryan Crescend is a member of my band, the Gavinners... ...He is also a detective, making the current charges serious indeed. Yet, after investigation, I have found no cause to alter our case, or file new charges.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And your reason is?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Weren't you aware, Herr Forehead? He has an impeccable alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An alibi?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let us review the facts again, shall we? The concert held on the night of the shooting was in three sets. The Gavinners ripped up the stage during the first set. For the second set, our guest took center stage... The only performers appearing were myself, Lamiroir, and Machi... ...along with a drummer and bassist, for a total of five. The shooting in the dressing room, however, took place during the third set. Lamiroir and the defendant, Machi Tobaye had left the stage at that point... ...and the Gavinners were already rocking. This is when two shots rang out at the scene of the crime. Shots heard by Detective Ema Skye, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And Apollo. You heard them too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I sure did.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Furthermore, Lamiroir herself witnessed the moment of the crime... ...Well, perhaps I should say, she "heard" the moment of the crime. ...When she claims to have heard Mr. LeTouse and Detective Crescend "talking".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's impossible! Detective Crescend was...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Precisely. Detective Crescend was on stage, getting his groove on, no less. Voila. A perfect alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Does the defense have anything to add to this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's true. When I heard those gunshots, he must have been on stage. Still, there's something here that doesn't quite add up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It appears the defense has no objections. I believe we can safely say that Daryan Crescend's alibi has been acknowledged.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which means that Lamiroir was sadly mistaken. Her testimony cannot be true.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Of course, if we disregard her testimony... ...then I see no evidence keeping us from declaring a verdict. ...If indeed, there are no objections?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uh oh, Apollo! If he declares a verdict now...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! But Prosecutor Gavin's case is airtight! Lamiroir might have been lying to protect Machi! How can I rely on her testimony...? Wait... What about yesterday in the detention center...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]........</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"About the case..."? What about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He wants to tell us about Mr. LeTouse's death!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking], [Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="???">This meeting's over.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Daryan?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi was trying to tell us something, I know it! ...Maybe the best thing to do is ask him... under oath!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court finds the defendant, er, what was his name again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, that wasn't it. It was something like "marquis" or-- ...Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor, before you declare a verdict, I would like to call another witness!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Exactly who else do you need to hear from?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A witness who, until now, has not been given a chance to speak in this court. ...Because he doesn't speak English.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do. The defense calls defendant Machi Tobaye to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!? But he doesn't speak English...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll use an interpreter!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Interpreter? I'm afraid you'll have to look elsewhere. I only speak a few phrases, such as, "I love you," and, "Where is the toilet?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense would like to request Lamiroir as the interpreter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">L-Lamiroir!? But there's a possibility she's protecting the defendant...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But she'd be interpreting for the defendant! Why would she lie?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most unusual...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha... Bravo, Herr Forehead. Herr Judge! The prosecution agrees with the defense's request. If Lamiroir lies, I'll be able to tell. Even my limited knowledge of the language should be enough for that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if both prosecution and defense are for this, I see little cause for refusal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Finally! Some progress!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Please show the defendant and Lamiroir to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I suppose there is a first time for everything. Shall we proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your name, to begin with. ...If you would, Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... He says, "Machi Tobaye, the defendant."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, this is certainly a first for this courtroom. Not that we really needed an interpretation of that message in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So far, so good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Justice, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? If I would what, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Would what"!? You called the defendant to the stand, did you not? What would you have him testify about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do I want him to testify about...? <thought>Ack, I hadn't thought that far yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Aren't you going to ask him what he was about to tell us yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How can I if I don't know what he was saying...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Excuse me, a moment. If I might speak?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Just now, Machi said there is something about which he "wishes to testify".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi wants to testify about something? What could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What sort of testimony is he talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...One moment, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! The suspense is killing me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What? What!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">According to Machi... He has "proof of his innocence".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...This is a surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yahoo! Victory, Apollo! We did it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is sounding too good to believe. And I know what that usually means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if that's true, then this is vital testimony! Lamiroir... I mean, Machi! Please testify to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"Very well."</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He says that word of Mr. LeTouse's death came as a great shock.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I see! He wouldn't have understood the English lyrics to the song. That would prevent him from following them so closely.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I wondered what he meant by "proof". Why, he would only have to ask Lamiroir to know the meaning of that song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir! Did you ever explain the lyrics of that song to him?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I did tell him, generally, what the song was about. But never in so much detail. And he never asked.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Has my oft-repeated warning already fled that forehead? Lamiroir might be protecting the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, anyway, let us proceed with the cross-examination. Mr. Justice, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Something's hidden in that testimony, I know it. I'll just have to trust my bracelet to tell me where! It worked yesterday, it'll work today!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He says that word of Mr. LeTouse's death came as a great shock.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Were Machi and Mr. LeTouse close?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, after we traveled around the world on tour together...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir... This is Machi's cross-examination, not yours.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But I knew the answer...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is a court of law. We'll play by the book.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When Prosecutor Gavin's tough, he's really tough!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi says he was very good friends with Mr. LeTouse. "Mr. LeTouse was always a gentle man, never angry.. We got along quite well. I never dreamed something like this would happen..."</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">But if the killing truly followed the lyrics of my song...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"The Guitar's Serenade", correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. "The crime followed the lyrics of the song... The theft of the key ring, the burning guitar, and the bullet... This is why it could not have been me!"</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I, that is, he, could not have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "could not have done it", you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It is very simple. Machi could not have done all the things that happened that day. For all those things followed the song lyrics closely...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He says that because the lyrics are in English, he does not understand them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wouldn't it be difficult for him to perform without knowing the meaning of the lyrics?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He did know what the song was about, its mood, shall we say. This was enough to play by. I told him it was a song about a "guitar in love".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's... not actually the guitar that's in love, strictly speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Oh? Perhaps I misunderstood!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, no, not really. Yours is also a valid interpretation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Um... OK?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">No, it is my fault. I am too used to singing in Borginian. It is much easier than trying to understand these English lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... ...You can't fool my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">........!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You glanced toward her the very moment Lamiroir said the word "English". Why? And don't bother interpreting that! He understands me!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi, tell the truth. You can understand English, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wh-What are you saying? Of course he can't!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Must he continue this charade...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. Justice, Machi says this: "I know the word 'English'."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Before coming to this country, he heard me speaking English. He learned the name for this language, that is all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Give me a break!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Is that such an unusual word to understand? Do you not know "Español", for instance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, yeah, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am sorry, but he truly does not understand your language.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well then explain this! How does he know the crime followed the lyrics!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Have you always been such a suspicious-minded lad? It is simple. So simple it hardly requires an explanation. ...He read about it in the newspaper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The newspaper!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The Borginian Daily Bugle. You can buy it in this country these days, you know. They have already begun to report about this case in our homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I was right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What is wrong, Mr. Justice? Your eyes, they are quite fierce all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Machi is lying! Maybe it's time to show them proof that he's lying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence proves that you're lying!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, perhaps my interpretation was at fault...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi says, "Try again, adhesive." No, no, sorry. "Try again, sucker."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Urk! I must have gotten it wrong... One more time! So, he claims he read about it in the newspaper...? That means he's lying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have here a Borginian Newspaper! The Borginian Daily Bugle, as a matter of fact!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Indeed, there is a feature article about the case. Could you read this for me, Machi?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. It doesn't mention the lyrics!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Wh-What? What is this all about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry Machi. You couldn't have read about the lyrics in a Borginian Newspaper!!!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">! ........................ [Borginese speaking]!!!!!!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">B-But I don't see how it's possible... Ah, I know! He must have heard the lyrics when the police were doing their questioning! Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not possible, the subject of the lyrics was not brought up in police questioning. I read the full report myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the lyrics weren't in the newspaper and the police didn't mention them. The only place you could have heard them was in this courtroom! ...In English, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will explain herself... er, himself!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi says... He says... ......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">..."It is true I read the newspaper. But this is not where I learned of the lyrics. I was mistaken. Now I remember..."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You remember...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...He says he heard of the lyrics from me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Yes. I'm afraid I had forgotten it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then it looks like Herr Forehead's been jumping to conclusions again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems so, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No... No! I was onto something, I know it! I can't let this chance slip away...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time is an issue today... Mr. Justice, are you finished with the cross-examination?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you going to do, Apollo!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If I'm going to keep on cross-examining, I'd better have an angle of attack... ...Or else!</thought> ......! <thought>My bracelet's still reacting!</thought> Your Honor! Please allow me to continue!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you must, you must. Very well. Witness?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He says that because the lyrics are in English, he does not fully understand them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was I who explained that the crime followed the song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly how much did you explain to Machi?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Ah, this is a question for me, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This interpretation thing is getting old fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I told him that Mr. LeTouse had been killed, and why he was a suspect. And I told him the crimes of that day followed my song.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you mention any particular words of the song relating to the case, such as "heart"?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, of course I explained this. He was quite surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yay! I knew he was innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe he is, too, Trucy. I do...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo? You got a tummy ache or something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something's hidden in that testimony... If it's the truth, I'll find it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir... I'm currently cross-examining Machi. ...Why should you be uncertain?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">! Me? Uncertain?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, you swallowed the very moment you told the court... ..."It was I who explained."</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I see there is little point in trying to hide anything from you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir, are you, indeed, protecting someone?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That... is not a question with a simple answer. To tell the truth, I do not believe it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then, allow me to answer for you. Lamiroir, you're protecting...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I'm afraid I don't understand what you're saying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">So sad to go through life being so misunderstood.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't need your pity! What I need is another chance. C'mon this is easy: Who is she protecting?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir, you are protecting Machi. That's why you lied and told us that you had explained how the crime followed the song!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't fault you for trying to help, but this is not the way!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi! I believe you didn't do it, really! I trust you! But you've lied to us twice. And now you have Lamiroir lying on your behalf!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If this is going to work, you have to trust me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your two lies cover a simple truth. You understand English. You have to!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">! ........................ Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Is this true? Do you understand English?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Y-Yes. A little, only.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">First he could see, now he can talk. And you... did not know about this, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... no. I did not! It is quite a surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How many secrets is this witness hiding!?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">Last... This is... last...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... could you tell us what really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">No shooting! I did no shooting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you weren't in the dressing room when I heard those two gunshots, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently, the answer to that question isn't simple either.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I was in... dressing room. Behind desk. Manager, he on floor...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Which would be after the shooting, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Then, there is voice...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Voice? Or voices? Was it you and Ema, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So when Machi went into the dressing room, Mr. LeTouse had already been shot. And then we came to the door.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Panel high up. I take off. Run away, run away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So it was you who escaped through that air vent!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha. As the prosecution has held all along, no less. The defendant has admitted to being at the scene. Might we take this as a confession?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! He's clearly denied that he did it!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I no shooting! Manager on floor. Already on floor...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim had already been shot, you say? I find that hard to believe. The defendant understood the song lyrics. He was at the scene of the crime... This can only mean one thing. He is the shooter!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the defendant have anything to say to this?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's clammed up, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's ask Mr. Justice. Will you require any further testimony from the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is that it? Is there nothing else I can get him to testify about? Wait... no, of course there is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is this cocoon, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"The cocoon, the silk, is a potent cure."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A cure...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, Machi? Are you... a smuggler?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He... won't tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That cocoon has to have something to do with this!</thought> Machi. Please, tell us the truth, for your own sake.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...No. No more speak. Not... to any of you.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So much for your precious trust, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, you were the one who didn't believe him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Regardless, this brings us to an impasse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does seem that the defense and defendant are at odds. ...I doubt we are likely to learn anything more of value should this continue. I see no other course but to declare a five minute recess! The defense will work things out with the defendant so that we might proceed!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Apollo Yoostis...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's "Justice". Better learn how to say it if you ever want to get some.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">Believe. I no shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi claims Mr. LeTouse was already down on the ground when he entered the room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe... it was a trap, and he walked right into it?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">Suddenly. I hear revolver. Close. Very close. Then, I hear voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You heard gunshots?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">Yes. Is true. I hear revolver. But only sound.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you're saying you went into the dressing room... ...and found Mr. LeTouse already dead, and THEN you heard shots? <thought>If that's true...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... you were at the scene of the crime when you heard those shots?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you escaped through the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? What do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I know if I opening vent... ...I can leave stage and back... backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the vents went to both the stage and the backstage area? Is that what he means...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, he's right! Look, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh... Yeah. But how did you know it was connected like that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, I bet his father was the architect that designed the hall or something!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I hear this. From magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Magician...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">D-Don't look at me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A magician, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, at least we're clear on one thing: Machi didn't shoot Mr. LeTouse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but what does that leave us with? We're supposed to say he went into the room to find the body and then he heard the shots? <thought>That one's going to go over well in court. Not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! You're his defense! You're supposed to believe whatever he says. Even lies! That's what Daddy always told me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I'll just pretend you misheard him. Every time. So... what do we do?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're sure you won't testify, Machi?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I... no talking. No.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm, well it was worth a shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That cocoon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"I can't go home"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can't go home!?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....[Borginese speaking]....[Borginese speaking] ....[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"I can't go home to Borginia. I do not want to go home." The penalty for taking a cocoon from Borginia... is death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right! It's punishable by death!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Of course... He's scared.</thought> ...Oh well, I guess we'll just have to try a different approach.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the spirit, Apollo! So, what's your plan?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If Machi won't testify about it, we'll have to get someone else to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone... else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think we're out of time. Let's get back in there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Court is now back in session. Mr. Justice. Have you sorted things out with the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. We had a good talk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, very well. So will he testify?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor, the defendant... will not testify.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Shame. And here I thought this was your big chance to turn the case around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, it is. ...The defense would like to approach this case from a different angle, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A different... angle?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If Machi won't testify... ...then I know who will!</thought> I would like to cross-examine the witness in this case... Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">L-Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What are you up to now? I thought we determined yesterday that Lamiroir's testimony was insubstantial! There's nothing you can--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Lamiroir was taken to the hospital yesterday with injuries.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She was assaulted, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Assaulted!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone wanted Lamiroir dead. Thankfully, she was able to save herself...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What!? I've heard no such report!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would anyone be out to kill Lamiroir? Can you think of a reason?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think of how she is known in our country... A singer, from overseas, who doesn't speak English, yes? Yet someone tried to keep her mouth shut! Who could that have been?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't think...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do! It was the same person who shot Mr. LeTouse! The killer was afraid of her, afraid of what she might say! The defense believes that something was hidden in her testimony yesterday. Something that the killer doesn't want getting out!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, am I to understand that this is what you are saying? Namely, that there is a nugget of "truth" in Lamiroir's testimony... ...A nugget we have yet to uncover?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... If Lamiroir was attacked, this has serious implications! Very well... There were some vague points in her testimony during yesterday's trial. Perhaps we did not inquire as deeply as we might have into some. The court will hear Lamiroir's testimony once more!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Lamiroir, I must apologize. We must ask you to stand again and speak.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">You need not apologize. I know that Machi is innocent. And I will do all that I can until the court realizes this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's review your testimony from yesterday. You told us you heard two gunshots and the shooter's voice through the window. ...And that the voice belonged to Daryan Crescend, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">At which point I proved she could not be correct. She couldn't have heard any of those things. The small window at the scene was closed, and was found to be quite soundproof.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You have nothing to say to that, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know exactly what, yet, but I do know there's something there!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There is, it seems, much you do not know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And yet it is my duty to hear him out. Perhaps the witness would be so kind as to testify once more to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Of course, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Pretty much the same as yesterday's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am sorry. I am not used to speaking much in this language. Perhaps my descriptions are lacking in some way. Yet, everything I have said here is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then it is my distinct displeasure to say this. What you have said to have happened... is impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do I have to repeat myself? Lamiroir was attacked because of this testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What? Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo... You know, for a moment there... ...You were pretty cool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Maybe I do better when I don't try to think ahead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. Perhaps you can "coolly" cross-examine the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I raised an objection... ...but she's saying the same thing she said before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry, it's nothing. Please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Now I know what they mean about the reckless youth these days.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The one in red over there is a shining example, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You're the last person who should be pointing fingers, Mr. Rock Star...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That's when I heard them: Mr. LeTouse and the detective.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daryan Crescend...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I did not know his name at the time. But yes, it was him, the one who took the stand yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How many times do I need to remind you that's impossible? There is no way you could have heard him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because the window at the scene was closed? Is that why?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! If we keep asking the same questions as yesterday we won't get anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's right. Maybe there's a different angle I can try?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you happen to hear anything else at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Anything else...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anything else besides the victim and the shooter's conversation. Anything at all.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's quite the vague question.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Other than the conversation? I heard a clock ticking, the two men breathing, footsteps. ...That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nothing new there, as expected.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! I was hoping for a little more than that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps we should just carry on with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>On second thought, maybe I'll just play it safe here. See, I can be calm and collected, too, sometimes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't get too calm, or you might grind to a halt.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for the vote of confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I liked you better before with the "do I have to repeat myself" bit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh, so which should I be? ...Maybe I am overthinking this whole thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir, do you by any chance remember what they were saying to each other? If so, please tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I have given it much reflection, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I was afraid of this. She doesn't remember...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I only heard one phrase clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A whole phrase!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You remember something that was said!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you say anything yesterday!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Though my memory is clear, I was afraid to speak. You see, I do not understand what was said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This could be it! The clue I've been waiting for!</thought> W-Well what did he say!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was the other man speaking, not Mr. LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The shooter, then. <thought>Daryan Crescend...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, what did he say!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... "It's over. Press the switch! Now!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Switch"...? And the shooter said this to the victim, Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I thought it quite strange myself, afterward.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It is a mystery. What could it possibly mean? Mr. Justice? Care to shed some light on this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk. Um, I mean, sure...! I-I'd be delighted... It's, um, very, very vital! Maybe we could add that to the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Maybe", Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Adds statement">"From the small window, I heard a voice say, "Press the switch! Now!""</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you remember a part of their conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, the conversation between Mr. LeTouse and the detective. I remember it quite clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">From the small window, I heard a voice say, "Press the switch! Now!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And it was Detective Daryan Crescend's voice?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I am sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"It's over. Press the switch." Why would he say that to Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! The murder weapon, the revolver was Mr. LeTouse's, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, maybe when he said, "Press the switch"... ...he really meant to say, "Pull the trigger!"</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Because his English isn't so good!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Daryan Crescend is a native speaker!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh. Oh, right! Sorry, I kind of forgot who was what.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Press the switch"... That's not something a killer usually says to his or her victim, is it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was there no one else in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I do not know. All I heard was Mr. LeTouse and the detective.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I heard the faint sound of a gunshot and stopped. Then I heard another gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There were two gunshots...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I heard two. One after the other.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That fits with the bullet holes at the scene. Nothing really new here to pick up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There was the smell of gunpowder... I knew I must tell someone, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you tell someone immediately?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">W-Well I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If it were me, I would have gone to the police right away. It's our duty as citizens!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This may be beside the point, but Lamiroir isn't a citizen. Though one would hope such common sense prevails in Borginia as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir seems awfully quiet all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's strange... Could she be hiding something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It is as you say, yet, at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was in a hurry, so I kept moving past the small window.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were in a hurry... to go where?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I was on my way to the backstage exit, as I have said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why were you in such a hurry then?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">W-Well... I don't think that has anything to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It very well might! Please answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Are you alright, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... Yes. I am just tired.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Recall what I told you yesterday, Herr Forehead. Lamiroir suffers from serious amnesia. Please refrain from traumatizing her further.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... What, so he can just dismiss questions he thinks are "too traumatizing"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why don't you prove her reason had a connection to the case before asking about it, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution's objection is sustained. The current question is moot. Mr. Justice, please continue with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir was attacked because of this testimony. I know she was... So something's got to be hidden here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe there's some detail we're missing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess we'll just have to get her to fill in the blanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..."Press the switch." There's only one key that can unlock the mystery of those words!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? Yet there was nothing at the scene that could be called a "switch". Save the lights'.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True, there wasn't a switch at the scene. But, it just so happens... I have a "switch" right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That certainly does look like a switch, doesn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The problem is... ...this was found not at the scene of the crime, but on the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The stage...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where the concert was held, yes. This was found hidden there!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">On the stage...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you claiming that the voice Lamiroir heard... ...was of someone commanding another to press this switch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, Herr Forehead? I'd call that an "impossibility".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's hardly necessary for me to remind the court of the layout of the concert forum. The stage is quite far from Lamiroir's dressing room. Not to mention that the Gavinners were in the middle of a concert on said stage. We aren't known for being a quiet band. You could shout all you wanted and not be heard.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The detective's voice was loud... but certainly not a shout.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, too, have Herr Forehead's cries of "possibility" fallen far short of being heard...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry, but he wouldn't have needed to shout.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You heard what I said. Or... do you need me to shout it out for you? It would have been quite simple to be heard on the stage from that dressing room. Oh, wait, you like evidence don't you? How about this! Using this, it would be easy to get a message to someone on stage from the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. So the shooter used this to erm, get his message to the stage? Perhaps you could demonstrate how this was done for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Um... Maybe I was wrong?</thought> ...Sorry, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? I can't hear you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ha ha, very funny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently, it is easier said than done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! If I might show another piece of evidence!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No need to shout, Mr. Justice. Go ahead, show your evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Neither did the shooter need to shout, Your Honor. Not with this...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin. Perhaps you're familiar with this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">! Wh-Why that's...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? What is it!? Is that some kind of new-fangled phone they invented while I wasn't looking!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is a type of transmitter. A communications device.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Communications? Device?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">From what I've heard, that night... ...everyone on stage was wearing one of these. Isn't that right, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, yes, actually. They're for talking between band members. We all had one on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you admit that if you were wearing one of these... ...talking from the backstage to the stage would be simple!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">True, but wait! Those send out an electronic signal. To avoid interference with the audio systems, their range is quite limited.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir said it was about thirty feet, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at this cross-section diagram of the concert forum.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. The walk from the stage to the backstage seems far. But the direct distance is less than thirty feet!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That... can't be...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, when Lamiroir heard the shooter's voice... ...he could have been talking to someone on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hah! You're claiming this is the "switch" in question? Why did it have to be on the stage at the time? It could be placed in a pocket and carried anywhere! Someone could have hid it on the stage after the fact!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey... he's got a point! How do we know where it was when she heard the voice? ...When the shooter said "press the switch"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess we don't...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... An unfortunate situation. I'm afraid that until we know where this switch was, there's little point in debating it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh... <thought>I was sure this was the way to go with this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What is this switch, anyway? We don't even know that basic fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Wait a second... I do know what this "switch" is! And if you follow that train of logic to its incredible conclusion... ...it ends up in proof that completely changes this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's up, Apollo? Apollo...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We know about this "switch", right? We know what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Y...Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... think of when it was used that day... Think of what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? If you have no further information to share concerning this switch...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've been remiss in not telling the court this before. I know what this "switch" is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, it seems the defense is set upon linking this switch to the case. Let's see your evidence of the link! What evidence do you have to explain what this "switch" is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I fail to see how this evidence links the "switch" to this case in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice... Might I recommend a "switch" of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I knew it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once again, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin, you remember this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ach! That's that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That what!? Is it another one of those new-fangled phones!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This... is an igniter. <thought>What phone looks like this!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I-Igniter? You mean it's like a lighter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You aren't saying this switch is a remote...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I am. This is a remote trigger for an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, I'll show you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.................. Yow yow yow yow yow! Mr. Justice! You will cease and desist from burning down this courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, sorry. That was a bit more fire than I'd expected.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If my whiskers had caught on fire...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin. Let me repeat myself. This switch is a remote igniter trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't that suggest something to you?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You're... talking about what happened to me, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. That night at the concert there was one unusual burst of flame. ...When your guitar caught fire in the middle of the performance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wasn't that part of the stage show, though?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin was entirely unaware such a thing had been planned. And the guitar that burned was a valuable keepsake.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right... He got it in Borginia from Lamiroir! He said the sound was amazing. Before it burned, of course. Now it just kind of smokes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The better the guitar, the brighter it burns. Herr Forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't tell me you're trying to tie these two things together? Those being the shooter's voice, heard by Lamiroir... ...and the guitar suddenly catching on fire?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I am. It's really simple when you think about it. Mr. LeTouse and the shooter were at the crime scene. The shooter was wearing a headset. He ordered someone on stage to "press the switch". The switch was pressed, and the guitar caught fire.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that does seem to make sense... Though something about it is bugging me. Can't quite put my finger on it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? It seems pretty simple to me.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead, don't destroy what little respect I have for you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I was expecting something a little more... sensible. I guess I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this all about, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">His simple story simply makes no sense. Think! That night, my guitar caught fire, yes. The cause... may have been this, indeed. However! The guitar caught fire during the second set!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack! That's right! Of course! The guitar caught fire during Lamiroir's song!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Indeed. Yet the shooting happened during the third set. The two are utterly unrelated!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes, that must have been what was bugging me. The whole premise for this is faulty!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">See? His story makes no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! What exactly do you mean, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it's not the premise for my explanation of the switch that's at fault... ...Maybe it's our premise for the entire case so far!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What premise is this, specifically?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm glad you asked. I'm saying that maybe the killing didn't take place in the third act!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What's this? But Detective Ema Skye heard shots and found the body. All of this happened in the third act!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gunshots rang out... And, according to his testimony, Machi was in that dressing room at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where are you going with this, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Stay with me, Your Honor! He also told us this in his testimony: Namely, that the victim had already been shot! We all heard gunshots... but no one saw the shooting!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This... This is insane!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just before the "shooting" took place, the "shooter" was heard on his headset... ...telling someone to "press the switch"! The next moment, Prosecutor Gavin's guitar burst into flame. We know that a remote triggered igniter was inside the guitar. From all these facts, we can draw only one conclusion! The crime did not take place during the third act... ...but during the ballad performance... The second act!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! B-But that goes against the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What does, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This crime was carried out according to the lyrics of that song, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, he's right! Look! The "bullet" is supposed to come after the "fire"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're thinking about it the wrong way.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look... Why would the shooter craft the events of the day to follow the lyrics anyway? It's an awful lot of trouble to go through. ...With little merit for the person doing it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I'm sure whoever it was had some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, they did. A reason that made it advantageous to follow the lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You're saying the order was reversed on purpose!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Reversed, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If the criminal followed the lyrics strictly, then yes... ...the shooting would have had to come after the guitar burst into flame. Yet, Herr Forehead has raised another possibility. He's claiming that the bullet came not after, but just before the "fire".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Couldn't have put it better myself. We were only meant to think that the shooting came after the guitar burst into flame! That was the criminal's objective! The crime followed the lyrics to a point, but that was the ruse! Why else would the killer risk discovery by moving the body? That was the final touch to make us think he'd followed the lyrics the whole way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! That would explain this most unusual situation...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It does! The killer changed the order of events to create himself an alibi! In other words... The killer was someone who had an alibi for the third set, but not the second!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I was hoping it wouldn't come to this. But sadly, it has. Let me tell you why your little fairy tale makes no sense at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, it sounds good, I'll give you that. You've given us a reason why the killer bothered following the lyrics of my song. But I question your logic! ...For it's flawed from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Flawed?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. A contradiction, Herr Forehead, one I've pointed out several times, no less. At the time of the crime, the small window at the scene was closed... How could Lamiroir have heard a voice through it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I know that you would like to divert our attention from this critical fact. But you're basing your entire line of reasoning on a false premise!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Right... Lamiroir's testimony is my entire case... ...That voice she heard... The shooter's voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">W-What if she couldn't hear it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, what do we have. A man saying "press the switch!" And near the crime scene, we have a switch. Which acts as a remote trigger for an igniter. And last, but not least, Prosecutor Gavin's flaming guitar. <thought>It can't all be coincidence! But how do I make it work?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see a more direct line of questioning is required. When the crime scene was investigated, immediately after the crime... ...that window was closed! Care to tell us how Lamiroir heard the voice?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A key point, to be sure. ...Mr. Justice! Can you explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK Justice, you've got one thing to prove, and one thing only. Lamiroir heard a "voice"... ...and she heard it during the second set! Think! How was Lamiroir able to hear the voice?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Obviously, the window was open... It had to be for her to hear the voice!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">News bulletin, Herr Forehead: That horse is dead. Stop beating it, for all our sakes. That window was closed! This is a hard fact, reported by the investigation team.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? You have evidence to the contrary, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, no, but...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then do be quiet. I tire of this charade.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... Time to rethink this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The window was closed, as you say, yet Lamiroir could still hear the voice... ...because she has the power of divine hearing! That's the only explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The witness is a Siren, Mr. Justice. Not a Saint.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I said "hearing", Your Honor, not "healing". <thought>Well that fell on deaf ears.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I'm not sure I know what this "divine hearing" ability is...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then perhaps we should hear it straight from the All-Powerful Voice himself. Care to explain how clairaudience has anything to do with this case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Erm... Can we just move on now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only if you can enlighten this court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to rethink this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When we investigated the scene, the window was closed. The shooter had no reason to close it, had it been open, either. Meaning, it was impossible to hear the voice through that window.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, it's good to hear you making sense again. For a moment, I was afraid you might be a Borginian, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...As I was saying, Lamiroir could not hear the voice through that window. So there can be only one explanation. She heard the voice from another location entirely!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ha ha ha, you do amuse me so. And here I thought you and good sense were back on speaking terms. Now, I'm afraid you and good sense speak two entirely different languages.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Shall I interpret for you, Herr Forehead? Lamiroir clearly stated she heard the voice through that small window! And there is only one "small window" at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about it... Isn't there another "small window" at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-There is!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I know that look. He wants us to ask him. Very well. You claim Lamiroir heard the voice from another location? Mr. Justice, show us where this location was!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir heard the voice from... here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There! That's a small window!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And this changes what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not much, I know...</thought> ...Erm, I couldn't find anything better, so...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court applauds your honesty. And weeps for your case, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You're not the only one crying here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Think it through again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know... I'm trying... <thought>Lamiroir claims she heard the voice through a "small window". ...And if the small window we know about was closed... ...there's only one other thing she could have meant!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Does this look like a small window to you, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The state of modern society can be read from numerous objects and artifacts. In a sense, anything can be a "window" on our society.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I didn't ask you to point out a window on society. I want a window on the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No points for trying...? Lamiroir claims she heard the voice through a "small window". ...And if the small window we know about was closed... ...there's only one other thing she could have meant!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This is where Lamiroir heard that voice from.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's no "small window"! That's the air vent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did she tell us? She said she's a Borginian, unfamiliar with our language! It's not a stretch to imagine she called this "air vent" a "small window"!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now you've done it. You've gone beyond ridiculous and into... ludicrous. So Lamiroir was up in the ventilation system listening to this man's voice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the only logical explanation, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Logical"? I do not think this word means what you think it means, Herr Forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK, what about it isn't logical?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hah! It hardly merits saying! Why would Lamiroir be in the ventilation system? Hiding like a rat! No offense intended to her, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The explanation for that is simple, Prosecutor Gavin. Isn't it... Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have been listening to our discussion here, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes. I admit, it's had me quite confused since yesterday. Yes, the small window was closed... ...but why should that mean I could not hear through it? I feared our prosecutor might himself need an interpreter...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The problem here is words. Lamiroir, this "small window" through which you heard the voice... Was it up high, on the ceiling of the room? Not low on a wall?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes, it was up on the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I will have order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness! You will clarify this statement to the court! Are you, in fact, saying that you were up above the ceiling of the room? And that's where you heard the moment of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, in fact, I was. I am sorry. I never imagined it would become such an important point...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, well... why the heck were you up there!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe it's time for another testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... I'm not sure I... I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May I remind you this is a murder trial? We will hear your testimony! Tell us why you "witnessed" the crime from above the ceiling of that room! ...Please.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well... Looks like I'm on the right track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I was above the ceiling when I heard the voice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Bound to secrecy!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">In my line of work, one has many obligations to uphold.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But you say you were in the middle of your performance! So this did happen during the second set!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I did not witness the crime, you must understand. I only know what I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but you must tell us what you were doing, in detail!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's what the cross-examination is for, ja, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Our mission in this court is to discern the truth. No obligation, no binding pact, may hinder that mission.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Mr. Justice, you may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What are you going to do, Apollo!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm going to find out the truth. <thought>...She was up above that ceiling for a reason. I just have to get it out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I was above the ceiling when I heard the voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Above the ceiling... Could you be more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... cannot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because you're bound to secrecy?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... To tell the truth, I was not supposed to even say I was above the ceiling. I dare not say more...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. Doesn't sound like I'll be able to coax it out of her just by asking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I had heard there was a, er, "small window" there before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "small window", you mean the air vent?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I only remembered I needed to be careful of where I put my hands and feet. I cannot see the light coming through the window, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The air vent grate could trip you up, certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">So, I was walking very carefully when I heard the gunshots. Startled, I crouched and listened. That is when I heard his voice come from the room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Daryan's voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I knew something terrible had happened, yet...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was in the middle of my performance... I had no time to report what I had heard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, without a word, you just let the third set start?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">After the curtain closed for the second set, there was still much to do...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could have prevented this whole misunderstanding if you had only told us sooner!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes, perhaps I could have.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see little point in badgering the witness. What's done is done! The mind works differently when one is in the middle of a performance. Why, I've lost my voice in the middle of a show and kept on singing, completely unaware.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Singing without a voice? ...If only all contradictions were so obvious. ...If only I could get Lamiroir to talk. Pressuring her like this doesn't seem to be getting me anywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As to why I was there... I cannot say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You heard the gunshots during the second set, during your performance. ...You're quite sure?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... Why would I lie about the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why didn't you tell us this yesterday!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">No one asked me. I thought you all knew...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I told you Machi was not the killer. I told you this many times!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, you did... ...But you never told us why.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I am sorry. I... was not able to speak of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Unable... or unwilling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's not talking, Apollo. What do we do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll just have to prove it ourselves. ...As long as she is bound by this pact of silence, she won't talk. But if I can prove why she was up there, she'll have to admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But how are you going to do that!? She was singing on the stage, Apollo! She couldn't have been up above the ceiling, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes she could.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've got a theory as to why, too... And maybe I've got the evidence to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am bound to secrecy on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly who bound you to secrecy?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I'm... not sure I'm allowed to say who it was. ...No, I think perhaps that is alright. It is just a name, after all. It was Valant Gramarye... Perhaps you know him?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Valant Gramarye! What!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean Uncle Valant!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Valant Gramarye!? ...... Who's Valant Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">A grand magician... the one responsible for the illusion performed during our concert.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Interesting reaction, Prosecutor Gavin...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir was bound to secrecy... ...It's going to take some hard-hitting proof to make her talk! I think I know why she was up there... but how do I prove it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir, truth be told, the reason for your presence above that ceiling is quite clear. Especially when you consider what happened during your performance.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What "happened"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. It's all right here on this video.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As we can see, Lamiroir was clearly not on stage for her entire performance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Though it saddens me to be so realistic... Lamiroir is incapable of actually vanishing, let alone teleportation. So, the only explanation is that she was hidden from view. And during that time, she moved to the back of the forum.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's not nice to reveal a magician's secrets! And it's against the rules!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I'm a lawyer! I'm not supposed to be nice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This... is all very fascinating. But how is it possible? There is only twenty seconds between when she disappears and reappears! She couldn't have moved that fast!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is... something wrong, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This was his concert, his show. He knows how the illusion was performed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's just realizing his own oversight. Let's look at the cross-section diagram again. Here, we can trace a route through the ceiling... It goes from the stage, through the backstage to the rear of the forum.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall Lamiroir's testimony from yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way from the stage to the backstage exit. There was something like a little window there... That's how I saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She went from the stage to the backstage exit... ...a perfect description of this route above the ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir knew of this because of her part in the illusion. But she wasn't the only one who knew.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just now in the lobby, Machi told me something:</line>
<line speaker="Machi">I know. I know if I opening vent...  ...I can leave stage and back... backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He said that!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, were you not informed, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">............ I... I knew about the vanishing act, of course. Yet, I had no idea of the route that would be used. Why didn't that magician tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Magicians only reveal details of their acts on a need-to-know basis. They're the bread and butter of a magician's life, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Which is why he bound Lamiroir to secrecy...</thought> ...Well, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I am impressed, Mr. Attorney. Machi was right about you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... what does this mean? Are you saying you used this route above the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...I did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that's that... but I'm still a little confused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why's that, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I said before... There was very little time between when she disappeared and when she reappeared. Twenty seconds, tops! How could she do it so fast? Especially if she stopped to hear the shooter's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That... That's a good question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can the witness explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... cannot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's all up to you. Do your thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what thing, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You need to explain how Lamiroir was able to teleport like she did. Or I'm throwing your case out with the bathwater.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh... <thought>Why do I get picked on? It's Lamiroir who isn't going along with the program here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As I have stated before... I am not at liberty to speak of the illusion that night in detail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, you'll just have to tell us what you can. We'll hear your testimony on this. Mr. Justice, it will be your job to wring the truth out of her.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, if you would, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right. <thought>I feel like a student before finals...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good luck, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I followed the route exactly as I was instructed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Two minutes, you say? The mystery deepens!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I suppose it was too much to hope that the judge would come up with something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As does my curiosity! Take it away, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right, Your Honor. <thought>All I have to do is find the contradiction between what Lamiroir is saying... ...and what we can see plainly in the video.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I figured it out already! I am a magician, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not a chance! I can't reveal another magician's secrets! C'mon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! You're supposed to be on my side here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I followed the route exactly as I was instructed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How did you, er, proceed along this "route"?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">How? Why, I walked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you arrived behind the forum much too fast to have been walking! Tell the truth Lamiroir... you rode some kind of vehicle!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? A vehicle!? What vehicle?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, what a novel idea. I like it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, that's not a bad guess! Wrong, but not bad!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hah hah, yes, laugh at the dumb attorney. I don't mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah ha ha. I'm sorry, but the girl is right. That vent was much too small for vehicles.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was a tight fit. Even I had to crouch as I walked. I cannot imagine a vehicle that would fit in such a small space.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! If it wasn't a vehicle what was it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You had me going for a while there, Mr. Justice. Too bad! Ready for the next part?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why do I feel like I'm on some kind of quiz show?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">There is an emergency exit in the backstage, where a stagehand waited.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did everyone on the concert staff know about the trick?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Not all. Only a few that were needed to help.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See? Like I said, it's on a need-to-know basis.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, not many people knew about the trick...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What were these stagehands required to do?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">One needed to open the emergency exit. The door to the stairs is locked, but once through there...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">From there, one can enter the forum on the opposite side from the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So when you came back out, you were behind the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, that is how it worked.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not a bad show, if I do say so myself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's Uncle Valant for you! The old Gramarye touch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But on the video, you were only gone for twenty seconds! How is that possible?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's the part I don't get either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah ha ha. Yes, it would be hard to go so far in only twenty seconds...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">The plan was for me to move there in two minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Two minutes...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. It can be done in one minute, if you are running.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Running? In that cramped, dark tunnel above the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ha ha, Mr. Attorney. Have you forgotten? Dark or lit, it makes no difference to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, that's true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you're saying that on the night of the concert, you made the trip in two minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... though I nearly didn't make it in time. You see... I stopped halfway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir disappears on the video for twenty seconds. But she says she made the trip in two minutes! How?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you want my professional opinion, I'll bet the answer's right there in that video.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Perhaps you have some evidence for us? Something that can explain the discrepancy between the video and her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Evidence explaining the discrepancy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's one piece of evidence that explains the discrepancy between video and testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir... do you happen to remember this brooch?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! The brooch! We saw that yesterday, did we not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was found at the scene, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And you're bringing this up now... why? I thought we had already determined when that was dropped.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So did I... but we hadn't.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take another look at the video... Here, you can see she's wearing the brooch!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So she is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's look a bit later.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaat? The brooch! It's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Whaaat...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes... the brooch disappeared in the short space of twenty seconds. And it takes a full minute to run from the stage to the backstage... Which means there can be only one explanation. The Lamiroir we see before the vanishing act and the Lamiroir we see after... ...are two different people!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The brooch was found on the floor at the crime scene. And not just on the floor... ...but on the floor directly beneath the air vent! Lamiroir, tell me... Did you drop the brooch on your way from the stage to the backstage? ...At the very moment you "witnessed" the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...Yes, I think I did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! P-Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...From your expression, I gather you had no idea this was the case, Herr Judge. I, of course, knew about it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't get me wrong, I wasn't hiding it. It just never occurred to me... ...that the switch and the shooting took place at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... I was right? There was a switch?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There was. Just before the stage's tower rose, Lamiroir was "replaced".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While we're on the subject, just who was this replacement Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why, the man behind the illusion. Valant Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It was Gramarye...!?</thought> That's... quite the illusion. But I still don't get one thing...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The switch happened before the tower rose, correct? So you weren't on the stage!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But this, er, fake Lamiroir is still singing! And she's pretty good!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's true!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">C'mon, Apollo! That's an easy one. They were just playing a recording!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha... The Gavinners aren't some kind of air guitar band, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? You mean, I'm wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">When we play a show live, we play live. No recordings. ...Perhaps you can explain, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Very well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, do tell! And add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! So this is it? The magical key to unlocking this illusion's dark secret!? Tell us how it works! Quickly! I can't bear the suspense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I was kind of hoping someone else would jump in at this point.</thought> W-Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Judge, I do hate to spoil the mood... ...but I haven't the faintest idea what he's talking about. And neither does he.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm a little confused, too, there, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right! By which I conclude that... I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Better luck next time, Polly-wog!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Justice. I'm holding you responsible for spoiling my mood!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Was that a tear I just saw in the judge's eye? ...Alright, nothing to do but rethink this through. The key's in the video somewhere. I'm sure of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What kind of evidence could prove that...?</thought> Um, what's your professional opinion about this one, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sorry. I don't work in evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I don't work in tricks! I'm an attorney, not a magician for crying out loud!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I'm sure Daddy would have loved working on this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, that makes me feel oh so much better.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I don't know about all of you, but I find this mystery fascinating! And I'm not letting this trial go any further until we get to the bottom of it! The defense will continue with the cross-examination until we have some answers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Easier said than done...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All made possible by the switching trick.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was quite a surprise to me at first. To think, a man, posing as me!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">An enchantment woven with music and magic... Perfection!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, above all else, I was careful that the music did not stop.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was on my way, when I heard the voice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And it was Daryan's voice you heard?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, I am certain it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A matter best left for later, ja? Put that forehead of yours to work on this illusion first.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hold on! I think the identity of the killer is a little more important, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Importance shmortance! Objection overruled! Tell us about the illusion!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No use trying to avoid the problem at hand, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trying to avoid the problem? This is a murder trial, the killer is the problem!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... had to keep singing, even while I moved.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The contradiction between Lamiroir's testimony and the video... Unraveling an illusion can't be so different from solving a normal case... Right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sorry, Apollo. I'm not telling. Not even if you make those puppy dog faces.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Fine, fine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were... singing...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. Mr. Gavin expressed a dislike for recordings... So I used this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... so you were singing the whole time? Even when you were crawling above the ceiling toward the backstage!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Why should it matter where I sing, when everywhere I go is the same darkness?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But if you were singing while you were walking...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Wouldn't the shooter and victim have heard? She was singing right over their heads, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That... is right!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You'd have to be pretty hard of hearing to miss someone singing in the ceiling!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Once again we come back to the state of the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What state...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack... I know what he means! That old speaker, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The speaker!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That speaker was blaring at the time of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, that's for monitoring the stage from this room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Monitoring?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It pipes in a real-time feed from the stage microphones. Useful for knowing when your set is coming up.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Satisfied? That dressing room was fitted with a large speaker playing a direct feed from the stage. ...At my request, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So Lamiroir singing in the ceiling... ...sounded just like Lamiroir singing over the speaker.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ingenious! Her voice was hidden... by her voice!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I... have just remembered something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do tell!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">When I heard the noise... the gunshots, yes? It startled me, so I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I stopped singing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I forgot the words I was supposed to sing!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The song... stopped!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Thankfully, it was the very beginning of the second verse. So not many would notice.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Forehead! That mixing board I lent you! Where is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mixing... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That machine, Apollo! The one that breaks music into tracks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, this! I'd completely forgotten about it... Let's take a listen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The song does stop there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? I must have missed it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at the lyrics sheet, at the top of the second verse. See where it says "Pleasure, Pleasure..."? Now listen again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This is evidence indeed! I believe we are guilty of making a terrible mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The crime didn't happen during the third set. It happened during the second, during Lamiroir's ballad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is true... ...then no one on stage during the second set could have been the shooter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which means that Daryan Crescend could have done it! He wasn't on stage for the second set!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I don't believe I've ever seen a trial turned around quite so thoroughly. ...Yet one problem remains.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead's theory does have a certain kind of logic to it. Yet it is entirely based upon Lamiroir's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes? Is there a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, it's quite simple, though it pains me to say it. What if she is lying to protect the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you have no proof...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All I'm saying is that the truth is as yet unclear. ...Until we hear directly from the man himself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The man... you don't mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Yes. Though he is a friend, and band member, Daryan Crescend must take the stand. I see no other way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As... someone with a new perspective on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...As a suspect, to be frank.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Finally! The rat's coming out of his hole! And I'm ready to catch him! Daryan Crescend, get ready for Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is as good a time as any to pause for a brief recess. The prosecution will summon the witness. Have him here and ready by the time we begin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I'm the last man who needs to be reminded of what his duties are.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, court is adjourned for a fifteen-minute recess!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! I can't believe it! It really happened during the second act? A-And right in the middle of Lamiroir's performance!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why she was in that air vent... ...and that "switch" and the flaming guitar. When you link it all together, that's what you end up with.</line>
<line speaker="???">...I knew you had what it took.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah... Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright! You... believed in me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just thought that'd make a cooler entrance than, say, "hiya"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why do I even bother hoping?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Where have you been lately, Daddy? You haven't been coming to the office at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, sorry about that, Trucy. I'm on a... secret mission.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Secret? You mean like, you're undercover?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like Mr. LeTouse, only shorter and not as well dressed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh no! What if you're shot, too, Daddy!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha! Would I do a thing like that to you? Anyway, I'm off for a while again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? You're leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, one thing before I go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............... Good luck.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Um... Is that all you came to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think you have things pretty much under control. You'll get Machi Tobaye off the hook, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you're after that detective, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daryan Crescend...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It won't be easy proving he did it. Especially not under the current court system...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The current court system...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did Prosecutor Gavin say during the trial? Your case is based on one fragile assumption. ...Namely, that our diva divine is telling the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But what about all the proof? The brooch... and the switch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A piece of jewelry, and a lyrical blunder... There are plenty of other ways to explain these things. The flaming guitar, too. ...All because you lack definitive proof of their connection to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the sultry songstress is lying... ...your case melts like butter in a frying pan. Leaving behind the faintly singed scent of failure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what do I do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like I said. Good luck. And be aware that it will be impossible to prove his guilt by conventional methods.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that reminds me. I have something to give you from our detective friend.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye... Ema!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see. This bag of snacks here was meant for me... Ah, here it is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are those, Daddy? They don't look like very good snacking material.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They were found at the scene. Analysis of the fragments revealed traces of gunpowder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Gunpowder...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably a firecracker or something similar, like the ones kids are into these days. These fragments were found under the sofa at the scene of the crime, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Under the sofa...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo! That's where we found that little device thingy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... this. <thought>Well, finally, some evidence that makes sense...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you think this was some kind of firecracker?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, or one of those noisemakers, like you shoot off on New Years!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you know that in China, they use firecrackers on New Years to scare off evil? So, it's kind of same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really!? I had no idea! Well did you know this? It takes more than 500 peanuts to make one 12-ounce jar of peanut butter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>At least my useless fact had something to do with the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all for me, I suppose. See you after the verdict. Maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Every man has an igniter inside him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Find Daryan Crescend's igniter... and set it off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And he walked out the door, just like... just like a magician. Normally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uhh... What does he want us to do? No "conventional methods"? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess we just have to take his advice, and hope it makes sense when the time comes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We're almost at the finish line. Hang in there, Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Court is now back in session. Prosecutor Gavin, where is Detective Crescend?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In the witness lounge, ready to be called at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Might I add... I don't believe any of this. He... Daryan was the first detective I ever worked with. We stopped working together when he moved to Criminal Affairs, Division 3... But his guitar playing... it fires my imagination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's nice, but it has nothing to do with the matter at hand. ...Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, I know. ...Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, call the final witness to the stand! ...Detective Daryan Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Daryan Crescend. Detective, Criminal Affairs, Division 3. That's the International Affairs Division, for those of you who didn't know. ...And I'm a guitarist for the Gavinners. Maybe you've heard of us?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you fully understand the circumstances under which you stand before us today?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, I understand, Your Honor. What I don't understand... is how you let this happen, "partner".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You gave me your word I wouldn't be standing here.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The situation's changed, Daryan... And don't call me "partner".</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Feh. So much for old friends.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I see what you're doing, Daryan. You're "pressing" the prosecution!</thought> ...Your Honor, if we could begin the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it's high time we did. Let's hear your testimony. You may begin with your response to Lamiroir's testimony. If, in fact you have anything to say about it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh I got plenty to say. Lying must be a national pastime in Borginia. ...And wherever you're from, Mr. "Justice". Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Conventional methods are out the window, huh... ...Here goes nothing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The diva's lying, plain and simple. She's got nothing to back up her story.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you claim Lamiroir's testimony was a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hey, don't get me wrong, I dig what she's doing, trying to protect that kid. And she's got the court eating vague statements out of her hand just 'cause she's blind.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You go too far, Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Look, all I'm saying is, you've got a reliable witness. Why not listen to the detective?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Skye...? Hmm... I see. Mr. Justice, you may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He didn't waste any time finding our weak spot... I can't do this with Lamiroir's testimony alone. I'll have to find some other way to prove when the shooting took place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The diva's lying, plain and simple. She's got nothing to back up her story.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't have any proof she was lying!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh yeah, kid? You saying I lied?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I'm just saying, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Glare back at him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I couldn't help it! I flinched by reflex!</thought> Detective Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah? What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, n-nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Chin up! Back straight! You're wilting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This guy's hard as nails! He makes Wocky look downright cooperative.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Look, there's no way the diva remembers my voice.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">In the first place, she never heard my voice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You never talked to her, even though you were playing in the same concert?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Not a word, as far as I can recall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, weren't there planning sessions or something?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Gavin took care of all that himself.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Daryan wasn't involved in any of the meetings with her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">As if you can just go around remembering everyone's voice like that anyway. Only an idiot would believe that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir's hearing is very sensitive... She could remember him if she heard him, I'm sure of it... I just can't prove it. And I need proof!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">She "forgot the words because she heard gunshots"? As if!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We know she missed the words. The mixing board proved it!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, yeah, there was a mistake. But blaming it on gunshots is just a lame excuse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The mixing board proves what? It proves there was a mistake in the song. A missed cue. So? She just flubbed it up, big time. That's all. She spins this story about a gunshot to protect the kid... and cover for her own goof. Man, I'd have to hand it to her... if she wasn't sticking it to me at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Daryan, watch what you say. Lamiroir is an artist. She "just flubbed it up"? That's no small accusation for a performer of her caliber.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh. She got to you, alright. I can see it in your eyes. I tell you, most of her stuff is so pretentious, it's way over my head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm detecting a rift in the Gavinners's ranks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Anyway, she's too close to the defendant. Her testimony can't be trusted. You ask me, I'd go with Detective Skye's story at the drop of a pick.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Didn't Detective Ema Skye hear those gunshots during the third set, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually... I was there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">So I hear. Which means you heard them, too, right? The gunshots.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. We heard "gunshots". Neither I nor Ema actually saw the shooting, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...... Heh. I guess you and Lamiroir got the same excuse then.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We know one thing for certain here. There were gunshot-like sounds that emanated from that room during the third set. What we must determine is whether those sounds were actually gunshots.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Machi heard them, too! Remember he said he ran for the air duct when he heard them?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So... how do we figure out just what those "gunshots" during the third set were?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Some things were found at the crime scene after yesterday's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What things?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The first was this small device...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...That's the remote-triggered igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Correct. And... one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are those? The remains of something burnt? Not another guitar, I hope!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Traces of gunpowder were found on these fragments. We have a report that it was something like a firecracker.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh... <thought>How did Gavin know about this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What? You think Detective Skye works for you? I received the report this morning, before coming here. That's when I made my decision, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What decision is this, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I registered Daryan as a witness in today's trial. ...Just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This raises another possibility. Those gunshot-like sounds during the third set... ...could have been two firecrackers rigged to go off by remote control!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ha ha! You got an active imagination, don't you? But you shouldn't say every little thing you think. Your explanation there seems a bit too convenient to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">So, you're saying these firecrackers just happened to go off... ...right when two witnesses came walking by? Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Daryan was out on stage when it happened, Apollo! How would he know someone was backstage right then!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">If a firecracker goes off in the forest, and there's no one there to hear... You get my drift! Why go through the trouble, man!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...! <thought>How do I explain this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...He may not look it, but Daryan is a gifted detective. Show any weakness, and he's sure to find it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">"He may not look it", partner? Gee, thanks, man.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...That reminds me. I happened to pass through that very hallway several times that day myself. And I saw something odd there just before the third set.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something... odd?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A headset. The kind all of the band and staff members were wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>That's right! We picked this up in front of the door to that dressing room!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What if that headset wasn't dropped, but placed? And what if it was turned on?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could hear what was going on in that hallway! Even if you were out on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Feh... Whose side are you on, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Listen to me, Daryan. There are no sides in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is why I now turn to you, Herr Forehead. I've a question for you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? For me...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The igniter and the burnt fragments that were found at the scene of the crime... It's certainly a possibility that they were part of a ruse to fake the sound of gunshots. Throw the headset from the hallway into the mix, and you could fabricate an alibi. But we're still no closer to proving anything. Those gunshots might have been real, or fake. We can't say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You've raised the possibility that the shots heard during the third set were faked. Now you need to prove the other half of the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The other half...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Look, I'll just tell him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He wants you to prove the thing went down in the second act... ...while our little piano player was on stage. That right, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Indeed. If you can't prove that... ...then to continue this cross-examination would be pointless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Justice? Can you prove the crime took place during the second set?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Yeah, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You'd better know, Apollo! Otherwise we're through...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It can be proven!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You make it sound like someone else is going to come along and do it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue with the cross-examination then, shall we? Witness, your testimony, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This isn't going to be easy. I need some decisive proof, and fast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh... You ready, kid? 'Cause I am.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The shooting took place when I was on stage, man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That could have been what the shooter wanted us to think!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I'll tell you what the shooter, that kid, wants you to think. He wants you to think the diva heard me in that room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! I'm back to relying on Lamiroir's testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As much as I'm enjoying the Daryan &amp; Forehead show, there is no need for such tempers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't make us into some comedy duo.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">This mean the Gavin &amp; Daryan show's cancelled?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Neither of your claims can be proven... or disproved. We could argue for days like this and get nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin is quite right. This court will hear no further discussion on this topic without new facts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>New facts, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Remember this, Detective Crescend?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...The mixing board? What about it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It seems there was clear proof left behind. ...Right here in Lamiroir's song.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Her song...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What exactly is this, erm, device thingy? A new variety of gramophone, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, we just used this! And don't get me started on "gramophone"!</thought> This device was used to record the performance part by part.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Part...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You move the sliders to adjust the volume. Each instrument is adjustable separately. Lamiroir's voice included.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho hoh! ...But what does this prove?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to Lamiroir's testimony... At the moment of the shooting, she forgot the words to the song.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah... You intend to examine the recording at that moment, ja? We might even hear those gunshots!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Ridiculous. How are you supposed to hear gunshots back in that dressing room out on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Have you forgotten, Daryan? We were all wearing these headsets.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We were all deeply involved in our performance... ...but Lamiroir's headset would've picked up what she heard all the same.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's get to analyzing that recording! ...Right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir stopped singing when she heard the shots fired... Find that spot, and I'll find the gunshots!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Listen to this part!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this!? ...... I hear nothing! How is this possible!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, isn't the judge hard of hearing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can hear just fine, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! He heard me thinking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I saw what you were thinking on your face.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Judge's hearing aside, I, too, heard nothing. ...Leading me to believe there is nothing there to be heard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I guess that's the wrong spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty, on behalf of all who are hearing-impaired, you insensitive braggart! Enjoy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Once more, if you would!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Listen closely to this part! This is the track with Lamiroir's vocals!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I did hear something faintly there, yes! Why... it sounded like a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Wh-What!? This has to be some kind of mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Or... the sound was coming over the headset along with her voice.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Gavin... You're crazy, man, crazy! An upstanding prosecutor like you even listening to this weak evidence!? Man, you can barely hear that! How do you know it's a gun?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps it is you who are hard of hearing, Daryan. It sounds like a gunshot to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Admit it! You lost, Detective Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">OK, so what about the gunshots Detective Skye heard? You heard 'em, too, didn't you? Don't even think about telling me you were "mistaken"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Were you thinking of telling him that, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, Your Honor. Detective Skye and I clearly heard what sounded like gunshots. But... they weren't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I have evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then I think you'd best show it to the court. Let's see this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you would, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence showing what we really heard... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is your "gunshot"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That's your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And I had such high hopes for you, Herr Forehead...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm having trouble understanding how that piece of evidence is a gunshot... Next you'll be throwing pie plates in the air and calling them UFOs!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Even I wouldn't stoop quite that low...</thought> S-Sorry, Your Honor. One more time, please?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why not. And... get it right this time, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Some things were found at the crime scene after yesterday's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What things?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The first was this small device...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...That's the remote-triggered igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Correct. And... one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are those? The remains of something burnt? Not another guitar, I hope!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Traces of gunpowder were found on these fragments. We have a report that it was something like a firecracker.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh... <thought>How did Gavin know about this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What? You think Detective Skye works for you? I received the report this morning, before coming here. That's when I made my decision, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What decision is this, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I registered Daryan as a witness in today's trial. ...Just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This raises another possibility. Those gunshot-like sounds during the third set... ...could have been two firecrackers rigged to go off by remote control!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ha ha! You got an active imagination, don't you? But you shouldn't say every little thing you think. Your explanation there seems a bit too convenient to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">So, you're saying these firecrackers just happened to go off... ...right when two witnesses came walking by? Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Daryan was out on stage when it happened, Apollo! How would he know someone was backstage right then!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">If a firecracker goes off in the forest, and there's no one there to hear... You get my drift! Why go through the trouble, man!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...! <thought>How do I explain this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...He may not look it, but Daryan is a gifted detective. Show any weakness, and he's sure to find it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">"He may not look it", partner? Gee, thanks, man.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...That reminds me. I happened to pass through that very hallway several times that day myself. And I saw something odd there just before the third set.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something... odd?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A headset. The kind all of the band and staff members were wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>That's right! We picked this up in front of the door to that dressing room!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What if that headset wasn't dropped, but placed? And what if it was turned on?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could hear what was going on in that hallway! Even if you were out on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Feh... Whose side are you on, Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Listen to me, Daryan. There are no sides in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In any case...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The shooting took place during the second set? If you're so sure, let's see your proof.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the "gunshots" heard during the third set could have been...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What? Some kind of set up? I've heard that one before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We need proof, Apollo! We need to prove that the shooting took place during the second set!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if you know how to do that, I'm all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe the gunshots are the key after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, Lamiroir said she heard them, right? Right in the middle of her illusion, when she was up above the ceiling.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...When she forgot the words to the song, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you can prove the gun was shot right when she missed those lyrics... ...we're home free, I'd think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True... Not easy, but true... <thought>Is there some way to prove that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's take a look through our evidence! Maybe there's something in there...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Hey, aren't you supposed to be cross-examining me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Try to refrain from private discussions during cross-examination, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, right, Your Honor! Sorry! <thought>Just let me take a quick look through the Court Record...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It seems there was clear proof left behind. ...Right here in Lamiroir's song.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Her song...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What exactly is this, erm, device thingy? A new variety of gramophone, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>C'mon, we just used this! And don't get me started on "gramophone"!</thought> This device was used to record the performance part by part.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Part...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You move the sliders to adjust the volume. Each instrument is adjustable separately. Lamiroir's voice included.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho hoh! ...But what does this prove?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to Lamiroir's testimony... At the moment of the shooting, she forgot the words to the song.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah... You intend to examine the recording at that moment, ja? We might even hear those gunshots!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Ridiculous. How are you supposed to hear gunshots back in that dressing room out on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Have you forgotten, Daryan? We were all wearing these headsets.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We were all deeply involved in our performance... ...but Lamiroir's headset would've picked up what she heard all the same.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's get to analyzing that recording! ...Right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir stopped singing when she heard the shots fired... Find that spot, and I'll find the gunshots!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Listen to this part!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this!? ...... I hear nothing! How is this possible!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, isn't the judge hard of hearing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can hear just fine, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! He heard me thinking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I saw what you were thinking on your face.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Judge's hearing aside, I, too, heard nothing. ...Leading me to believe there is nothing there to be heard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I guess that's the wrong spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty, on behalf of all who are hearing-impaired, you insensitive braggart! Enjoy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Once more, if you would!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Listen closely to this part! This is the track with Lamiroir's vocals!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I did hear something faintly there, yes! Why... it sounded like a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Wh-What!? This has to be some kind of mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's pretty eager to paint Lamiroir as a liar, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, because her testimony is basically our entire case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... This is tough. So, what do we do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I've got a few ideas. <thought>I just need to find another way to prove it didn't happen when he says it did!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe a case has been made. Gunshots were heard during the second set. Which means Lamiroir's testimony... was true.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Grah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! So... she was telling the truth about what she heard?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It was the other man speaking, not Mr. LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, what did he say!?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"It's over. Press the switch! Now!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just after that, there was a gunshot... and then the guitar caught on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Detective Crescend... You weren't on stage during the second set. You could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But why did we only hear one gunshot on the recording? Weren't two bullets fired from this weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir was moving through the air vent, Your Honor. She must not have been close enough for her mic to catch the first shot. But then, as she passed over the dressing room... ...the gun fired again, and Mr. LeTouse's life was taken. Well, Detective Crescend?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, once again I am reminded of something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Our performance that day...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your performance?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Seeing the mixing board jogged my memory. You were there, too, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What is it with today!? Problem after problem! Achtung! My hog won't start. My guitar case is busted... ...my guitar's been burnt to a crisp, and to top it all off, someone's dead! ...And then there was that performance just now. What was that all about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This part is off.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is that? Hmm... 2nd Guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was you Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I thought it strange at the time. How could you miss such a simple cue? I know you, I know how you play. You're better than that.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, well, I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You what? And Prosecutor Gavin, what are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm talking about the murder weapon. Mr. LeTouse's 45-caliber hand cannon. As we have learned, even the shooter doesn't go unscarred with a revolver that size. The kickback is enough to dislocate your shoulder, if you're an amateur.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait...! You mean his playing was affected because he hurt himself shooting that revolver?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! You're forgetting something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Detective Crescend...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I am a trained police officer, you know. I've had firearms training. Plenty of it. I'm no amateur.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The standard sidearm issued to police officers is a 38-caliber weapon. A much tamer beast. Also, the murder weapon belonged to the victim, Mr. LeTouse. ...Which suggests there was a struggle between killer and victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... the killer might not have been holding the revolver correctly when he fired! Is that what you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The thought had occurred to me, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, does the witness have anything to say to this?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Crescend!!!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What I want to ask is what Mr. Sleeves-rolled-up-ready-for-action has to say. Hey, you. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Exactly which piece of your evidence is decisive, again? You got a little noise on a tape that could be anything. And you have an alleged guitar cue miss due to a 45-caliber kickback. I weep for this case, Gavin, I really do.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You can line up your little weak pieces of evidence all you want. I didn't shoot that manager. And that's the obvious truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The witness has a point. The defense's arguments, while persuasive, are not decisive. I believe we should hear what the witness has to say in response to the case so far. ...Your testimony, please, Detective Crescend. Tell us your reasons why you couldn't have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">C'mon! Why would I even want to kill that manager?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. A simple reason, indeed. Prosecutor Gavin. Is it the case that Mr. LeTouse had not been to our country before?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">According to our records... Yes. Not even once.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Very well! Mr. Justice, you may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, now I need to find a motive...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">C'mon! Why would I even want to kill that manager?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Her manager, sure, but Mr. LeTouse was...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, right. Sorry. An Interpol agent, wasn't he? I just have trouble picturing that big lunk as an undercover cop, you dig? And not a very good one, seeing as how he got wasted. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's cold, dawg!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Not that it matters, either way. See, I had no reason to kill the man, whatever he was.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You want a reason? Easy. I got no motive, man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's the same for Machi! No motive was proven for him!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">C'mon, he traveled around the world with that old fart! He had plenty of time to come up with a motive of his own.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">More than I sure did. I mean, think about it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">This was that diva's first trip to this country, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daryan, you're a detective with International Affairs?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah? What of it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even if this was Mr. LeTouse's first trip to this country... ...you still could have met him prior to the concert!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or don't you take any international trips in International Affairs...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's right! Well, Detective Crescend?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh heh heh. That's your game, is it? Guess I'd better confess, then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Confess"...!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah. It's a bit of an embarrassment... but I've never been sent overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What!? But you're in International...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">See, me and planes got a difference of opinion. We don't like each other much.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My condolences, Herr Forehead, but he's telling the truth. He's never set foot outside the country. I can guarantee it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">As it turns out, my division has plenty of work to do locally as well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's... so unfair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">How could I possibly know her manager?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you didn't fraternize with him at all during the concert?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Fraternize? Hah! I don't think we exchanged a single word. As if anyone would want to talk to that old Eastern "Bloc"-head. Now the ladies, that's a different matter altogether. So, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">If I didn't know him, why would I want to kill him!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What? What!? Wipe that look off your face before I do it for you. Listen! You try throwing out one of your wild accusations... ...I'll throw it back at you so hard you'll forget who you're accusing of what.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead, perhaps it's best if you let your evidence do the talking, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah ha ha ha! Man, what evidence? That's what I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he's using this motive question as ammunition, huh? Well, I've got ammunition too... Evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor... Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? Hmm... Looks like candy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, it's not. Don't lick it, please. Detective Crescend. ...Ever seen this?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Looks like a piece of candy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What it is... is evidence. Don't lick it before you try it.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Specifically, this is a replica of a cocoon... ...It was found among the victim's belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A cocoon? Never seen one that color.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is a variety only found in the Republic of Borginia. Nowhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright... But what is this cocoon replica doing in my courtroom? Surely, this has nothing to do with a motive for killing Mr. LeTouse! ...Does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It does! ...Wait! I mean, I think it does.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...You don't sound so confident, man.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A cocoon... Is it one of those silky cocoons? The kind that you can make, well, silk out of?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not this one. This cocoon makes a powerful "curative".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A curative? For what...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently, it is most efficacious at treating a disease thought incurable. It is the only medicine of its kind. ...However, it is illegal to take one of these healing cocoons out of Borginia.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whatever for? If it's such a miracle cure, why not share it with the world?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, that's what I've been wondering!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We looked into the matter at some length. Apparently, it isn't difficult at all to manufacture the remedy from the cocoon. Yet, if you change the process only slightly... ...you can easily make a large quantity of something else entirely. ...A deadly poison, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There was an incident, several years ago, where some of these got out onto the black market. It caused quite the commotion in the global community. Though the media was kept largely unaware.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Intriguing!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All this has led to a strict ban on the cocoons' export. One rigidly enforced... by Interpol, among others.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Interpol...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! The victim, Romein LeTouse, was an Interpol agent. Detective Crescend! You insist on referring to him as a "manager"... But that is misleading! Romein LeTouse wasn't killed as a manager! He was killed as an undercover agent!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...... So I was trying to smuggle this gumball into the country? That what you're trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm saying that could well be a motive for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, so I was going to sell it on the black market, make myself a pretty penny? ...Ridiculous. I mean, totally unthinkable.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Unthinkable", you say? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it's time for another testimony... ...about this "smuggling of cocoons" business!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">International Affairs got a memo about these cocoons.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... Interpol wanted these cocoons bad enough to send Mr. LeTouse undercover.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You kids think up the craziest things... But no way am I going to risk life and limb... ...just to get my hands on some dirty cocoon money!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not the most noble of statements, but duly noted.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">According to reports, these cocoons top Interpol's list. Selling them to an underground organization would be risky.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, you may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is the only motive I've got... He was up to something, and I'm going to find out what!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">International Affairs got a memo about these cocoons.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That memo! That's how you knew about the cocoons!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, nice one, nice one! I'm runnin' scared now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You had to know about the cocoons to plan this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just how well known are these cocoons? I'm embarrassed to admit it, but I'd never heard of them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Lamiroir knew about them, though not their use.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My reports indicate that there are ongoing efforts to control information about the cocoons. Most people only know they're illegal to export, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... I've nothing to be embarrassed about after all!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You could say people like me who know about them are a minority, yeah. But that includes everyone in International Affairs, man! And everyone in Interpol, too, for that matter. Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Interpol's all hot and bothered about 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there are other Interpol agents like Mr. LeTouse?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">All over the world, likely. Deep undercover, most of 'em. That's why these cocoons are too hot for the black market. You don't want Interpol sniffing through your wares. Most came to the conclusion that...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Can't sell 'em on the black market. Too dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dangerous...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, Interpol finds you, they arrest you on the spot. Or another marketeer might think you're part of a sting and take you out himself. Times have changed...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why not choose a less dangerous buyer then? I would.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">How clueless are you? Everyone in the market's dangerous! The second they found out I was a cop, I could kiss my keester goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why sell to a black market buyer? How about someone... like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That article... That's about the Chief Justice's...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A deadly poison can be extracted from the cocoon. But so can a cure! And not a cure for just any disease... ...A cure for Incuritis!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Incuritis! ...I've heard of that somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You went to visit a victim of the disease this morning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aha! Why, that's the disease the Chief Justice's son has! You aren't saying...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Our witness is a detective. He would have contact with the Chief Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are saying! The Chief Justice would never deal in contraband!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not even to save his own son's life?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! But, even if the deal went through... Why it'd be an international scandal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Detective Crescend's insurance! If word ever got out, the one with his neck on the line... ...would be the Chief Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Crescend! Is this true!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">First I'm a murderer, now I'm a smuggler...? How many crimes are you trying to pin on me, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Distasteful as it is to think about, if the Chief Justice were the buyer... ...why, a seller couldn't hope for a better deal. A very cowardly seller!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Don't let Sleeves over there trick you. So I made a deal with the Chief Justice? Where's your proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh yeah, and you're forgetting one other important thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Do tell.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Interpol isn't the only ones out there watching this. Borginian Customs barely sleeps, they're so worried about cocoons getting out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So we were informed. Let's continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Borginian Customs is very thorough. Everything and everyone gets checked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just how strict is this Customs' check?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Way strict. They keep planes on the ground for hours.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I do recall it being a bit extreme. They were even confiscating gumdrops and marshmallows.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... it would be hard to distinguish them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right. Gavin was in Borginia, wasn't he.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I remember setting off the metal detectors several times. I had to practically strip naked to walk through.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Here's a travel tip for you, Gavin: leave the bling at home, you glimmerous fop.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, cocoon smuggling ain't exactly lucrative anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, wouldn't scarcity drive up prices?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, and attention. Every gangster and his brother would want a piece of that action! They'd turn your forehead into swiss cheese before you could say, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Maybe we could get them to cut his hair, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Who's on trial here again?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Man, you so obviously know nothing about the market!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...And that's a bad thing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Don't even try to mess with me about this stuff...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why not choose a less dangerous buyer then? I would.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">How clueless are you? Everyone in the market's dangerous! The second they found out I was a cop, I could kiss my keester goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why sell to a black market buyer? How about someone... like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That article... That's about the Chief Justice's...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A deadly poison can be extracted from the cocoon. But so can a cure! And not a cure for just any disease... ...A cure for Incuritis!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Incuritis! ...I've heard of that somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You went to visit a victim of the disease this morning!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aha! Why, that's the disease the Chief Justice's son has! You aren't saying...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Our witness is a detective. He would have contact with the Chief Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You are saying! The Chief Justice would never deal in contraband!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not even to save his own son's life?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! But, even if the deal went through... Why it'd be an international scandal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Detective Crescend's insurance! If word ever got out, the one with his neck on the line... ...would be the Chief Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Crescend! Is this true!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">First I'm a murderer, now I'm a smuggler...? How many crimes are you trying to pin on me, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Distasteful as it is to think about, if the Chief Justice were the buyer... ...why, a seller couldn't hope for a better deal. A very cowardly seller!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Don't let Sleeves over there trick you. So I made a deal with the Chief Justice? Where's your proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh yeah, and you're forgetting one other important thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Do tell.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Interpol isn't the only ones out there watching this. Borginian Customs barely sleeps, they're so worried about cocoons getting out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So we were informed. Let's continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Cocoon possession will get you arrested on the spot, and then sentenced to death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's pretty extreme.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Borginia has this rep as an idyllic, laid back place. Truth is, they're beyond hard core with security.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The Republic of Borginia is a peaceful, pleasant country. So this level of security shows us how truly concerned they are about these cocoons.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">That's the situation...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Man, I'm in International Affairs! I know the deal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which is why you'd know how to find a loophole in the system!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hey... You can say what you want about me, but back off of International Affairs! There ain't no "loopholes", OK? What do you think we are, boy scouts?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That wasn't what I was trying to... um...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Down, Daryan. ...It's as you say. There are no loopholes, at least in the case of these cocoons. International Affairs, Interpol, and Borginian Customs are all watching.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">See, we know what we're doing! Not like some yipping little doggies that lap up every word that diva says.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Why I oughta...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oughta what? You want some of this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha. Chill, both of you. Let's do this cool, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr! Screw cool! I want this guy's head on a stick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hey, man, if there's a way to get cocoons out of there, I'd sure like to know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're in a position to know quite a bit about smuggling.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, I need to know a bit for work, sure. But all we get are reports on the failed smuggling ops. Not exactly something you want to go copying. But if you want, I can tell you a few of them. Maybe you'll succeed and get rich!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I would be interested in hearing. Purely from a legal perspective, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I weep for our judicial system.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...The replica has to be the key to his motive... There's got to be a way to find out what he was up to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, there is one way.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Whaa--!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One way to get something out of the country, no checks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You become a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah... Aaaaaaaaaaah! I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Believe it, Prosecutor Gavin. What was it that you told me yesterday at your office?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It was a beautiful instrument. It was played lovingly for many years. A guitar befitting a woman like Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How did it end up here?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I mentioned how much I enjoyed playing it that night, and she made a present of it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So this guitar is from Borginia?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That it is. We couldn't carry it on the plane. Changes in air pressure and humidity ruin the wood. So, we vacuum packed it in Lamiroir's studio. I used a special shipping service available to me for transporting evidence. They brought it right up to my office for me. ...Pristine and untouched.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did I get that right, Prosecutor Gavin? "Untouched"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Quite. The guitar was wrapped in several sheets and vacuum packed in Borginia. The pack was untouched until the day of the concert. Are you saying that guitar was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With cocoons this small, it would've been very easy... ...to use your guitar as a mule to smuggle a cocoon out of Borginia!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which reminds me, Prosecutor Gavin. That guitar had some "work" done on it recently, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Work...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good memory, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, you know how guitars have a round hole in the front? It is called the "sound hole". Well, they found something attached to the wood just inside the hole. ...A broken device of some sort.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A broken... device?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. This, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An igniter...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. Consider this, if you will. What if that igniter wasn't the only thing that was attached inside your guitar?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You... You mean...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He means this, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah. Aaaaaaaah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There was a way to get a cocoon out of the country! They could use picky Prosecutor Gavin's privileged guitar as a mule!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And who better to do that than someone with access... ...like a member of the band!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yooooooooooooooooowrk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! So the igniter...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Was placed in there for a clear reason, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was a safety precaution!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A precaution...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ahh... Herr Forehead. At last, it all comes together.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Every strange thing that happened that day. Care to review? Maestro, the gentle sounds of Lamiroir's ballad, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">First... my keys were stolen. A harmless misdemeanor. Which forced me to break the lock on my guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The key was stolen to retrieve the cocoon from the guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... things didn't go so well. The smuggler wasn't counting on the guitar being wrapped! Only a member of the band could get near that case. Unwrapping the guitar would raise too many suspicions. ...Then the concert began. Right about this time... ...a very large problem presented itself to the smuggler.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Mr. LeTouse, an undercover agent, was on to something. He would have known about the guitar. He'd only have to check the shipping records. So... Mr. LeTouse tried to examine the guitar himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the cocoon were confiscated then, the gig would be up. The only thing left for the smuggler to do was to get rid of the whole lot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The guitar burst into flames, and the cocoon... was lost. And then... Mr. LeTouse died.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">With Lamiroir there to "witness" it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's your case.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Eh heh. Heh heh ha ha! Brilliant, man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Crescend...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I gotta know, you make all that up on the fly?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For a made-up story... ...it makes a great deal of sense... Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Feh! The Republic of Borginia? Sorry, man, but I haven't even been there.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">True, you haven't.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Let's see you make up a story for that, kid! How'd I hide the cocoon in the first place, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not so hard to imagine. You had help. A Borginian accomplice. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That you had an accomplice was clear from the start! The voice Lamiroir heard proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You made this transmission from backstage.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">While your co-conspirator was on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... But who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it, the coup de grâce! And for once I know what I'm doing... There's only one person who could have helped him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear what Mr. Justice has to say, then. But be warned. With a great accusation comes great responsibility. Make up your answer "on the fly" as it were, and you'll be harshly penalized! ...Are you ready, Mr. Justice? Who was the smuggler's accomplice!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Lamiroir was the accomplice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you should get that forehead checked out... As you may recall, Lamiroir was attacked yesterday! Hardly something one does to one's accomplice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... I'd like to commend Prosecutor Gavin on his superb reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, and here, have this penalty for your trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me ask again...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This person is the accomplice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Eh? I thought you said the accomplice was Borginian!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, actually... can I take that back?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Certainly, and here, have this penalty for your trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me ask again...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There is only one person who meets all the requirements of the accomplice... ...and that person is the defendant, Machi Tobaye!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... Mr. Justice... He's your client!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">A defense attorney accusing his client? That's a new one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I assure you, no one is more unhappy about this than I. But, I am here to defend him in the murder of Mr. LeTouse. And I stand by my statement earlier that he is innocent of that particular crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... the defendant is Borginian. He does meet the basic requirements to be the accomplice. But, what if it was, in fact, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It couldn't have been.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, you seem sure of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The reason... is electronic signals, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Electronic signals...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall that this remote only works to a range of 30 feet. Beyond that, it's useless.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now, think back to the testimony... When the shooter made his transmission, Lamiroir was in the air vent. Right above the dressing room where the shooter stood. Let's look at the stage diagram! This is the area that the remote could reach from the air vent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, looking at this... ...it seems that Lamiroir still could have done the deed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No. When the shooter made that transmission... ...the stage was slightly different than shown here. It was in the middle of "The Guitar's Serenade". Part of the stage... was raised. Prosecutor Gavin and the Lamiroir stand-in were in the air! They were on a tower which happens to be 15 feet tall! In other words! The remote couldn't have worked from Lamiroir's position in the air vent!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Detective Crescend? What do you say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Could we see the video where Gavin's guitar burns? Just one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah? Ah... Well. I don't see why not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh-What? Don't tell me he has a way out of this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Ah ha ha ha ha! Too bad, so sad... punk!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Punk...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">First you were "Sleeves", then "kid", now "punk". You're losing rank fast, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What exactly were we supposed to see in this video?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The problem isn't in what we "see". Correct, Daryan?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Right. It's what you hear. We are musicians after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Care to explain for us non-musicians?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Sure thing, punk. Let me get your yarn straight first: You're saying I ordered the wee pianist to set off that igniter? That right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Well in order to do that, he'd have to press a switch. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...OK...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Well, take another listen. Pay attention to the piano.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Piano...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What seems to be the problem there? The piano sounded just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">And that's the problem! Man, you still don't get it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah. How's he supposed to hit that switch if he's playing? You've got Ms. Diva, the guitar, the bass, the piano, and the drums... The only one with her hands free was the diva!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">But according to you... ...she couldn't have been the accomplice, could she?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Your accomplice would have had a hard time helping out... ...if they couldn't even press a switch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Uuuuuuuuuurrrrgh! <thought>The piano plays non-stop! He couldn't have pressed that switch...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? The piano does seem to be playing when the guitar catches fire.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">It's OK. We all make mistakes sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo!? Were you wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't be wrong! Everything makes perfect sense! How could it all... just...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Strange.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No, it's just... Something's odd about the performance there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..."Odd"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. If Machi Tobaye didn't press that switch... ...then he could not be the accomplice you claim he is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But everything points to it! Every fact says he's the accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...You got the facts wrong, man.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Here're some facts for you: Gavin's guitar is on fire. But the pianist didn't press that switch. In other words, your story is full of holes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, let's hear your final opinion on this matter now. Was the defendant, Machi Tobaye, the accomplice? Your answer will reflect on everything you've said here. Give it some thought.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! If Machi's not the accomplice... ...then our whole case is ruined!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know that! It has to be him... He was the only one who could have helped the smuggler... He had to have pressed that switch!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you'd better find a way to prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh! What do I do... What do I do!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack... There has to be something that doesn't fit! ...Something odd.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something odd...! Wait a second...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What? You thought of something!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What was Gavin saying just now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Strange.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's strange?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No, it's just... Something's odd about the performance there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...It's not much to go on, but it's all I've got! What exactly did he hear that was "odd"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Have you come up with something, Mr. Justice? May I remind you that everything rests on this. Can you prove Machi Tobaye pressed that switch? Let's hear your final answer! Can you prove that Machi Tobaye pressed that switch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I don't know if you call this "proof", per se... But... I can prove it was possible!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... can't prove it. But... I can prove it was possible!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then, as prosecutor, it falls to me to ask you to show us evidence supporting this. Herr Forehead. You're sure about this?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Accept it! There's no evidence, man!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see your evidence, Mr. Justice. On what do you base your claim that the defendant pressed that switch?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The basis for my claim... is this evidence, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! You can't bluff your way out of this one!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nor can you prove anyone pressed the switch with that... "evidence".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe... I picked the wrong evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">For every bluff, there is an equal and opposite penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Urgh... What did Gavin hear that was "odd"? That's the only hint I've got here. If Machi's hands were tied up playing the piano...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you can show us your evidence again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The basis for my claim... is music, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Music? What about music?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's listen to the piano part, around the time when the switch was to be pressed... ...right before the guitar burst into flame.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I hear a piano being played.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... doesn't it sound kind of simple?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Simple...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, I think I know what he's suggesting. You think Machi could have played that part... with one hand?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One hand...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He only needed one hand to press that switch! He could play the piano with the other!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! What, so you're some kind of piano savant?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, actually no.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Then what do you know!? You can't play a part like that with one hand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...! <thought>Maybe... I don't know what I'm talking about here.</thought> Wait! I know! Hey, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah? You got something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, your father, he's a pianist! Could he...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Daddy? He couldn't play a part like that even if he had three hands!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">So sorry... So sad for you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... ...No. Not really.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">H-Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was just the easy way to prove it. There's always the hard way.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Man... How are you going to prove whether he played it with one hand or two!? You can't!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I admit, it will be rather difficult to prove. But it's highly likely he was playing with one hand.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">H-How do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The clue is what Prosecutor Gavin described as sounding "odd".</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What sounded odd? I'll bet we can tell by listening to a certain part of the song.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">No... No way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it seems we've come to the moment of truth at last. Let's hear what Mr. Justice has to say for himself. Show us the part that proves the defendant was playing with one hand... ...right before the guitar burst into flame!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Machi was definitely playing one-handed just before the guitar caught fire! And one section of the song proves it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the section? Hmm... I'm afraid I don't hear it. What's your opinion as an artist, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's a beautiful song. And the lyrics... are outstanding.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll take that to mean there isn't a problem with this section at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, so what was the "odd" thing that Gavin heard? The switch was pressed in the first half of the second verse, right? I know! I just need to find a place to compare to that!</thought> Your Honor! If you'll give me one more chance, I think I can find it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose we don't have a choice. Very well. You claim the defendant was playing with one hand when the switch was pressed... Show us the part that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin... I'm sure you've realized by now... ...just what it was that sounded "odd" to you.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As I'm sure you've realized it yourself, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-Realized what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll demonstrate. Let's listen to the part in question again, shall we? Pay particular attention to the "But a fleeting melody" phrase.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Man, man, man! How many times do we have to listen to the same thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right. Enough of that!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's listen to another section, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Another section...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The guitar burst into flame at the end of the second verse. Let's listen to the same spot... in the first verse. Pay attention to "O that night in your embrace"...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...! P-Play verse two again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There! Did you hear that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They "feel" the same, true... ...but they're clearly very different!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well put, Your Honor! The phrase in verse two is quite simple... But the same phrase in verse one has high and low notes! You'd have to use two hands to play that for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Urk... Hrrah! Wh-What's that prove!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would think you'd know that by now.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">This is why I hate dealing with amateurs, man... So the two verses had different arrangements! Happens all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not this time, Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There's no point in changing an arrangement if you can't hear it clearly. And that wasn't the point. I had him play specifically so that the piano would stay in the background.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh. Ohhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That was what I noticed. "Why should the same phrase sound slightly different?" I asked myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now ask yourselves why Machi changed how he played... and there's only one answer! He needed a free hand in order to press the switch!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Unh... Unnnnoooooooooork!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!! Order!!!!! I believe this ties all the facts together... Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, quite. Though, personally, this comes as a terrible disappointment.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Heh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What? No comeback...? I can't believe it! I finally did it! I shut him up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Barring an objection from the prosecution... I will now state the court's opinion on this matter...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh... Heh heh heh... Ah ha ha ha ha ha haaaah! Good show, Sleeves. No, great show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's not over? <thought>I don't like it when he looks so... so happy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">You tell him Gavin. Tell him what's so disappointing!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Personally, I'm terribly disappointed... ...in you, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh... M-Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. Don't get me wrong, your case is solid. The facts all check out. But, even now... ...you have yet to show us a single piece of decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but the facts... Anyone can see it was him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately, "anyone" does not include the law. I'm afraid your case doesn't cut it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... But...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A thousand facts might point toward the same conclusion... ...but without decisive evidence, it's not proof. That's the rule under our current legal system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't believe it...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does not seem as though the defense has any more evidence to present.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Oh, I think if he did we already would have seen it a long ways back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is unfortunate... ...but, at present, this court is unable to acknowledge your accusation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaat!? <thought>The truth is staring us all right in the face! Why can't they see it!? What's the point of a legal system that protects criminals!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Remember what Daddy said?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It won't be easy proving he did it. Especially not under the current court system...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what do I do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like I said. Good luck. And be aware that it will be impossible to prove his guilt by conventional methods.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Every man has an igniter inside him. Find Daryan Crescend's igniter... and set it off.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what he meant by every man's "igniter"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think he just meant a weak spot, no? The kind of thing that a single spark could turn into a wildfire of emotion... <thought>I won't be able to press him further by conventional means... I've got to find a weak spot in this guy... Something fatal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...So, can I get back to work now, or what? It may look like I got a lot of time on my hands... ...but I got no more time to play pretend with this deadweight attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Well, Mr. Justice? We've come this far without decisive evidence... ...This witness won't be coming back to the stand once we let him go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Every man has an igniter.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Didn't you say "the better the guitar, the brighter it burns", Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, yes. Good guitars are kept dry, is why. That provides the best sound.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even a small spark could cause irreparable damage. Your plan has an "igniter" in it, too, Detective. ...It was there from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Fightin' time, Justice. If you blow this one... ...he'll be out of your hands for good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Go for it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What, and this igniter's supposed to come "burn" me up? That's almost poetic there, Mr. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All the better. I'm rather fond of poetry... And I intend to hear this one through to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead. You are accusing this man, Daryan Crescend of two crimes: The murder of Mr. LeTouse, and the smuggling of a Borginian Cocoon. ...This is your last chance to prove your case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial has already run on for far too long. Mr. Justice, this will be my last warning. The moment this "igniter" of yours turns out to be a dud... ...is the moment this cross-examination ends. ...Understood?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, let's have it. Show us the basis for these accusations against Daryan Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK... This is really my last chance! The key that will take apart Daryan Crescend's plan is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is prepared to show the court evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Be my guest!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Be all of our guests, Mr. Justice. Show us evidence supporting your accusations against Daryan Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This is your igniter?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Bwa ha ha ha ha ha ha!!! So, exactly how am I suppose [sic] to react to that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! He's not flustered at all! I picked a dud...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm afraid your poetic tale ended up to be mere fantasy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Reality bites, Mr. Justice. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ow ow ow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose we should let you try once more... Show us the basis for your accusations against Daryan Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Think, Justice! Are you sure about this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your "igniter" isn't a piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Huh? So what is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It is true that I couldn't show decisive evidence. But perhaps what I needed to prove my case was something else.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You mean... a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Proving his guilt is a tall order... ...but I've got just the person to do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well, Mr. Justice. Who is this person who can prove Daryan Crescend's guilt?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This person... is your "igniter"?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hah! Exactly what are they going to testify about!? Go for it! Call 'em to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's... not scared at all, is he? *sigh* Wrong person.</thought> I'm sorry... it was an honest mistake. One more try, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court advises you to be aware that your chances are limited in number. I think you're the one in need of a little igniting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose we should let you try once more... Show us the basis for your accusations against Daryan Crescend!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Think, Justice! Are you sure about this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The one person who can prove Daryan Crescend's guilt... ...is the defendant, Machi Tobaye!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Your client? Again!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi Tobaye was an accomplice to the cocoon smuggling plot. Without him, Daryan Crescend could not have gotten the cocoon. Furthermore, he can easily prove that the one who plotted to smuggle that cocoon... ...is the real criminal in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How so?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would require just one of the very cocoons Mr. LeTouse was looking for. With the cooperation of the Republic of Borginia, we could burn a cocoon. The burnt cocoon would leave a particular residue. A residue we would, no doubt, also find inside the burnt-out guitar!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aha! Very scientific of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thus, if Machi Tobaye acknowledges his agreement with Daryan Crescend... ...concerning the attempted smuggling of a Borginian Cocoon... ...the case is solved!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh... Heh heh heh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, Daryan's laughing again...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Your unrelenting passion is... remarkable. You really want to get me, don't you? ...Too bad you'll never be able to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">The little key-tickler won't acknowledge anything! Especially not anything to do with cocoon smuggling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this all about?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Taking a cocoon out of the country means death... ...by Borginian law.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah! See? If our pianist really was a smuggler... ...then testifying about it would be suicide! ...Believe me, he's not talking--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you're wrong, Detective Crescend.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the other way around! If Machi doesn't admit to smuggling here... He's in deep trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Huh? H-How?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, if Machi admits to smuggling here... ...then he'll be tried in our courts, by our laws. You don't get the death penalty for smuggling in our country.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim in this case was an undercover Interpol agent. I'm sure that news has already reached Borginia.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And they'll likely broadcast our dealings in court today. ...Including the part about the Borginian Cocoon.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah but... but... But...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, if Machi doesn't admit to smuggling now... ...he'll eventually be picked up by the Borginian police. And it's not like he's in any danger in our court. We're not going to find him guilty of murder here, not now!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Yeah, but... you can't do this! You can't... You can't accuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe the "law" doesn't allow it... But who's going to think you're really innocent after hearing this trial? ...The same goes for Machi Tobaye.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The cocoon smuggling, your entire plan... ...Machi Tobaye knows everything. There's only one way out of it for him. And that's to acknowledge his own crime! The crime of cocoon smuggling!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...... ...... Heh. D-Don't worry, there. I'll get... I'll get you out of the country. I'll set you up someplace. A hidden mansion? Real nice. You want a house made out of cookies? Or no, a house made out of pianos? C'mon... ...Please! Don't taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaalk!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Daryan. I consider that my last session with you. ...We rocked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm guessing we can treat that outburst as a confession?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Heh...heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uh oh, he's laughing again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a kind of sick desperation in it now, though.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... have you been listening to today's trial?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you'll talk? You [sic] tell this court everything?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I didn't want it to turn out this way. But... I'm not the kind of lawyer that can overlook a crime.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Today's trial... was all for your benefit, you know? I see no reason why you should hesitate now.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...I knew. From beginning, I knew.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi...</line>
<line speaker="Machi">Situation... I cannot explain. But money. I needed. Very much money.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Today's trial... ...raises a delicate issue with our legal system. "The only thing definite in a court of law... ...is evidence." This is the golden rule. However...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It has become apparent that not all things can be tried by this standard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Should another case of this sort surface... ...we may have to consider an alternate system by which to administer justice. ...Anyway, Mr. Machi Tobaye?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I promise you will receive a fair trial by the laws of our country. And, with regards to the current charges for the murder of Mr. LeTouse... ...this court is prepared to announce a verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...I thank you. I... only lie. But you see truth! You find... truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That's our job. Very well...! This court finds the defendant, Machi Tobaye...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what'll happen to Machi...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he did smuggle a cocoon out of Borginia. I guess there'll be another trial here...</line>
<line speaker="???">All's well that ends well.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I owe you both my thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">My, is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry...! I... Machi was your partner on stage! Your friend...!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Yes. I thought of him as my own son. Even now, I do. Yet... Something got ahold of him, something evil. I see that. And he must pay for what he has done. Is that not how it should be?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm still sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Do not be sorry. You have given me courage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Courage...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am considering an eye operation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was my suggestion, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean, you'll be able to see again?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">It's funny. I have always been afraid of the "light". Light seems so harsh, so unforgiving...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the doctor... ...Lamiroir lost her sight due to some kind of "accident".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An accident...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">As you know, I suffer from amnesia. I feared that, if I could see... ...perhaps it would open my eyes to the truth I have been running from. ...I was scared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know what changed her mind? Hearing your defense in there today. She could feel your gaze, unwavering, always looking straight at the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...If the light returns to my eyes... ...I think I will take up painting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Painting...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! She's the "landscape painter in sound", after all!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I will paint the two of you. I promise.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo hoo! I can't wait, Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I owe you my thanks, too, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, thanks, Mr. Wright, but for what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You reminded me I need to hurry things along. ...On my secret mission, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Your secret mission.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Apollo, Trucy... I hope that we will meet again someday soon.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You bet! Me, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And so, like a ballad, the trial flowed on and on... until it came to the end. Thanks to the trial... ..."The Guitar's Serenade" was a huge hit. Prosecutor Gavin's even more dazzling to look at now. But... there's something I want to say to that guy. Next time you write a ballad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Have them catch the killer at the end!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Machi... you're not telling us the entire truth. I can see it as clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Perhaps... my interpretation is at fault...? Now he says, "I have no idea what you're talking about."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Neither of them looks uncertain at all!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir, it is not your interpretation that is to blame here. It is the lack of anything resembling intelligence in that wide forehead you see.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...... Hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't have to interpret that for him! <thought>Hmm. Looks like I pointed at the wrong spot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you know that the body reveals our thoughts? And yours is telling me you were uncertain just now!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... Ah, should I be interpreting this, or not?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I must admit, I find it hard to interpret that which makes no sense.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, maybe you got it wrong, Apollo? Just a thought...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You might have a point there, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, no need to interpret that after all, Lamiroir...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Oh, I'm sorry, I've already told him.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...... Hee hee.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Great, now even my client's laughing at me. Guess that was the wrong spot after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Machi Tobaye...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>