<xml>
<title>Turnabout Time Traveler</title>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat?! So the whole time traveling thing... ...was just a ruse put on by the guests at the reception?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it. I knew there had to be some kind of trick to it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow. Two wedding receptions! Can you imagine? I wonder how much THAT must've cost them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I have no idea... But if you have to ask, you're not rich enough to want to know... Still, if you've got the money, it's a pretty good way to cover things up, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got that right...! I'm sure I would've been completely fooled.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hi! I'm back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Maya. Are you all set to go?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Ready when you are! So! What should we start with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Let's start with reviewing what we learned at the trial. What Ellen thought was time travel was really just a performance put on by the Sprockets. But other than that, it seems that what Ellen told us was actually all true.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what really matters right now is... ...the identity of the mystery person Ellen said she saw while she was being attacked!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, who IS this mystery person?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the million-dollar question, I'm afraid. But if we want to clear Ellen of any suspicion, then figuring out who they are is key.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think I'll take "Toilets" for $200, instead, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, at least there were only so many people on that airship that night. And we know who the mastermind of the whole cover-up plot was, too, so that's good.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean the groom, Sorin Sprocket, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. He might know something that could help us out.</line>
<line speaker="???">So then, what am I doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I'm a very busy man, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, all of the other people involved are Sorin's family members. So I thought I'd better start by interviewing you. <thought>Even if I probably shouldn't trust a word out of your mouth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, man... I have a really tight schedule, but... aw heck, what are friends for, right? Okay, pal! Go ahead, ask me anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Um, you DO remember it was you who came to me for help in the first place, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to go over exactly WHAT happened WHEN before I step outside this office again. Since you were there, Larry, do you think you could help me get it all straight in my head?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">*sigh* If I gotta...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. So, the first reception was held at 7 PM on the day of the incident. That's the one you tried to crash, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Oh, yeah, that's right. And then they locked me up in a cabin! It was awful, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad we're not here to focus on you, Larry.</thought> And then the incident occurred after this first reception, at around 10 PM. Ellen was attacked in the reception hall by Gloomsbury. He forced her out onto the vista deck and was just about to kill her... </line>
<line speaker="Larry">But Elly fought back, and ended up killing ol' Gloomsbury instead. To cover it up, the family quickly threw together a second reception. That's what Edgey is claiming, anyway. But I know my Elly didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key point here is the mystery person Ellen said she saw strike Gloomsbury... ...just before she passed out. Did you see anybody suspicious skulking around that day?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nope. Not a soul! Because I was locked up in a cabin at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you managed to escape, and sneak back into the reception hall. That's when you switched the lantern in the event hall with the lantern in the hold, right? Did you see anybody then?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nope. The place was completely deserted. I guess 'cause that Pierce butler guy had everybody gathered together somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That makes sense. He must've been going over the cover-up plan with them. <thought>So, clearly, the murder had already happened by the time Larry got out...</thought> They must've gotten everything ready fast, and had the second reception soon after that.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Then, after that second reception, Elly went to clean up the reception hall... ...and, as luck would have it, that's when she found the body in the lantern I'd brought up. I tried to do something nice for Elly out of the goodness of my heart, and THIS happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... We still don't know exactly what happened during the actual murder itself. We'll just have to look into it, along with the identity of that mystery person...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So while the murder was taking place, you were locked up in a cabin. Did you see anything unusual while you were in there?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">In the cabin? Let's see... Well... there was that pterodactyl flying through the sky! That's pretty unusual!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. That drawing of that "pterodactyl" you "saw"...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What's with all the air quotes?! I really did see it! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Larry, the time travel thing never actually happened. Which means you couldn't have seen a real pterodactyl flying through the sky!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">O-Oh... Are you doubting the eye of a super-popular picture book author?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I'm sure you saw something else, and mistook that for a flying reptile.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Niiiiiick! You're making me doubt my own eyes! Now I'm not even sure WHAT I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Either way, you have no idea what actually happened at the real scene of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">That's right! And I can say that with every confidence! Oh, wow. Would ya look at the time? I'd better go. I have a book signing to get to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A book signing? Whose book?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whose do you think?! It's mine, of course! It's a Laurice Deauxnim book signing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet you went around and begged a bunch of bookstores to let you do one. </line>
<line speaker="Larry">O-Of course not! Th-They're the ones coming around to beg ME!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I guessed right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">A-Anyway, I have to go! I'll send you ten copies of my new book that just got released the other day, all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Ten? That's very generous of you...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What are you talking about? I'm gonna send you the bill, too, of course. Just put 'em down as office expenses or something. Well, see ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, Larry! We don't need... ...Argh. He's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll take a copy, Boss! Oh, and make sure it's signed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, boy... <thought>Trucy's not gonna like this "office expense."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There goes our first lead. What do you want to tackle next, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, we should really hit the streets now, huh? How about we go see Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sounds good, Boss! I bet I can cheer her up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought you were going to help Trucy with her magic show again today, Athena? Weren't you supposed to go meet her right about now? Trucy said she was going to practice her new trick on you, if I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"On me"...?! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy's show is an important source of income for our agency, you know. You can leave the case to us, so you go ahead and run along, now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But, Boss...! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Off you go, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooo... I don't wanna dieeeee...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd better get going, too, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why the long face, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe time travel isn't real after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought I'd get to go back in time and see real dinosaurs and ninjas and stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Too bad, huh? <thought>I couldn't be more relieved, personally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I don't know... I mean, shouldn't we just keep investigating stuff or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's really lost that spark... ...ever since I proved that time traveling wasn't real in court today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oooooh... My poor, sweet Sorin...! I wonder how he's getting along without me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oh, Mr. Wright! What's going to happen with the trial, do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, first and foremost... ...we have to hurry up and find this mystery person you saw just before you passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Do you think that person could be the real killer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite possible. And if we can prove that, we can clear you of all charges. Actually, would you happen to know where Sorin is right now?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">He's usually busy with meetings all afternoon, but he should be home by evening.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I'd better go have a chat with him later, then. <thought>Why am I being treated to a view of someone's underwear...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Wright! Don't tell me... ...you suspect my sweet Sorin?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he is the one who masterminded the second reception after the "time skip"... ...so I thought he might be able to tell us something.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">How COULD you, Mr. Wright?! You can't possibly think--! My Sorin would NEVER kill anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right, all right! Just calm down!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">NO, not if you're accusing my Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please! I'm not accusing anybody! So please put the pan and ladle down, all right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C-Cross my heart. So, for now, would you mind if I ask you a few more things about the case? <thought>I'd better be careful not to provoke her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about Sorin?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">There's nothing to tell! He's squeaky clean!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right, okay! <thought>Maybe I should avoid the topic of Sorin right now.</thought> L-Let's talk about something else, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Fine, but you won't hear a peep out of me about Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Talk about pulling teeth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about Pierce Nichody, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Pierce... He came to Sprocket Manor about a year ago. As the family butler, he's now in charge of everything in the household.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only a year ago? Did he have some kind of special connection with the family?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I'm just a maid, so I'm not privy to such things, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It might've been Sorin's order, but Pierce is the one who coordinated the whole thing. He's the one who really orchestrated the grand "time travel" farce. He must have quite a bit of authority in that family...</thought> But, no matter how good he is at his job... ...how could anybody gain that much influence in a single year?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I really don't know... I mean, he IS an excellent butler. Wouldn't that explain it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Is it really as simple as that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What you thought was time travel was really just a cover-up carried out by your in-laws. Pierce said Sorin was the one who ordered the whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I still can't believe it. Even if the second reception was fake... ...Sorin would never use time travel for something like that! He's very serious about his time machine research, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard there's a reason he's researching time machines, actually... ...Something about "something he wishes he could change"... But isn't the whole idea of traveling back in time itself a little... fantastic?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I don't think so! After all, Sorin said real time travelers do exist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really, now? You think he knows someone who actually traveled through time?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">That's right. I haven't seen it personally, but Sorin said as much... ...so I believe it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somebody who actually traveled through time, huh? It's pretty hard to believe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">You're going out to do your investigation now, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Please make sure you don't cause Sorin any trouble, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid... I can't promise you that.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?! Please! Whatever you do! Please don't upset my poor Sorin any further! I'm begging you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'll do my best to not cause him any unnecessary trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Ooh, I couldn't bear it if Sorin ever came under suspicion! I'd rather be found guilty myseeeeeeeelf! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! Ellen, please! Don't work yourself up like this! You don't want Sorin to worry, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">N-No. You're right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the flood waters recede once more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So what do we do now, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Ellen said Sorin is usually in meetings until the evening, so... ...let's save our house call until then. Why don't we go to the mooring dock and figure out our next move from there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Roger, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, where should we start?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Let's see. Are there any places we haven't examined yet? We already investigated the reception hall, and Sprocket Manor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I know! We haven't looked at the vista deck or the hold yet!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, you're right! We've still got some pretty important places left to examine, don't we! The vista deck is the actual scene of the murder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the lantern with the body in it was stored in the hold. I think there's a good chance we'll find some important clues in those locations.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do we know how to get to the hold?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good question. I think it was labeled in that diagram of the airship in this pamphlet. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">There it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what are we waiting for? Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that one little tower is all that's keeping the airship from being blown away?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently. It must be sturdier than it looks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know what it reminds me of? A single mom raising three kids while holding down a full-time job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sure... <thought>Where did that analogy even come from...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A strong wind blew this bench straight through the air, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like they fixed the sign, but left the bench right where it landed. I wonder why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe the repair guy just hasn't gotten around to it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the hold... <thought>This is where Pierce orchestrated the whole cover-up operation... We'd better go over this place with a fine-tooth comb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick...? Weren't we supposed to need a key card to get in here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, you're right. I wonder why it was unlocked?</line>
<line speaker="???">How's it going, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just a little independent investigating, for my own sake. Gotta keep the mind sharp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, so the door's security system was turned off for the police investigation.</thought> We'd like to investigate the hold ourselves. Would that be all right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, sure. The police just finished their examination anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. We'll just take a quick look around, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, right! You should know that the floor doubles as a huge lift. You can use that lever way back there to raise it up to the vista deck. The police inspected it already, but didn't find anything of particular interest, it seems. If you do go up to the vista deck with the lift, be careful not to fall off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That goes double for you, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, let's get this show on the road.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the airship's engine. It's pretty impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And it's all rhythmic, like a heartbeat! It's the literal heart of the Flying Chapel! Look at all those huge gears spinning around and around and around and around and... Ulp! I think I'm starting to get dizzy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Me, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These must be the dishes and glasses they use for receptions. Very fancy. I bet we'd be in big trouble if we broke any of them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! I wanna see, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You, young lady, need to stay far, far away from them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You think I'm going to break them, don't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just say your rap sheet for breaking things doesn't help your case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These are the flowers we saw in Larry's photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The petals make them look like little gears. The perfect flower for the Sprocket family, huh? Maybe they were going to shower the couple with the petals?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean, kind of like how people throw rice or confetti?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, like that. Only, these were found at the scene of a murder instead...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, look, Nick! It's an airplane!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if Sorin built that one, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, why don't we take it for a spin? Just a quick tour around the neighborhood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And who do you propose is going to pilot that wooden deathtrap?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me, of course! Who else? Don't worry. I've seen people fly airplanes on TV plenty of times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I think I'll pass. <thought>I've still got my whole life ahead of me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that? A wedding bell?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">According to the pamphlet... ...it's used on the vista deck during wedding ceremonies to bless the newlyweds.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess they disassemble and store it away here in the hold when it's not being used.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, it's a cake, Nick! A cake! It's so big, they wouldn't miss one little piece, would they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you're that in the mood for a mouthful of styrofoam, knock yourself out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean it's not real...? Well, it sure fooled me... I was so ready to have some that I'm really craving cake now... Come on, Nick! Let's go get some!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe after the trial is over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So there are two male Pegabull lanterns in the reception hall. That must mean... ...that these two are female Pegacow lanterns.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry got their sexes mixed up when he replaced the one in the reception hall, huh? Didn't he see the horns? The difference is pretty glaring, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And yet he managed not to notice. That's what makes Larry Larry. <thought>And Larry being Larry is why I've seen more than my fair share of trouble for a lifetime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, Mr. Wright...? You know that lantern the victim was found inside of in the reception hall...? I'm just about to go piece it back together so the police can examine it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Okay. We'll stop by for a look, too, once you're done fixing it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, look. There's the lever to the lift Ema told us about.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's try going up on it! I'll go flip the switch. Here goes nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! I'm not even on it yet! H-Hey, Maya! Stop the lift!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoops, sorry! I got a little carried away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind that. Move over a little!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that... blood?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-Blood? Let me see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could it be Mr. Gloomsbury's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, this lift goes up to the vista deck where the murder took place, so... ...I think that's the most logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I thought the victim was clubbed to death and that there wasn't much blood...? Something tells me I'd better take a picture of this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should ask Ema about it some more later.</thought> Maya, can you bring the lift back down now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got it! I'll go flip the switch again! There! Done!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to find out some more about that bloodstain... But, for now, I guess we should go up to the vista deck... ...and take a look around the actual crime scene for ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The view must be great from up there! I bet it'll be awesome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You mean, it would be, if it wasn't the scene of a murder...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay! To the vista deck we go! Make sure you actually get ON the lift this time, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, I'll just flip the switch again, and... awaaaay we go! Wow! Look at the gorgeous view!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is where Ellen was attacked, and Mr. Gloomsbury was killed... Yeesh. One wrong step, and it's "kersplat!" on the ground below.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Should we go investigate the stuff that's a little closer to the edge?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't see much of anything over there. The police investigation didn't turn up any clues either, so... Maybe we don't need to?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I get it! You're SCARED, aren't you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course not! C'mon, let's go back down and finish checking out the hold!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the lever for the lift... What should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's go up to the vista deck again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okey-dokey! Aaaand up we go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Well, I guess there really isn't anything to see up here... Let's go back down to the hold.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we just got here! Let's enjoy the view a little more!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Time's a-wasting! L-Let's go, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, could you operate the lift for me? I want to see that bloodstain again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got it! I just have to stop it partway up, right? So, first I'll throw the switch... there! Then, I'll press stop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... That's quite a bit of blood, all right. It's dry, but it doesn't look all that old.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think it's from the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think so, but I'd need more info to be sure. Could you bring the lift back down now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aye-aye, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd better just leave it alone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awwwww! I wanted to throw the switch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe later...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? It looks like there are some fingerprints on this candelabra.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah. I just got done dusting that. I was able to pull a set of left hand prints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know whose prints they are?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. The prints belong to the victim, Dumas Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I just figured out something amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Get this -- if the fingerprints on the candelabra were from his left hand... ...then Mister Doom-n'-Gloom must've been... left-handed! What do you think of that? Do I have the makings of a great detective, or what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yes. Your deductive reasoning skills are nearly Encyclopedic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, you're pretty good, Maya! I looked into it myself, and sure enough, the victim really was left-handed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? I got it right? Awesome!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, good for you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Good for you"? That's all you've got to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh, think you did a real great job, Maya. Way to go! <thought>I guess one can never have too much info...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now you're talking! Heh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, come to think of it... ...this candelabra isn't in the photo Larry took of the hold, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That picture was taken when they were getting ready for the first reception, right? The candelabra must've been brought in here sometime after that, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... It's still possible it has something to do with the incident, though. I'd better add it to the evidence file, just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, by the way, Mr. Wright... You can have this fingerprint powder, if you like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're giving this to us?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure. I have four other sets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks... <thought>I feel like there's something more to the candelabra, but I can't put my finger on it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder where they sell candelabras like these...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, are you looking to buy some?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was thinking they'd be perfect for the altar candles in the Channeling Chamber at home. It might class up the place a little!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno... I can't really see them fitting in with the vibe of Kurain Village...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any progress with your investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Nothing conclusive yet, I'm afraid. Almost everybody was involved with the cover-up... ...so it's hard to know who or what to believe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Unless you have some compelling evidence, I'm afraid it's going to be a tough trial for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're telling me... There isn't much time left, so I've just got to make do and see what I can turn up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, can we check out this candelabra a little more?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A little more? What do you -- Oops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I almost dropped the candelabra, and the candles slipped off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, let's be careful with that. It might be important evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait a minute... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">One of the pins that hold the candles is broken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's definitely something fishy about this candelabra!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is? What makes you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Call it forensic investigator's intuition! We already dusted this for prints earlier... ...so let's test it with luminol this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Knowing Ema, she'd use every test she has at the same time if she could...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just hang on. This will only take a second.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope this turns up a new lead somehow...</thought> Well, Ema? Did you find anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Take a look at this, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is all that blood doing on there?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe somebody got hurt while they were setting up for the reception? These pins are pretty sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But if one of the pins is broken... ...it means there was some force involved. Do you think maybe somebody got stabbed?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">B-But nobody reported anything like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's quite a bit of blood. I wonder whose it is... If I have anything that might shed some light on that, I should probably show it to Ema...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, about this bloodstain...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm thinking it's probably the victim's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the victim was clubbed to death, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, but he could've been bleeding from his nose, or maybe he spat it out. I won't really know for sure until I look into it some more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. <thought>There's still something about it that bothers me, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About this bloodstain...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something about it that's been bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, yeah? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's a huge bloodstain on the crime scene lift, and a bloodstained candelabra... Now, this is only a guess, but I'm thinking maybe these two bloodstains are from...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm thinking maybe these two bloodstains are from completely different sources.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, that's what I'm thinking, too. So, what about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, hmm... Being in agreement won't lead us anywhere new... I need to find out more about these bloodstains somehow...</thought> Sorry! That's not what I meant to say... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm thinking maybe these two bloodstains are from the same source.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... I guess that IS a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we compare the two bloodstains? Would that take a lot of time?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are you kidding? Don't underestimate the power of science! It'll be done in a jiffy! And the results are in! That didn't take long, now, did it? Hmm... It seems that the blood from the lift and candelabra are from the same person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the victim was clubbed to death, and there wasn't all that much blood...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But if this isn't Mr. Gloomsbury's blood...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, this is just a guess, but... ...what if Mr. Gloomsbury stabbed somebody with the candelabra pin? That would explain both the huge bloodstain on the lift and the blood on the candelabra.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, my goodness! If that's true... ...then that means there was somebody else present at the scene of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It does, doesn't it? <thought>This just might substantiate Ellen's statement about a third person!</thought> Ema, could you have this blood analyzed?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema, about this bloodstain... Doesn't something about it strike you as odd?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's so odd about the victim's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not exactly... There's just something about it that bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... Now that you mention it... ...I can't say I necessarily disagree with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should talk about this some more with her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... A mysterious bloodstain on a candelabra with the victim's prints on it... This just might back up Ellen's memory of seeing a third person. Next up, the reception hall. It might be worth taking another look around in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The reception hall? The forensics team is in there investigating right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, they are?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we don't have time to just sit around, so let's go check out something else!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. We could go question some people. <thought>Especially Sorin. I have quite a few questions for that guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds good, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Off to do some legwork, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. I thought we'd head to Sorin's house for starters.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He was accompanying the police on their investigation here earlier, but... ...he's probably home by now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Great, thanks. Later, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I still can't get over how gorgeous Sprocket Manor is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just don't touch anything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I--! I wasn't going to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was DEFINITELY going to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I was told I had guests...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for seeing us, Sorin. We know you're busy. We'd like to ask you a few questions about the case, if you wouldn't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Sorin?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">You're Ellen's lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Y-Yes, that's right. <thought>Don't tell me he doesn't remember me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Will Ellen be found guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're doing everything we can to prevent that. That's why we're here, investigating. Will you please tell us what you know?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin...?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">.........All right. Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What was that pause all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Man">Aha! Come back to hear more about my camera, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, but I'm afraid I'm really busy right now.</line>
<line speaker="Man">Oh. What a shame. Well, if you ever want to talk about cameras, come back and see me anytime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like even his own family members don't want to listen to him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Better watch out, or you'll be cursed by the bouquet of woe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, come on, Maya. Like I'm going to believe an urban legend you just made up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was you who gave the order for that large-scale cover-up plan, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">What "large-scale cover-up"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't play dumb with us! You held two wedding receptions in order to try and cover up Mr. Gloomsbury's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen thought that, through the power of the Time Keeper you built... ...she traveled back in time.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Ah... So that's why there were two receptions...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, does he seriously not know why the reception was held twice? Looks like I'll have to delve deeper here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, the cover-up scheme -- that fake trip through time... ...you're not the one who was behind it all? Pierce Nichody stated in court that you were the one who ordered it to be carried out.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Pierce said that...? I see. I leave him in charge of everything around me. So whatever he decides is, in essence, my decision, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I take it that you didn't know anything about the cover-up? </line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......That's none of your business.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you were in two wedding receptions in a row! And still, you claim to know nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">... I have nothing more to say to you. Please leave.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But, Sorin...! Ow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, there's something written on this paper airplane! Let's see... "Go away!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't get clearer than that, huh... <thought>He's looking especially uncooperative, but... ...maybe I can grab his attention somehow. There's still that one piece of evidence I don't know much about... It's worth a try...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Sis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure your sister would want the truth of this case to be known.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...How rude. Is intruding on the private lives of others... ...a part of your job as a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I, uh... I apologize. <thought>I guess showing him the picture of his sister wasn't such a good idea after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin, have you ever seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Th-That's... That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">N-Nothing...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did his whole demeanor change all of a sudden? He's gone pale as a ghost, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look at his stomach! He's bleeding!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Somebody, help! Sorin's collapsed!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Master Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Relative">Get him to the hospital! Quickly, now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Sorin... That must be one serious wound...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, when I showed him the candelabra, his whole demeanor changed... So I was just thinking that maybe his injury is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's Sorin's notebook. He must've dropped it in the rush to get him to the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, his notebook, huh...? I wonder what's written in it. Don't you? Come on! You know you wanna take a peek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's notebook... What to do, what to do...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really don't think we should...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But it might have some really, really, REALLY important information in it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's quite possible, but still... <thought>Well, I guess it IS for Ellen's sake, at the end of the day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I feel guilty, snooping around in somebody's personal notebook, but... ...maybe we SHOULD take a little look-see. Whoa! It's filled with big words written in tiny letters! I guess he uses this notebook to write down his invention ideas? ...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it? Did you find something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... After March 8th of last year, the content of this notebook changes dramatically.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like how?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... Ever since that date, Sorin's been writing down every detail of his life. As in EVERY.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he decided to start keeping a diary?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this is way too detailed to be an ordinary diary.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Either he's really compulsive... ...or maybe just plain forgetful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But is it really as simple as that...?</thought> I feel like something happened on March 8th that made Sorin change.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, why don't you let me take a look at that, and I'll tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Maya! Let go or we'll rip it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eep! Now look what you did! You dropped it! You should've just let me take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How is this MY fault...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, no! Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! It fell into that pool of Sorin's blood! I can't read a thing on these two pages now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-oh! You're gonna get it now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I guess it really is my fault after all...</thought> Let's just put it away carefully for now. We can't let anything else happen to it, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Hey look, there's something sticking out of the notebook. It looks like a newspaper article.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... It's about the car accident Sorin's sister died in! It happened on... March 8th... That's the day Sorin's notebook completely changed... Oh, wow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What else does it say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says the driver at the time of the accident was... Dumas Gloomsbury. It says Sorin was in the car, too, and that he had sustained severe injuries. It's just like Pierce said. Sorin completely changed after the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Gloomsbury was driving the car when they got into that accident... That opens up the distinct possibility... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of Sorin holding a grudge against Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You think Sorin could've...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. It's not like I have any proof... We should talk to Pierce about this when we return Sorin's notebook to him. ...Though he doesn't seem to be here right now. Maybe he's at the Flying Chapel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To think they fought for their lives here, on what was supposed to be an uplifting day...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You do realize this a murder case, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? D-Did I say something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What pun? All I said was that it was supposed to be an uplifting day... Oh. Th-That wasn't supposed to be a pun!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I strongly suggest you don't say anything like that in front of the Sprocket family!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, ma'am...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's quite a fancy candelabra, huh? Maybe I should get a few just like it for the altar in the Channeling Chamber at home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't really see these things going well with the vibe of Kurain Village...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But they're perfect! They can even hold the really big candles! And they look so cool, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's going to be one eclectic altar once Maya's done redecorating...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, it's the notebook you dropped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The notebook "I" dropped?! It only ended up where it did because you tried to snatch it out of my hands!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... maybe I was a TINY bit complicit in it... Look! No one's to blame here, right? It was just an accident! Right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I think we both know who's more to blame...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is about the car accident Sorin's sister died in... I bet she would've wanted to see her little brother get married...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... But with the way things are, I don't think she'll be able to rest in peace. So we'll just have to figure out the truth somehow... For her sake, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Let's not leave a single stone unturned and push on in our investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I sure hope Pierce is around here somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, Mr. Wright and Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, Pierce. We were just looking for you.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I'm sorry for Master Sorin's sudden departure earlier. You have my sincerest apologies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was totally understandable, really. But shouldn't you be at his side right now?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It's fine. The other servants are with him, and I am in constant contact with them. Do not forget to give him his pain medication, and be sure to keep him hydrated. Also, see to it that he is not up and about. He needs complete bed rest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this what happens when you're too rich for normal, peasant phones...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I must return to Master Sorin now, but... ...did you want something of me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, here's Sorin's notebook. He dropped it when he collapsed. <thought>I hope Pierce doesn't notice the bloodstain!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh. Thank you very much for this. I will see to it personally that Master Sorin gets it back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I trust you did not look inside?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, of course not! Aha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Because it is filled with numerous patent-worthy ideas, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, I know you're busy, but would you mind if I asked you a few questions about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Well, as I said, I must be getting back to Master Sorin. So if you could make it quick, I would greatly appreciate it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. I'll make this as quick as I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like to ask you about the cover-up you tried to pull off, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I told everything there is to tell in court already. Disposing of anything that may harm the Sprocket family's reputation... ...is simply a part of my job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like a lovely job description...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I have nothing more to say on the matter. I will say, I do not think it's wise to spend time on topics that have already been discussed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce, could you tell us more about this accident?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Where did you find that...? And did I not already tell you about that accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did, but you conveniently left out one crucial detail: The fact that Dumas Gloomsbury was driving the car at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh? Did I not mention that? I suppose it simply did not come up then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Mr. Gloomsbury caused the accident... ...why didn't the Sprocket family fire him? Wouldn't that usually be the natural consequence of such a huge mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Please do not misunderstand. Gloomsbury stayed on with the family... ...on Master Sorin's request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">That is the type of person Master Sorin is. Perhaps it was the influence of Miss Selena's kind nature. She was such a sweet person that even in her last moments, she thought of Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not only did Sorin NOT hold a grudge against Gloomsbury, he insisted on keeping him on. Now I REALLY don't understand how that guy's mind works...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were present for Selena Sprocket's last moments...?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes, in my professional capacity... The accident happened on the way to a certain party.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what kind of a party was it?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It was Miss Selena's engagement party. Gloomsbury's injuries were minor, but Miss Selena's and Master Sorin's were critical. They were brought to the Sprocket family's regular hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... To have such a terrible thing happen on what was to be a day of celebration...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Thanks to the surgeon in charge, Master Sorin pulled through. But Miss Selena... She...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">The last words Miss Selena said to me were...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Ever since then, I have attended Master Sorin and tried to help him in any way I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Selena's fianc must have been devastated.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Indeed. The shock of losing Miss Selena was so great, he quit being a surgeon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was a surgeon? Wait... So the surgeon who tried to save them both, was he...?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes, he was Miss Selena's fianc.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a terrible tragedy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How awful... So where is her fianc now?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Good question. I wonder that sometimes myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Selena had a fianc... I'd like to find out more about him, but I doubt I'll find him any time soon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I hope you will refrain from showing this to Master Sorin. He is still suffering the loss of Miss Selena. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I do not believe rubbing salt in people's wounds is part of a lawyer's job. Or am I mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you recognize this, Pierce?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...It is not really something I care to look at.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it was you and the others who tried to cover things up in the hold, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I left that entirely to my subordinates, so I really don't know anything about it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pierce was in charge of handling the guests and relatives... ...so he must know a lot more than he's letting on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Even now, it is painful to remember the accident. And Master Sorin is not the only one who suffers still. The entire Sprocket family was plunged into deep sorrow. A sorrow they still feel to this day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I can understand why Sorin changed so much after the accident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">That is why I do not want you to bring up the car accident again. I hope you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I understand. <thought>So I guess that topic is out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">So, are we done here? I'm afraid I must be going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you please just tell me... ...a little more about Sorin?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">There is nothing more to tell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't seem to get any real answers out of him just by asking him questions. But there IS that piece of evidence I still don't know much about... Maybe he'll be able to tell me something about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce. Have you ever seen this candelabra before?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I-I... No, I don't know anything about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My magatama reacted! Pierce must be trying to hide something from me. I have to break those Psyche-Locks and find out what!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce. You're hiding something from me about this candelabra, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It is one of the candelabras from the Flying Chapel, is it not? Is there something special about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My magatama is definitely reacting. I guess I'll just have to break those Psyche-Locks and find out what he's got to hide!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">-- Pierce's Secret --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce. You're hiding something from me about this candelabra, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It is one of the candelabras from the Flying Chapel, is it not? Is there something special about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, yes -- there's some blood on it, you see. I think the blood might belong to this person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nichody:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ack! That's not who I meant to name!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I do not have time for meaningless conversation...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry! Please give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin has a rather nasty wound on his body, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes, Master Sorin is indeed injured.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are any of the other people involved with this case injured?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">N-Not as far as I know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I see. Then, let me ask you this, Pierce. Do you suppose Sorin could have been more directly involved than you're letting on?</line>
<line speaker="NIchody">Wh-What in the world would make you think that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I've got my reasons. Mr. Gloomsbury's fingerprints were found on this candelabra's stem. Which leads me to believe that Mr. Gloomsbury stabbed Sorin with it.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You cannot possibly think Master Sorin is the one responsible for the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't have any conclusive evidence of that at the moment... ...but I do think he had a motive. This proves that Sorin had a motive to kill Mr. Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nichody:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Wrong piece, I guess!</thought> Never mind that. I didn't mean it!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">My time is limited, Mr. Wright, so please do hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even though it was an accident... ...Mr. Gloomsbury was the man responsible for taking Sorin's sister away.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Let us suppose... that Gloomsbury did stab Master Sorin with the candelabra... Can you prove that it had anything to do with this case? He might have been stabbed at some other location, for some other reason...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I can prove it WAS related to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's stabbing and Mr. Gloomsbury's death are definitely connected.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Are they now...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the piece of evidence that ties Sorin's injury to Mr. Gloomsbury's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nichody:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! Guess that wasn't it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I'll have a servant send you home...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, wait! Please give me another chance.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Please, Mr. Wright. Do not detain me with nonsense any longer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bloodstain was found on the side of the lift that goes between the hold and vista deck. Its blood matches the blood that's on the candelabra. I obtained the results straight from the police, so I can assure you this information is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This bloodstain on the lift indicates an important fact. It shows us that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true scene of the murder was in the reception hall.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ ............ ............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, so I kinda just said the first thing that popped into my mind... ...but now that I think about it, I take it back.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Twenty-six seconds, Mr. Wright. It took you twenty-six seconds to realize your mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, just please forget about that one!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Gloomsbury wasn't at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">How does the bloodstain on the lift tell you that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, er... I guess it really doesn't, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">If you insist on speaking nonsense, I will have to ask you to let me leave.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No more nonsense this time! I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's blood is on the lift, which can only mean one thing. He was there, wasn't he? Sorin was at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You are very astute, Mr. Wright. It appears I cannot hide this from you any longer. Very well. I will tell you everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about Sorin's injury?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Very well. This is what I heard directly from Master Sorin himself. As you surmised, Master Sorin was stabbed by Gloomsbury on the day of the murder. It happened after the first wedding reception. The happy couple was in the reception hall when, suddenly, Gloomsbury appeared... He attacked Miss Ellen and tried to take her away. Master Sorin went to stop him, and found himself in a struggle with Gloomsbury. That is when Master Sorin was stabbed with the candelabra, he said. Even though Master Sorin was badly injured, he went after Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Sorin really was at the scene of the murder, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes, that is correct. However, by the time Master Sorin arrived at the scene... ...Gloomsbury had already been murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Pierce is saying that Sorin WAS at the crime scene... ...but that he didn't have anything to do with the murder itself. Hmm...</thought> Even still, why did you try to keep such an important piece of information from me?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I am very sorry. Master Sorin's injury and Gloomsbury's murder were not directly related... ...so I decided not to mention it, so as not to unnecessarily complicate the investigation. ...Now, then. I am sorry, but I am afraid I really must go now. Please excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for your time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pierce should've just told us everything in the first place and saved us all a lot of time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... But I guess it isn't that simple for him -- he is the family butler, after all. He sure didn't make our job any easier, though, did he? But at least we learned something new. Sorin was at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's true! One step forward is better than none! So, what next, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Let's see. The forensics team might be done investigating the reception hall by now. Let's go check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like a plan!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it just me, or does Sorin seem kinda suspicious...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... I mean, he's so quiet, who knows what he's thinking, right? And that Pierce isn't exactly an open book, either. It seems like they're both hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, though that could be true of everyone involved in this case, for all we know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, I know! Let's make a new rule! The next time anybody lies in court, we get to bop them on the head with the judge's gavel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds more like a game of Whack-A-Mole than a trial to me... Still, I wouldn't necessarily say no...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I was just thinking about how hard it's been to find out the truth this time around...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about? When has it EVER been easy to find out the truth in any of our cases? You just do what you always do! Bluff your way through things, and we'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But that's supposed to be my tactic of last resort...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like the police are done with their investigation in here. I wonder if it's okay for us to take a look around now.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, hi, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hi, Ema. Would it be all right if we investigate in this room now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure. The police are all done, so go for it. Oh, remember that broken lantern? I restored it to perfection! I have to say, it's some of my best work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like the repair job was a resounding success...</thought> Thanks, Ema. We'll take a good look at it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I have to be getting back to the station... Try not to mess up the crime scene if you can help it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll be seeing you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bye, Ema! And thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, shall we get started?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, take a look at that door. I wonder where it goes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Shall we open it up and see?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Wait! Please don't open that! It's the emergency escape hatch! It leads directly outside! You'll fall to your death!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew... That was a close one, huh, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'll say...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Excuse me. Is the fog machine ready to use now?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">No, I'm afraid not. We only put dry ice in it when there's an actual reception.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She still wants to blast me with a cloud of smoke, doesn't she...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... N-Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong, Maya?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......This hasn't moved an inch since the last time we looked at it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It would be pretty creepy if it had...</thought> Look, we're in the middle of an important investigation, so try not to shout, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was just hoping it had changed somehow. You know, so it would be more interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The last thing we need is for things to get more "interesting."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's another beautiful day outside, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. If only it wasn't the scene of a murder, we could really enjoy it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">True...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must be tough for the maids to have to work on a beautiful day like today.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh, we don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! I didn't think you could hear me way over here!</line>
<line speaker="Maid">We don't think of it as simply cleaning. It's more like we're wiping away all of the sadness stuck to this airship...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. Talk about devoted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I think that tablecloth is new. They must've changed it since yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because the food stains that were there are now gone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've known it's because it's food-related...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where the murder weapon, the Time Keeper, was displayed. I guess it's in police custody now. ...Huh? What's this? A key?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's ask the maid about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. She might be able to tell us something. Excuse me. Could I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh, of course. What would you like to know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this key?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">It's the key that starts up the Time Keeper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A startup key?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">That's right. Oh, the First Startup of Love ceremony was so beautiful! The bride and groom each had a symbol of their love, and when they put them together... Oh, how romantic it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First Startup of Love ceremony? What exactly did that entail?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Oh, er... It's a ceremony in which the couple activated the Time Keeper together for the first time. I suppose it was kind of like a cake-cutting ceremony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what are these "symbols of their love" you mentioned?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">Well... that's kind of an industry secret, so I can't really say. I'm sorry. I'd better be getting back to my work...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like there's an order from above not to talk about it.</thought> I guess we've checked out everything of interest in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's the broken lantern, all patched up. <thought>And I do mean "patched"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ema said this was some of her best work, so I know she put a lot of effort into it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was pretty smashed up. It must've been a lot of work to piece it back together. <thought>Well, she gets an A for effort, at any rate...</thought> ... Huh? This wheel handle on the back has some blood on it! It looks like somebody gripped it with a bloody hand...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe the blood got there when the killer was putting ol' Doom-n'-Gloom's body inside? Do you see anything else worth noting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's another one of these lanterns over there... ...so it might be a good idea to really compare the two later.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ema must've worked really hard on this.</line>
<line speaker="Maid">You mean that police lady? She was going at it like a jigsaw puzzle. All "Not this piece" here, "Not that piece" there...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was pretty busted up. I can just imagine what a hard time she had figuring it all out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She should've asked me to help! I would've loved to restore this thing with her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's best to leave that kind of thing to the police. <thought>Besides, who knows what kind of liberties Maya would've taken in the process...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the unbroken Pegabull lantern. And this is the one that Ema restored. I wouldn't say they look exactly the same... More that they're made up of the same parts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think there's something off about this Pegabull.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just about everything about it looks off to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not quite sure what it is, but some detail isn't quite right. Show me the restored lantern again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I know! It's this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The thing about the restored lantern that's off is the...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The shape of the horns is different, isn't it? How they're curved, and their size, and stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know... The curve and size seem the same as the unbroken one to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess you're right. They're pretty much identical, huh. In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got it! The angle of that wing is different. And it's attached all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well duh, Nick! I could've told you THAT! I mean there's something more subtle... Something that feels just slightly off. You know what I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, not really... Still, maybe it's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look. It's the wheel handle. It's a different color altogether. Ema got the inside and outside wheel handles switched around.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, wow! You're right! And there's blood here on this handle -- as if somebody gripped it with a bloody hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Which means that the blood got on the handle from inside the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think the blood got there when the killer was putting the body in the lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... It's really hard to say, at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know... I really wonder about that Pierce...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know what you mean. He seems to have a lot of power over everybody and everything, doesn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, what I was really wondering about is that shoulder mech of his... I mean, it's pretty amazing how many things that tiny little contraption can do. Ooh! What if that  mech is actually Pierce's true control center, like his brain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And what if, somewhere in Sprocket Manor, he has another shiny, golden body! And then, during emergencies, he can switch bodies and become Super Pierce Nichody!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is what I get for trying to have a serious conversation with a super geek...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet all Ellen wants is to start her happy new life with Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... I bet you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But do you think the truth will really set her free...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All you can do is do your job to the best of your ability! And if we can bring Ellen joy that way, all the better, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Either way, I think true happiness can only be found in the truth. ... Um, what are you looking at me like that for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just thinking about how wise that sounded. Looks like our little Maya is growing up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Would you knock it off? I'm trying to be serious here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ema did a pretty good job fixing this guy up. Is it just me, or does this Pegabull look happy to be whole again? Still...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If Ema had let me do it, I could've made it ten times cooler! I would've made the wings bigger, given it three horns, and painted it all red. But that's not all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would've ceased to be a Pegabull waaay before that point, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew! Well, I think we've checked out everything relevant to this case.</line>
<line speaker="???">What are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, what are YOU doing here?! Sorin! Shouldn't you be resting in bed? You're injured!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">How do you know about that?! ...Um, never mind. My notebook... Have you seen my notebook? I can't find it anywhere. My notebook... I need my notebook...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's the matter with him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">M-My notebook... I need... I have to have... I-I...</line>
<line speaker="???">Master Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin! I told you to stay in bed!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">M-My notebook...!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Yes... This is it...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Sorin gets emotionally unstable without that notebook of his...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Phew.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like he's calmed down now.</thought> Sorin, do you mind if I talk to you for a minute?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I cannot allow you to do that. What if his wound were to open up again? He needs to rest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh... I guess you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Now, if you will excuse us. Master Sorin, let us retire.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">... All right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There they go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce is right. I guess he really isn't in any condition to be questioned. Well, let's go back to the agency and sort through what we've learned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Larry... I thought you had a book signing?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, but I snuck off early. I was worried about how your investigation was going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nobody came to get their book signed, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What kind of a thing is that to say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, how many people showed up, then?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, um... Fine! It was four people, if you gotta know! Including the employees...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... I shouldn't have asked...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Quit looking at me like I'm some pitiful piglet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, why don't you get back to your signing? Another two or three people could show up before the store closes...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">They already put away the book signing table and cleaned everything up! I... I don't have anywhere else to go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gee, Larry... I'm sorry I gave you such a hard time.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I told you to quit looking at me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, have you been to see Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nah. Edgey told me to stay away. He said things always get complicated whenever I'm around. Can you believe the guy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, I'd tell Larry the exact same thing if I were Edgeworth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">So... How's the investigation coming along?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've made some progress, but I don't feel like we've gotten to the heart of things yet.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Come on, Nick! You gotta do better than that! Me and Elly's whole future is riding on you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't think I can take on the heavy responsibility of your future, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whaaat? First, Edgey, and now YOU, Nick? Why does everybody gotta be so mean to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C'mon, Larry! I really don't have time to be standing around shooting the breeze! Why don't you just get back to your book signing, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">W-Will you come with me, ol' buddy...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a chance!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Ooooooooh...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Enough is enough already, Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're back. Anybody here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, hi, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena? I thought you were with Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... I guess you could say that I'm... I-I'm taking a short break! B-But enough about me! What about the investigation! Did you find out anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, turns out that the third person Ellen says she saw at the crime scene... ...might have been Sorin Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Really? I always thought he seemed suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thing is, by the time Sorin got to the vista deck... ...the murder had already occurred, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! I don't buy that! Not for a second! It's a cover-up! A cover-up, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... certainly a possibility. And, as a lawyer, it's certainly a possibility I have to pursue, but...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But what? It's your job, right? So pursue the heck out of it! Just do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but... ...is that really what's best for Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorin could be found guilty if the truth comes out tomorrow... But if we don't pursue this possibility, Ellen could be found guilty instead...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, man... Either way, it sure doesn't spell out "happily ever after" for the two of them... So what are you gonna do, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't let an innocent person get convicted. So I guess all I can really do... is pursue the truth. Even if it ends up devastating Ellen...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What a tough call to make...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-Still, there's always a chance, right? Maybe something will come up during the trial that will save their marriage!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hope so. I really do... ......Well, Maya, let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Break the news to Ellen, you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Please take me with you! I bet I could help you counsel Ellen through this piece of bad news!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena... I appreciate the offer, but don't you have somewhere else to be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Do I?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Athena! What are you doing here?! I've been looking all over for you! Come on, now! Let's get back to practicing!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No... Wait...! My body can't take it anymore! B-Boss, you gotta help me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lawyer always keeps their promises, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But, Boooooss...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If you bail on me one more time, Athena, I'm going to use a real blade on you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry, Athena, but somebody's gotta do it... Better you than me, though... Hang in there, kiddo!</thought> Come on, Maya. We'd better get going.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello, Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">How did your investigation go, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before I answer that, I need to ask you something. Was Sorin with you when Mr. Gloomsbury attacked you in the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I, uh...... I'm sorry I kept it from you. I was afraid that he'd come under suspicion if I told you. So I kept quiet about it. I'm really sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I see. I thought it was probably something like that. Listen, Ellen... I'm afraid I had to make a very difficult decision based on what I found out...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">...What kind of decision?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is... very hard for me to say, but... The mysterious person you saw at the scene of the crime... was most likely Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, in court tomorrow... ...I'm afraid I'll have to propose the possibility that Sorin is the true culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No... Sorin is innocent... Nooo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But don't you see? If I don't try to pursue that line of thought, you'll be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No... Nooooo... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, Ellen! Calm down!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Sorin just can't be found guilty! I'd much rather I be found guilty instead!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ellen! You can't let yourself think like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">But..! But...! But...! Nooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Marriage is for life, right? Do you really think you can run away from the truth and still be truly happy with him?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! You're not married, so how can you possibly understand?! Sometimes you've just got to do whatever it takes to make things wooooork!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But...! N-Nick, you talk to her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hey! Don't just dump this all on me!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Wright! I'm innocent, and Sorin is, too! So, please...! Prove our innocence in coooourt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'll certainly do everything in my power... <thought>I just hope she doesn't lose control like this in court tomorrow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'd better take a step back and gather my thoughts a little more...</thought></line>
</xml>