<xml>
<title>Turnabout Succession</title>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo! Look, on TV! Look! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... uh, I'm kinda busy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa! Look at that! He's the last Gramarye, alright! Amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, you should be watching this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ow ow ow! What? What!? ...I was writing about our last case in my journal.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lawyers are supposed to write things in "records", Apollo, not journals. And why now? That case was three months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, it's a long story. ...I did a lot, you know. I want to vacuum pack the feel of the moment for later. Right now I'm wowing the crowd by figuring out how Lamiroir disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Uncle Valant did that illusion, too! But you're missing him on TV right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh*... I was just getting to the good part. <thought>I suppose I should watch a little TV with her. After all, her father's expecting me to look after her while he's away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Announcer">What you're now seeing is a rehearsal for the greatest magic show on Earth... ...happening right here at our very own Sunshine Coliseum!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Sunshine Coliseum? Hey, that's where the Gavinners concert was!</line>
<line speaker="Announcer">...Only three more days until miracles happen here, right before your unbelieving eyes! The legendary Troupe Gramarye is performing for the first time in seven years!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's going to be great! I'm so there! You and Daddy are coming, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The legendary Gramaryes... ...If Trucy's real father were still alive... ...he'd be on that stage performing miracles.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've got the tickets and everything! Here's yours, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, you are here. Working hard or hardly working? Hey! How have you been?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hi there, stranger!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not exactly the kind of greeting I'd want to hear from my own kid. Though he has been gone a long time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha, how goes it, Trucy? Here, I got a present for you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yay! Pudding! I love pudding! Ooh, it's farm-fresh! And not just one pudding, but three whole cups! I'll have to pace myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm beat.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right, Daddy. You're on a top secret mission! You've got to take it easy with the secrets, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. How right you are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you still can't tell us what your "mission" is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Maybe it is time. It has something to do with you, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? With... me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Maybe you're getting a top secret mission, too! Maybe you can be one of those guys! A spy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Can't I just be a defense attorney...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha! To be honest... ...telling you about the mission was my whole reason for coming here today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me... ...you've heard of the Jurist System, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Jurist System...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. The new legal system everyone's talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Have you heard of it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Uh... Maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Maybe not as many people are talking about it as I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The "Jurist System", huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, those legal books were left by my mentor. Too bad I gave up the practice before reading them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's quite a few magic books in there, too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. Those would be Trucy's. She'll remember they're there eventually, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>For a moment, I thought Mr. Wright might do magic, too... A scary thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The plant. It intrigues you, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not really. It's just the only thing in here that doesn't have some secret function.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. No, no secrets. But lots of memories. And a name, too. Want to hear it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name... is Charley. If you were curious.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Really, I wasn't.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Want to have a go at that ring, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no, I was just touching it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">C'mon, there's no need to be shy! Just slip it on... There!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yoooooowwwwwwwwch!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're way too tense! You gotta loosen up, there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The human body wasn't meant to bend like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can't believe you're using this cutting-a-person-apart box as... shelf space.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, I used that trick on stage the other night. Imagine my surprise when I pulled one of my shirts out of the box!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You should really examine your props before the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That magician in the photo, is that your...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My real Daddy, yup! Zak Gramarye! He disappeared when I was little. I hung that up there so I wouldn't forget what he looked like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I see. <thought>She's smiling, but I'll bet that smile doesn't go very deep...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No one's practicing the piano, as usual. Even calling him a pianist is an insult to pianists everywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK, Apollo! I'm going to guess what you're thinking right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What, was I making a funny face or something?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Argh! I'm so hungry!"... I'm right, right? Of course I am.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's no "of course" about it! You guessed wrong. ...Besides, that's not what I'm thinking... it's what you're thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack! How did you do that!? You read my mind, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">At least you've got that pudding.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Try not to eat my share, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That hat... Is that a spare? It looks exactly like the one you always wear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the first rule of a professional: be prepared! You know, I put it on the other day... ...and this strange white substance fell all over me! It was like magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or... like fingerprint powder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A plate of plastic spaghetti for displaying in a shop. ...Where the heck does she get this stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, careful there, Apollo. A lot of people run into that table, you know. Why, some client knocked the pot clean over the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, why not get a more sturdy table?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. Maybe the table is partially to blame...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...There's no "maybe" to this. That thing is a deathtrap.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahem. I wasn't finished talking to you, you know. Or rather, you weren't finished asking me questions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why try to fight it? I can't win...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Daddy, what's this "Jurist System" thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Trucy, do you know what a "jury" is?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've heard of it. Isn't that those people who sit in court in those old courtroom dramas? The ones who get to decide if a guy's innocent or guilty? Do you know, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Only from TV. It's twelve people, chosen from the community, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, they're thinking about reviving that system. They're calling the new system, the "Jurist System".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"No more doing whatever you like, Your Honor!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not quite that harsh. The jurists cooperate with the judge. They help analyze the case from different angles.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, and there will be only six of them under the current proposal, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, you know your stuff, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Their findings directly affect the verdict. Hopefully, people will start taking the courts a little more seriously now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I feel like I'm on some kind of educational TV show! Starring Dr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dr. Wright, his assistant Trucy... ...and mascot Apollo. The perfect team!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mascot...? Hey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... What is this secret mission?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Jurist System is my mission... more or less. Anyway, keep in mind that new ideas like this system are always risky, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too true... Everyone's got an opinion, and they just talk and talk and nothing gets decided. Kind of like you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, I'm not that bad. Am I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case... ...we're going to give it a shot. A test, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't like tests.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll take a case as a sample, and choose six jurists. I'll be the one helping with that process, incidentally.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Helping... how?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, for one, I'll be chair of the Jurist System Simulated Court Committee. The chair constructs the ideal situation... choosing the case, the jurist candidates... ...even the judge and the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! It's like you have a real job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I was never that good at the piano, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Once a lawyer, always a lawyer, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trial's tomorrow, by the way. Don't miss it. The trial simulation that is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A simulation, huh... Sounds interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo, I know you're all excited about that secret mission... ...but what about this!? The "Troupe Gramarye Grand Magic Show"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, right. The card tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They're not "card tricks"! They're grand illusions! Miracles! The apocalypse! Heaven and Earth will shake!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So what, that's three whole days from now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's at Sunshine Coliseum! Let's go! Let's go today! We can say hi to Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Have fun.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaat!? I can't go by myself! You know I'm not very outgoing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Riiight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not go with her?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... what about the "secret mission"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, don't worry about that. You'll hear all about it tomorrow, regardless.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't trust that smile. He knows something that he's not telling me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yippee! Now you can take me to the coliseum!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* I suppose it wouldn't kill me to pop over there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, "presenting", are we? I did my fair share of that back in the day. Showed my attorney's badge a lot, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He may look cool and calm now, but you should have seen him before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. You know me too well, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm glad I provided this opportunity for a little family bonding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a number inscribed on the back of the badge. There are many numbers like it, but this one is mine. Proof that I'm an attorney. To tell the truth, I get a happy feeling inside just looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are you ready, Apollo!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ready? For what?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">For what!? For the Troupe Gramarye Grand Magic Show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-It's not like I'm getting up on stage or anything...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What are you talking about, Apollo!? You can't enjoy magic if you're not part of what's going on up on stage! I'll lend you my spare costume if you need one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? You mean, I can't go in this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Doesn't get more straightforward than that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, lookey here. A handwritten signature. It says... I can't read it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That seems odd to me. I mean, isn't a signature intended to show ownership? What's the use if no one can read it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't enough if you can read your own? &lt;!- potential typo? --&gt;</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Oh! I never thought of it that way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... what kind of case is the trial simulation about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, since it is the first run through of a new system, I wanted something simple.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good thinking! No sense wearing yourself out on something too serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True. The case is a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not simple at all!!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">By "simple", did you mean that the defendant is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Guilty. Yes. Most likely. ...So, good luck, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... with what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With the trial tomorrow. You're defending, of course. Recall that I said it had something to do with you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Go for it, Apollo! It's just a test case, anyway. No sweat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but there's still a verdict to be decided.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And a potentially serious sentence. The most serious, in a worst-case scenario.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! You mean... the verdict's for real!? That's not a "test" trial! That's a... real trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All the forms have been filed. There's no turning back now. The trial begins tomorrow at 10 AM. Hope you can make room in your schedule.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Why am I only hearing about this now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah, yes. There was a change this morning. ...I picked a new case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Something that happened last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alright, so what case are you going to use?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really want to know don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course I do! I mean... I'm going to be defending, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If all goes well, then yes. Of course, this is just a test. We wanted everyone to start without preconceptions. A blank slate, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a difference between having a blank slate and just being totally clueless. Who's [sic] dumb idea was that anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well mine. Committee chair, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you want to know that badly, I suppose... ...I could give you permission to examine the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good! That's better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...But you can't talk to anyone involved with the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What!? Then how am I supposed to defend...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You let me worry about the details, there. Remember... I'm in charge of this trial. All of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you don't want it to backfire, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo... ...if I am in charge of the whole trial... ...that means the entire affair is my responsibility. For good, or for bad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just do what you can. And don't worry. I know what I'm doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... Alright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you just said I couldn't talk to anyone involved...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, you can talk to your client. If... you can get her to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, time's a wasting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's 20 minutes we've been waiting here! 20 minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe I should complain? I'm sure that guard has better things to do than stand there pretending he doesn't see us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know the minute we get angry, the client will show. It always works that way.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Like shouting, "Oh, waiter!" and they're standing right behind you? Oh, guaaaaard! Is our client going to be much longer?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">What are you talking about!? Haven't you already started the meeting, yet!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Huh? Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh-Where'd you come from!?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-W-W-Well... ...Anyway! Please have a seat!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... I'm nervous, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the silence. It builds suspense. Why don't you do something, Trucy? You're a magician, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-That's right. OK...</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">I'm the Amazing Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeek! She passed out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. Ms. Magic Underwear might have been a better bet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's "Magic Panties", Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The security camera stares down from the ceiling, all-seeing, unblinking. Not that I'm nervous or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The same old security guard is glaring at us. ...He winked. Maybe he's not such a bad guy after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um. Uh. Hi! Well, I'm your defense... ...I really think it has to be fate, you know!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And by fate, I mean destiny! Did you know I'm good with astrology? Tell me, what's your sign?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I can tell you mine, if you'd like, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No, never mind. I just got carried away there. <thought>I seem destined to get difficult clients, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... So, what's your name?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right, I'm supposed to introduce myself first! I'm Apollo! Apollo Justice!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And I'm Trucy Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I know. <thought>This is getting nowhere fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I know! Maybe you can tell us what happened? I'm your defense attorney, after all!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, anything out of the ordinary happen lately?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, the other day this tourist from out of town stopped to ask me directions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Later, Trucy. <thought>I feel like I need to ask directions myself here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, see this here?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, does it ring any bells?</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does anything I say ring anything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You did good, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">L-Look! She's doing her nails!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Are nails more important than defense? Is that it!? ...Let's go, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">C-Could you... Could you read this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I feel like a teenager on a first date! And this is the love letter we passed from desk to desk at school...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Stop looking so wistful and read it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It... It's a business card. With a name and an address. The name is... Vera Misham? The address is for "Drew Studio".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you're giving me this card because...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Well, looks like we're finished here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder if Drew Studio is the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's go find out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a pretty business card. Looks like a postcard, almost.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And on the back... Hmm. Just her name.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That seems odd to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What does?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why write your name on the front and back of the card? Why not use the space on the back for a self-portrait! Or a caricature! Then people would remember what you look like, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not a bad idea, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Here, give me one of your cards, Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...She's drawing something. Hey! My hair's not THAT spiky!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">Ah, you're here to see Vera Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">She's in the medical office at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Medical office...? Is she OK?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">She's just lying down. Said she didn't feel so good. I'm sorry but I can't allow any meetings at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Most. Annoying. Client. Ever.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guess we should come back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, this looks like... it looks like a studio.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's like life imitating art... Or, maybe, it's the other way around... Hmm. But the tape on the ground there... It's a bit jarring...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Looks like we found our crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Look at all those paintings!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, don't touch those.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's OK, I'm just looking. Huh? Apollo... Look at this one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Looks half finished. <thought>You can still see the rough sketch underneath.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, that's odd. The rough part doesn't look like the rest of the painting at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, good point. <thought>That is odd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...All the paintings have a really different style, too.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! I thought I might find you two here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ema! Long time no see!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh? Seems like I run into you far too often. I'll bet I know why you're here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know about the trial simulation tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I've heard about it, sure. So Mr. Wright chose you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We don't even know what the case is about.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, he was killed. The artist who owns this studio, that is. Mr. Drew Misham.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Misham...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And his daughter was put under arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... We just saw her at the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was funny, though. She seemed more like a victim than the kind of person who could commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You don't say. Not even by poisoning? That's how it was done, you know. Poisoning's a common way to get the job done, when the murderer is a woman.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">P-Poisoning...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Anyway, Mr. Wright told me you'd be coming. Feel free to take a look around. I'll just be over here. With my Snackoos.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We can't talk to anyone related to the case this time around... ...Which means we'd better find out as much as we can here at the scene. ...Or else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, that's the victim's coffee mug.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah ha! So the poison was in here! This is my first time seeing a real poisoned mug of coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would hope so.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... "Poisoned Coffee"...? Not exactly, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No traces of poison were found in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...You'll have to figure out the rest yourself. I'm officially not on your side, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That coffee mug... it's not what you'd expect. No traces of poison were found in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Whaaaat?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yet the only thing the victim drank that night was this coffee... ...so the poison definitely reached him through this mug.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... I like you better when you tell us stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look... Just figure it out yourselves, OK? I have my "position" here to consider.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eek, Apollo! Th-That's where the body was!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's the spot where Mr. Drew Misham passed away. He put the coffee mug to his lips, and the next moment...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's quite a bit of paint on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">See that half-painted painting there? He must have been working on that right up to the moment he died.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! A true artist to the end!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Or maybe he started it a year ago and was procrastinating.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey... There's a painting hidden back here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What if it's embarrassing somehow, and he didn't want anyone to see it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You certainly seem pleased by the possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh. It's so... normal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's hardly something to get mad about... ......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, doesn't this painting look like... never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better get a professional opinion on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, doesn't this painting look like... never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better get a professional opinion on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That letter box looks funny sitting inside a room like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's take a look... Empty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The other half of that letter box is actually connected to the outside of the studio. Mr. Misham would put his letters in there... ...and the postman took them away.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Impressive that someone still writes letters in this day and age. Or wrote, rather.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wouldn't mind taking a closer look at those paintings. I just love oils! You know, how they're so thick? Is that the word?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...These paints are all dry. I'm just surprised at how different these all are.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah... And what's going on with this half-finished one?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It must have been a work in progress. You can still see the rough sketch below...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...That's what's so weird. The sketched part doesn't really fit the finished parts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I noticed. <thought>That is weird...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This painting here looks like a work in progress.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... the rough sketch part doesn't fit the other parts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. <thought>Very peculiar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's take a closer look! Why are two of the paintings identical? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It certainly is a bit curious. <thought>...And a whole lot of suspicious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I imagine this coffee cup was for guests to use.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Guests?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did the police already analyze this cup, too?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not a trace of poison was found on that cup.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the killer was after Drew Misham alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is this desk for painting, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That would be a drafting table.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Drafting?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Basically, it's a tool for making precise diagrams.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Wow, painting is harder than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why would a painter need a drafting table? Was he an architect, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is all this equipment here for? It doesn't look very artistic, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He had everything from a lathe to a laser cutter. Looks like he was ready to work on metals and wood, too. ...Though his equipment's a bit old, to tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would a painter need all this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">From the dust, I'd say he hasn't used this stuff for years.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This corner doesn't fit with the rest of the studio.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, do you think I could borrow this? I want to cut a quarter in half to make a trick coin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This is a crime scene, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But these cost like 50 bucks at the magic shop!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's take a closer look at this desk here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This envelope has been opened and resealed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I know how to do that! You take a pot of boiling water, and hold the envelope up to the steam. The glue melts and it opens! Cool, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoever did this wasn't so delicate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're right. Looks like they just ripped it open and stuck it back together. ...Huh? The postmark on this letter is from seven years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why would someone open a letter, then seal it again? Hmm... I'd better hang on to this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This envelope has been opened and resealed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're right. Looks like they just ripped it open and stuck it back together.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Very strange... <thought>Why would someone open a letter, then seal it again? Hmm... I'd better hang on to this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo, what's this feather-thingy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't that a pen? Like an old-fashioned quill pen?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But it doesn't have a pointy end.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That was most likely for sweeping detritus off the desk.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, you sure know a lot, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Bold and scientific, that's my motto.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Exactly what about that was "bold" or "scientific"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. Something about the way that figure is posed...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I've seen that pose before! It's you, Apollo! See, you're making one of your flamboyant gestures!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, I am a professional. <thought>...I wonder why it's posed like that? Coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this... a journal?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, talk about a clue! Let's read it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What is it, Apollo!? He didn't write the name of the killer, did he!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's new. He didn't write a single line.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Argh! You had me going for a while there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is Drew Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And this little girl must be Vera!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, they took that some years ago. They look close. A happy little family.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Until you arrested his daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Ack! Look, I was personally against that, OK? She just didn't seem very suspicious. Scientifically speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh huh. Right.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Cute! Look at the tiny frame, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tiny is right. That thing's barely two inches high. What picture would fit in that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">None, apparently. It's empty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's no glass in it, either. What's it doing sitting on the desk?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is a lesson for us all: be sure to check the size when you buy frames!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder why there's poison on this tiny frame.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Very strange indeed. Wait, I know! I'll bet it was poisoned from the time he bought it! Haven't you heard about some kinds of green paint being toxic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think they sell that kind anymore. And the poison was atroquinine, anyway. <thought>A tiny, mysterious, poisoned frame...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look at all these paints, Apollo! There's so many! He's got like... twenty kinds of red! We could repaint your suit, Apollo! How about this shade of... green!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That'll be enough of that, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, this, um, Drew Misham was some kind of artist?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently. Did a lot of illustrations for books, I hear. Had a lot of female fans, too, for what it's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? Well, I guess his stuff is kinda pretty. Like that oil painting over there, for instance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Um... yeah. That... wasn't one of his illustrations, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh? So it was a standalone painting or something? Is that what she means?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">He was an odd bird, Misham. Hadn't shown his face to anyone until the end.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean, "to anyone"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He was always locked up here in this studio, apparently. His only connection to the outside world... ...was through letters he'd put in that letter box there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Letters? Do people still write letters?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I mean, when was the last time you wrote a real letter? Don't most people use e-mail and stuff these days?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not Mr. Misham. Couldn't stand technology, it seems. He did everything by mail.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe he thought that way was more artistic, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In any case, the only person besides him allowed in here... ...was his daughter, Vera.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you mean the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The "suspect", please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We took some fingerprints, of course. The only ones found in the room were Mr. Misham's and Vera's, basically.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Basically"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually, last night... ...Mr. Misham gave an interview to a reporter for the first time. It happened during the interview, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">His first interview ever...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you tell us a bit more about what happened the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this woman, Vera... She's Mr. Misham's daughter, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yep. A real sickly girl, ever since she was little. Hardly ever went outside.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She did kind of give off a withdrawn sort of aura...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">She was home-schooled by her father, apparently. It was quite a scene when they took her to the detention center. She was screaming about how she'd die "if they took her outside".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That... does sound like a scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In the end, she agreed to leave if she was allowed her "good luck charm" for company.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Her "good luck charm"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently, she has this charm that magically gives her the courage to go outside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Why can't I ever get a normal client?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But why would a shut-in daughter kill her own dad?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't look at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, about the poison... It was found to be in his coffee, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No... Not precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not precisely? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It means "see for yourself", I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Like I said. Last night was the first time someone from the "outside" came into this studio. I guess mysterious painters who never go outside make for good articles.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And it just so happened that he died the night of his first interview...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...At around 9:00 PM every night... ...Vera always made him a cup of coffee. Last night, he drank his usual coffee, and suddenly became violently ill...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...And died? She poisoned him on the night of his interview!? Wouldn't the reporter see?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He wasn't near Mr. Misham when she brought her father his coffee. He was checking out some equipment in the back of the room. ...Supposedly, that's why she didn't notice he was there. It was the reporter who called the police, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, but why is she the suspect? If anyone is suspicious, it's the reporter!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yet the reporter never got near Mr. Misham's coffee. Even Vera acknowledges that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Regardless, I want to know more about this "reporter".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, about the reporter...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I can't tell you much. I hear he's going to be a witness tomorrow, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I bet Ema could help us out here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't forget, flattery will get you everywhere with her, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? What are you two whispering about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... I was thinking. I mean, what is it we always do when we run into you at a crime scene? What is it we always do... scientifically?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, you know me too well! OK...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK... meaning we can get erm, scientific now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I suppose. Just this once! Bring me anything you find suspicious and we'll check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was hoping we could do a little forensics works...</line>
<line speaker="Emma">...I suppose. If we must. Just this once!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, about this painting...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, that? Quite good, isn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, that's not what I wanted to ask you about.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You want to examine it, is that it? I'd be happy to let you, if you had a good reason. But without that... sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I guess she wants us to do a little footwork on our own first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, Ema, I was wondering about this painting here...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah. Aaah. That one? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"What about it"!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, what about it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a closer look at it, both of you. Now... look at this one. This is the third painting he was working on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey. They're the same!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I was hoping you wouldn't find that. You're right, though. Drew Misham was copying this painting.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. It's pretty good!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Copying a painting...? What for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Ema, about this coffee mug...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I hope you aren't trying to grill me for information. You know I'm not talking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I suppose you are the detective here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why don't you two take a look yourselves? If you find a clue, I might not be unwilling to lend a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think she's going to help us, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's check out this mug, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Ema, about this mug... ...there's a pale blue, uh, "residue" on the rim.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Eh? Ah! Th-That! Yes, well, it's just a rumor... ...but I've heard there's a kind of coffee called "Blue Mountain"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm pretty sure it isn't actually blue, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah. Right. OK, you got me. That's left over from my testing spray.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Forensic science! I knew your hobby was behind this somehow, Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's not a "hobby"!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, what kind of scientific stuff were you up to?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This spray, that's what. It turns blue when it touches poison.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, the poison that killed the victim was on this mug?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. See? It wasn't in the coffee. The killer applied it to the rim of the mug itself!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! Science is amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It certainly is helpful... Maybe Ema'd be willing to help us out a bit more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You should try buttering her up, Apollo. They say flattery will get you everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's certainly worth talking to her a bit more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh! Th-That! Y-Yes, why that's a bright red envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She sure is jumpy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone opened this, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... My lips are sealed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Your "lips are sealed"...? <thought>That's a first!</thought> You mean... you know what's inside the envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure. I read it, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! You mean you were the one who ripped this open!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hah! Please! I would have steamed it open.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But she did sneak a peek at it, apparently.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Know that I have a powerful weapon on my side.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Weapon...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes! The use of tools! Highly specialized tools for information gathering.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Tools I wouldn't mind getting my hands on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You should try flattering her, Apollo... They say a little praise can open big doors.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Never heard that one, but it's good advice... Let's try talking to her some more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But we just did the X-ray detection thing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, I was wondering if you could take a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, I'm a detective. A detective! You can't just ask me any old thing and expect an answer, OK? I think you need to be a little more focused in your inquiries. Scientific, even.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Somehow I knew she'd get around to science.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, what do we have here...? It looks like a person... thinking about something.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they're worried? Like, what should I have for supper: a hot dog, or a hamburger? ...... You know, I've always wondered about that. Why is there "supper" and "dinner"? Are they different meals or the same thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Maybe that's what this person's thinking about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that... a pufferfish?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! That's clearly a porcupinefish!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...They're not the same thing?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what gets me? They're got all these needles, right? But what's protecting that soft spot on the lower belly there? Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Must remember to keep Trucy away from small, round fish.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, look at this painting. You can see the rough sketch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. Looks like it was only half-completed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? That's funny. Do the rough sketch and the finished painting look totally different to you, too?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...They do, actually! <thought>What's that all about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo. This painting, I know it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's that story where the old woman is doing the wash in the river... ...and this giant peach comes a' floating on down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That might possibly be the strangest thing I have ever heard.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey... look there! That stain doesn't look so healthy, Apollo! That must be the "Blue Mountain" stuff we've been hearing about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something tells me that even Blue Mountain Coffee isn't THIS blue. No, this stain is probably... <thought>Hmm, better ask Ema.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, look! It's been opened once here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're right. I wonder if there's some way we can see what's inside?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Should I try to get it open and then stick it back shut?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's not tamper with the evidence, shall we? I've got a better idea...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Ema! Let's ask her!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I was afraid you were going to ask about that. See, this solution is used to test for atroquinine.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Atro... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Atroquinine! The deadly poison found in the autopsy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Uh oh, I know that spark in her eyes. She's getting excited. Best tread lightly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's one of the most virulent poisons, but is absorbed into the body astonishingly slowly. It takes at least 15 minutes from the time of ingestion for adverse effects to show. Oh, and guess what!? Recent research has shown...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's fine, really. We don't need to know all the gory details.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think I get it. You just spray this stuff on something you want to test, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Precisely! You can find even the slightest trace of poison with this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wanna try, too, Ema! Pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You don't have to ask twice! ...I already used it on everything suspicious, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yay! Let's give it a whirl, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaugh! What are you doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was just seeing if I got a reaction off of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How's this for a reaction: Never do that again! I'm not poisonous!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tell that to those hapless witnesses on the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's just get down to checking for real poisons, shall we?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad. No reaction there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure Ema checked out all the likely spots. ...Wait a second.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you spray that little desk over there?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't think so... The spray probably can't reach that far, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's check it out, just to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeek! A reaction, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aaaaaaugh! Where, where!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The inside of that cute little frame! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, would you look at that. Nice going, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm known to work magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Never mind that I was the one who found it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why would the inside of that frame have poison on it? ...It looks like we found the only other place that was poisoned, in any case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are we going to test for poison again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why not? Just to be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But, you found your clue already. Isn't that enough? This stuff isn't cheap, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I bet she doesn't have a lot of spending money.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I bet she spends it all on Snackoos.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See that, there? That's poison.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't lick it, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, I'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, you won't! You'll die!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, I know! I meant I won't lick it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Who knows what you do when I'm not watching...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...The concern is touching, really. Next thing you know she'll be telling me not to drink coffee before bedtime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Looks like you have to take this back part off first to put a photo inside.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It'd have to be a really small photo to fit in there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">True. And that pale bluish stain... Why would there be poison in a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, there's one obvious reason. Whoever put poison in the coffee rubbed a bit on here, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not very obvious, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About that envelope we found... ...I was wondering if you could help us out with that "tool" you were mentioning?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Eh heh heh, you want to know about my tool do you? It's called an X-Ray Analyzer.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">X-Ray... like the x-rays you get at the dentist?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right! At least, that's what I call it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It has a real name, but it's much more complicated: the X-Ray Spectraliziation... ...something. How am I supposed to remember all that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, basically, it lets you see inside things... like envelopes?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right! You're sharp, Trucy! But it's a bit more complicated than that, in practice, of course. Actually, to tell the truth, I'm not really sure how it works, scientifically.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can I try it out, Ema? Please!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I suppose. ...Of course, I've already checked out everything suspicious myself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Alright! Let's give it a spin, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeeeeargh! What are you doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, just seeing if I could see through your hair... But it's like lead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Point that thing at me any more, and it might all fall out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Then I wouldn't need an x-ray machine to see through it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's just get down to business, shall we?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. Let's test it on a sample, first. It just so happens that I have a lottery ticket here. You set the sample in the device like so...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I don't see anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Patience. There's no need to get all antsy. Look at the right side of the screen. That's the "layer view" of the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Layer view...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You've got it set to display the outside of the envelope now, see? Actually, it's quicker to just have you give it a try. Turn that dial there for me, would you? That's right. That's how you choose what "depth" you want to scan.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! I got something!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">See? That's how you can read the letters on the ticket inside. Cool, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Except... I can't read them.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just turn the dial a little more. What you have to understand is that a sheet of paper isn't really flat at all. When you zoom in that much, you see that paper is like a bunch of hills and valleys.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This x-ray device uses a beam with a wavelength of only 0.05 microns! It breaks cards down into thin layers, so it can only show what's written on that layer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not entirely following you, but what good is it if you can't read anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's why we go on to step two! Try rubbing the image a bit, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"The image"? You mean rub the screen?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There. That fixes the image on the screen. Now, turn the dial again, just a little. Good. Now you can rub this image to "fix" it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, I get it! We just keep doing this until we've got the whole thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Exactly! Not bad!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Neat! Let's do some more!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo hoo! I'm a big winner!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah ha ha. See! This is the true hidden power of my weapon. Neat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Hmm. Does this mean I have to buy another one to win?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's Ema's ticket. Let her buy another one.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's OK, there's no need. But see, this is the true hidden power of my weapon. Neat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ouch. "You lose".</line>
<line speaker="Ema">At least you know where you stand, eh? Anyway, now you see the true hidden power of my weapon. Neat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now let's try it out on the real thing, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone deposited $100,000 into Mr. Misham's account? His paintings must be really valuable!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's another page in there. ...Care to take a look?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You bet I do! If you're going to read someone's mail you might as well read it all!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here goes with the second page, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...So it was a letter about payment for one of his paintings.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why all the secrecy, though? And...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...And what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why was this letter the only one in here? ...It's seven years old, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe it had some special significance to him? Well, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well indeed. ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She knows something she's not telling us. ...Looks like she's keeping mum about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's take a closer look. Mr. Misham sure worked on a lot of different paintings. You think his works really go for a 100 grand a piece? Maybe I should take up painting. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think his paintings are worth THAT much. Something's not right here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Ema, I was wondering... What's the story about this reporter that came here for a story the night of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah! I'm afraid I can't tell you, because he's going to be a witness tomorrow, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I thought so.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll never forget that face, but what was his name...? Oh, right. Brushel.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Brushel...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's after a scoop to sell to the papers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So a reporter comes for an interview with a painter. His first interview ever, and that night, he's killed. Seem strange to you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really strange.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It does raise a few questions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd like to speak with this reporter if I could.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I hear he's on the beat today, too. ...He said something about covering a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Magician...? <thought>Well, if it's not Trucy, that leaves only one other person.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It wasn't Valant Gramarye, by any chance, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, something like that! He's got some big show lined up, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he's out interviewing Valant Gramarye... Looks like I'll be heading out to that coliseum again sooner than I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Here, I'll give you that reporter's card if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess you gotta have a good business card if you work freelance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really. What's this... a camera lens finder?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do reporters take photos too?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess if he's freelance, he'd have to.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe you should try being a prosecutor and a defense attorney! You'd always win!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why don't I become a rock star too, while I'm at it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo hoo! This is it, Apollo! The place where magic and dreams converge!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just a while ago it was the place where murder and nightmares converged.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's go say hi to Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What about the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Waaaah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Only a performer laughs like that...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The young Miss Trucy! How often I hoped we'd meet again only to tell myself it was an impossible dream!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee, Uncle Valant! How's it going? I'm glad to see you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Of course you are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Humility is definitely NOT one of his stronger traits...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Well, Miss Trucy, how does the day find you? If you've come to give me flowers, do it after the show, I beg you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Actually, we came to wish you good luck! And congratulations on your big magic show!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Oh? But it is I who wish to congratulate you! Not everyone is so lucky as to witness miracles such as I shall perform!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, yeah, you're amazing, we get the picture.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">The world will watch in wonderment as Magnifi's illusions are reborn! Here, on stage! By my hand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey, that creature there. He was handing out balloons during our last case, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's not a "creature", Apollo! Poor guy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, sorry. Was I mean somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know how hot it is inside one of those suits? He's stuck in there, with only the smell of his own sweat to keep him company. On the verge of passing out, he hands out each balloon as though it were his last!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kind of takes the fun out of seeing the Blue Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, I thought this at the time of the Gavinners's concert, too, but... ...this coliseum is just way too big. It's huge.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's got a big-sounding name, too... "Sunshine Coliseum", was it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha ha! Would you like to hear what the grand finale of the show in three days will be?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!? Really!? Yeah, yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Eh heh heh... The grand finale will be nothing other than...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't tell me. You're going to make the coliseum disappear, right?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh. Oops. Looks like I was right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! I can't believe you'd use your power of perception on something like this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was just a wild guess, really.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, Apollo! A balloon! A hot air balloon!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With the Gramarye seal on it, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Well, this is a long-awaited revival, after all! And it's been seven years, you know. I've spent plenty of time and a pretty penny on promotion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I hope it's a huge success, Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Oh, I intend for it to be nothing less, I assure you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They both sure seem excited about it. I guess it's a big deal for magicians.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They've changed the sign since our last case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It was all Gavinners back then, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hope nothing bizarre and mysterious happens this time.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">But it shall! Why, the show itself will be bizarre and mysterious, I assure you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't have a problem with mystery as long as it's legal.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't think lawyers and magicians were really meant to have conversations like this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Everyone's talking about the big magic show! Is it true that the "Gramarye Miracle" is back after a seven year absence?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Miss Trucy. I must apologize. This show, and this honor, should have been his.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">My co-magician-in-training Zak Gramarye... If that terrible thing hadn't...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...It's OK.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Your father was a great magician, Trucy. If he were alive, then I, Valant Gramarye... ...would have been proud to stand upon this stage as his assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks... Uncle Valant. You know, I'm happy you're doing the show! To think, we get to see the Great Magnifi's illusions again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She really is looking forward to this, isn't she.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">My mentor, the magnificent Magnifi Gramarye was a true deity among magicians. A creator-god who gave birth to magic and illusions that defied our very imaginations!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was so little when I last saw one, but I still remember his shows! He did wheelies in a sports car through the air above the audience...! And then sped off to outer spac, faster than the speed of sound!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm guessing that memory was a bit embellished.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">For seven long years, the world has been waiting for a miracle to match his. As heir to the Gramarye Troupe's secrets, it falls to me to provide one. It is my god-given destiny!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes! You, nameless face who speaks for the nameless masses. How can I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the world was waiting, why did you hold off for seven long years?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Hmm... It appears the lad is uninformed! Perhaps you have heard of the magic known as "law" which governs our land?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I have, though I'm not sure it qualifies as "magic".</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The performance of Magnifi's miracle was impossible. ...A certain "law" prevented it for seven years. But no more!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Seven years"... That phrase sure likes to pop up, doesn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...And why was that?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">A little matter called "performance rights", Miss Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can you tell us about these "performance rights"?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Magnifi's magic relied on an incredibly innovative idea... a "trick", if you will. That trick... was considered his property, and as such, was protected by property laws.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Intellectual property, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Magnifi knew this and bequeathed it in his will... ...to one person.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean... him!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. Miss Trucy, it was your father. Zak Gramarye was the inheritor of the Gramarye Miracle!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet, as you well know, he is gone. He disappeared suddenly, seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I see where this story is going...</thought> Once a person is classified missing for a certain period of time... ...they're considered legally deceased, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...In all absoluteness. Those rolled-up sleeves conceal your competence well, young man! That "certain period of time" of which you speak... is seven years.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes, Miss Trucy... Though it pains me to say it. This past Spring... April to be precise, was the time. Your father was legally declared deceased. In the absence of a formal will... ...the secrets of our mighty mentor Magnifi passed to me. This was, in fact, stipulated in the will by Magnifi himself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is... that how it works, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It's called "death in absentia". He's declared missing... permanently.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">A man by that name called on me just now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just now...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Valant's vision is always toward tomorrow! Valant's feet step always forward! ...That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's all... very confusing.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I am to perform a big magic show, yes? I wanted someone to cover it. Yet, he had ears only for that incident...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That incident?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">In any case, I requested that the rapacious reporter remove himself. So a painter has died, what of it!? It is but a footnote in the footlights compared to the magic of Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uncle Valant! Do you know where the reporter went?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I recommended he visit that place popular with penalized perpetrators.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The detention center...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I was wondering if you could tell me about this?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha! Why, that bears the Gramarye seal! ...... Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Uncle Valant? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Trucy. Where... did you get this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Um, Daddy gave it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Your... Y-Y-Y-Your D-D-D-Daddy!? My partner, Zak Gramar--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, no, no. My other daddy, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Why now... Why would your Lord Daddy...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Lord Daddy"? That's kind of stretching the whole archaic thing a bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">This signature upon the back. Do you recognize it? That belongs to none other than Zak Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaaaaaaat!? Daddy signed this!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Might I be so bold as to open it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I-I'm sorry, but I can't let you do that!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Mmmmnk. Ah... Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's in this envelope, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">This signature... Why, it's none other than Zak Gramarye! Perhaps I might take a look inside?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No means no! Trucy's father didn't want us to open it yet.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Hrmmmm... Ah... Ah. Your Lord Daddy... Why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...What could be in this envelope...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, a journalist was here on a story?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">All eyes in the universe are upon my stage. All pens seek to commit its mysteries to paper!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, his name was Brushel.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Brushel... Brushel... Brushel... Brushel...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think he remembers him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He doesn't look too happy about it.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Brushel... That cloying smell of mint when he smiles, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, could you tell us more about him? What did he want?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Put that away. I care not to see it ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He really didn't like that guy, did he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's ask why, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha ha! A challenge, is it? You want me to make that disappear? Very well! Give it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! N-N-No thanks! <thought>Are all magicians like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo? What was that look just now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was just thinking how hard it is to get any information out of a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">He was a rude individual. Might I see that card?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, sure...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...He would tear apart my respectability? I will tear apart him!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Here it comes, Apollo! Uncle Valant's big magic trick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is he going to fix the card? <thought>Not sure that qualifies as "big" magic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Valant">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What happened to the big magic...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah ha ha ha ha ha! Is it not more miraculous for it to stay ripped?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He must have really not liked that journalist...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks, Uncle Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Three days from now... make ready for a miracle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you think that journalist was after? And why did Valant react like that to this envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think it's time to pay the detention center another visit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Workers are busily preparing the coliseum for the magic show three days from now. Maybe we should go check it out... once this case is solved.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A hot air balloon. You hardly see those anymore these days. It kind of reminds me of when I was a kid. Maybe Valant's playing the nostalgia card to drum up interest in the show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was a Gavinners sign last time, wasn't it? I hope nothing strange happens this time around...</line>
<line speaker="???">...I think I hear what you're saying. "We're All Doing It For The Money", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">No no no no! Not at all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Looks like someone's already meeting here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe that reporter?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey there! How ya doing? Who might you be?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, sorry, we didn't know someone was already here. I'm Apollo Justice, attorney at law. <thought>Talk about a nervous monkey.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You? You're Justice!? You?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... know me?</line>
<line speaker="???">Do I know you? Of course I know you! "Stares Down Witnesses On Stand Till They Spill Beans", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's not true! <thought>What's he writing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are you a reporter by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="???">Woo! You! You're Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh? Am I famous?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh yeah. Oh yeah! "Trucy Wright Hates Carrying A Bag: Puts Everything She Owns In Her Panties", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeek! That's so not true!</line>
<line speaker="???">Just hold on to your breeches, there. I'll wrap up this interview in a jiffy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Interview...?</line>
<line speaker="???">So, guard. I think I know what's going on here. "Guarding Rooms Is My Life. What Else Could I Possibly Need?" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">No! How many times do I have to tell you this? Look, I've got work to do. You deal with him.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... did you come here to interview the guard?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ooh wee, what a pickle! "Accused Wouldn't Talk, Had To Interview Someone Or Go Plum Crazy", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I should've guessed.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Where're my manners!? Name's Brushel. Spark Brushel. "I'm Not Picky -- Journalist Just Closes Eyes, Writes", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that nauseatingly strong mint smell every time he grins?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Until you've been interviewed by me, you don't know what thrilling is! "Wild Romp Through Crossroads Of Mayhem, Madness", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I can see that. <thought>He's writing something again! Well, if he's a reporter, maybe he knows something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Mr. Brushel... You're a journalist?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah me? Look, let me state one thing for the record here...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I'm the interviewer. You understand, yeah? "I'm The One Asking The Questions Here", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...For instance! You think a movie director watches movies?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Well, I think he probably does.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Exactly! I knew you'd understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, the night of the murder... ...you were at Drew Studio?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Who? Me? Look, let me state one thing for the record...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I may look calm and collected, but I'm busy. Real busy. Always on the road. "Journalist Always Buys One-Way Tickets, Never Looks Back", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can understand that philosophy, but...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You want to know the thing about one-way tickets? Once you use them, they're gone. ...All because you have to give them to the guy at the airport.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">True enough. But don't they give normal tickets away, too?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Exactly! See? It's the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, you went to do a story on Drew Misham... ...and he'd never had a story done about him before?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">That's right! Look, let me state one thing for the record here...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I'm sure you're going to want to know about my source. What tipped me off to Drew? Why do the interview in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well... yes.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Look, it's like... Oh! I've got it! Say there's this burger joint with fabulous ketchup. You think the burger guy's going to tell me where he got it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...At the supermarket, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Exactly! See? That's what I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think I may have actually understood that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, right. Let me go on the record here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I know what you're going to say. "Brushel! Take This, Write Brilliant Column!" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think so!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Look, buddy, I write brilliant columns about one thing: ...and that's food. Try to understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What could he possibly be writing? He didn't listen to a word I said!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Guess we'll leave then.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, but since you're here... ...might as well tell you a tidbit of news I saw. Just for the heck of it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure, tell us! ...Just for the heck of it.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I remember it like it was yesterday... ...I'd seen a movie on a trip, and wandered into this burger place with amazing ketchup... ...when an article in a tabloid caught my eye. "Famous Oil Painting Stolen From Art Dealer's Gallery", end quote, I believe it was.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An oil painting...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Happens every day, right? But, I thought I'd seen that painting somewhere before. ...A painting of a giant peach floating down a river.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Someone stole an oil painting... of a giant peach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Journalist Can Smell Scoop Better Than Burgers", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, how'd it go? Find anything out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, there was one thing I wanted to check with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What's with that scary face you're making?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And what's with the "I know something but I'm not telling" face you've got going, Ema?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This painting... came from behind that dresser.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, yes. So?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It was stolen, no?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... I was hoping you wouldn't figure that out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you think you could tell us a bit about this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I suppose. It's what you think. Drew Misham... was a forger.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A forger...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema... about this painting from behind the dresser there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Ah, yes. It's what you think. Drew Misham... was a forger.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A forger...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, what exactly is a "forger"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, basically, it's someone who makes "forgeries". Fakes, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Fakes...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Copies of an original. Exact copies, so precise, you can't tell them apart.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, why not just photocopy them?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The big problem with forgeries... ...is that people try to sell them as the real article. It's a crime, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, Drew Misham was...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A criminal? I'm afraid so. He received money to create elaborate forgeries. ...To supplement his work in illustration, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually... ...that's why I brought this here in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">When you're trying to determine if a painting is a forgery... ...the rough sketch underneath can be a valuable clue.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So the rough sketch is like practice for the real thing! Like doing a magic trick in front of a mirror before you go on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...But not in the case of a forgery. Not necessarily, anyway. You know what the finished product is going to look like, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, yeah. I guess you would.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's why I brought this. I'm going to use it to see what's under the paint of the finished pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I get it now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not that I really needed to go to such lengths. Seeing as how one of the paintings was only half-finished anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Still, it'd be neat to see Mr. Misham's rough sketches. Kind of like what he was drawing when he thought no one was looking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>True... That would be interesting. And maybe valuable for our case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You should try buttering her up, Apollo! Flattery will get you everywhere, they say!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Hmm, maybe I should ask Ema to help us out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I kind of wanted to see the rough sketch under this painting. And I was wondering if your "tool" there might do the trick?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, fine. Fine! Just this time, though.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What... What the heck?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, he really blows! The finished painting isn't anything like the rough!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Devices like mine didn't exist until recently. He probably thought he could draw any sort of thing he wanted to for the rough.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, in the past, you could only analyze the composition of a rough sketch.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Composition?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">In other words, the traces of charcoal between paint and canvas. So you could tell if there had been a rough sketch... ...but not what it looked like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, I think I follow you. So, in essence, it wouldn't matter what was underneath the finished painting.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Some pros would actually paint out a rough sketch entirely. Then do a completely new painting on top of that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So Mr. Misham was drawing whatever he wanted before painting over them...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Possibly. Is there a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not particularly... But something about the sketch itself is kind of... odd.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're awfully silent all of a sudden, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You think we could check out one of the other paintings!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, sure. You like this detection stuff, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This one, too!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo? You look so serious all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, you think I could just look at the last of these?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Fine by me. Knock yourself out.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, let's print this one out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh... What the heck is all this!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I hesitate to ask why you're getting so excited.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You sure your device isn't leaking some kind of strange radiation?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! Look at these three sketches! ...Do you notice anything?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! Th-Th-They're...!!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Now you're both white as sheets! What's going on!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These sketches... are of the three cases I worked on!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder in the poker room at the Borscht Bowl Club! The dead man pulling the noodle stand! And then... ...the events that transpired during the Gavinners concert!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...What could it mean? How could he have painted those things... and why!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's what I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait! Is Drew Misham... ...your father?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Give me a break! Does that seem even REMOTELY possible to you!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd never even heard of any Drew Misham before. I hadn't even seen a picture of him. But there were my cases, drawn on his canvas! ...Every single one of them. It couldn't have been a coincidence. Just who was this Drew Misham... and what did he have to do with me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No clues here.</line>
</xml>