<xml>
<title>Turnabout Target</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Word of this must have reached every corner of the world by now. An assassination attempt on the president of the Republic of Zheng Fa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My name is Miles Edgeworth. I am a prosecutor. I was asked to investigate this grave incident, but upon my arrival...</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Edgeworth! We've been waiting for you, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is Dick Gumshoe. He's a detective with the local precinct who assists me on all cases under my jurisdiction.</thought> What is the president's current condition?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm still not sure, sir! The paramedics just entered his plane a few moments ago...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... <thought>I hope it's nothing too serious...</thought> Very well, Detective. Please show me around the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What's this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mister! Yer the prosecutor in charge 'round these parts, right? Can I ask you a little somethin' real quick?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid I must refrain from commenting for now. Let's go, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! Wait! Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Hold on, Mr. Edgeworth! Wait for me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Detective. Care to fill me in on the details?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Basically, the whole thing happened here, in Gourd Lake Park. There was a big welcoming event for the president of the Republic of Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The president of Zheng Fa, Di-Jun Huang... As I recall, newspapers and news programs were making quite a deal over his visit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It rained a bit, but it stopped just before his plane landed... He came out, and all of a sudden, in the middle of his speech... BANG! A gunshot! ...At least, I think it was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You think?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Truth is, I just got here as well, so I don't know all the details, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were also called here on short notice?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup... And today was supposed to be my day off!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I was supposed to be at the High Prosecutor's Office, preparing a case for trial...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The chief prosecutor asked for you personally, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The chief prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The chief prosecutor was taking part in the welcoming event. Apparently, the chief called out right after the incident occurred. "Call Prosecutor Edgeworth! He's the only one who can solve this case!" ...He said.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... So that's what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After the incident, we sealed off the park right away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means the assassin is still in the park...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">An assassin in this crowd... This could get dangerous, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If there is another incident, these civilians could get in harm's way. This is a race against time. Let's begin the investigation. First...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...we investigate the crime scene and gather some information!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. <thought>There's no mistaking it. The president was targeted with a gun (Shooting of the President - Even under such tight security, the president was fired at during the speech.</thought>. ...Hmm. This is something I'll have to keep in mind.) Detective Gumshoe! Where was security at the time of the gunfire?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The police were only in charge of guarding the park's perimeter. The president was being protected by his own personal bodyguards. It's those guys over there... Why don't you try talking to them, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To talk to someone, press the A Button while standing near them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! The bodyguards are in front of the airplane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I know. <thought>Press the A Button to talk with the bodyguards in front of the airplane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! The bodyguards aren't over there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I know. <thought>Press the A Button to talk with the bodyguards in front of the airplane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bodyguard">What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are the president's bodyguards, correct? What was the president's security detail like during the speech?</line>
<line speaker="Bodyguard">The president had his two best men by his side. The rest were stationed near the stage area. We are professionals. We constantly kept our eyes on the crowd, scanning for any signs of suspicious activity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... In other words, security was flawless during the president's speech <thought>Security during the speech - Security was flawless. Any suspicious people would've been noticed.</thought>. Let's keep going. We should talk to other people and examine anything suspicious... ...in order to collect the remaining pieces of information from the scene of the crime. ...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="???">I see! So that's how ya round up yer info. So, whaddaya do with all that info after it's squared away?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone in the crowd is making quite a ruckus, but I don't have time for that now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Heeey, Mr. Prosecutooor! Tell me how! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After gathering some pieces of information, you try to find the connections between them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey now, don't be such a stick-in-the-mud! What's this about findin' connections?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You connect the two pieces of information that share a link. That's Mr. Edgeworth's specialty. It's called Logic, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the L Button to use Logic, and the X Button to connect my thoughts... I should start by pressing the L Button to use Logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone was able to fire a gun under flawless security. And they were able to avoid being spotted by professional bodyguards... This is no easy task. There had to be a certain amount of preparation beforehand. It's very likely that the president's assassination <thought>Assassination attempt - The president was targeted during his speech. This was likely a premeditated crime.</thought> was a premeditated crime.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I expected nothing less from Mr. Edgeworth. What brilliant Logic, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... When you follow the facts and finds a connection, you will begin to see the truth. <thought>However... If the information doesn't line up properly, I may stray farther from the truth. But if I think carefully before piecing the leads together, the Logic should flow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! Let's start by examining everything we can!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To Examine, I approach anything that looks suspicious and press the A Button. And if I want to consult with Gumshoe, I press the Y Button.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The rain... it stopped, sir. It was pouring right up until the president arrived. Even the mist after the rain has cleared up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you looking forward to the rain?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I planned to go fishing at the lake. Rain gives you a better chance at a big catch, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">During the president's welcoming event, all regular activities in the park were prohibited.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not a "regular" activity! There's no activity more special to me than fishing in the lake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective Gumshoe. No court of law would recognize that as a "special" activity. <thought>Even in the midst of such a momentous case, the detective is still his usual self.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. I assume you understand how to conduct an investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, sir! The basis of any good investigation is collecting information! Examine suspicious objects! Talk to suspicious people!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the A Button to Examine objects and Talk to people...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Also, each person may have something different to say about the evidence you've collected. You can Present evidence from your Organizer to the people you're talking to, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the R Button to go over the evidence that I've collected in my Organizer... And press the X Button when talking with someone to Present evidence to them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've been with you for so long, Mr. Edgeworth. I've pretty much got most of basics down!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...And that's pretty much why you still haven't been promoted, Detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gathering information will be the key to solving this case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After you collect enough information, try to find connections between them, sir! Connect the pieces of information that share a link.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that's right. We'll use Logic to pursue the truth. <thought>Press the L Button to look over the information I've collected... Then press the X Button to connect two pieces of information that share a link.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright! I'm looking forward to witnessing some of your amazing Logic today, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Such a tiny object. I'm surprised you don't lose it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is an identification badge for us prosecutors, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see... It must be tough. If it were me, I'd definitely lose it, sir! I'm always losing my police badge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Having such a talent for losing things must be tough.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">With so many spin-offs in the Steel Samurai series, it's hard to keep track of all the characters.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The ruptured balloon was made to resemble the original Steel Samurai. Everyone should know that much, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I didn't know that, sir. Besides, they all have two eyes, one nose, and one mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Every human has those exact same attributes as well.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Humans don't have silver skin, though.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't even know how to respond to him anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! Mr. Edgeworth, you're such a joker! Even if you show that to me, I still have no idea what it is, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He proclaimed that quite proudly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An apple-red balloon is floating in the soft breese coming off from the lake.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When I was a kid, I used to send letters by balloon. That's when you tie a letter on a balloon and let it float away, hoping you'll find a pen pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's an interesting method of communication. Did you acquire any pen pals?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually... I never found one. I don't even know if my balloons made it out of my backyard, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They didn't even get that far!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you found any races of the assassin?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Nope! None at all, sir! No fingerprints or footprints of any kind! It's because everyone's touching everything and walking wherever they want!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, don't you think that was a bit out of line...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I agree, sir! I'll report it and see that it shows up on his next salary assessment!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is he taking pictures of?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">"The Hammer of Justice shall be brought down upon all evil!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like he's reading the speech notes on the floor, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">"Guide to Public Speaking 3: Speak slowly and yell loudly with confidence", it says. I see, so that's how it's done. I guess I'll take another photo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have an "objection" to his behavior at work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A gun was fired during the president's speech.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I remember when I had to give a speech in grade school. What an awful day! Right in the middle of my speech, an earthquake broke out and shook the classroom, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That really is awful... <thought>I don't do well with earthquakes, myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Are you listening to me? You're ignoring me, aren't you, sir...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, Mr. Prosecutor! How's this here investigation comin' along?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. It's that woman from before...</thought> I cannot disclose any details concerning the investigation to the general public.</line>
<line speaker="???">Aww... Help a gal out here, Mr. Prosecutor! *sigh*... At this rate, I ain't never gonna face my mentor, Lotta.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? That name just now sounded familiar... ...It's probably just my imagination.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the president's condition?</line>
<line speaker="Bodyguard">...We cannot divulge that information to anyone of this country.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, don't say that! We want to investigate the plane too, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Bodyguard">No one shall pass!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ohh... I don't think they trust the police here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This could develop into an international incident... Time is of the essence. We have no choice but to find the assassin!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I was surprised too. No matter how you look at it, it's definitely...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...the Steel Samurai. <thought>The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo. A hero from a popular TV program. Popular with both children and adults, it has broad appeal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why would they use a Steel Samurai balloon at the welcoming event, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps he was chosen as the hero to represent our country.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These flowers were delivered from a foreign country. I don't even know their names.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... My favorite flowers are roses and carnations. Because when I see roses, I think of weddings. And when I see carnations, I think of birthday parties.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You're probably just thinking about all of the cake you're allowed to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">P-Please don't be so blunt about it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the flag of the Republic of Zheng Fa. Its symbol appears to be a phoenix motif. Hm! This is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What is it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you noticed? There is an unusual spot on this flag... Compare it to the flag on the opposite side of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... There isn't a speck of dirt on it. This flag is spotless, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... That is what the flag is supposed to look like. However, there is one spot on this flag that is out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Where is it, sir? Please explain it so I can understand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...What a helpless man. I suppose I should point it out to him. Move the cursor to the unusual spot on the flag and press the X Button to Present it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...? I don't see an unusual spot anywhere at all, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... Sorry. It seems I made a mistake. <thought>I should take a closer look at these two flags. There should be one spot that is different from the original flag...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is an unusual hole in this flag.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judging from the burn marks around the hole... it appears to be a bullet hole.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A bullet hole <thought>Flag with a bullet hole - Decorated the right side of the stage. Has a bullet hole.</thought>? Then the bullet from the gun must've gone through the flag!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the flag of the Republic of Zheng Fa. Its symbol appears to be a phoenix motif. Hm! This is...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What is it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you noticed? There is an unusual spot on this flag...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-It... looks like the flag is made out of some real expensive material. It's even nicer than the curtains in your office, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What kind of comparison is that? My curtains have nothing to do with this. I am not interested in such trivial matters. Compare it to the flag on the opposite side of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is an unusual hole in this flag. Judging from the burn marks around the hole... it appears to be a bullet hole.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A bullet hole? Then the bullet from the gun must've gone through the flag!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Poor Steel Samurai balloon. It looks so miserable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. What did it to deserve such a fate?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">According to witnesses, a gunshot was heard when the balloon popped.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did a bullet from the gun (Ruptured balloon - Burst at the time of the gunshot. Was it hit by the bullet?</thought> hit the Steel Samurai balloon?)</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe it was an assassination attempt on the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To desecrate the Steel Samurai like this... This is a serious crime.</thought> ...Detective. We must not let this reprehensible assassin get away with this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, I seem to have gathered a few pieces of pertinent information. Now to calmly use some Logic and figure out if any of them are connected to each other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As a result of the gunshots, there is a bullet hole in a flag and a ruptured balloon...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That must mean two shots were fired, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we include the shot that hit the president, it's possible that three shots were fired in total. No, it's also possible that the flag and the balloon were punctured by the same bullet. If only we could be certain about the number of gunshots...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, let's continue the investigation... Hm?</line>
<line speaker="???">Heeey, Mr. Prosecutooor! If ya find anythin' new, could ya please lemme know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I've been wondering for a while now, but who exactly is that woman?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I thought she was just a nosy onlooker, but it looks like she's investigating, too.</line>
<line speaker="???">Heeey! Please, I'm beggin' ya!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... In order to figure out how many shots were fired, we'll need to talk to a witness... ...It can't be helped. Let's try talking to her.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ah! Mr. Prosecutor! The name's Nicole Swift! Jus' between you and me, this case is gonna be my exclusive scoop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Exclusive...?</thought> Ms. Swift, is it? Could you tell me what you witnessed during...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">So how's yer investigation comin' along?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Y'all got a suspect yet? Where'd ya get that frilly doohickey 'round yer neck?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please stop talking for a moment? I will be the one asking the questions.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">What is this, an interrogation? I reckoned I was gonna get myself an interview...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to know how many gunshots were fired. Can you please tell me what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Weeeeell... I guess... I ain't tellin' ya nuthin'.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">My life depends on info. I ain't givin' it up that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't be selfish, pal... Won't you please cooperate with us?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Selfish? If ya ain't gonna share no info with me, then I'mma go get it from elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Wait a minute, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">If I wait, are ya gonna gimme what I want? If not... Adiós amigos!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...She won't budge. We're at a stalemate here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"A stalemate"... I wonder about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you know, chess is one of my hobbies. How does one go on the offensive against a defensive opponent...? There are many tactics available on the chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">R-Really? I don't know much about chess. I prefer checkers...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if it appears to be a flawless defense... There is always an opening. Observe, as I break down her defense with my words...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In order to get her to talk, I'll need to use the right strategy. Using the image of a chess game, I need to stay one step ahead of my opponent...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then... Let's analyze the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Until ya gimme some info, my trap's sealed shut!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She has her guard up... So this is her defensive strategy. If I waste too much time, she may grow impatient. I need to pay attention to the time limit...</thought> I must not be careless with my words. When my opponent becomes agitated or aggressive...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I told ya I ain't talkin'! Yer stubborn as a mule!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>For example, during times like this I should calmly wait and see how things play out.</thought> The moment my opponent shows an opening I'll be able to strike. First, I should ask about her identity. Now... let us begin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, could you tell me your occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">No way. If I told ya, then ya might get the wrong idea.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The wrong idea...? In other words, it's a job that you cannot tell others about?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I never said that! I ain't some kinda suspicious person!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Huh? What's goin' on with ya? I don't get what yer sayin' at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A-Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I'm just yer run-of-the-mill model citizen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please excuse my rudeness. I did not mean to offend you. I may not know the details of your job, but I'm sure that it is a reputable one.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Eh? W-Well... Y-Ya might be givin' me too much credit, there. I ain't even done any major articles yet...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">C'mon, man! If yer gonna clam up, I'm outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there...</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... I heard you mention "articles" just now... Does your job involve writing articles by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">D-Dangnabbiiiit! ...Th-That's right. I'm an investigative reporter! A bona fide-up-and-comin' news journalist!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... A reporter. She may already have some information about the case. This will be my next line of questioning. ...This is where the real battle begins. I'll need to draw out even more information from her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You said that you are a reporter, Did you come here to gather news material?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">If ya wanna know that bad... Gimme some info first!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, you first! Show me what you've gathered.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Honest to Besty, I don't know what yer talkin' about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........ I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning... Maybe I should try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you present at the time the incident occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. How 'bout somma that info ya promised me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, ladies first. I insist.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I told ya, my trap's sealed shut! You ain't gettin' my info that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Huh? What's goin' on with ya? I don't get what yer sayin' at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A-Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">This is my livelihood here... Please, I'm beggin' ya.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you stick your head in too deep, you may putting yourself in danger.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...I-I'm a pro after all. A few gunshots... don't scare me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">C'mon, man! If yer gonna clam up, I'm outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there...</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Heh. I'll admit, you're dedicated to your job. However, you still have much to learn. The fact that you heard the gunshots clearly means that you were present during the incident. You must have seen something!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...B-Busted again. I jus' happened to be here coverin' the speech, and that's when it all went south... That's all, I swear. I ain't sayin' another word!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So she was here to write an article about the speech... She should still have the materials she gathered for her article. Hmm... This could be a useful clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let me try using that clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">C'mon, man! If yer gonna clam up, I'm outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there...</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you telling me that you came here to gather material and you left empty-handed? You should still have materials you collected with you!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Th-That's... Darn tootin'! I'm a pro! I collect info with my own two feet! That's why I ain't givin' it up without a fight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As the prosecutor in charge of this case, I am making a serious plea for your cooperation...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Don't you mess with me! I ain't handin' it over and that's final!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but I am just messing with you. Do you have a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Wh-What!? If yer messin' with me yer gonna be in a world of hurt! I won't give ya nuthin' no matter how much ya beg me!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I went too far. I mustn't be careless with my words.</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Please understand where I'm comin' from, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Being a reporter is a tough job... isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ah, so yer finally gettin' it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How has your job performance been?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Um. W-Well... I'm always tryin' to be the best reporter I can be. This here tape recorder... I always carry it by my side.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were too careless... There is a big problem with your statement just now!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Huh? What's goin' on with ya? I don't get what yer sayin' at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A-Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">C'mon, man! If yer gonna clam up, I'm outta here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there...</thought> When the opponent is agitated, I must calmly wait and see... But when they let their guard down, I mustn't hesitate to strike!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... If you're trying to be the best reporter that you can be... ...then it would be unnatural for you to not have collected any news materials. You recorded it on your tape recorder, didn't you? The information regarding this case...!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ugh! Doggone iiiiiit! There goes my exclusive scoop...! That's right... I have it on my tape recorder. All the information I recorded for my article is right here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Checkmate.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Th-That's amazing, Mr. Prosecutor... Before I knew it, ya done had me chatterin' like a chipmunk.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me hear what you have on the tape recorder... <thought>If I listen to the tape, I should be able to determine the exact number of gunshots...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Fine. But... I won't let ya have it for free. Other than my mentor, yer the only person to push me this far... In other words, yer gonna be my second mentor! Yup, that's how it's gonna be!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see... it's kind of like a "second home", sir!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">And I got one more request... A 24-hour exclusive interview! Please, Mr. Prosecutor! This is my first and final request as yer apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...This is difficult to accept, but unless I agree to it I won't be able to listen to the tape.</thought> 24 hours is out of the question, but I will grant you an interview after we solve this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Wh-What about bein' my second mentor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Also out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Awww... Don't be so ornery... W-Well, I guess ya take what ya get. It's all for the sake of my news scoop. Time to get the ball rollin'! Let's begin our exclusive coverage!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, Ms. Swift... Please begin the playback of the tape recorder for me.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">My dear friends! There is a reason for my visit! A few days ago, a smuggling ring that has long plagued my nation was exposed and crushed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... This was the president's speech.</line>
<line speaker="???">The president passionately addresses the crowd! He's deflatin' the rumors flyin' 'round about a recent decline in his approval ratings!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">This was my own commentary. I tried to create the feelin' of actually bein' there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="???">...According to the schedule, there's a meeting after this...? You seem quite pleased that the Yatagarasu Incident has been resolved... Well, of course... It's a great honor for us as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whose voice is this?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Those're from the folks standin' in front of me. I reckon it was two older men. They kept on whisperin' to each other.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Where have I heard this voice before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh! The gunshot's comin' up!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">The president raises his fist in the air! The atmosphere is boilin' to a fever pitch!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">However, The battle is still not over! I declare here, and now! The Hammer of Justice shall be brought down upon all evil!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Wh-What in tarnation!? Whoa whoa whoa whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that... two shots were fired.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">And what do ya reckon?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's quite simple, really. Using the bullet's trajectory... we can deduce its flight path. Two shots were fired. One bullet hit the president. That means the other shot left a hole in the flag and punctured the balloon. Do you understand now? The location of the perpetrator who fired the gun... The bullet that stuck both the flag and the balloon was fired from here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Over here. That's right, the perpetrator definitely fired his gun from here!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Um... Would them bullets really hit their mark from there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's Mr. Edgeworth we're talking about here, pal! I'm sure he has amazing Logic to back it up! And when it's all said and done, he'll show you another one of his brilliant deductions! I'm looking forward to it myself! Come on, Mr. Edgeworth! ...Do your thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait a second... Let me think. Hm...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor, don't push yerself too hard, now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Argh! <thought>Th-This isn't the right spot... Two shots were fired, I'm certain of it. If I follow the direct path of the bullets... The point where the two paths cross will reveal the location of the shooter!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By connecting the bullet marks from the flag and the balloon... ...we learn the bullet's trajectory. It's likely that the bullet was fired from the left side of the audience area.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Just what I'd expect from Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. I would like to investigate the left side of the audience area.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir... Wait, you mean we have to move all these people?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. There's no time. We could be losing vital evidence for every second we let slip by. We must hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Mentor Number 2! ...Hey, Mentor Number 2!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift. I assume you are addressing me?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Of course, Mentor Number 2. This is my time to shine! I'm an expert at crowd dispersal! Light the torches, release the hounds, and run 'em down!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I appreciate your help, but please do not use those methods. Also, please stop addressing me as your mentor. I never agreed to that position.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I hear ya. I'll try to keep that in mind, Mentor... I mean Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh*...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! We're ready to begin the investigation, sir! Ms. Swift here was all over the crowd helping us round 'em up, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Heh, this ain't nothin' compared to my first mentor's mob wrangling skills!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She seems to be used to this sort of thing...</thought> However, Ms. Swift. All that running around seems to have caused your clothes... ...to be covered with mud. I'll take care of the cleaning bill, if you like.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Eh? Oh. Yer talkin' about my parka? Don't you worry yer fancy lil' head about it! It's reversible, so I can just flip it 'round later and it's good as new!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That won't do much for mud stains, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Well, Mr. Edgeworth. Let's restart the investigation, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The crowd has made a mess of the crime scene... I hope some traces of the criminal are still left behind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">These camera flashes have been blinding me all day, sir. The media and even these onlookers have been in a photo frenzy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a rare event for them. Just let them be.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But they're clearly taking pictures of you and me, Mr. Edgeworth. This is a violation of our publicity rights! I'm going to do something about it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Before I could stop him, he had already run off... ...Searching for cameras that took pictures of him and making the crowd angry in the process. This is a man who truly never betrays your expectations.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can press the L Button to look over information that you've collected so far, sir. By the way, Mr. Edgeworth, do you still remember my name?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I do. What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Evidence and people related to the case are recorded in the Organizer, sir. You can also use MY profile to refresh your memory of me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. I'll try it out later by pressing the R Button.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's no point in just holding on to the evidence, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Evidence should be presented. ...Obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's why each piece of evidence needs to be examined in greater detail, sir. Front to back, side to side, corner to corner! Near, far, wherever you are! You have to put the evidence through the wringer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree with everything except that last statement. You'll risk damaging the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! That's just a figure of speech. I wouldn't literally put the evidence through a wringer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You can never tell with this man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a wooden signpost. It seems to have been erected recently.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let's see... the Gourdy Museum is about 50 yards ahead. And 80 yards from here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Detective? Speak up.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...80 yards from here, there's a boat rental shop.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It really hasn't been very long since I was involved in that case...</thought> That brings back memories, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir. ...It brings back memories for me, too.</line>
<line speaker="???">This is a terrible incident indeed, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...... <thought>Who is this man again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I, Winston Payne, am willing to assist as a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>H-He's a prosecutor...?</thought> Why did you come here today?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee. I accompanied the chief prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? His voice sounds like the one that I heard on the tape earlier... Was he one of the men standing in front of Ms. Swift?</thought> And where is the chief now?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The chief is a busy man. He had special permission to leave the premises.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The chief called me here, and then left by himself... I'm not completely satisfied with this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Y'all need to go through the garbage? You prosecutors got a tough job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right away, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">So it's the detective's job to go through the trash. Prosecutors don't wanna dirty their hands.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm. Let's see... I hope I find something good!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The detective seems to be a little too eager about searching through the trash...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-This is...! A winning popsicle stick!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-Sorry, sir! Let's see... Something related to the case... Hm? Look what I found, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Good work. Let's have a closer look. I'll need to view this object from various angles to uncover the truth hidden within.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Just give me the word and I'll spin the evidence round and round.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hold the R Button and use the D-Pad to rotate the object to a desired viewing angle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you want to zoom in or zoom out, I'll move the evidence for you, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the X Button to zoom in, and the Y Button to zoom out. Investigate every fine detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you find something suspicious, please let us know immediately, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Move the cursor to a spot of interest and press the X Button to investigate it.</thought> Alright. Let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a document of some sort...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Let's see... "President's Security Detail"...? These are the plans for the president's security, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It depicts the security layout.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The bodyguards' names are written on here, too! Rooke and Knightley...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? The bodyguards are not from the Republic of Zheng Fa?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It seems that the president hired a local security firm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't he use the police force of Zheng Fa?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ya wanna know the reason? That's another big scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know something about it?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I was just at the Zheng Fa embassy the other day, fixin' to get me some news material. That's when I heard... It sounds like the president's got plenty of enemies. He also don't get along too well with the top brass of the Zheng Fa police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. He doesn't even trust the people of his own country. <thought>This could be related to the assassination attempt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why would this document be in the bag?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That is strange indeed. It concerns the safety of the president. Normally, it would be under tight security...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hm? This bag... There's something else in it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-This is...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a g-gun, sir! Mr. Edgeworth! Could this bag have belonged to the...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. It is possible that the assassin may have thrown it away. <thought>It's a revolver (Six-shot revolver - Found in the trash near the audience area. A gun that is prohibited in this country.</thought>. For something like this to appear in a place like this... Is this the work of a professional assassin?)</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He must've used that document to carry out the crime, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This revolver... I will need to take a closer look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... a laser pointer.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's an implement you attach to a gun to help you aim with a laser, sir! Just press here and... It's firing a red laser, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did the assassin use this laser pointer (Laser pointer - A device that aims with a red laser. Found attached to the assassination gun.</thought> to target the president?)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... a laser pointer.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's an implement you attach to a gun to help you aim with a laser, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm. Even though it does make it easier to aim... The drawback is that you're more easily detected.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, if you were the target, you probably wouldn't detect a thing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because I'm wearing red... Is that what you're saying...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh? H-How did you know, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gun fired two bullets? That matches the number of gunshots heard...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This must be the murder weapon, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This would be the grip. I've held the grip of several guns in the past, but... ...it's never been a very pleasant feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This bag has provided us with lots of useful evidence! Dumpster diving really paid off, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good work, Detective. I have one more request. Please tell the forensics team to check the gun and the bag for fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If we can obtain fingerprints, it would be a huge breakthrough in our investigation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've got the results back, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That was fast...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course! I made them double-time it. Unfortunately, we couldn't find any fingerprints, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you certain you did a thorough search?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course, we combed every inch! We even took out the bullets and examined them, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As expected, this won't be easy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the trash can where we found the bag that contained the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That gun... I wonder if it was thrown away by the assassin. I'm impressed that the assassin properly disposed of his trash in the trash can, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why are you becoming impressed with the assassin...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a news van for the local media. The tires are stuck in the mud.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That reminds me of the time when I helped push your car out of the mud, sir. You just drove off and left me behind. I was totally bummed out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>N-Now that he mentions it, I do seem to recall something like that happening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But 15 minutes later, you did a U-turn and came back to pick me up! As expected of Mr. Edgeworth! I knew that you wouldn't forget about me, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes. Of course not. <thought>Except for those 15 minutes... Of course.</thought></line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">Oh no, the lens is cracked... What should I do... How can I fix this? The circuitry is completely exposed, and there's a crackling noise coming from inside. It's like one of those sparkler fireworks. It'd probably be best not to touch it...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You should never touch fireworks! Don't make the same mistake I did, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He sure asserted that quite strongly... <thought>This man seems distracted. Looks like I'll have to ask him later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you come here to cover the welcoming event?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">You betcha! I wouldn't have missed it for the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What time did the event start?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It started after the rain stopped pourin'. It'd been rainin' all mornin' long. The president's plane got here at 1:45 PM. Then, the president began his speech at around 2 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When did the shooting occur?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Umm. I reckon it happened sometime around 2:20 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So it occurred about 20 minutes after the speech began.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Yup! It was right then! The sound of gunshots ripped through the air! And the poor ol' president collapsed on stage! And that's what went down... on March 25th, 2:25 PM at Gourd Lake Park.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What was that all of a sudden...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh. That? I was just recordin' some notes. It's for my report. If I think of somethin' good, I take note of it right away. It ain't often ya get the chance to cover a presidential assassination. Gotta make it dramatic and heart-wrenchin'! I'm gonna write me one action-packed article!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did the president actually collapse on stage?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The bodyguards escorted him onto the plane, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ah. Y'all have ta pardon my embellishments. Sometimes I get a little carried away...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems that it would be best if I took this woman's testimony with a grain of salt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">W-Well now... I guess ya could call me a reporter. It sure sounds different when somebody else calls ya that. Reporter Nicole Swift. Yup, it's got a nice ring to it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Just to be clear, you are an actual reporter, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">In trainin'.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha...!? Then how many articles have you written so far?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh, ya mean like actual published works? None at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yet... You still call yourself a reporter?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Well, this case is gonna put me in the spotlight. I done captured the whole entire speech perfectly! No bloopers at all! With this mic! And this tape recorder! I'm gonna be a shinin' star in the broadcast world, just like my mentor!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">So Mr. Prosecutor, how do ya know my mentor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are the one who brought up the subject.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Umm... I may or may not have said somethin' like that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As a reporter, you should take responsability for your words!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">But my mentor always tells me... "A reporter should always leak information freely."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What a public nuisance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">She told me that when she gave me this here tape recorder. "Get out there and record all the scandalous scoops ya can get."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you create smoke where there is no fire. I amazed you call yourself a reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I don't start the fires. ...I just fan out the smoke. As far and wide as I can.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't that what I just said!?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">This here's the famous...! Why ain'tcha wearin' it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's just not my custom.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I see them attorneys wearin' 'em all the time... Whaddaya have to say about that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No comment.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hmm. The difference between public prosecutors and private attorneys becomes clear as day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd appreciate it if you didn't fabricate such false comments!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I can't believe I got this scoop because of this here article. The newspaper sure is amazin'.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You came here because you read this article.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">That's right! I started preparin' for this two days ago!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So the news media gets its news from other outlets now?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Say what ya will, but I'm workin' my tail off here. Of course, it'd be a different story if Mr. Prosecutor would actually cooperate with me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What a shameless reporter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Speakin' of which, you ain't given me my interview yet. Well, let's begin. What's yer favorite food, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's tea, pal. He even has his own original blend in the office.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh ho ho... Mr. Prosecutor's quite the bourgeois, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Who are you calling bourgeois? And why are you answering her questions, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's alright, sir! I know pretty much all there is to know about you.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ooh! What else can ya tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's dangerous to leave these two alone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">President Huang's got lots of enemies, both inside and outside his country. It ain't a question of whether or not someone would shoot him, but where someone'd shoot him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Don't tell me that you came here hoping for him to get shot?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">O-Of course not! The president's an important person, right? So I reckoned if I came here, I'd get myself a little scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Covering the president's visit isn't much of a scoop, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ooh... Ya just don't get it, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">At that moment, the prosecutor presents his evidence! A faintly shinin'... shinin'... ...Umm. What'd ya just show me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Never mind. <thought>Looks like she doesn't know anything about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor, but I have no interest in doing so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Each Prosecutor's Badge is engraved with the number of its owner on the back. Hmph. Numbers. As if we're not human on the inside like everyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You are with the television crew, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">Oh. Umm. That's right, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then you must have recorded the speech. I'd like to see the footage.</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">Y-Yeah, umm, about that. That will be difficult...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What was that, pal!? It's your duty as a citizen to cooperate with the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">After the incident, the guests knocked over the TV camera in the panic. All the footage was lost...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If there was any footage left, it could've been vital evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. It's too bad, sir.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha ha! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What was that?</line>
<line speaker="???">Looks like you're in a jam, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That voice! Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Long time no see, Mr. Edgeworth! The Hero of Justice... ...Kay Faraday, is here to save the day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hero... I guess she wouldn't refer to herself as a heroine...</thought> So, have you given up on this "Great Thief" business yet?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nope, I haven't stopped. I'm just on vacation! I'm still in training to become the second Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About two weeks ago, this girl became involved in one of my cases. The mysterious phantom thief, the "Yatagarasu". The case of a gentleman thief who steals the truth for the sake of justice. This girl is the successor to that Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you need to pick a lock or untie a rope, leave it to me! But... since I'm still in training, I haven't actually stolen anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, what are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Isn't it obvious? I wanted to join in the festivities!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She does seem to have a fondness for these kind of events...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Afterwards, I thought I'd come meet up with you guys.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, we're glad to see you! You look like you've been doing well, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's been a while, Gummy! I'm glad you're well too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, you said earlier that you could help me out...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he. Please don't be surprised, Mr. Edgeworth. I took a photo that captures the exact moment of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Could you show it to us at once?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The same as usual, I see. Can't you act even a little surprised?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Yeah! That prosecutor's always in a sour mood. He even got annoyed when I called him my second mentor... Oh. By the way. I'm Nicole Swift, up n' comin' investigative reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nice to meet you, Nicole! Yeah, Mr. Edgeworth's really...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Enough idle chatter. Can you please just show us the photo?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Tsk. Fine! Here! This is a photo I took right at the moment of the gunshot! It was awful! Everyone in the audience was running in panic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This photo depicts the president and his two bodyguards. Judging from the names written on the security plan, these two must be Rooke and Knightley... Hm? What is this...?</thought> ...Thank you, Kay. This will be a very important clue.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh! Ya got that sharp look in yer eyes! Did ya find somethin', Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In this photo... There is a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">This photo...? I don't see nothin'...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you don't understand, then I'll show you. <thought>The scene captured in the photo and the evidence I have on hand... By comparing the two, I'll find the contradiction. It's time for my deductive skills to come into play. First, I have to find the spot that holds the contradiction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Once I've found the contradiction, I press the X Button with conviction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Then, I Present the evidence that contradicts the spot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This spot clearly contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't really see the connection, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You still don't see? There's definitely a... contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth... when you're wrong, you should just admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I couldn't have been wrong! Just wait, I'll show you proof! <thought>First, I have to find the spot that holds the contradiction...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift. This newspaper contains a photograph of the president. I'd like you to compare it with the photo Kay took at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hm? Whaddaya mean... ......Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right... There's something on the president's forehead that wasn't there before.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Is that... a mole?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mm-hmm, it certainly looks like a red mole <thought>Red mole - In the photo of the incident, a red dot can be seen on the president's forehead.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's foolish. It's hard to believe that a mole would pop out of thin air like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe a bug bit him, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">That all? I thought you were onto somethin', turns out it's just an itty bitty bug bite. You were talkin' with such a serious look on yer face, I was gettin' all excited.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. The way to the truth... ...always begins with small contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ooh! That's a great way of puttin' it! I'll be usin' that for my article!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A revolver, huh. Hmm... It's a nice gun, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you also use a revolver, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Spinning the cylinder and blowing smoke from the barrel... It's every man's dream! Isn't that right, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You've been watching too many detective dramas.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm glad we could meet again. It's going to get lively around here once more, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're mistaking lively with noisy.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha! You're such a shy guy, Mr. Edgeworth! It's OK, sir! Nobody will laugh if you say you're happy to see her again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's not that I'm not happy. <thought>It's a complicated feeling, in my ways.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there any way to recover the lost footage?</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">Y-Yeah, umm, about that. That will be difficult...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why's that, pal? Couldn't you just repair the footage piece-by-piece?</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">But... the tape was crushed to pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">C-Crushed to pieces...</line>
<line speaker="TV Crew">That's right. The guests in the audience were stepping all over the tape! Argh! The director's gonna kill me!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you think? Just like a real hero, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. A new truth has come to light thanks to you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm trying to live up to the reputation as the second generation Yatagarasu. ...Still, I hoped to show you more of what I learned from my training.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In regards to your training, please tell me you didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't worry! I didn't steal anything!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'll still taking a break from being a Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's... nice to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I want to hurry up and fight for the truth, just like my father. But I'm still in training... And I haven't found any members to join me yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The Yatagarasu, huh... She said that she wanted to recruit some girls to join her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">There just aren't that many girls out there who want to become a Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, I would hope not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">This photo of the president and the president from the newspaper... No matter how you look at it, the "red mole" is a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's hard to believe that the red mole just appeared out of thin air.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I got it! Let me steal a line that you said earlier! "The way to the truth... Always begins with small thefts."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not what I said at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Stealing is an art. I rearranged it to fit my style!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Your version seems to have lost the true essence of my words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's a really cool badge. It depicts a blazing sun on top of winter frost, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It symbolizes the severity of the criminal justice system.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">My badge has symbols too! U-Uh Umm... It symbolizes Love and Justice and Peace and Courage and Honor and Kindness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What happened to "Truth"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">The Steel Samurai is cool, but I like the Jammin' Ninja best! Armed with only his singing voice, he journeys his way through the warring Muromachi Age... He's so awesome.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If I recall, the protagonist isn't your ordinary ninja.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right. He uses his Ninja Songs to propel himself towards stardom! Maybe I should give it a try as the "Singin' Great Thief".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would make her easier to catch... I guess I shouldn't stop her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">A red mole, huh? Hmm... I've got it! Looks like someone got out the good ol' sharpie while the president was asleep...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, this photo has no connection to our case.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, no! There's definitely a connection! After all, I'm the one who stole the photo!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I believe that even a Great Thief has rights. For example, we have the right to choose what we want to steal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I guess she doesn't consider this valuable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Well, that's an amateur for ya. A news photo ain't supposed to be a commemorative photo.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it actually is a commemorative photo.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Even so! A photo needs to be more DRAMATIC! The president's been struck down by the assassin's bullet! I-It's terrible... The crowd's in chaos!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I will ask you one more time, just to be certain. Did you really see the president go down?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Yer a stubborn one ain'tcha? That was just an example. He didn't really go down.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stop talking in such a confusing manner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've solved the mystery of the red mole.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh? You mean it's not a bug bite, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's nothing like a bug bite or an itchy rash. This is the light from a laser pointer.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean a gun was aimed at the president's forehead!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And right after that, the second gunshot was heard...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's certainly more than just an itch, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. I'm concerned for the president's well-being... <thought>It's become more and more likely that this gun was the weapon used in the attack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why did the criminal use a laser pointer, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right! They would've had a beam of light shining from their heads! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Way too conspicuous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And if you follow the path of the laser, you will find out who fired the shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's not good at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, yeah! I also took some other photos. Maybe the light from the laser pointer was captured on those!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's a long shot, but there may be a chance...</thought> Kay, could you show us those photos?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Coming right up! Firstly, the photo from before the incident...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your face is taking up most of the frame.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh. I wanted to get a "two-shot" of me and the president... This was taken a little before the gunshots. And here's the one I showed you before. This was right after the first gunshot. And immediately after that, a second gunshot rang out! And then...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this? You can't really see much in this photo...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">After that last photo, one of the running guests knocked me down. It looks like the shutter clicked just then.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This doesn't look too helpful, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, those were all the photos I took.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'd like to examine these in a bit more detail.</thought> Investigate which photo?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the light from the laser pointer be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the light from the laser pointer be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the light from the laser pointer be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I found it...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look just in front of this person in the red hood.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! There!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. That's probably the light from the laser pointer.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-Then! That red hooded person!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would be... the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We did it! It's all thanks to me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. As expected, the Great Thief has stolen the Truth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he he.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps the criminal can also be seen in the other photos. Let me examine these photos one more time. Investigate which photo?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the red hooded assassin be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From this point, it is clear which way the assassin ran!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Umm. This is hard for me to say, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it? This isn't like you. Say it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir! I have no clue what you're talking about, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No clue?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Absolutely no clue, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It seems I was mistaken. Let me try a different spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the red hooded assassin be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From this point, it is clear which way the assassin ran!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Umm. This is hard for me to say, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it? This isn't like you. Say it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir! I have no clue what you're talking about, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No clue?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Absolutely no clue, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It seems I was mistaken. Let me try a different spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where can the red hooded assassin be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From this point, it is clear which way the assassin ran!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Umm. This is hard for me to say, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it? This isn't like you. Say it clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir! I have no clue what you're talking about, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No clue?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Absolutely no clue, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It seems I was mistaken. Let me try a different spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! There!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The "red hooded"... assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like they're escaping in the panic, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We can see the direction they ran in...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! The Samurai Dog banner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. The assassin escaped towards the right side of the audience area. Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Got it, sir! We'll investigate the right side of the audience area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm counting on you. <thought>The red hooded assassin... Since the park was sealed off, there's nowhere they could've run to... If we follow their trail, we'll definitely catch them!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, then. Let's continue with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We'll definitely find some traces of the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At the crime scene, there will be some spots that need further investigation, sir. You can Examine these spots in greater detail.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, sometimes simply examining them may not have the investigation along.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! If there's a difference between the crime scene and what's in your Organizer... ...it's time for your Deduction to come into play! Present evidence to point out the contradiction, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the X Button to Present evidence. That's how I begin my deductive reasoning...</thought> In doing so, the truth will naturally reveal itself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A red hood will really stand out, sir! It's almost like he's asking to be arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, that's not enough. <thought>I need to search for additional identifying factors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In other words... There'd be a huge backlash! "You can't arrest someone just for wearing a red hood!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective. You've been watching too much...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Kids' Masterpiece Theater, sir. I like the quizzes at the end of the show...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, getting back to the trail of the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh... Don't ignore me, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">♪ Red raincoat style! Red Red Red Red ♬ Red raincoat style ♪</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was that all of a sudden!? Why are you singing that weird song!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a catchy song I heard on the internet. Seeing that red raincoat reminded me of it, sir. Ehhhhhh ♬ Sexy Raincoat ♪ Red raincoat style ♪</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And now he's doing a strange dance...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the trash can where we found the bag that contained the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The gun has a laser pointer attached to it, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. He probably used it to target the president.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The suspect must be adept at using laser pointers... Eureka! He must be a school teacher, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, college professors and the police chief should also be added to the list of suspects.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... That could be a problem, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There was already a problem when you first brought it up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a hand from the Steel Samurai balloon... Or rather, it's a fan.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Mr. Edgeworth! There could be a dying message, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's nonsense. The president isn't dead.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, I meant from the Steel Samurai. He could have left one behind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Listen up, Detective. That Steel Samurai is a balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You've said it before yourself, "Every piece of evidence had a story to tell," sir! I'm certain that this Steel Samurai has one to tell too...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That wasn't what I meant... In any case, there's no new information here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can see the sky reflected in the puddle... ...after the rain stopped.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Was that a haiku, sir? You're quite a poet, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was not my intention... Well then, how would you describe it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How's this, sir? The rain leaves behind a puddle. Just like Mr. Edgeworth's logic leaves me in a muddle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Not bad for a poet... Not good for a detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a cheap looking food stall made out of plywood. They're selling Samurai Dogs...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I've got 2 dollars, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Am I imagining things, or are you suggesting we take a snack break during our investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Of course not, sir! I just thought... Umm... It could help us with our investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'll buy you a box when we're finished with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry, sir! I... huh, what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's with that look on your face? Is there a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No... That was just, unexpected, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a red button <thought>Red button - Found near the stand. Appears to have been ripped off from something.</thought>, sir. Could this be...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This could be related to the person in the red hood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could this button be related to the person in the red hood?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A red hood, a red button, a red balloon and Mr. Edgeworth... This case is full of red things, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold it. Why am I included in the list?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, your clothes are red... Ah! Maybe the person in the red hood is an acquaintance of yours, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you truly believe that, then I suggest that you should carefully think this through one more time. ...Especially in regards to your next salary assessment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're selling Cherry Cherry Samurai Dogs. I don't believe I've ever had a cherry dog.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've always wondered, what do cherry dogs taste like, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They use cherries instead of a hotdog... so it probably tastes like cherries.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But why do they call it a cherry dog if there's no hotdog in it, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... Hmm. You have a point...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The truth about cherry dogs...! It remains a mystery, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's something red down here...</thought> Detective Gumshoe. Please check underneath the food stall.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something's stuck down here. Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a red raincoat...! Could this be!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The assassin's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that he got rid of his raincoat before he ran away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This sleeve <thought>Raincoat sleeve - The right sleeve is turned inside out, and a button is missing.</thought>... it's inside out. It's also missing a button.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The left sleeve... There doesn't appear to be anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not turned inside out, and the button is still tightly in place.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even though it was thrown away, it looks a bit too clean...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are toy rifles lined up neatly on top of the counter.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh! It's a shooting booth, sir. I hate to brag, but I'm actually pretty good at these!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought you said that you weren't good with guns?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not that I'm not good with them. I just... don't like guns, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Normally, that's what you would call "not being good with guns."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The flag from the shooting booth is lying on the ground. The crowd probably knocked it over. Judging from all the footprints on the flag... There must have been quite a panic.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Do you know where you can buy these flags, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you want to know? Are you going to write Gumshoe on the flag and carry it around with you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gyaaah! How did you know, sir!? Don't tell me... Mr. Edgeworth, did you just read my mind, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I meant it as a joke, though. For him to actually have thought that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like the fallen button came from the raincoat. It probably fell off when the assassin took off the raincoat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you look closely, you can see that the right sleeve is inside out,</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears they took it off in a hurry... The button was probably torn off. After shooting the president, the assassin disposed of the gun and the bag in the garbage bin. Then, during the panic, they moved from the left to the right side of the audience area. The bullet's trajectory led us to suspect someone who was on the left side of the audience area. The assassin then took off the raincoat and hid it under the stand... The assassin was in a hurry to remove the raincoat. That's why there are signs that the right sleeve was hastily removed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It also explains why the button was torn off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case... Why is the left sleeve not in the same state?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! That sleeve isn't inside out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the contrary, the button is still tightly fixed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What do you mean, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To find the answer... we must examine this raincoat in detail.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This raincoat is a brilliant bright red! Just looking at it makes me want to charge at it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Like in a bullfight...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! My heart is always fired up like a bull!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'd say you're just simple-minded...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The right sleeve is turned inside-out.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And you can see where the button's been torn off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. This raincoat must have been removed in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to investigate the inside of this raincoat. Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... a bloodstain! Judging by the location... This is most likely the assassin's own blood.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, we're looking for someone who's injured, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not just any injury, Detective. An injury on their left arm.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Wh-What do you mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The criminal was in a hurry to take off their coat. That's why the right sleeve is inside out. On the other hand, the left sleeve remained unchanged. How did this difference arise? Quite simply, the assassin couldn't get his arm through the left sleeve... If you think of it like that, it all starts to add up. Furthermore, a bloodstain was found on the left side of the raincoat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see! He couldn't get his injured arm to fit through the sleeve!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, indeed. I'd say the possibility is quite high.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's all coming together...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, I want you to pull our assassin out of the crowd!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The red raincoat is stained with blood... We should be able to tell who its owner is just by looking at them.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger that, sir! Someone with an injured left arm, right?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">You must have a good head on yer shoulders if ya did see through me, Mr. Prosecutor! Findin' the assassin with only that much evidence shouldn't be a problem at all!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's our Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>With everyone in the park sealed in, the assassin should still be within the crowd. I'm counting on you, Detective Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! We found a suspicious person in that condition, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's gotta be the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. We haven't proven that this person is the assassin yet. For now, this is just a "person of interest". Don't jump to conclusions.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Got it! I'll control myself!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's no doubt that this is the guy who targeted the president, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It takes a daring person to target someone's life in front of an audience...</thought> Detective. Bring him here... courteously.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Hey, you guys! Bring him here!</line>
<line speaker="???">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's not carrying an umbrella, and his left arm is bandaged...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You there! State your name!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">My name is... John Doe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">John Doe...? <thought>That's... an unusual name.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">That is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man... Have I seen him somewhere before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You know my name?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...Yes. I have been observing your investigation. ...May I ask why you have called me here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We are searching for the assassin who attempted to murder the president. ...Do you recognize this red raincoat?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I'm terribly sorry... but I'm afraid I do not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that this raincoat belongs to the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Oh my. That is terrible indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This person should also have a severe injury on the left side of their body... Precisely like yours...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...I have no relation to this.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">A stare down! Mano-a-mano! It's like they're firin' laser beams outta their eyes! ...So, what happens next?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Obviously, a confrontation, pal! A battle of wits between two gentleman!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Should I hear his explanation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A witness might lie or misunderstand. If you find a contradiction in their statement, you Present evidence, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Press the R Button to look at the Organizer, and the X Button to Present.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">And if you don't find a contradiction, whaddaya do then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At those times, you Press the witness for more details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To Press, press the L Button.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All right, sir. Could you give us a demonstration, please!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Go Mr. Prosecutor! You are America's best!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She just won't quit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. How long do you plan on talking with a civilian?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">AAAAAAAH! Sorry about that, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">What, hey! That's mean! At least let me learn something!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I understand that the person in the raincoat is suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't wear a raincoat... That's your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes. Not everyone uses a raincoat for protection against the rain. I am an umbrella person after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm definitely a raincoat person. Umbrellas will hinder your movement!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Well, I don't use raincoats or umbrellas. Come rain or snow, all I need is my trusty parka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This wasn't what I wanted to talk about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I hope you understand. I am not the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, leaving a testimony unexamined goes against my principles.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">How troublesome. I am but a simple ice cream salesman... Oops. Please excuse me. In the panic earlier, my wound seems to have reopened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's no mistaking that the owner of this raincoat is the assassin. Furthermore, the owner has an injured left arm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Doe, I shall reveal your true colors for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I understand that the person in the raincoat is suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you admit that the person in the red raincoat is suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes. I have been watching your investigation from the audience seating. An "assassin"... How dreadful.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">However, that doesn't mean that he was injured. I don't suppose you have proof?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What if I had evidence to prove that he was injured?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">You certainly seem confident. ...I expected no less of you, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... You know of me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's because you're famous, sir! Maybe he read about you in the newspaper?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...I have been observing your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is clearly suspicious. If I expose his lies, I should be able to uncover the assassin's true identity!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Doe">Clearly, my left arm is injured, but I can still use my right arm.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That looks quite severe. When did you suffer that injury?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...A short while ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's it?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Even preparing a single ice cream cone is now a difficult task. Due to the injury, I could not hold an umbrella with my left hand.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">When it was raining, I used an umbrella. I have no need for a raincoat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From what I can see, you don't seem to be carrying an umbrella. I'm sure you're well aware, that the rain stopped just before the incident occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I do remember. Afterwards the number of spectators swelled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It hasn't even been an hour since then. Are you saying you lost it in only a matter of minutes!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes... Exactly. Having your umbrella stolen in that crowd wouldn't have taken more than that, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah... That's... <thought>He has a point, but...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">The fact is, I had an umbrella when it was raining.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess it'd be inevitable to lose an umbrella in the panic, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you also intend to say it was inevitable his wound just happened to open?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So then... it wasn't?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All we know is, the assassin's left arm is injured. Mr. Doe has such an injury. His left arm is even bleeding.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Very suspicious, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The problem is, how to link this fact to Mr. Doe. I should use the R Button to open up the Organizer and review the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Doe. You seem to be a very cautious person. However, today seems to be different. Because you left this behind.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">You must be mistaken. That does not belong to me. Or perhaps... you have evidence that proves otherwise?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Doe. Is your injury alright? The wound seems to have opened.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Indeed. It is... quite troublesome.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'm sure it is. You have my deepest sympathies. After all, you would have escaped had your wounds not opened up.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no mistaking that the one who wore this raincoat was injured. And I can prove that person was you. With this...!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the inside of this raincoat, there is a small bloodstain. It's the blood of the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Attacking the president is a serious crime, pal! You'll cause an international incident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No matter how long you keep silent, your true nature will soon come to light. A blood test will settle this. The blood from the raincoat, and the blood from your bandaged arm...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have all the evidence I need. Why don't you just admit it? You're the assassin who attacked the president!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...I am not the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't know when to give up. If this was a game of chess... ...you would have been checkmated a long time ago. Admit your defeat gracefully!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He seems completely unfazed...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I suppose I have no choice. I'll admit it. Indeed, the raincoat is mine.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He confessed, sir! Arrest him! Arrest him!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...However, that does not mean I shot the president.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's that, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Prosecutor Edgeworth. All you have proven is that I wore the raincoat. What sort of crime is that?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I am no assassin. I'm just a simple ice cream salesman.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Are you satisfied this time?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">His story's getting fisher by the minute! He's really suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">G-Glaring at me won't help! We've got evidence! Here, look at this guy in the red raincoat! That's gotta be the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...I see. That is certainly not me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Prosecutor Edgeworth. Please consider this carefully. Was I really the only one who wore a red raincoat?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Whether he was or not, the person in the photo can only be Mr. Doe. But, why? This man's self-confidence... and intensity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I am no assassin. I'm just a simple ice cream salesman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As an ice cream salesman, you must know quite a bit. About ice cream...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">But of course. Ask me anything you wish. </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........ <thought>C-Curses...! I don't know anything about ice cream!</thought> Hm. So, um... What's the most important thing about making ice cream?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">The most important thing about making ice cream is honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Honor... To make ice cream?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Without honor, ice cream is nothing more than sweet ice. Do you understand? I am just a simple ice cream salesman.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">All I did was put on that red raincoat and listen to the president's speech.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you use a raincoat instead of an umbrella?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Is it strange to wear a raincoat on a rainy day?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's strange to purposely wear a raincoat when you can't get your arm into it.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">If both my hands were occupied, I wouldn't be able to serve ice cream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't you mention that in your testimony earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I'm terribly sorry. It must have slipped my mind. After all, I had just gone through all that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All that...?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">The shooting of the president, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It surprised me to see the bodyguards take action just before the gunshot rang out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the bodyguards reacted before the gunshot went off?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes. The bodyguards moved first. The one on the left side of the stage, in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw it all quite clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...I have good eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The names are written on the upper left of the security plan...</thought> The bodyguard on the left side would be... Mr. Rooke?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">That is correct. A Mr. Ethan Rooke, I believe. Perhaps he noticed the light from the laser pointer? That man is no ordinary individual.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>From their actions, I don't believe that the bodyguards were amateurs. This man isn't an ordinary individual either.</thought> Please add that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">As you wish...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The man on the left side of the stage was exceptionally quick. A Mr. Ethan Rooke, as I recall."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the bodyguards reacted before the gunshot went off?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">There's no mistake. I have good eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About that... you appear to be wearing a monocle?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">If I couldn't see the ice cream, I'd be a poor ice cream salesman. I wear it to ensure I deliver the best quality ice cream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've heard all that I can... Any further arguing on this subject is pointless.</thought> Back to what you said before. Of the two bodyguards, which one made the first move?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">The man on the left side of the stage was exceptionally quick. A Mr. Ethan Rooke, as I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the bodyguard on the left was faster?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">He reacted in just an instant. His response time was superb. I believe his name was Ethan Rooke.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... He had plenty of time to react.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...Not necessarily.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>His expression never changes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Doe">Everyone in the audience immediately tried to escape, creating a state of panic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But you yourself did not run?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">No, I did not.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aha! What were you doing then?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Amidst the panic, someone gave my wound a big wallop. I was in terrible pain... I felt like sparks would shoot out of my eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... in reality, no sparks came out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Sparks don't come out of people's eyes, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person who wore the red raincoat is the assassin. That's very clear from the photo. However...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Doe is saying that person wasn't him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's just some story he made up, sir! Rip off his disguise! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. In any case, I need to start exposing his lies.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's right! And in order to do that, we should press him for more details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems you aren't just a simple ice cream salesman after all.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...You think too highly of me. Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why would a simple ice cream salesman... ...know the name of the president's bodyguard?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...The name of the bodyguard? Surely you jest. Didn't you say their names just a moment ago? Mr. Knightley and Mr. Rooke... Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a diagram of the security plans. We learnt their names from this. However, please look. Only their surnames are written here.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You distinctly said Ethan Rooke. How did you know his full name when we did not?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's pretty weird, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you know his name? Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...That was merely a slip of the tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's true! This guy is the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Young lady. You're being a little hasty. The reason I knew his name is quite simple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I am an acquaintance of Mr. Rooke's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">He and I have a bit of a connection. His is a name that I will never forget.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! He's just telling a big fat lie!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">This is not a lie. I am just a simple ice cream salesman... ...and an acquaintance of Ethan Rooke's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, let's just ask Rooke himself about this. Whether or not he's acquainted with this dubious ice cream salesman...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">As you wish. However, that may prove difficult now. He is currently busy with the president's security, after all. Besides, even if I am not an acquaintance of Mr. Rooke's... ...does that prove that I fired the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you aren't the assassin, then why did you remove your raincoat!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It was a little hot. And the rain had stopped. I wanted to air out the wound. Is there a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Urgh... I just can't seem to corner him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Edgeworth! What are you doing! Hurry up and arrest him! That man's so suspicious, I'd even arrest him myself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arrest him without evidence? How could I do such a thing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on! Mr. Edgeworth! Can't you do something!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Breaking News! The criminal is on the verge of escaping the prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Oh dear... They're already treating me like a criminal. I understand. Since I've been suspected this far, it seems I will have to tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The truth? <thought>What is he up to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I saw... another person wearing a red hood...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Surely, that was the person who was in the photo. I first noticed him right before the speech when it was still raining... He caught my eye because his raincoat was the same color as mine. In his hand I saw a laser pointer with the light aimed directly at the president.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It can't be...! There was another person wearing a red hood?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I knew that if I wore the red raincoat, I'd be mistaken for the assassin. That is why I took off the raincoat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You saw an assassin wearing the same color hood as yours? Hmph. Wouldn't that be a nice coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">That's what I expected you would say, which is why I did not testify as such. Prosecutors and the police are a suspicious lot. I knew that nobody would believe me... At the moment of the incident, the assassin was very close to the prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Prosecutor? I only arrived after the incident...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Not you, Prosecutor Edgeworth. That prosecutor over there.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh? M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes. You should be visible in that photo. Here. Right in front of the person in the red hood.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That's me alright... What's your point?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's this man driving at?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">I have been observing your investigation this entire time, Prosecutor Edgeworth. And I have noticed something strange.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something strange?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Hmm. It seems you still haven't noticed this contradiction yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A contradiction...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In this photo the people who can be seen are the chief, Mr. Payne, and the assassin... ...I don't see anything strange!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Please think back carefully. About that circumstances during the president's speech. I believe you are holding the evidence that contradicts this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Do I have evidence that contradicts this photo?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Honestly, I'm not sure, but... I'll present this!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-Mr. Edgeworth! Is it really OK to present evidence you're not sure about!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In times like this, maybe you should hold back, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... Y-Yes. That's right. I didn't mean to go this far...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It's a shame, but you should just accept your mistake and try again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrgh...! <thought>Not good... The photo shows the chief, Mr. Payne, and the person in the red hood. And this was taken during the president's speech. ...I should think this over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It can't be...! <thought>There's a contradiction between the photo and the tape!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">It seems you've noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a person missing from this photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Wh-Who is it?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Yes... It's rather strange. Someone who should be there, but is not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person who should be in this photo is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...this person, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...Mr. Detective. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I... uh... Just what I expected from Mr. Edgeworth! R-Right, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-M-M-M-Me? Errrr... That's... Just what I expected from Mr. Edgeworth! Right, Mr. Doe?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">In a sense, it's just what I expected. ...Right, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrrrrghhh...! <thought>The people in the photo and the evidence from before... I have to consider both of them to uncover the truth. The one who must be here is...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Ms. Swift?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">..........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why would you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Payne's voice was recorded on Ms. Swift's tape. He was whispering quietly with the chief prosecutor...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Those're from the folks standin' in front of me. I reckon it was two older men. They kept on whisperin' to each other.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Ms. Swift was near Mr. Payne when she recorded the speech.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! But she isn't anywhere in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">That is correct. ...Now, Mr. Prosecutor... Who is the one you should be pursuing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ngh...!</thought> Nicole Swift. Would you mind giving us your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...C'mon. It feels weird when you talk all formal like that. It's fine. I ain't got nothin' to hide.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It ain't like I stayed in one spot while I was recording.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ms. Swift's tape recorded a conversation between my colleagues... Mr. Payne and the chief prosecutor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why would Nicole be lying? That... would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It'd mean Nicole Swift is the assassin, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Y'all gotta be kiddin' me. I ain't done nothin' like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Be that as it may, however, there is a contradiction in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">H-Huh... I don't reckon so, no sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears I must reveal this contradiction with evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It ain't like I stayed in one spot while I was recording.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were moving around while you were recording... Why were you doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">H-Huh? Whaddaya mean "why"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surely when recording a speech, it is best to remain still.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Th-That's... Well, y'know the importance of coverin' a story from every angle? I wanted to convey the livin', breathin' event in print... Yesiree! You betcha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you were moving around, I doubt your tape would have picked up anything coherent!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">W-Well, it's like I done said!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I was movin' around the audience area. Shufflin' here and there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here and there... Could you be more specific? Such as the side you were on?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">When I say "here and there" it means just that... I was all about the place! You couldn't swing a dead cat in that crowd. You expect me to remember where I was?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you at least remember if it was the left or right side?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">L-Left... I reckon...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The person in the photo is also on the left side. Is this just a coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I reckon this picture must'a been snapped at a different time to my tape recordin'.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying it is logical that you can't be seen in the photo?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Yep! I was near that prosecutor when his voice got recorded... ...but I reckon this picture must'a been taken when I was far away, no doubt about it. Ain't nothin' wrong here, far as I can see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying the photo and the recording were taken at different times.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Darn tootin'! It ain't about the equipment, it's all about the timin'!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What if they were both taken at the same time... If I can prove that, her entire testimony will collapse...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">So quit makin' that scary face. It ain't what ya think.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Scary face? The way I speak to others is not intended to come across as intimidating.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Then, why don'tcha try relaxin' a bit more? You make that face when you put all that tension in yer brow. No matter what you do, always do it with a smile! Don'tcha agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am searching for the criminal who attacked the president. This is no laughing matter.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Said the prosecutor with a grin on his chin like the Cheshire Cat. End quote.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What frumious nonsense. I should show her what a real scary face looks like.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nicole seems rather aloof about all of this. Still, she just doesn't seem like the kind of person to tell harmful lies.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree that she doesn't seem like a person with ill intent, but... <thought>...if that's the case, there must be something even worse troubling her. In any case, Ms. Swift's movements have been recorded on that tape. Surely I have evidence that sheds some light on this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift. A reporter shouldn't lie.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I ain't lyin'! I'm an honest journalist!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps, but there's no denying that the photo and the recording were taken at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">That so? And what makes you say that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The truth lies in these photos. This photo could only have been taken at the same time as your recording! Which spot shows that this was taken at the same time as the recording?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here. Study this area closely. Therein lies the answer to this mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hmmm... Nope, I don't see it. Where is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here... here! Look closely. Can't you see it?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Either yer talkin' a load of hot gas, or this is one of them paranormal photos... Mr. Prosecutor, are ya tellin' me yer into yoofohs and such?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bah! <thought>She's misunderstood me. I need to have another listen to Ms. Swift's tape... It's clear the tape was recorded at the moment this photo was taken. And the evidence that shows this is hidden somewhere within the photo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can you see the president, with his fist raised in the air?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift, might we hear your tape one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Nuh-uh! You ain't gonna hear a word, way ya been treatin' me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you rather we charge you with obstruction of justice and seize it from you?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Uh... F-Fine, you win. I'm no match for you, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The question is... during which part of his speech did the president raise his fist?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">The president raises his fist in the air! The atmosphere is boilin' to a fever pitch!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aha! "Raises his fist" straight from the horse's mouth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This tape was recorded at the moment the president raised his fist overhead.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-Then that means! Nicole not being in this photo is really strange!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, but she is in the photo. Right here! The person in the red hood... it was you, Nicole Swift!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Aaaaaaaaahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're the real assassin, aren't you, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Th-Th-That ain't so! I... I... ...I ain't never worn that red raincoat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. This red raincoat in question belongs to...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person in the red hood is Ms. Swift. And so, the owner of the raincoat must be... ...Ms. Swift! It can only be you!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Ah, but does that young lady have an injury, I wonder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh...? What do you mean, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Have you forgotten about the bloodstain in the raincoat?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>H-He's right... The right sleeve with the button torn off was stained with blood...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The raincoat belongs to neither Ms. Swift nor Mr. Doe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then... whose is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Don't you get it? It can only belong to one person.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't get it. Who is that person, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait, I'd like to take back what I just said...</line>
<line speaker="Doe">If I didn't know better, I'd say this was your first day on the job, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should remember the details of Mr. Doe and Ms. Swift's testimonies. Especially the numerous things we found out about that raincoat...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The raincoat's owner is Mr. Doe. That much has been proven. You were wearing something else. A different red hood...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You mean there were two red hoodies, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Doe's last testimony was true.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But we didn't find any other red raincoats.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What Mr. Doe saw was a red hood. Not a raincoat. Ms. Swift, what was it you told us earlier about your parka...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hm? Oh, ya mean when I said I ain't worried about it gettin' all dirty? It's reversible, so all I gotta do is turn it inside out and... Aaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...As I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">M-Mr. Edgeworth! The inside of her parka is... red!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. And during the incident, she was using that side.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!? Hey, pal! What's the big idea?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Y-Yer wrong! I've been wearin' it like this the whole day...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, will you allow me to examine your parka?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Wh-What're ya expectin' to find?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We know it was raining prior to the president's speech. I believe you said earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Well, I don't use raincoats or umbrellas. Come rain or snow, all I need is my trusty parka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you really didn't turn your parka inside out... ...then the inside should be dry!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">H-Hang on a minute. I ain't back takin' off this heavy backpack and puttin' it back on again! S-S-Sorry... but can't we do this another time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You think you can fool Mr. Edgeworth with that, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Uu...Uuhn... Uuuuhn...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright then, pal! If we're really wrong, prove it. Show us the inside of the parka!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I... It wasn't me. I ain't no assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift. If you want me to believe that, then you need to cooperate with us. Will you please tell us why you wore the red side of the parka?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I'm sorry, Mr. Prosecutor. I... had my reasons, honest. I'll tell y'all everythin, jus' quit bullyin' me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Whose voice was that?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hold on a sec, It's a little too early for the endgame.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, you in the fancy suit. Haven't you been jumping the gun ever since your opening move?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man was in Kay's photo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whoa, I guess I should introduce myself first. My name is... ...Horace Knightley. The president's bodyguard. Second-in-command of his personal security unit.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Watch it, pal! That's not a toy!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whoa, my bad. She just wants to come out and play. I can't seem to help it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you have a gun if you're not a police officer!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">She's a lady of Zheng Fa. Only the president's bodyguards are authorized to use it. Anyway, back to business. I've got some news for you. There's good news and bad news. Which do you wanna hear first?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It makes no difference to me. Do as you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You sure? I'm giving you the first move. Alright. I got you. I'll start with my pawn.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It seems you enjoy chess.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You play too, Mr. Fancy-Suit?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's Edgeworth. And I do have a fondness for chess.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Is that so? Well then, Chessmaster Edgeworth, I'll start with the good news. The president's safe. Not even a scratch on him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really? That's great, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It seems that the young lady was not a murderer after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Good for you, Nicole!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">B-But I...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whoa there. Don't forget, there's still the bad news. The president is safe because his bodyguards protected him. Actually... I had nothing to do with it. It was the leader who protected him. At the cost of his own life...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would be the other bodyguard... Rooke, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah. That's right. Rooke died to protect the president...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Is that so... Rooke is dead. What a shame.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-That means... Nicole...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">It means that the little lady killed him. My brother in arms.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Th-That ain't true! I ain't a murderer...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whoa there. Pipe down, Little Miss Murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Geez. Even if we had to make a sacrifice to protect the King... It was a pretty bad move. That castling...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sacrifices and castles? What's he talking about, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're all chess terms. He's saying Rooke's life was exchanged for the president's.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This guy sure talks funny, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hm? Whaddaya want?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to examine the victim's body as soon as possible. And if it's possible, I'd like to question the president...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Sorry, but... I can't let you do that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh... What?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I got another piece of news for you. And this one's a doozy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's another piece of news?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">From here on out, this investigation will be handled by the Zheng Fa Police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's going on, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This case is under our jurisdiction! You have no right to interfere!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You're Prosecutor Edgeworth, right? The president knows about you solving the Yatagarasu case..</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm honored.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's why the chief prosecutor designated you to be in charge of the case...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems the chief prosecutor made a little appeal to the president.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">But... it looks like you're the wrong guy for the job. I didn't know you'd have this kind of reaction. ...It's the president's orders. If you oppose you'll cause an international incident. Capisce?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, little lady! Get over here! We'll continue your questioning inside the president's plane.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">N... No... I... I didn't do nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey now, don't be a baby. You scared of a little Zheng Fa justice?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Mr. Prosecutor! Please... Please help me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift? <thought>It's clear that Ms. Swift was the person in the red hood. However, that doesn't mean that the whole truth has been revealed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I really didn't do it. Please believe me...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is it really alright...? For it to end this way...?  All I see is a girl with eyes full of fear, pleading for help. Certainly not someone who's committed a heinous crime! If I stand aside now and do nothing, the truth will be lost to the darkness!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wha-!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Wh-What the... You...!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">...Silence. "What the" is an impolite way to greet someone. Your neck injury has yet to heal, and you've already forgotten?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">N-No...! Not you, not now!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">It seems you've remembered.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! What are you doing!? Cut it out, pal! You've got some nerve to do that right in front of a detective and a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">S-Stop! Stay out of this! He's out of your league!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Doe... Who on earth are you?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I am not merely a simple ice cream salesman.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">H-He's a professional assassin. His name is... ...Shelly de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Shelly de Killer!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no one in law enforcement who doesn't know the name De Killer. An assassin who will carry out any request without fail. He was once involved in a case I handled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The real assassin was you all along...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should have seen his face before in the case files... Curses...! I was careless...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A knife...? Not a gun?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...What are your demands?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Investigative authority...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Wh-What are you playing at?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Why do you want that?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Why you... You're just using the investigation to get close to the president!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">As the leader of the president's bodyguards, I won't allow it!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Now that Rooke's gone, I'm in charge!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Wh-What are you saying!? I'm totally the leader now!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Gah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's using the investigation as an excuse? Why would he go to all that trouble? What is this man thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! Wh-What should we do, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For now, we have no choice but to accept his proposal. At least we'll be able to investigate. But... Listen well, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'll use the investigation to buy us time. Meanwhile, gather up all your men. Surround the president's plane so that he can't escape...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Right! Roger that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The death of the bodyguard Ethan Rooke, and the arrival of Shelly de Killer. A new development in this case has come to light. Under Knightley's direction, the door of the president's plane was opened... After the paramedics attending Mr. Rooke left... ...we set foot inside the plane, one by one...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Who knows...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You think he'd just show himself in front of a hitman!? Ha ha ha ha! Not a chance!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right... <thought>For now, I have no choice but to obey and continue the investigation. The rest is up to Detective Gumshoe... I'm counting on you!</thought> The attempted assassination of the president became the murder of a bodyguard...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he... It looks like you could use some help, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I don't deny it, but...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">See? Exactly! If that's the case, then it can't be helped! Just leave it to the Great Thief Kay Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Right. So are you saying you can solve this case?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nope!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Said with such certainly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Instead, I'll stick to being your support! Right, let's get straight to the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>We need to buy time for the police to prepare. I'll need to draw out this investigation for as long as I can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These two guns... They're the exact same model. These guns came from Zheng Fa...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like all the bodyguards were provided with guns from Zheng Fa.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are those guns rare?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. Not particularly. They're not easy to obtain domestically, but it isn't impossible either.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What! I thought they might be a treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... It's unfortunate.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh! Mr. Edgeworth, are you talking about treasure!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not quite... If it was a rare model, it would have been easier to identify. Even evidence can become treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see! Even during your investigations, you search for treasure.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I didn't quite say that.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Okay! Let's investigate! Where's the treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And suddenly she's motivated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two bullets were fired, we know that from the number of gunshots. One hit the Steel Samurai's balloon, and the other took Rooke's life.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, didn't a bullet also hit the president's bulletproof vest?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. It doesn't match up with the number of shots... However, there is one way to solve this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">One way?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet that stole Rooke's life pierced through his body, and then hit the vest. In other words, Rooke and the President were hit by the same bullet.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I see!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...That's right. It'd be dangerous if he hadn't worn that bulletproof vest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is the president alright? Even while wearing a bulletproof vest, you can still get injured...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, the bullet's impact can still fracture your bones. But, don't worry, he's fine. The president's trained himself like no other!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe the President didn't even need a bulletproof vest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think that might be pushing it.</thought> I'd like to examine the bullet. There's a chance there may still be ballistic markings.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ballistic markings? ...What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ballistic markings are always left on a bullet. Each gun leaves a different marking. So if we examine the ballistic markings, we'll know which gun the bullet was fired from. You could say they're like a gun's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I get it now! Let's investigate right away!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I think that'd be difficult... The bullet was completely flattened when it hit the bulletproof vest. There's no way you could investigate the ballistic markings.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaa! I wanted to investigate them.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, what's up?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So there were actually two people who dressed up as the assassin in the red hood...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, it's too early to say for sure at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But there's Mr. de Killer, who's a professional assassin... And then there's Nicole, who aimed the laser pointer at the president... Ungh, this is making my head spin.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason we cannot see the truth is because something is obstructing it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I get it! If we stole that something, then we'd also be stealing the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. Well, I suppose that's one way to look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Actually, I've been studying up on investigation techniques.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, that sounds promising.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">First, Examine the evidence and information that you stole! Present the stolen evidence, Connect the stolen information... ...and a new truth will appear for you to steal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">How was that? I worked really hard at it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. You get points... for effort, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't believe a real professional assassin asked us to investigate this case for him...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I couldn't agree more. <thought>Just what is he thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">In any case, let's continue the investigation. Let's do this for Mr. Rooke's sake as well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not what I said at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Stealing is an art. I rearranged it to fit my style!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Your version seems to have lost the true essence of my words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Being an assistant sure is hard work.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't recall ever making you my assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">On the other hand, being a detective seems really fun. You're so clever, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I also don't recall ever becoming a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Anyway, if you have a good brain and a pipe in your mouth, you're a detective, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm not quite sure where you're going with this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">However! Think about the job description of an assistant! They carry organizers with them and record information. But you do that all yourself, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I shouldn't have asked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">The truth of the laser pointer was just as we thought... ...but I didn't think that I would end up stealing the truth about Mr. de Killer as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It was thanks to you that we were able to spot him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh... Next time I'll steal something even more amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay. We've gone over this many times...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I know, I know. I'll only steal the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I pray that's true, for your sake.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He was shot just below the armpit...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. The bulletproof vest didn't protect that spot.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The paramedics didn't arrive in time. Poor Mr. Rooke must have been in a lot of pain...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no time to feel sad. If we don't find the truth, he will never rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Yes! I'll do my best!!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wish I had something like this. Bulletproof thief bags or bulletproof ninja boots. Maybe Gummy can get me some.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A thief who needs those things cannot be called a Great Thief.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But the climax usually involved running through a shower of bullets, right? Without the bulletproof goods, the treasure and I would be Swiss cheese!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>C-Climax...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So this is what a bulletproof vest looks like. It's just a thick old vest... I'm kind of dissapointed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry to disappoint you, but it is a bulletproof "vest" after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But don't you think it would be cooler if it looked like samurai armor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's called a "vest" for a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you're too hung up on the name, then you'll never evolve!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Historically speaking, wouldn't that be a downgrade?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's an inflatable lifeboat with an oar sitting on top. Looks like it's ready to be used at any time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey...! There's only one oar!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well, I guess you could try to paddle with your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two gas masks lay on the table, ready to protect against poison gas attacks. The president seems to be quite fearful of assassinations.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So this is the rumored gas mask. It's my first time seeing the real thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rumored? Among the Great Thieves?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, the Jammin' Ninja! The children's program! During Princess Viola's wedding ceremony, the poison-tongued ninja Saimon Kowal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should stop listening to her so seriously. ...It never seems to pay off.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's an assortment of protective gear, from bulletproof vests to hazmat suits.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! There's even a space suit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The president seems to be very protective of himself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... what happens if he gets shot, and then gets exposed to poison gas? And then on top of all that, he gets ejected into space!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...He would probably wear everything that you see here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That... would be a sight to see.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It ain't me. I'm... just a journalist. All I wanted was a scoop, I'd never kill nobody...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, you still haven't told us why you concealed the parka from us.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">W-Well, that's... because I thought y'all would get suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that really the only reason?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ya gotta believe me, Mr. Prosecutor! I didn't do nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I won't tell you not to worry. But there's no need to be overly frightened. If you truly are innocent, I swear I will prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...Yeah! My mentor DOES believe in me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the last time, Ms. Swift: I am not your mentor.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh yeah... I'm sorry. Mr. Prosecutor, you'll always be my second mentor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's not quite what I meant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">The prosecutor presents his shiny pointy badge and asks... ..."How about a nice cold glass of water..."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I said no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">The detective adds, "Or would you prefer some grape juice instead, pal?"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">*sigh* I'm just gettin' ready for the real deal. ...My interrogation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Prosecutors don't handle the interrogations...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Guess I'll be the star of tomorrow's headlines...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be so hasty, Ms. Swift. The truth has yet to be found. It still hasn't been decided...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">"Journalist Is Truly Deadlier Than Her Pen!" "Beautiful Assassin Masquerades as Reporter!" From livin' room to diner, I'll be the talk of the town.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think those headlines are a little unlikely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">It's just as ya said, I was the one behind them recordings. But... I ain't never...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Say no more, Ms. Swift. I'm on your side.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Y-Yer right. I'll pipe down. I'm just... a useless reporter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not what I meant. Even if you do not say a word, the evidence will speak for you. The truth is out there... All we have to do is reveal it.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Mr. Prosecutor...! I reckon I'm gonna use that as my next headline!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... sure. <thought>Whatever cheers her up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Suddenly, the prosecutor points the gun at the reporter. I fear that this unlucky reporter will soon find herself at the bottom of the lake...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You shouldn't talk like that, save it for when you actually get shot.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">......... If I did get shot, I reckon I wouldn't be saying much at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. I guess you have a point.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I'm tellin' ya, I don't know this Rooke fella from Adam! The heck would I shoot him for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He took a bullet meant for the president, and now he's dead.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">W-Well, I don't know much at all 'bout the president either!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Then what did you come here for?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I told ya... I had my reasons. Don't make a poor gal spill the beans, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">This here bulletproof vest must'a caught the bullet... Look at that dent, I reckon the president must'a been hollerin' like a coyote when he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hate to keep bringing this up, but the president wasn't the one who got shot.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Just lemme say what I please. Besides... it ain't like my article's gonna get published.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's not what concerns me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Against the prosecutor's stern glare and his unrelenting questioning... ...I am at a loss for words...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I haven't even done anything yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim is Ethan Rooke. He was the president's bodyguard.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">After hearing the gunshots, he immediately evacuated the president into the plane...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He gave up his life to fulfill his duties.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Does this mean he'll receive a posthumous promotion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. There's no need for forced comments.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...How did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bodyguards don't follow that promotion system.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a square outline cut into the floor. In the gaps, you can see some hinges.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This is...! A secret entrance disguised as an escape hatch! Using a rope ladder, the president will make his great escape!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So is he going in, or is he coming out? Which one is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I just told you! It's a secret entrance for escaping, it's just disguised as an escape hatch... ...Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Looks like she confused herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The lever on that strange statue operates this trapdoor.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If we pull that lever, they would both fall down. Mr. Rooke... and Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I wasn't thinking about pulling the lever! It's not like I want to be the hero who caught De Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. Your inner voice is leaking out.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet pierced his body <thought>Bullet that pierced through - The bullet went straight through the victim's body. Where did it go?</thought>, just below his armpit. Unfortunately, he was hit in an area his bulletproof vest didn't cover...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It really seems like a well-aimed shot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cause of death was most likely blood loss. The bleeding has stopped...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That paramedics were called to treat Mr. Rooke, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid they didn't make it in time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet pierced his body, just below his armpit. The cause of death was most likely blood loss. The bleeding has stopped...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It was too late... for both him and the paramedics.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems the victim also carried a gun.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Did he try to shoot something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He may have drawn it out instinctively to return fire. <thought>We need to check to see if the gun has fired any bullets.</thought> ...Hm. It's still fully loaded. There's no evidence of any shots being fired. This gun is also from Zheng Fa, right?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Ah, yeah. We were always issued the same model revolver <thought>Rooke's gun - Hasn't fired a single shot. Manufactured in Zheng Fa. A six-shot revolver.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the victim's pistol. It hasn't fired a single shot.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like Zheng Fa's bodyguards all carried the same type of gun. Mr. Rooke... Did he try to shoot something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He may have drawn it out instinctively to return fire.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a bulletproof attaché case. It's a tool bodyguards use to protect themselves from bullets. It can be seen in Kay's photo. <thought>It seems Rooke and Knightley both had one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! That's the scene I stole on film!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You didn't do anything illegal in taking this.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Anywhere, anytime, I'm always in the mood to steal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You just wanted to use the word "steal", didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He he he. Have I been caught?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the attaché case the bodyguards were using. This tool protects them from bullets... Unfortunately, it didn't seems to help this time.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's in the photo I took... It appears that both Mr. Rooke and Mr. Knightley each had one of these.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The president is just beyond this door...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This door...! I'm getting a sense that it's challenging me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. There's no need to feel challenged by a door.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, look at how big it is! All those electronic locks! It's challenging me to unlock it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calm down and think it over. What is the purpose of a key?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What is the purpose... To unlock treasure?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right, to unlock treasure...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Was that the right answer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no need for concern. It is proceeding smoothly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All too well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ngh... I have no choice but to obey him for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">This is nuts! I'm being used to get an assassin onto the president's plane!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You're not fooling anymore! I know what you're after!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, what about the person who hired you to assassinate the president?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Ugh... Gah, agh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... Very well, let's continue the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-You mean... There's actually a license to kill?!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">D-Don't worry about it! That's one truth I don't need to steal, Mr. de Killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even a Great Thief's pride is nothing before the presence of a professional killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Err...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-Wh-What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You... Where'd you get that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If I'm not mistaken, this is the security plan for today's event.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">......... Yeah, that's right. It outlines where Rooke and I were stationed. If only I'd been in his position, then I'd be the one who...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears this man has a complex of sorts regarding Rooke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In what would can one consider a murder weapon to be honorable?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you actually believe there is...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes! Of course there is! Don't be rude, Mr. Edgeworth. Apologize to the man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-Why must I apologize!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This raincoat was found stuffed under the food stalls...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>De Killer seems to be telling the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I bet even Rooke had no idea. That he'd meet his end at the hands of that little lady!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Urgh... Wh...Why you...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes. <thought>What is this man thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Is that gonna solve the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, of course. <thought>I shouldn't provoke him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The internal and external views of the plane are being monitored by these monitors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These monitors show the cockpit and the aircraft's exterior... There doesn't seem to be anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This monitor shows what's happening in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">They've got some pretty good tech.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so? I don't know much about these types of things...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It even captures the fine lines around your eyes, Mr. Edgeworth! Oops, my bad. Those are the usual wrinkles on your forehead...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. Is that all you wanted to say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this... thing?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Oh, that's the president's precious stuffed animal. I don't really get it, but it's some kind of keepsake. Don't touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precious? That's unexpected...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, it kinda looks like there's been a break-in...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed, the area it stands on does look a bit unnatural. Hm? Are those glass shards underneath the stuffed animal? This unnatural empty space... Perhaps... Was there another monitor here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the president's precious stuffed animal. It seems to be a memento of some kind. Glass shards have fallen underneath...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are these some kind of official documents?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I know it's a bit rude, but let's take a peek inside!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. This seems to be a security plan.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! This looks like the one we found earlier in the trash can!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it does. <thought>But... what's this? Something seems out of place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It certainly is a very sketchy drawing...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um, this... seems to be a security plan document.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If so, we obtained something like this earlier. Hm? Something's different about this one. Could it be... <thought>Perhaps I should try deducing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look! There's a clear contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">........Eh? A-Ahah! The ink is smudged!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Just joking. Here, alright? The printing alignment is a bit off... Oh... I'm sorry. I need to work harder at following your lead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, it's fine. It's not your fault... <thought>I should think this over once more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this...? The details of the security plans were changed?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? ...Aah! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah. That's right. It was changed yesterday. President's orders...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why the sudden change?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Because... two days ago, De Killer attacked the president. He disguised himself as a bodyguard. Rooke was the first to notice. He had already gotten close to the president. Rooke managed to stop him just in the nick of time. Rooke grabbed his left arm and twisted it! And then he fired one bullet, square into his left arm!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What were you doing at that time, Mr. Knightley?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I-I was...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oops. Was that a touchy subject?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Shut up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So back then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Doe">Your neck injury has yet to heal, and you've already forgotten?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">N-No...! Not you, not now!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Since that day, I haven't been able to turn my head right. It sucks.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Tsk! What's so different about me and Rooke?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you remembered Rooke's name because he was highly capable...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this was the "connection" De Killer was talking about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The security arrangements were changed... ...so that De Killer would not be able to sneak in as a bodyguard again. Only the president's two most trusted subordinates would accompany him on the stage. In short, me and Rooke...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears your positions were also changed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's true! He's now on the right side!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">'Cuz I can't turn my head to the right. My position got changed to the president's left side... In other words, I was relocated to the right side of the stage <thought>Knightley's position - His head couldn't turn right. Plans were altered so he could stand on the right side.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We found a security plan among those documents. Earlier, we found something similar in the trash.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So the horse symbol is Mr. Knightley, and the castle is Mr. Rooke, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a knight and a rook. They're based off chess pieces.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm. So it's a chess game between the criminal and the bodyguards... ...and Mr. Knightley, who can't move his neck, powers up by crowning himself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, knights can't crown themselves in chess.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, when the King's in danger, he can send in additional bodyguards as reinforcements!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, you can't just send in "reinforcements" in chess.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ehhh. Well, why don't we just steal all the other side's chess pieces?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, that's now how chess is played.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's a heavy looking vest. The president's clothes must be made from some special fabric!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed. It's to protect against bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! It even does that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally. This is a bulletproof vest <thought>Bulletproof vest - Found on top of the desk. A bullet is embedded in it. Was this the president's?</thought> after all.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! So that's what it is! This is the first time I've seen one! You could've said something earlier! That really surprised me!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This is a bulletproof vest! You wear it to protect yourself from bullets! There seems to be a bullet stuck in here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What was that all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh. I've always wanted to describe things like you do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Kay. I don't talk like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A strange decoration based off some strange animal is staring at me with its strange eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's a lever on this stage! See, right here on its butt!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh! Ah! I'm sorry! I didn't mean anything by it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, then... <thought>That hatch is actually a pitfall trap.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>When a killer talks about your best interests, it would be wise to do as he says.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a collection of colorful personal security alarms. They all seem to have been used before.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The president... He sure is a nice guy! He bought these security alarms to protect his wife and kids!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then why would he leave them all here? It's obvious that they're for his own personal use.</line>
<line speaker="Kay"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn> A single person can't carry that many security alarms! Because... A person only has two hands!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That objection... is worth zero points.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A sturdy life preserver rests against the table. It is an essential lifesaving tool. I suppose this is a precaution in case someone accidentally falls into the ocean.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The ocean, huh... Hey Mr. Edgeworth, how about we go together sometime?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you want to go, just go by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aw, don't be such a party pooper! Let's go visit the ocean! Think about the hot dogs and the shaved ice. It'll be delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You just want to go to the ocean to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Next to the riot shield, there's a canary in a cage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww, it's so cute! I want one to be my partner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Partner?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Of course, it can help me open locks and do other odd jobs at the crime scene. A Great Thief should always use nature to her advantage!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've heard of canaries being used to detect poison gas. Don't tell me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This would be... a laser pointer. A device you attach to a gun to help you aim.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gun fired two bullets? That matches the number of gunshots heard... It seems this is the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This would be the grip. I've held the grip of several guns in the past, but... ...it's never been a very pleasant feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, this raincoat is really red! Almost seems like a bullfight will beak out any moment now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You know, in a real bullfight, what causes the reaction... ...is not the red colour, but the fluttering movements of the cloth.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah, so then the bull would be aiming right at you, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay... you're not in a position to say that about others...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ngh... Still no sign of Detective Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No. Not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone... involved in the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-You mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Of course, the President himself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">There's no chance in hell I'm letting that happen! You think you can just summon the President like a witness in court? Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">M-Mr. President! S-Stop it! Take it easy! Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Still nothing! Come on, Detective Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ahhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What...!? The lights!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">S-Stop! Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ahhh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay! De Killer, you...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Where... Where is he...?</thought> Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>D-Detective Gumshoe...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did... Did I pass out...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! Thank goodness you're safe!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Are you OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay! What about you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I just woke up myself. My head's throbbing a bit, but it's no big deal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! What happened to De Killer?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ms. Swift came running out of the plane... She told us De Killer made a run for it, but... ...we were too late, sir. We heard from that bodyguard... ...that the emergency lifeboat over there had been stolen. He's probably at the other side of the lake by now, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Didn't you seal off the park?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The police were all called back to surround the plane. Right now, there's no one guarding the opposite shore...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... that means he succeeded in giving us the slip.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure seems that way, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley... It seems you also had a narrow escape.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, that sucked. That punk!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Come to think of it... We found this near where you fell, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is... De Killer's calling card...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like a message from him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He always leaves this card next to his victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But you're not dead, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Perhaps this signifies something similar to a killing. <thought>Which reminds me, the last thing he said still bothers me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Seen the truth? What did he mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Yeah. It's safe now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? What was that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...The president will be making his entrance now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The president...!?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is the president of Zheng Fa, Di-Jun Huang!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">...You are?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is an honor to meet you. My name is Miles Edgeworth. I am a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I am Di-Jun Huang. I have heard of your deeds. You saved my country from a great crisis.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is he referring to the Yatagarasu case...?</thought> I was simply solving a murder, nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Such modesty. I have been observing your investigation. An astounding performance. ...Despite allowing De Killer to get away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you very much. <thought>So he was watching through the security cameras...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">...However. I regret that it ends here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">........ Heed my words! Foolish prosecutor! You should have already been informed! By Knightley...! This investigation will be handed over to the esteemed police force of Zheng Fa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now that De Killer is gone, they intend to take over the investigation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! What're you doing! And what's with that attitude!? It's because of De Killer and Mr. Edgeworth that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Enough, Detective! ...Mr. President. I cannot agree to this. Why must this investigation be handed over to your country's police?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Why... you say? Know your place! Puny prosecutor! Must I explain my actions? Nay! ...I think not! You shall hand over all the evidence you've found so far and leave this plane at once.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. Be a good boy and do as you're told.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! <thought>I... cannot resist any longer...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why? Why won't he allow me to investigate this case any further?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Now then, would you kindly take your leave? Knightley! Place the suspect under firm restraint.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I'm on it! Mr. President!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">An attempt on my life, the murder of my subordinate! Such evil! Such sin!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I... I! I didn't kill nobody! I swear...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Shut your trap, lady.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Uhn... Uhn...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You dare question me! You dare stain this world with deceit! Should we pardon this sin? Nay! Absolutely not! It is most unforgivable! My reasons being...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's no mistake. The president is hiding something. If I turn back now, the truth will be lost forever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Is there nothing you can do?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........ <thought>I remember... The countless times I've faced this dilemma in the courtroom. The lies of the witness. The rebuttals of the defense. I did not always have evidence to counter them... Nonetheless, I was still able to draw out the truth from them. That's right... My words alone are my weapons!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then... Let's analyze the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Leave this place at once! This is a direct order from the president himself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's not even listening. Any rebuttal I give, he cuts off. When he has that forceful attitude, I'll need to watch the situation carefully...</thought> My opponent is the president of Zheng Fa. I don't think he'll show any weakness easily. His words may be overbearing... but I need not be intimidated. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions. First... I'll start by asking about his reasons for taking over the investigation. Now, let's begin! A good opening line will put me at an advantage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, allow ne to confirm something about the investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nay! I don't recall granting you permission to speak!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I am the president of Zheng Fa. You shall not talk back to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not talking back. I am simply asking for confirmation. This investigation will be taken over by the police of your country. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Exactly. That is all I will say! Restrain yourself from making any more unnecessary comments!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Hmph. That's enough. Being on this plane is tantamount to being on my country's soil. You cannot do as you please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This plane...? Is there something significant about this place? I should remember this clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to explain your reasons for depriving us of our right to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Impudent fool! Hold your tongue! There is no reason! That should be enough of an explanation for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. Let me try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm. Perhaps that clue may be useful here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Huang">If you have nothing to say, begone! You're wasting my time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there... I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gathering from what you've said so far... Does that forceful attitude of yours have some connection to this place?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Hmph. You insolent...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Earlier, you said that being on this plane is like being on your country's soil. From those words, I was able to deduce the answer. Namely, that is... You wish to claim extraterritorial rights inside this plane. Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">That's enough! I shall brook no insolence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Huang">If you have nothing to say, begone! You're wasting my time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there... I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your words are forceful... but I cannot overlook them. The moment I mentioned extraterritorial rights... Your face grow pale.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...... In light of your brazen courage, I shall grant you an answer. That's right. I am claiming extraterritorial rights inside this place. However! What does that change? You are still powerless! There is nothing you can do about it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Under international law, the plane would be considered part of Zheng Fa. How convenient. ......Hmph. If he wishes to stake this claim... Then I shall question its validity. The next move will decide the outcome. He may be the president, but there is a hole in his logic. Let me break it wide open!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I challenge the validity of your claim to extraterritorial rights.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Do you truly understand... What it is you're saying?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. And I stand by it.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You dare doubt my words... You have no shame!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Such irredeemable ignorance. It troubles me greatly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no need to worry. I do not need to be saved. It is Ms. Swift whom I wish to save from these false charges that you have laid against her.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I admire your tenacity. However! Your wish is unattainable. The extraterritoriality laws are unshakable. This plane is Zheng Fa territory!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't have enough clues to proceed with this line of questioning. I should try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Permit me to say this... Don't you feel that your actions are too forceful?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Who asked for your opinion? All you need to do is obey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">"Forceful" is the wrong word. It is authority. Leadership!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you arrested Ms. Swift because you felt you had the authority to do so?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Yes! That girl is a criminal! There is no room for dispute!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't you realized it yet? I have you cornered!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nonsense! You're just wasting my time with pointless chatter!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Argh... That was a needless statement.</thought> I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">The shooting took place outside the plane. Only she could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...That's it! The shooting occurred outside the plane. This could be a very important clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've run this line of questioning to its conclusion... Let's try another line of attack.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm. It's time to use that clue.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">........</line>
<line speaker="Huang">If you have nothing to say, begone! You're wasting my time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... It seems I should have been more a bit more decisive there... I must not be intimidated by his words. If I observe his behavior closely, I should be able to read his emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, I do not question your extraterritorial rights inside this plane. ...However! You just claimed that the shooting took place "outside the plane". Yes! If it didn't happen inside the plane, extraterritorial laws do not apply! Your claim has fallen apart! Ms. Swift's arrest is invalid!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Grrrrrrrrrrrgh! I-Impossible! To be bested by a mere prosecutor...! I am the presideeent!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Checkmate, Mr. President.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. President... Will you allow us to continue with our investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Nngh. I... yield. I will allow it! My heart is generous. My heart is tolerant and merciful. Therefore! As such... ......Certainly! Thus, we shall... ....It is our duty! For a most noble cause... ...Gentlemen! Now is the time! I, the President of Zheng Fa, for the sake of the investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This guy sure likes beating around the bush.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knightley. We have received the President's permission. Could you return our evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Tsk. Here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You did it, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Now we can resume the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Heh! It's funny how happy you are just because I gave you your "precious" pieces back! Now let's see how well you use them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm. Pay attention, then. Here is my next move... ...Mr. President. May I make one more request of you?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you please testify about the moment of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Testify?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, hey! Hold on a sec! THAT'S your next move!? Isn't that the sort of thing you'd leave to the courts!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally, it's a courtroom procedure. However, I'd still like to hear what he has to say. If he refuses to cooperate with the investigation... ...he will have to give a clear reason.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">......</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Knightley. Stand down. I shall grant the honorable Prosecutor's request.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thank you for your cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Now, heed my words!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Where was I when the incident occurred? Ah, yes. The stage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If that's the case, then the president's a victim too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was an assassination attempt. Mr. Rooke just happened to get caught up in it, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But isn't it strange? Why would the victim want to interrupt the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. If this becomes public, it would cause problems.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see! There's still some deep, dark secret behind this case, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Certainly the president, and perhaps Knightley, too, know of this "secret". Without fail, I shall reveal it for all to see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">Where was I when the incident occurred? Ah, yes. The stage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you aware of just how serious this incident is?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You naïve man! Did you think I would be perturbed by that question!? Of course! I am well aware that a coward attempted to shoot me! At the time, I was on the stage delivering my speech!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Then! Rooke and Knightley suddenly appeared and stood in front of me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you realize there was a shooter when they appeared in front of you?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">What was I doing at that time? Ah, yes! The speech! During my speech, I was in a euphoric state! A state of nothingness and enlightenment!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So... You got nervous and you blanked out?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nay! I have not forgotten a single occurrence that transpired during my speech! When Rooke and Knightley appeared in front of me, I was surprised!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">After that, I heard a gunshot and a red balloon bursting!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A red balloon?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You try my patience, Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was not my intention. I just want to make sure your recollections are reliable.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Hmph! There were balloons on both sides of the stage! Swelling red in the cloudy sky... As laid out in the security plan!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The security plans... Ah, the one from the bag...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">They stepped in front of me just before the balloon burst!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Huang">And so! Those two attempted to escort me into the plane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..."Attempted" to escort you? What actually happened?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">That's right, "attempted". Rooke and Knightley raised their attaché cases...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's the moment shown in Kay's photo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">They led me towards the plane!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">But then... the second gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What happened after the second gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Pitiful Prosecutor! If you don't know that much, you're not fit for duty!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mfph...! What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I grow weary of needless repetition! It should be quite obvious! ...Even you should know the path of the second bullet!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">The bullet pierced through Rooke's body and struck my bulletproof vest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When the bullet hit, what condition was the victim in?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Ohh! He was truly a man among men! Still groaning from the bullet's impact, he grabbed hold of me... ...and dashed into the plane!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you entered the plane along with the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I am to be protected... Rooke was to protect me! That was his role!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He speaks firmly... But it feels like he's just dodging the question, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's a president. That's to be expected.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... There doesn't seem to be anything out of place...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Since he's also a victim... He wouldn't have a reason to lie, sir. So, what he's said should be nothing but the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the contrary, there is one point that stands out to me as odd. Try to recall the state of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ehh!? Really...? S-Show me the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps I should review it one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A red balloon burst...? I'm afraid that's not the case.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please have a look at this piece of evidence. Can you see... what has burst?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Nuoooooooooooh! Th-This is...! ...What, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. It's the Steel Samurai, Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo. You'd do well to remember it. If you wish to win the support of this nation's people!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And don't forget the rival show, The Jammin' Ninja!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The balloon that was ruptured by the bullet was no ordinary red balloon! It was a Steel Samurai balloon!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">......? But according to the plans, there should have been two red balloons... It says so right here in this security plan.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It certainly looks like there are only two round balloons drawn here.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! What is the meaning of this!? Explain at once!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yes, sir! That Steel Samurai balloon was a last minute replacement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Replacement...?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's what we were told. Seems that information didn't make it to the president. We ran into a little trouble during setup last night. One of the balloons that we had prepared burst.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, you scrambled to find a replacement?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Exactly. We just happened to run into a guy manning a stand in the park. He said he'd lend us the Steel Samurai balloon. He was... kind of a poser.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A stand, a Steel Samurai balloon, and a poser...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">We pumped air into its red samurai pants, to create a makeshift balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the Steel Samurai balloon looked just like an ordinary red balloon. Is that what you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! Why was I not informed of this?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Sir! I'm terribly sorry. I didn't think it was important enough to report...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Couldn't you tell by just looking at it?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Hmm... I did not notice it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he mistook the Steel Samurai's pants for an ordinary balloon?</thought> Was there a reason why you made that mistake...?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Oooh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh-What now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">A moment please. I just remembered now... I could not see the balloon very well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You couldn't see it?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Exactly. At the time, the wind was strong. The flags on the stage were fluttering wildly, and they obstructed my view.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The flags?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Did you not see the flags that were set up on both sides of the stage? Due to the strong wind, they were waving about. Just like this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So a strong wind was blowing at the time of the incident. The flags were fluttering wildly... Is there a problem with that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing... particularly wrong with that.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Exactly. Because of the flags, I could not see the balloon. I did not realize it until I was informed of the fact. I assumed it was just an ordinary red balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">H-Hey, Mr. Edgeworth! Are you just going to let the president get away like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ungh, but... The president's statement...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He refuses to testify and interferes with our investigation. That's reaaaaally suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let me rethink this through one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">President Huang. You have my gratitude. Your testimony has helped uncover a new contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">A contradiction... you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, one that turns the very foundation of this case on its head...! <thought>During my investigation, there was no wind at the crime scene, so the flags remained still... However, the flags were actually fluttering in the strong wind... This completely changes the meaning of that piece of evidence...!</thought> Which evidence contradicts the state of the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the evidence...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...that turns the case...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...on its head...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, Edgeworth! Do you even know how to use your "pieces"? The one that's been taken is yours!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhoooh...! <thought>I must have evidence that shows the situation at the time of the incident. First, I need to think back to the president's testimony and compare it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The gunshot rang out during the president's speech. The bullet struck the balloon... ...and also pierced through the national flag. I had previously deduced the bullet's trajectory using these facts. The assassin fired the bullet from the left side of the audience area... However, if the flags were fluttering about like so, my reasoning changes!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ahh! Since the flag's position has changed...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. The bullet's trajectory must also change.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And if we trace the trajectory of the bullet, we can tell who fired the shot.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? But, Mr. Edgeworth! That person is...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Indeed... I still don't understand why. However, it can be none other than him.</thought> By tracing the bullet's path, who was the person who fired the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet's trajectory points to this person!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Ah... so the murder weapon was not a gun, but a boomerang.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's it... With that kind of trajectory, it could only have been a boomerang.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Well then, Prosecutor! Show us this murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">He he heh... You really got something like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's no need to consider the impossible. I only need to follow the bullet's path! And after that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person who shot the balloon... was none other than you, Horace Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Connect the bullet holes in the balloon and the flag... and the line points to you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But that's guy's one of the president's bodyguards! Why would he have shot the Steel Samurai balloon, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Preposterous! I agree with the detective. There is no reason. Are you saying Knightley, who has saved my life on numerous occasions, is an assassin!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Prosecutor Edgeworth, I've had it up to here with you! My job is to protect the president!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! Control yourself...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">S-Sorry, sir... Prosecutor. Indeed, the wind was strong during my speech. However, the wind's strength can change very quickly. Evidence! Show us evidence that the flag was flying at the moment of the gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The gunshot occurred the moment the president raised his fist to the sky. The evidence that shows this moment is... Do I have something that shows the state of the flag?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This evidence...! ......... <thought>Th-This doesn't really show it...</thought> Kay. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What... You mean that "thing" you're holding, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Err... this. Do you want to hold it?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I think you should just admit that you were wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Evidence that shows the moment of the incident... Let me check again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The evidence is in this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Interesting. And where in this photo, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Proof that the flag was flying in this photo is: Right here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you think? If you look at the state of the flags...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, not that! Look here! At this point...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't see anything there, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... <thought>I have to prove the state of the flags at the time of the incident. There must be something in this photo that shows this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you see? The fluttering flag can be seen in this photo!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">N-No...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no mistaking that the flags were flying at the moment of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-So then. It really was that guy who shot the balloon...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That would mean Mr. Knightley is the assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally, he's the assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">That is terrible. Yet, what would be the merit?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh? The merit... What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Like he says, if I were the assassin, I'd need to have something to gain from it. Because the moment I killed the president... ...I'd be out of a job as a bodyguard!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah... Um... That's... <thought>That's true, there is no plausible motive.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley is... not the assassin. The only thing he shot was a balloon. A balloon on the opposite side of the president... He wasn't aiming at the president.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Why then! Why was it necessary for me to do a thing like that!? Depending on your answer, I might take aim at your pretty lil' head!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why was it necessary...? I presume the reason is connected to the one thing that's felt out of place...! ...The one who shot the balloon (Knightley shot the balloon - Bullet's trajectory shows that Knightley shot the balloon on the right side.</thought> was the president's bodyguard, Knightley. That fact will change the entire viewpoint of this case!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why was Knightley's position changed?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">'Cuz I can't turn my head to the right. My position got changed to the president's left side... In other words, I was relocated to the right side of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was that really the only reason? If the plans had not changed, and Knightley remained on the left side of the stage... Knightley can't turn his head to the right... Would he have been able to aim at the balloon on the left side of the stage? Perhaps... the security plans were altered so that Knightley could shoot the balloon? If that's the case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this...? The details of the security plans were changed?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah. That's right. It was changed yesterday. President's orders...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The security plans were changed on the president's orders (Change in the security plans - Ordered by the president. Was this done so Knightley could shoot the balloon?</thought>!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In other words, the president knew about the balloon being shot... He knew about the attempt on his own life!</thought> If you think about it that way, everything that's been out of place is beginning to add up! <thought>Why was the assassin able to get a gun past such tight security? Why was the assassin wearing a conspicuous red hood? Why did they use a laser sight that would so easily reveal their location? Why was the president so calm after being shot? This was the truth the president and his subordinates tried to conceal!</thought> There can only be one reason why Knightley fired the gun...! The entire assassination was a set-up!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...How dare you!? Do you seriously understand what you're implying with this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I understand. In fact, now I understand everything. Mr. President, you wished to take the investigation rights from me. That was all so you could conceal the real truth.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">How dare you mock me with these spurious allegations!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mock you? That was not my intention. I simply used logic to uncover the truth. That, is all. Knightley fired the first shot in order to rupture the balloon. Hearing the gunshot, and the sound of the balloon bursting, the audience began to panic. This was followed by one more shot...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait... one more shot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Knightley turned towards the balloon and pulled the trigger a second time. The second gunshot was also fired by Knightley... ...to create the illusion of the second shot hitting the president.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So what about the bullet that hit the president's bulletproof vest?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What if that bulletproof vest had been prepared in advance?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Uuuuughh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's the matter, Mr. President? Afraid of facing a little bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Th-That's not true! I was definitely shot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we examined the bullet in your vest, it would answer the question for us. Will we find Rooke's blood on that bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Ugh! But! Th-The person in the red hood who shot me is in that photo...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Weren't you listening, Mr. President? From the bullet's trajectory, the one who fired the shot must have been Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, Nicole...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She too was part of the president's plan... She was to bear the blame, and become the false assassin.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The red hooded figure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. I don't know how much of the plan Ms. Swift knew beforehand. However, she didn't fire the gun. All she did was aim the laser pointer at the president's head.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Th-That's right! I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Once the crowd began to panic, you would turn your parka inside out... ...and thus, the red hooded figure vanished. After that, you discarded the gun and security plan in the trash... ...and the illusion of the assassin vanishing like a ghost was complete.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And with the assassin gone, the case would go unsolved, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that was what he hoped for.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's why he wouldn't let Mr. Edgeworth investigate the case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. All of this... was an asinine publicity stunt from a lying president!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">But... you... YOU! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You... you are wrong... I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He revealed his true form.</thought> The assassination is a lie, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">The chief... why did he have to pick you... This... should not have happened...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well played, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Kn-Kn-Kn-Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I am speaking with the president now, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You're a chess player. You know knights always strive to protect their King. So shut up. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are... are you threatening me, Mr. Knightley?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aaagh! What's with this guy!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Oops, sorry. I went over the top there. But onto business... As my first move, I wanna ask you a question. You say I fired a gun on the stage, right? Then I should've been caught. The entire audience was watching me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Now it's my move. You used a certain object to prevent the spectators from seeing you.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">A certain object...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What did Knightley use to prevent the audience from seeing him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe... you used this. Am I getting close?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">How should I know? You tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There's definitely something... strange about that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">So, what exactly is so strange, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If Knightley really did fire the gun, the issue is whether the audience could see him. He had to have used something to solve that issue. The question is, do I have that piece of evidence right now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The attaché case...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. I'd like you to have a look at this photo Kay took. Your right hand is completely hidden by the case. This photo captures the exact moment you secretly fired the gun. You used the attaché case as a screen!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You seem to enjoy making up convenient stories, Mr. Prosecutor. But, you've missed something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What have I missed?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That everything you've said is just a hypothesis. A theory. Flags flapping in the wind? Using the case as a screen? The security plans were modified 'cause I can't move my neck? You've got no decisive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, it'd be great if you had the bullet that hit the balloon. Then you could examine it, and see if the ballistic markings matched my gun. But that bullet's probably at the bottom of the lake. Finding it would be real tough, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I hate to admit it, but it's as he says. There's no decisive evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If there's no proof, the only thing you can do is shut up. So do so!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ah, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it! If she speaks, we cold hear new testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey lady! You got something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Ah, err... never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">There we go. I thought so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nicole!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be afraid! The truth will escape if you let that man intimidate you. You're a reporter... A journalist, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">........ I... I... I will NOT remain silent!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You'd better consider your position! Use your head before saying something you'll regret.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I forgot the number one rule of journalism... Journalists must not tell lies... You can't call it a scoop if it ain't the truth! Mr. Edgeworth. I'm sorry. I've been hiding this the whole time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I used this laser pointer to aim at the president. That's all I did... I never fired the gun!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You stupid womaaan! If you testify, you'll be admitting you're an accomplice!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I... I don't care! I'm gonna tell him everything. Three days ago, I was covering an event at the Zheng Fa Embassy. Then some of the president's men called me over. They said if I cooperated, I'd get an exclusive interview with the president.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And the gun in the trash?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I really don't know. All I was told... ...was to come wearing a red hood and to aim the laser pointer. I never thought it would snowball into all of this... I'm really, truly sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nicole, thank you. That was a testimony worthy of the courtroom. This is sufficient testimony to verify the fake assassination plot.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Damn you! The lot of you! You're all a bunch of mindless morons...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a shame. If only you had been able to usurp the investigation as planned... ...you would have been able to silence this young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Blast!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, tommorrow's headlines now read... "Fake Assassination Plan Exposed, Becomes a Murder!" ...Right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe that you'd do something this horrible, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I-I admit nothing...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The president...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley. That's enough. We have no choice but to admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, Mr. President, You admit that you planned a fake assassination?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Yes... I admit it. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, why? Why did you have to do this?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">My approval ratings in Zheng Fa have fallen... I wanted to appeal to them as a strong president who survived an assassination... ...but in the end, it was just a lie. A stupid lie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And the bullet in the bulletproof vest...?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Prepared earlier. It was not fired today.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, what about Mr. de Killer?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">It seems our plan was leaked... Someone wanted to make this fake assassination real.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's why De Killer wore the red raincoat. He would impersonate the culprit from the plan, in order to approach the president.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">But, there's still one thing I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Why did Rooke die? His death was not a part of this charade... and yet it really happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes... why was his life taken?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">Ethan was an outstanding bodyguard. Even though he wasn't from my country, he had my utmost trust.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">......</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wouldn't think that having the trust of a cowardly president meant that much, honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, that's the same sort of bond between me and Mr. Edgeworth, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wouldn't put it that way...</thought> Did Rooke know of your plan?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Not the exact details. ...I asked him to cooperate, and he refused.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should have listened to his advice.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Yes, indeed. I wouldn't have done all this if I had known...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Tsk... You're being too dramatic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>? Wh-What?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Rooke was just one piece of the president's defense.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley...? That's...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">And it's not as if he cooperated with your plan. I did. He ran away, taking whatever dignity he had left with him. Good riddance.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I know you're a valuable bodyguard, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I don't have time for this, sir. I'm the team leader now. There's going to be a lot of changes now that the chicken's gone. After all, adaption is the most important principle in chess!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I knew you always wanted to be the team leader... B-But... Isn't this a bit imprudent?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">He he he. I will orchestrate even more perfect plans, just like this one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You definitely have ambition. But, wasn't your "perfect plan" today a failure?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If it weren't for you and that idiot Rooke, it would have been perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did Rooke do?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If he hadn't died, De Killer wouldn't have threatened me... ...and you would have never set foot in this plane.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! How can you say such a thing...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, he died trying to save you, Mr. President. Maybe he fulfilled his lifelong ambition.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He died protecting the president?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? But the assassination was fake... right?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Of course it was, But you need to listen closer, little girl. Remember the "guy who wanted to make the fake assassination real"? There were two gunshots at the time of the incident. The first was as you said. I shot the balloon. BUT... The second one wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So who fired the second shot?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The REAL assassin. ...But, it wasn't De Killer. He intended to attack the president with a knife, not a gun. The lucky winner was the hidden Queen... ...or should I say, the lady in the coat over there.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Eh!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're accusing Nicole, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I-I ain't no assassin!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Really? I don't believe you. The gun that was left in the trash... That was yours, right?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I shot the balloon and entered the plane with Rooke and the president.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you're saying you don't know exactly when the victim was shot?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">A knight's job isn't to protect the Rook. It's to protect the King!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What he's trying to say is that his job was to protect the president only.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">It's over if you lose the King. Checkmate. That's the first rule of chess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you let your pieces get taken right in front of you, you're not likely to win...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">But I did win! Look! The president is safe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Don't claim victory when the game has only just begun!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I shot the balloon and entered the plane with Rooke and the president.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the victim had no part in your plan?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, that's right. He didn't even know it was all fake.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So you're saying he thought it was a real assassination attempt? Ah, But you fired the gun right next to him. Wouldn't he have noticed...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Maybe he did. Not that it matters now. Besides, even if he thought the assassination attempt was a fake... His duty was to protect the King.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He made a split-second decision to sacrifice himself... The victim was truly a man of honor.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You're wrong. It was all part of my plan. He simply assisted in our little performance on stage!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Rooke waited in the cabin while I led the president into the security room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you do that? The assassination was supposed to be fake.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">There were a lot of "guests" milling around outside. Wouldn't it be bad if the president, who just escaped an assassination... ...was seen lounging around and drinking grape juice? Imagine the headlines.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was the victim doing at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">How should I know? I was with the president inside the security room. Anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">When I came out, Rooke was already on the ground...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where did you find the body?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">About where he is now. He collapsed in the middle of this room. When I returned, the door to the plane was already closed... The bullet must've hit Rooke right before the door closed. Talk about a hassle. It's all his fault that this plan failed.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! That's too far...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Even if he protected the king, he couldn't protect his honor. He was careless in his duty and he paid the price for it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This man is truly despicable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">As I was saying...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The bullet that lady fired must have hit him while we escorted the president to the plane.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Weren't you both carrying bulletproof attaché cases?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah. When Rooke noticed the laser pointer... We opened up those bad boys and became the president's shield.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're telling me the bullet slipped through the space between your shields? Are you claiming that Ms. Swift has such precise aim?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, she was targeting the president. I wouldn't say her aim is precise at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the bullet was off-target and just happened to hit the victim instead? Through the tiny gap between his bulletproof vest AND case?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I don't want to believe it either, but they say the truth is stranger than fiction. Rooke was hit by a one-in-a-million shot. And you have the evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The shot was fired from the gun you found in the trash!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the second shot wasn't part of your plan?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's right. She did that on her own. If you think about it, wasn't she desperate for a scoop?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I'm a journalist! I ain't no murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well then, who was the one who joined the plan in order to get exclusive coverage?</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Uuh... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">It's just like you said, I orchestrated this fake assassination attempt. She was only supposed to aim the laser pointer... I guess it wasn't enough for her. She prepared her own gun and took aim at the president. She probably thought she wouldn't get caught if she went on and shot me too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knightley fired the first shot, and then Ms. Swift fired the second one...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In other words, Nicole also had a gun. I never thought she was the type...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Without any proof, it's just pure speculation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then BAM! Let's present some evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you shot the balloon, and Ms. Swift shot Rooke? Is that really true?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I can't see it any other way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The gun we discovered in the trash was fired twice. The number of gunshots don't add up!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why don't the gunshots add up? It's simple. This gun is fake evidence, left behind by the real criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Fake evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think about it. The criminal planted this for a reason. By finding the gun, we'd assume that the assassin was in the audience. In order to make us believe that the gun was used by the assassin... ...the gun needed to appear as if it had been fired twice.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I get it! Because two shots were fired during the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, we proved that the bullet that hit the balloon did not come from this gun. Therefore, I have my doubts as to whether this gun also took Rooke's life.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...He he he. Here it comes. You're packing some serious heat. Enough with the song and dance. You've come this far, go ahead and say it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I won't just say it. I'll prove it. The one who really shot Rooke is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at this! It was this person!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, you... You really don't know anything, do you? Was that supposed to be a joke, or are you serious?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey... That's not right! Mr. Edgeworth's so smart that our feeble minds just can't comprehend his reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-Ngghhh... <thought>I don't think so, Kay. The real murder weapon was not the gun we found in the park. That was planted to throw us off the trail. And the person who planted it... It can only be one person!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Horace Knightley! You murdered Rooke!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey... You finally said it.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley! You couldn't have!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">De Killer wasn't the only one who took advantage of the fake assassination plot. You intended to murder Rooke and claim he was a victim of the assassination! Once the president had entered the security room and the door to the plane was closed... ...only the victim and Knightley would have been left in this room. And at that moment, you fired a third bullet. Directly at Rooke...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">A third bullet...? Hah! Only two gunshots were heard! The numbers don't match up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The plane's walls are soundproof. If the door was closed... ...the gunshot would not have been heard outside.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But, wasn't the president in the next room?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's true... The president may have heard the gunshot!</thought> Mr. President! Did you hear a gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I... didn't hear any gunshots...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But! Weren't you watching this room through the security cameras...?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">The cameras in this room aren't usually turned on. I turned on the power after I entered the security room.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So you didn't turn on the power immediately after entering the room?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">......No. Actually... I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is it? He's not being clear...</thought> Mr. President! Focus! This is vital!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">......I-I-I was... That is... I...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Please!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I was hiding under the bed, covering my ears...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaa!? But you knew the assassination was fake!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">It doesn't matter! I simply hate the sound of guns! That terrifying sound! I just can't help it!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">........</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...That definitely ain't going in my article.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ahem. Knightley! You saw the president hiding under the bed!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Furthermore... ...you could tell if the security cameras had been turned on by looking at the monitors! In that moment, when the president wouldn't hear the gunshot or see the room... You had a chance to fire a third bullet at Rooke!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Knightley... Did you really...! You deceived me?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You really think I killed that moron? That's cold, Mr. President. Have a little faith in me. The bodyguard who's risking his life to protect you.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I-I want to believe you. I really do, but...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I just don't get it. Why are you suspecting me alone? There's still the possibility that she's the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gun is not the murder weapon. The number of missing bullets makes that clear.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Maybe it was one short to begin with. Ever think of that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Maybe it already fired a shot yesterday, or the day before. And the second shot was fired today. The one that hit Rooke...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, isn't that just the perfect excuse!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Excuse? The possibility exists, you can't deny that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's right, I can't deny it completely...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You need decisive evidence! Evidence so decisive that it makes my heart stop and my logic crumble! You got something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Can't you do anything? At this rate, Nicole will...!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Mr. Prosecutor... It's true, I did an awful thing for a scoop. But, I never killed nobody, I could never do a thing like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Decisive evidence... If I could prove the murder weapon was Knightley's gun... Proof it was his gun...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Yeah, it'd be great if you had the bullet that hit the balloon. Then you could examine it, and see if the ballistic markings matched my gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If we can find the bullet that took Rooke's life... ...We can determine which gun fired the shot from the ballistic markings!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If you've got no evidence, then we're done talking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Wh-What? You don't seriously have decisive evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's a big joke. Well, come on now, show us! What is this so-called evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The bullet that took Rooke's life. That's the decisive evidence I need...!</thought> This evidence... <thought>Do I have it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have the bullet... right... umm... here... somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If the canary doesn't sing, just shoot it! ...Or so the saying goes. Just as I hoped, I'm gonna blast a hole in ya! Right in your chest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhoooh! <thought>Rooke was killed here. So, where did the bullet go...? Come to think of it, there's one thing in this room that's always felt out of place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... don't have it.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">OK! OK! It's Game Over, man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However... It is somewhere in this room!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet that killed Rooke pierced through his body. So where did the bullet go? Earlier, you explained it like this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The bullet that stole Rooke's life pierced through his body, and then hit the vest.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...That's right. It'd be dangerous if he hadn't worn that bulletproof vest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, now that the fake assassination plan has come to light... ...we know that the bullet in the bulletproof vest was prepared earlier. So then, where did the bullet go?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...Interesting. Very interesting. Do you have the answer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Do I have evidence that shows the location of the bullet that killed Mr. Rooke?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, what do you think!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well then, why don't you take the bullet out and show it to us?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm. Not quite yet. It would be inconvenient to do it today.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Ho ho. Well, maybe by tomorrow, a bullet will have appeared in it. Have you decided to join the Gramarye magician group?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah...! <thought>Rooke was killed here. So, where did the bullet go...? Come to think of it, there's one thing in this room that's always felt out of place...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In this room there is one thing that's clearly missing.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Something missing? You sure it's not your brain?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to look at the rack of security monitors.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems you've noticed, Mr. President. Among these images of the plane's surroundings... ...only the feed from the right side of the plane is absent. That's what's missing. A single monitor...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Nrrrgghh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. President. There was originally a monitor here, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Th-That's right. Why is there a stuffed toy now...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That must have been put there to hide the empty space where the monitor used to be. Why is the monitor missing and where did it go? Why... Undoubtedly, because it was hit by the bullet. In order to make us think that the bullet really hit the bulletproof vest... ...it would be a problem if another bullet hole was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So then, where did the monitor go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where... It should be hidden somewhere inside this plane. There hasn't been a chance to dispose of it outside since it was shot. Detective Gumshoe! Search this plane!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger that, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">President Huang! You said extraterritorial laws apply to this plane...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I-I will allow it. There is no problem. I just want to know the truth of Rooke's death...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Dammit! You think this is a joke!? You're always like this! Rooke this, Rooke that...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective. We have his approval. Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I found it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good work, Detective. Now let's extract the bullet from the monitor!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm. If I do this here, and then do that... I got it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it's definitely stained with blood. I'm certain this is the bullet that killed Rooke.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the bullet that will crush your arguments! The decisive evidence that blows a hole in your logic! If the ballistic markings on this bullet do not match the gun found in the audience area... ...Ms. Swift will be cleared of suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong? Cat got your tongue? Detective. We need to examine the ballistic markings. Send the gun and bullet to forensics.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger! We should be able to find clear markings on this bullet, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, let's listen to the forensic report.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">.......</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Reporting! First, the blood on this bullet matches the victim's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So, this bullet really did take Rooke's life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Also, Horace Knightley's fingerprints were found on this gun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Knightley's fingerprints probably came from when he took all our evidence. The real issue, is the ballistic markings. If the markings don't match... Ms. Swift will be cleared of suspicion!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Forensics">And the bullet's ballistic markings... match this gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What! <thought>They... match?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whaa!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">N-No way!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">There's no mistake. The bullet was fired from this gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...He he he he he he. Huh? That's strange. Looks like I was right after all... naturally. Did you really think you had me cornered? You misread the board... The one who's been cornered... is you!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If the ballistic markings match the gun, there can be no doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, it's your move, Mr. Prosecutor. Where did you find this gun again? And which gun fired the bullet? At least we know... It ain't me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... <thought>This can't be happening!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The president and I have admitted to the fake assassination plot. Now it's your turn to admit who the real criminal is!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That doesn't make Nicole the criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't get riled up, Kay. Let him have his say first. After he's done, it won't be too late to begin our counterattack.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...! Alright, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">If the ballistic markings match the gun, there can be no doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No. That's...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Didn't you say it earlier? This is the decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well? How does it feel to have a hole blown through your reasoning?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The ballistic markings matched the gun we found, so... ...does that mean Nicole really was the shooter?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to believe otherwise...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But, he's got the decisive evidence on his side, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, indeed... How should I proeed...? If Ms. Swift isn't the killer, then the ballistic markings should not match.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thoughts, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm. If the evidence is impossible... ...then maybe we should doubt the evidence itself, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doubt the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Nicole's definitely not a criminal! So, if the evidence says that she's a criminal, there must be something wrong with it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You seem awfully sure of yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a Great Thief's intuition!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Intuition...? Still, it's quite possible. Above all, Ms. Swift doesn't seem like the type of person to tell such elaborate lies. Hmph. In court, the evidence is everything... And yet, here I am doubting it. Which evidence do I doubt...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Could there be something strange about the bullet...?</thought> Detective, did you do anything to the bullet when you first discovered it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Like what, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know... like, step on it. Or perhaps fall on it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">........Terrible, sir. YOU'RE TERRIBLE, MR. EDGEWORTH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhoooh...! <thought>My ears! The bullet was only just found. Not even Gumshoe could have bungled it that fast. I should doubt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">None of the evidence seems particularly doubtful...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, your prosecutor's badge seems a little doubtful to me. Could be a fake. That'd explain the poor job you're doing here. Aha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I-It's too early to draw conclusions. I don't have enough information yet...</thought> ...Knightley, continue with your testimony. Please tell me about the bullet and the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If anything's suspect here, it can only be the gun. The bullet was discovered just a moment ago... It couldn't have been tampered with yet. Did Knightley have a chance to tamper with the gun?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">You shall hand over all the evidence you've found so far and leave this plane at once.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. Be a good boy and do as you're told.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! <thought>I... cannot resist any longer...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it! He could have tampered with the gun at that time...! There's no doubt that this gun is the real murder weapon. In that case, the owner of this gun is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe this person...? W-Wait, no! They never had the opportunity to switch the guns! If this gun was switched with the real murder weapon... No other could have done it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He must have switched the guns... ...Without a doubt, this is Knightley's own gun!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's true, the markings match. However...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You just don't know when to quit. Are you secretly having doubts about the evidence? You should know better than anyone that the evidence never lies. Besides... ...don't you know it's against the rules to yell "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn>" during chess?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh...! <thought>He's avoiding my question. But, I can already see the answer. When we handed over the evidence to Knightley... ...he switched his own gun with the one we found in the trash can. So, it's only natural the ballistic markings match...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Looks like your turn's over. It's my move now.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">The bullet that killed Rooke was fired from the gun you found in the audience area.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knightley, you...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You're the one who should "Hold it". You proved it yourself. Don't tell me that you're going to betray your own logic?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The bullet is stained with the victim's blood. So it's clear it took the victim's life. And the ballistic markings match the gun we found in the trash can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Nice. Nice. Your face betrays your thoughts, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... <thought>At this rate he'll get away!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Now that you've got a firm grasp of reality, it's time to take the next step... The link between the gun and the bullet is clear. So...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Who could've used the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Who... indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You already know the answer, you just don't wanna admit it, huh? I know the feeling. It's probably like how I felt before. Feeling so irritated, you're just itching to pull the trigger!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...But, this ain't the time to be joking around. Only one person could have used that gun...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Not me, 'cuz I was onstage. But what about that lady reporter in the audience?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have proof that Ms. Swift fired the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whoa there, didn't the boys in blue already prove that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But... Nicole's fingerprints weren't found on the gun!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And YOURS were all over it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, that's 'cuz I was handling all the evidence earlier. If that lady isn't the killer, who else could it be? You were the one who cornered the assassin in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Capisce? In fact, from every angle on the board...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">All the evidence points to that young lady as the assassin who killed Rooke!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't recall that being proven!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, what exactly HAVE you proved? Oh, yeah. You proved that I fired the first bullet. But, you're forgetting one crucial thing. Why were you called here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's obvious, pal! We came to find the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Do you consider the worsening relationship with Zheng Fa to be the truth? No. Your purpose here was to solve the attempted assassination incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...My purpose here is for me to decide. It is not to be decided by the likes of you.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Whatever. If you spend all day arguing like this, the case is gonna go unsolved. Just give it up already. The real criminal is that lady over there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>No, the real criminal can be none other than this man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The ballistic markings match the gun we discovered in the trash can. When did Knightley have the opportunity to touch the gun...? It could only have been when I handed over the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth... Is there anything we can do?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Our reasoning up until now has not been wrong. This is an obstacle we'll have to overcome.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But doesn't he have decisive evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A testimony born from lies will always contain a contradiction. Firstly, I'll need to press Knightley for more details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Knightley! You fiend! You switched the guns! The gun that matched the ballistic markings was yours all along!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">......Heh. Interesting choice of move you've made there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The switched occurred at the time you seized the evidence. When we were arguing with the president over the investigation rights. You detached the laser right from the gun found in the audience area... ...and attached it to your gun! Then, when you returned the evidence, you gave me your own gun...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">He he heh. Did I do that? So, what you're saying is that I knew you'd want to examine the ballistic markings?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Staying one move ahead of your opponent... Isn't that the fundamental rule of chess?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I'm glad you feel that way, Mr. Prosecutor. But you're giving me too much credit. Besides... can you even prove I pulled the old switcheroo with the guns?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">So the gun happens to be the same model as mine. Pure coincidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Giving you too much credit? That hardly sounds like something you'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Guess I'm just more modest than you. Well... Except when I'm in front of a chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... But we're not in front of a chessboard.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That's too bad. Don't use that as an excuse later. "I didn't lose the game. I just couldn't find enough evidence."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're the one who should have an excuse ready. "You didn't beat me at chess. You only found the evidence."</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">So the gun happens to be the same model as mine. Pure coincidence...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Coincidence" ...you say?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Or perhaps, it was simply bound to happen.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Which was it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Us bodyguards needed to use them to protect the president. And no matter how you slice it, that lady is a total amateur with guns. It was necessary for both of us to use revolvers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A revolver... Like the one Knightley's carrying? Why would it be necessary...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It has a simpler mechanism, so it's easier to use... something along those lines, probably.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">When you gotta get the job done, or if you're new to this sorta thing, there's nothing better. The truth is, I thought it was "pure coincidence" all along.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">But, take a closer look. Only one of them has a laser pointer attached to it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You attached the laser pointer to the gun yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Oh yeah? Prove it. Show me the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, w-well... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You can't go around calling people liars without proof... Didn't your daddy teach you that? On that point, I've got evidence on my side.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Check the number of bullets left in the chamber. Only two shots fired, see?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something's been bothering me for a while now... What about the chamber of your own gun?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">My woman here? ...Now that you mention it. I've been firing it off for a while now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm? Every time he fires, he reloads the gun...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">So there's no way to check its status from the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it! In order to switch the guns, he would have needed to reload the bullets! Knightley is barehanded. And he had no time to put on gloves when the switch was made...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Well, I think it's about time for you to resign. How about it, Prosecutor Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">There's no evidence that I switched the guns, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">There isn't any. If there is, show it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We know there is, pal! Don't we, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is no time for another investigation. I can only use what I have right now. Think. Consider all the possibilities...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">He he he... If you've got something to show, let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Evidence that Knightley switched the guns? Does that even exist...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's no evidence that directly proves that Knightley switched the guns... Yet, we know for a fact he did.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If he didn't, there would be no explanation for the ballistic markings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I need to carefully consider the meaning behind every piece of evidence linked to his testimony. The truth must be there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That evidence... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You call that evidence? Prosecutor Edgeworth. You're trying too hard.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Certain traces were left on this gun. Traces that prove this gun belongs to you!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Show it to me! What kinda piece you got! A Rook? A Bishop? It better not be a pawn!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The traces Knightley left on the gun are...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...the ballistic markings, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth. About the ballistic markings...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know how they work, Detective. I don't need an explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You sure about that? You don't seem to get it. The markings point to me, huh? Just what kind of ballistic markings are they, anyway? Do they spell out my name? Great joke, Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He's right. Ballistic markings only link a bullet to a certain gun, not to its user. What I need is evidence that directly links Knightley to the gun...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It must be the bloodstains!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...And which bloodstain would that be? The only bloodstains I can recall belonged to De Killer and Rooke. Did you find another one? Please do tell. Or perhaps their bloodstains somehow link to the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnngh... Th-That's... <thought>I can't make such a mistake after coming this far!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You left your fingerprints on this gun.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Fingerprints...? Hah! That should be expected! I handled the gun earlier when I seized your evidence. Of course my fingerprints are on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But what if the fingerprints are in a place they should not be?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">What!? Th-That's not possible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Allow me to show you. There is one place where your fingerprints should not be... This piece of evidence will deal the final blow to your king!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here. Detective Gumshoe, please have a look at the cylinder.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Two shots were fired, sir. But... Where would the fingerprints be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You made the switch when you seized the evidence earlier. However, if all you did was switch the guns, you would've been found out right away. That's because the number of bullets fired by the two guns are different.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The gun found in the audience area had fired two shots, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then, what about Mr. Knightley's gun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He fired two shots at the balloon when he was on the stage... And later, one shot to kill Rooke... Three shots in total... Not counting the number of shots he's fired since then. And after each of those times, you would reload the bullets! Tell us, Knightley, were you wearing gloves when doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Nngggh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Officer! In your report earlier, where were Knightley's fingerprints found on the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! The prints weren't just found on the outside of the gun... ...they were also found on the bullets as well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If all you did was handle the evidence, why would your fingerprints be on the bullets?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Gah! Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">...I-I, I'm, I'm!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Checkmate.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">M-M... M... MMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPPHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">I-I... I should've been made leader! Me! Rooke! That piece of scum! If it hadn't been for him! I would've had complete control over everybody! My assassination plan... It was perfect... My plan... was perfect...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... Detective Gumshoe. If you please.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Roger that, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">EEEEEDGEWOOOOOORTH!!! This game isn't over yet! You hear me! I...! I...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's enough. The rest of this "game" will continue in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Gr-Grrr...! Damn it...! Damn... you...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">You have my gratitude. You exposed a murder amongst my bodyguards, and for that, I am truly in your debt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As soon as he stepped outside the plane, he reverted back to his king-like persona...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Huang">Some time ago, when I proposed the fake assassination plan...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">You want me, and not Rooke?</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Rooke declined... so I'm asking you. What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">........... Alright. Let's do this. I'll come up with the perfect plan. I can even use that guy as a chess piece...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">When Knightley said that, his eyes were overflowing with hatred towards Rooke. Frankly, I was quite anxious about asking Knightley instead of Rooke. Now that I recall those events, he probably sense the anxiety in my countenance. Perhaps that is what gave him the impetus for murder...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. President. If you had not orchestrated that fake plan, this would not have happened. That is your sin. ...A sin that won't disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...Yes. You are absolutely correct. You have my sincerest apologies. I too must bear some responsibility for this. Even so, I am most grateful to you. I thank you for solving the mystery of Rooke's death. I am scheduled to stay in this country for a little longer... But if any of you ever wish to visit the Republic of Zheng Fa, you will always be welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Oh Lawdy, Thank ya, thank ya, thank ya!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm so happy for you, Nicole!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were set up as the suspect for the murder. Still, your involvement with the fake assassination plan remains a fact. You will have to submit to police questioning later. You should know that there's still a possibility you may be charged with some crime.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Yeah, I know... Sorry 'bout all this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand you want to catch a scoop, but there's a line that should not be crossed.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I hear ya, I promise to reflect on this...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We did it, Mr. Edgeworth! That was awesome! "Prosecutor Edgeworth Solves Presidential Assassination Attempt!" It's gonna be big news!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">B-Big news...! M-Mr. Prosecutor, would ya mind tellin' us how ya feel about solving this case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That was certainly a quick change of attitude...</thought> No comment.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Aww, don't be so ornery!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason is because... this case is not over yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Not over? What do you mean, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What shows that this case is not over yet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">De Killer's card...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Do you understand what I'm trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Oh, y-yeah! It's um... Nope, sir. I haven't got a clue!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Darn it... I must have presented the wrong piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I do remember Mr. de Killer talking about something earlier... but that's probably unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No... that's exactly it! That is what I meant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">De Killer still hasn't carried out his request.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You mean killing the president...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I hope this doesn't turn into a larger incident...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"An Assassination Attempt on the President of Zheng Fa"... News of this incident spread across the entire country. The mass media also hounded me as I began to prepare for the trial of Horace Knightley. Everyone had seen the news, and everyone was talking about it. However, amidst the commotion, nobody noticed... ...that the game had only just begun...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right... I need to reconsider the information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information. I need to think this over one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your statement just now, it contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Is that so? ...Do you need glasses?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No, I do not.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Is that so? ...What about hearing aids?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gah... There's no contradiction. I should take another look at the evidence while I listen to his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your testimony clearly contradicts this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Prosecutor Edgeworth. Can't you see my ice cream is melting?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The problem now is not your ice cream, but your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">I would say the real problem lies with your statement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I-I was wrong...! I should only present evidence when I'm sure that I've found the contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to have a look at this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Doe">But of course. To what do I have the pleasure of looking at? ........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you have anything to say?</line>
<line speaker="Doe">Nothing in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this is the wrong piece of evidence... I need to pay close attention to his testimony, in order to find the contradiction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift... This proves that you're lying!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Hearsay! Defamation! World exclusive as reporter exposes the truth behind false arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's not quite...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">His temper's risin'! You can almost see the steam comin' outta his ears!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gah! <thought>I-I think I'm coming at this wrong...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to take a look at this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">..........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, this piece of of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">Mr. Prosecutor, err...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, I've got nothing more to say on the matter. <thought>I need to think this over one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Swift! You're lying!</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">...I see. So that's how it is. Must be tough on ya. No matter where you go, ya gotta fulfill yer quotas. How many more folks y'all plannin' to arrest this month? Hm? Care to comment?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must have given her the wrong idea... It seems this isn't the piece of evidence I need.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I won't let that statement pass. It contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Your reasoning is at fault! My reasoning stands like steel! Feeble Prosecutor! Accept my reasoning!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That... reasoning is...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">There is no use arguing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I was the one at fault here...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a contradiction in your testimony. This piece of evidence proves it...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">I admire your spirit! However! As the head of Zheng Fa, I cannot turn a blind eye to any evil! You have the courage of a foolish child! You alone must suffer for your mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rrrgggh... <thought>I-I was mistaken!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement is contradictory! Have a look at this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">It was inevitable! Knightley!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Got it, Mr. President! Hey Mr. Prosecutor, the only thing contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Huang">Is your own statement!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghooh! Th-They're ganging up on me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's a glaring contradiction in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">That so? The only flaw I see... ...is that it's just too perfect, there are no contradictions! Better wipe the board clean, Mr. Prosecutor. Looks like you're out of your league!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I-I can't argue with that... I'd better look over the facts before I try again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you think of this!</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Mr. Prosecutor... Haven't you forgotten the rules of chess?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm... Maybe I should present this instead...</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">GOTCHA! It's against the rules to touch a piece and then not move it! Take the penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh... <thought>What was I thinking...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't see the point of your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Knightley">Oh, and you think you're any better? Always rambling on and on, you're the one who can't make a straight point! You sure you have the capacity for this? Mentally speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There was no contradiction... I need to calm down and think things over again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! To come this far, only to lose the truth...! But... it seems there's nothing I can do now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Nicole">I got no clue what you've been talkin' about, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">C-Confound it...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't give up now. I have to stand my ground... Now... Let's try this again!</line>
<line speaker="Huang">...I've heard enough. Leave now, before I order my men to show you out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">C-Confound it...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't give up now. I have to stand my ground... Now... Let's try this again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing of interest here.</line>
</xml>