<xml>
<title>Turnabout Big Top</title>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow... That was like living a dream... I haven't even caught my breath yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe... That was amazing! Wasn't it Pearly!?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It was great! There was a dancing bear... And a tiger that jumped though* <thought>[sic]</thought> a ring of fire... An elephant who rode a giant ball... Not to mention that guy who flew through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! Max Galactica! He was absolutely fabulous!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Huh? ...What? Max...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max Galactica! The World's Greatest Magician!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">A magic-ician?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What is it Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Does magic have anything to do with channeling spirits?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think it has anything to do with channeling...</thought> You don't know about magic, do you Pearls?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I braved the winter cold and took Pearls to see the circus... It's been six months since the incident in Kurain Village... It was during that terrible time that I met Pearls...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems like she is starting to get back to normal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh... It's time to go.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're right. We can't miss the last train.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls! You remembered the train!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Of course I did! But I don't really understand what everyone means by "express train".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick... See you later. I'll come by to help clean the office. It's gotta be spotless for the New Year.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry about it. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You are going to visit Mr. Nick on New Year's?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I am glad you will get to spend your New Year's with your special someone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-PEARL!! Look! It's time to go!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Happy New Year Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Happy New Year"... I really hope it will turn out that way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well... Today wraps it up for this year... I hope I can finish cleaning this place up in one day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">.............................. ...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Hello. This is the Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!! It's t-t-terrible!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh, Maya. Perfect timing... Things are terrible here too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The office is a terrible mess! And I have to clean it up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ummm... My dirty office. What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Listen Nick! You have to turn on the TV!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The TV?</thought></line>
<line speaker="TV">...Now let's check in at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? What happened...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="TV">...Thank you. We're here at the Berry Big Circus. The Berry Big Circus has become the center of a sensational murder. The scene has created quite a stir among the throngs of excited onlookers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Very... I mean... The Berry Big Circus...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the circus we went to!! Right!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're saying that there was a... murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! They arrested him too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Arrested who?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max! They arrested Max Galactica!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maximillion Galactica. Fans call him Max. A popular magician who can fly through the sky at will... Maya said she was a huge fan of Max...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright Nick! I'll see you in two hours at the Detention Center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See you there. You've still got plenty of time to clean up your office later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-WWWHHHAATTT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...*beep*...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. I wouldn't mind dumping some of these off at the used bookstore... But that might not be such a good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley. A quite decorative plant. I wouldn't mind his help cleaning this place up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My desk. Since I don't have time to sit, it's unusually clean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of the newest member of the "Steel Samurai" universe. Maya went out and bought it right away. She's a sucker for all things Steel Samurai. I hear they're even giving the new guy his own movie. I just know Maya is going to drag me out to see it with her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a giant building just outside the window. It's the Gatewater Hotel, a high-class, luxury hotel. Until recently, it had been a normal, business-class hotel.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are they talking about? Why did they arrest Max?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're asking the wrong man on that one, Maya. Maybe he used his magical skills to deal death with a slight* <thought>[sic]</thought> of hand...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maximillion Galactica would never do such a thing!!</line>
<line speaker="???">FABULOUS!! What the young lady just said was absolutely fabulous! What a clever girl! Such a fabulous understanding of events!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What's with all this fabulous talk...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Welcome to the Visitor's Room!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's MAX!! Nick!! Look! It's the real Maximillion Galactica!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Alright sweetie. Pick a card, any card.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-H-He called me sweetie! *swoon* Nick!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Ah ha ha ha... Time's running out sweetie! Pick a card, any card!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">T-This one...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Uh-huh. I thought you would pick that one sweetie. The ace of hearts!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHHH!!! He got it! He got it! NICK! LOOK! HE GOT IT!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">What can I say sweetie... You've stolen one of my most valued possessions. One of Maximillion Galactica's hearts...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max... *swoon*</line>
<line speaker="Max">Well... Time to make this an absolutely fabulous time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max! You should let Nick pick a card!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eek... I don't want to steal one of his hearts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">And you are...? Oh, how silly of me! You must be sweetie's driver!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Her driver?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Whatever... Hurry up and pick a card, any card...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I want this one.</line>
<line speaker="Max">So sweetie, let's be honest here... You came to this visitor's room to visit me, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yes! I'm your biggest fan!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Fabulous! Absolutely fabulous! Thank you so much!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey... Umm... What about my card?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Think of it as a souvenir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well Nick... I think it's time to get to work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter, Nick? Why are you looking at the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just thinking about what I should have for lunch.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Sweetie... Drop porcupine head over there. Shower me with your attention. OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Y-Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Ab-so-lute-ly... FABULOUS!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Absolutely cringe inducing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera. Max keeps sneaking glances up at the security camera on the wall... I wonder if he is still trying to be a star?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He's so quiet, you could forget he was even there... If he wasn't watching everything. He's pushed up against the wall... Kinda like a magnet on a refrigerator.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max, I was hoping you could tell me a little bit more about yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Max">FABULOUS! I think we should get to know each other better, too! Why don't you come sit next to me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... There's a big piece of security glass between us...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh sweet geebus! What in the world!? If only I could use magic! Then I could make this wall disappear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is this guy talking about!?</thought> Anyways... Lately, you've become awfully famous, haven't you Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's Maximillion to you, porcupine head! Get it straight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jeez, people nowadays... They get their panties all in a bunch over nothing!</thought> Anyway, Maximillion, you won a very prestigious award recently, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I did indeed! It was FABULOUS! I won the Magician's Grand Prix, held by the Association of International Magicians. It's an award that recognizes that I am the most fabulouso of fabulous world magicians. There was a trophy, and a bust. It was a fab... I mean it was an amazing day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! That's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Isn't it!? I'm certainly the greatest magician in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going to guess he didn't win a trophy for most modest magician.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You are signed to an exclusive contract with the Berry Big Circus, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's the long and short of it. You sure do your research sweetie! I'm impressed. You just can't watch a magician on TV, you know!? Magic is so fabulous, you have to see it with your own eyes, sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right! You're so right!</line>
<line speaker="Max">However, the circus... It's a dinosaur. A thing of the past. Nowadays, no one even cares about what goes on there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's why I signed the contract!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's why you signed the contract?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Thanks to me, the Berry Big Circus is fabulously popular! People come out in droves to catch a glimpse of the magic of Max Galactica! I revived the dinosaur that is the circus! But to me, it was just another magic trick! Isn't it just wonderful, sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Max">I made all the old crusty performances obsolete!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But I kinda like the circus performances...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya looks a bit down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me what happened at the Berry Big Circus.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Ahh... Last night. The Ringmaster was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Ringmaster... You mean Russell Berry?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Someone smashed him over the head, I hear. He was slumped over on the ground. Even though it was the middle of the night, the police presence was fabulous. The police questioned me at length...</line>
<line speaker="Max">About everything... I was the last one to see the Ringmaster before he was murdered. I saw him that night... In his room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then why were you arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Arrested? Don't make an ant hill into a mountain, sweetie. They just wanted to consult with me on the matters... That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... I don't think Max understands how serious this is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right... I think I should shock him back to reality...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before the murder, you met with the Ringmaster?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Uh-huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Things that aren't for your ears.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya. Would you please ask him?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What did you talk about with the Ringmaster, Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">It was nothing... Small talk really... We were just having a chat about my salary.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Salary?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I am the one bringing in all of the crowds to the circus. I think that I should be compensated as such. You agree, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all you talked about?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Of course! It was a fabulous chat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fabulous! Why does he have to keep saying fabulous!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter, Nick? You look all bent out of shape.</line>
<line speaker="Max">When you make absolutely fabulous magic... It costs enormous sums of money. Sums that will boggle your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's why you went to his room that night...?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I went to ask him for a fabulous raise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder how people can lie with such a straight face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">What is that badge? Is it used in a disappearing act?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not a magician, Max. I'm an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Max">An attorney? Then why are you wasting your time talking to me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He isn't wasting his time! Max... You're...</line>
<line speaker="Max">OK! OK! Relax, sweetie... You're just a little overanxious I think...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*whimper*</line>
<line speaker="Max">So, would you like to come up on stage with me sometime?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Re-Really? Is that really OK?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'll bring you up on stage as a volunteer from the audience!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">REALLY!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'll give you something before the show, and then on stage you'll sneak it to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second... He's planting her in the audience to rig a magic trick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I guess I have no choice... But really, is this the proper time or place for this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He signed his own photo...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... You mind giving that to me when the case is over?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Fabulous!! You'd like me to sign this for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">... Anyways... I've been curious about something for a while now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Why do you keep looking at me with such a sad look on your face, sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Be-Because! You've been arrested! For murder!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh, don't be ignorant. They wouldn't arrest someone like me!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Obviously because I'm the fabulous Maximillion Galactica!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'm the very big star of the Berry Big Circus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that means?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'm rich. I'm paid fabulous sums!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which means what?</line>
<line speaker="Max">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Quit joking around! You've got to be pulling my magic wand! The police aren't really serious about all this, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They don't arrest people as a joke.</line>
<line speaker="Max">...!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at Max... He's crushed...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well he needed to wake up and smell the coffee. <thought>This is serious business.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Umm... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Porcu... I mean, Sir. You're a lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, yeah. I'm an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Please! Help me! I didn't kill nobody!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Didn't kill nobody!?"</line>
<line speaker="Max">I may be more spoiled than a hog in a hamburger mud pit... But a killer!? That's insane... I... I... I could never...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I swear!! I just wanted to pay off my daddy's debt... He's back on the farm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK... OK... I'll take your case.</line>
<line speaker="Max">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Uh... Thank ya much. Ya'll sure are nice folks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Max.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's your real name?</line>
<line speaker="Max">It's Billy Bob Johns...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's really just a country bumpkin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Max">...Ahem. I must apologize for not being my absolutely fabulous self just now, sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Mr. Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Max">A few minutes ago, you took one of my cards, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Now that he mentions it... I did take a card.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">It was the 10 of Hearts. Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wha... How'd he... He got it right, again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">What can I say? You too... You've stolen some of my most valued possessions. Ten of Maximillion Galactica's hearts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You sure do have a lot of hearts, don't you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Ah ha ha ha... I'm putting my faith in you sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He didn't just call me sweetie, did he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! Let's make this an absolutely fabulous case! C'mon Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright... We've got lots of things we have to look into. No time for slacking. Let's get going.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">? What's the matter? You seem down.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maximilion Galactica... Who would have guessed he was country bumpkin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So now what do we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? There's still lots of things we can do! Go to the scene of the crime, talk to witnesses, gather evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We still don't even know what happened in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We don't have enough information to make a case yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I could have sworn I've heard that before.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we never have enough information!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just admit it, you don't have a clue what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Your badge is still shining. Barely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It may be showing a bit of wear, but I try to take good care of this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You sure do love to show that off, don't you Nick? Who knows how many times you have shown it to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right... I whip it out at the drop of a hat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Once you start channeling spirits... They say you lose sight of who you actually are...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Do you really believe that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not really. But... Just in case, I plan to write my autobiography.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your autobiography...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter? You've been acting strange for a while now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max... He's just some country bumpkin...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So? Why does that matter? He's still a famous magician right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess. But his real name is... Billy Bob Johns.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! The poor guy's got three first names! I guess that is pretty odd.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh well! If a big star can do it, then you should pretend to be exotic too, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"A big star..."?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max Galactica is a pretty big name! Anyways, what do you think about Naruhodo A. Wrighto?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-N-Na... *cough* Umm... What's the "A" stand for?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "A" stands for "Attorney".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll think about it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is kinda pointless don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If it's that pointless, then you don't have to worry about showing it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When she's right... She's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're here again...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. But this time we are here for work. <thought>It hasn't been that long since the crime, so the police are still on the scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's find someone who might know something about what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sounds like a plan.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Berry Big Top is so... Very... B... *cough* Enormous...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. One look at the huge tent looming over you and you realize "This is the circus!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know! I know! It really gets your blood pumping doesn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look! Look! It's Max!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even when you don't want to see him... *poof* He's right in front of you. <thought>Sure the sign says "Berry Big Circus"... But looking around... It might as well be Cirque du Galactica...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The stars on his cheek sure are dreamy... How about I draw a star on your cheek Nick? I've got a marker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah! Nah! It's alright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those streamers do a nice job introducing the circus performers.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Maximillion Galactica and his comical comrades!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... You don't really see too many streamers nowadays, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right. I haven't seen one in ages. I bet they stopped using them due to little kids climbing up to the top...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... I don't think that was why...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a snack stand. They have hot dogs, hamburgers, and drinks... Not to mention...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Candy and popcorn... They've even got snow cones!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who would eat snow cones in the middle of winter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Do you think we can buy some snow cones?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look around... There's tons of snow piled up all around here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">YAY!! Wait a second... There's no syrup though! I want syrup!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hopefully she doesn't notice that discolored snow in the corner. That's not syrup!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... The entrance is right here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya. The circus is closed today. No clowns. No elephants. No shows.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know that! Nick... You can get your picture taken with Dali the elephant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no Dali. Not today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know that too! Oh well... I'll just have to take a picture with whoever I stumble across...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh* It's not like we're here on business or anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the Box Office where they sell all the tickets for the circus.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They also sell programs. I forgot to buy one when we came to the circus last time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So then why don't you buy one now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Sounds like a plan. Oh no... It looks like I forgot my wallet. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you want me to buy it for you, just ask me already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know I'd never do that to you, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... This door must lead to the lodging house.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"No Entry To Unauthorized Personnel"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you really need to say "No Entry" if no one's actually entering? It's almost like a zen riddle, isn't it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not even going to justify that question with a response...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet all of the stars stay at that lodging house.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This seems to be a dorm where all the performers in the circus stay...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? So that stoogey clown should be here, huh? He's so kooky!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahhh! It's you two!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I always see you hanging around when I'm working a crime scene, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You always seem to be working so hard, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'd rather not be working hard, but with crime you don't make your own hours. If I have to be at the circus anyways, I want to see the lion tamer and the tightrope. However, no matter where I go, the show is always the same... Dead body. Stage left.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Nick! He complained!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh heh... That's a rarity. Let's get back to business now, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some evidence under the tarp over there...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Watch it, pal! The killer is behind that tarp!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho! Ho! Ho! Got ya! I was just kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">GRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho! Ho! Ho! Ho! Ho!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This year, I finally won an air conditioner!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? You didn't have an air conditioner? Did you ride your triceratops to work too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what do you mean you "won" an air conditioner? You didn't buy it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't afford one of those things!! But I got lucky and won it as a door prize at the Annual Police Christmas Party!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They really pay you peanuts don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Peanuts? I don't even get paid enough for peanut butter, let alone peanuts!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The safety lights around the circus are kept on all night long. So, they should have been on at the time of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he's saying the murder took place in the light...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How strange...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How strange indeed... Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the only place that the snow has been trounced upon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The murderer was sloppy leaving all these prints all over!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No no no no no... We're the ones who left the prints... An investigation can be a messy thing sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I also slipped and fell in that spot over there. The other detectives all got a good laugh when the prosecutor whipped me. Thank god there was all this snow around to bring down the swelling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's great to know that the police aren't worried about preserving the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know who will be the prosecutor in court tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course. It will be Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhhh... She isn't gonna hit me with her whip again, is she?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What do you have to worry about? You only have to see her in court! When she shows up at the precinct, the sound of that whip never ends, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe... That's enough about Von Karma. What about that guy? What is he up to?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That guy?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What happened to Edgeworth? You know! The Edgeworth that's Nick's rival! What in the world happened when I went back home!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth... You haven't heard what happened to him?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick won't tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, to be honest... I'm not at liberty to tell you either. Let's just say he's not around anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's not around!?!? Nick! What does he mean Mr. Edgeworth isn't around!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly what he said. He's not around. Edgeworth is gone... Don't say his name again, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Ringmaster of the circus was murdered, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep. Last night around 10 PM. He died outside in the cold. A pretty sad way to go out if you ask me, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... It was rather cold.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is the scene of the crime, pal. The body was found right over there. Right about where you are standing now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHHHHHHHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho! Ho! Ho! Surprised you, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not laughing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but do you mind telling me what happened to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was killed by a blow to the noggin, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeep!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's pretty clear cut as far as murders go. He was discovered quickly. But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's just one thing that doesn't quite fit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hah! There always seems to be something that doesn't quite fit!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was this one thing that just didn't quite fit? The thing you mentioned earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Footprints, pal. Footprints.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look at this picture of the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? This wooden box under the body?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No clue, pal. Some forensics experts took it back and are examining it now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... And... What is so mysterious about the footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa. Calm down now. Take a good look at the footprints in this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim's footprints are on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal. The problem is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! The killer's footprints aren't there!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bingo. Where did the killer come from, and where did the killer run off to? Obviously, there is no way the killer committed this crime while flying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A flying... Criminal? <thought>That's when something just clicked in my head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">T-There's no way! Flying is impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Flying is impossible! Absolutely impossible! Haha...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's with the hollow laugh, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I meant nothing by it, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Better stated, it means I don't want to talk about it. Maybe I can get some info about Max out of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... How about any eyewitnesses...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho! Ho! Ho! You know I'm not going to tell you that! That's the prosecution's trump card!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Oh well...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Oh! I just remembered!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I forgot to mention that you two are barred from entering that lodging house.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh... No reason! Just something I remembered to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It must be because there's an eyewitness inside that Lodging House.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh no you don't, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">C'non. You've flashed that badge at me so many times it doesn't work anymore! Why don't you try wearing a different badge every now and again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... I do have a Steel Samurai Badge with me. How about that one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll only wear it if Detective Gumshoe carries a Steel Samurai Police Badge.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then it's a deal! I hear that Detective Gumshoe has that very badge! ...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Don't look at me like that!! You're making me nervous!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Being a spirit medium is quite an accomplishment... And you're so young too! That's really something!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, I've been thinking of taking a break from channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't want to have another incident like last time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It looks like Max is the most unpopular guy in the circus tent. You know what they say... A bad attitude follows you everywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, he's a bit arrogant, but he didn't seem that bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">But just because someone has a bad attitude doesn't make them a criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not just his attitude... I've got proof, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He left something at the scene of the crime! One of his magician's trademarks! An incredibly well-made silk hat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well it does have very classy decorative elements.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Max uses a cloak, silk hat, and white roses as his signature symbols.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Pretty mundane, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who cares if they are mundane!? At least they are easy to understand!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I must have hit a nerve...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who said?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The eyewitness.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-Tell us about the eyewitness!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I'm making a really strange tired looking face here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Are you sure you weren't born looking like that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wish I was more lively... ... Right now, I'm just tired.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, there's not much you can do about that, so you just gotta keep on being tired!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Glad I stayed out of that one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're going down this time, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She's been practicing 100 cracks a day, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cracks? Wait... You don't mean cracks of the...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep. Cracks of the WHIP!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know I can't tell you two anything about the evidence we have gathered!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stingy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Stingy!? When you put it so bluntly, it kinda hurts my feelings, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The name tag on the door says "Moe" on it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess he's not here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... It's a real mess in here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My room's probably worse though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh well... I give up. We'll have to come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All those clown costumes lined up like that... I dunno about you, but it's creepy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look at the collection he's got! It's incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must be a collection of clown costumes from around the world.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I almost forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it now? <thought>She better not want me to try one of those on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I was thinking of starting a costume collection myself! I'll call it "World Spirit Channels"... We can display it in our office!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In OUR office!? As soon as you start paying the bills, you can say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the ceiling... It looks like someone punched a hole in it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right. I wonder what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I don't even want to imagine what goes on in here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What the!? There's a string of carrots here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How strange. The carrots seem to come in all different shapes... Weird... I can't tell if Moe just likes carrots, or if he is using them for some sort of gag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you can see the scene of the crime from here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You can even tell that the ground has been disturbed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's right in front of this window, about 30 feet away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it wouldn't have been strange for someone to have seen the crime from here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe's got an excellent pair of pajamas... Laid on his bed in an excellent manner.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Those are pajamas? You mean he goes to bed dressed as a clown? Eww...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe seems to be a voracious reader. Look at all the hard books he has here. "Clowns for Dummies", "The Joke's On You", "Treat Your Peons Right", And the classic "Funny Jokes Are Funny."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. Moe is very studious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"The Joke's On You"... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tee hee... Clown equipment is so funny looking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's got a balancing ball, a unicycle... He's even got a trampoline!! ... But they're all broken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe he was just a little too excited during practice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who knows with that guy. Maybe that's part of the gag?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awesome! Look at these shoes! They're great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Forget the shoes! Check out the great gag banana peel!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You sure it wasn't Moe's snack after lunch?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you blind? Look at how many scratches there are from people slipping on it!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The circus stage sure doesn't look this small from out in the audience...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... This is where they all perform, isn't it? Nick! Do some somersaults!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not doing any somersaults.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why not!? You look like you'd be great at it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I look like I'd be great at somersaults!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Grrrrrrrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="???">Grrrrrrrrrrr... Grawwwwwww!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">T-T-T-T-T-T-T... TIGER!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-H-H-He's c-c-coming this way!!</line>
<line speaker="???">Grrrrrrrrr... Grawwwwwww!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AHHHHHHHHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You're too young to die! NICK!!</line>
<line speaker="???">STAY! STAY! HEEL!</line>
<line speaker="???">Grrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm still here... I'm not dead, yet!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Nick! Are you OK?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahahaha! Scared ya didn't I? Regent is such a cute tiger! Isn't he!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="???">What's the matter? You two sure are quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't "What's the matter?" me! N-Nick... He almost died there!!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hah! He wasn't anywhere close to getting hurt, let alone dying! This little tiger hardly ever bites people. And besides, people normally never get to play with a wild tiger, right? So if you think about it, you're actually really lucky!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="???">You agree, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-W-W-What do you mean you guess!? Why are you agreeing with her?</line>
<line speaker="???">Woohoo!! Your costume...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="???">It's cute. I wanna try it on!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C-Costume? You mean my clothes...?</line>
<line speaker="???">You don't mind letting me try it on, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uhh... I guess not...</line>
<line speaker="???">REALLY!? Hehehehehe!! You're the best!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... The tables turned quickly on that one. So much for the tiger thing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh! I forgot to introduce myself. I'm Regina Berry... The renowned animal tamer of the Berry Big Circus!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My name's Maya Fey. I'm a spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix Wright. Attorney at law. <thought>When you put us up next to an animal tamer, I bet we really look odd!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">Nice to meet ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh... Likewise...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The seats are kinda far away don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They are, but it also means that lots of people can fit in the big top.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">He's right. We can fit 500 people into a show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Five hundred... That's amazing.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Flying around above that many people is a "real rush". At least that's what Max said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah, a ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the difference? They do the same thing, right? I think you should stick with the basic facts of the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... Uh... OK. <thought>It's not even worth arguing with her on this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look! That's where Max comes out during the show!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got to admit, that was a pretty cool effect!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">We're planning for me to start coming out of the lion during the show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's great Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah. I will ride on Regent's back and jump out of the lion's mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wanna try it too! I'll ride on Nick's back and jump out of the lion's mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sometimes I wonder about this girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There doesn't seem to be anything here that can help us... Not a single clue.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know I've been meaning to ask you... What exactly do you mean when you say "clue"? What are you looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... A bloody chainsaw for instance...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well there's definitely not one of those here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! It's a rope!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably for tightrope walking...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's a bit strange... There weren't any tightrope walkers in the show when we saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! Those lights are huge!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I love lights!! Whenever I appear under the spotlight, everyone claps for me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's because everyone knows that you're cute!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">No... I'm not cute. You're cute!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Of course! I'm sure you'd make an incredible heroine!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? You think so!? Nick! Did you hear that!? Me!! A heroine!! What about Nick, Regina?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">... Hmm... Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's no hero, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch... Thanks a lot Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Regina... What do you know about what happened last night?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">You mean the murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh huh.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">My dad was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't imagine how hard this must be for you... <thought>Urk! That was insensitive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! The Ringmaster was your...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yep. The Ringmaster was my dad.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm so sorry about what happened to him...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Why do you say you're sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Anyways... Everyone was here practicing last night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even your dad?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes. Everyone was here. We finished up around 10 PM. After that, everyone went off on their own. I was the only one who stayed around here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why did you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I was playing with Regent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Regent... So she was with that beast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">That's when the police showed up. When they took me to check things out, Dad was dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For someone who's* ([sic]</thought> father was just murdered, she seems awfully perky... I wish she would tell us more about her dad...)</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's incredible that you are an animal tamer!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">If you say so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It has to be really scary!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Scary? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Regent isn't scary! He's cute! Ever since Léon died, Regent has been my best friend.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Léon?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes. Léon the lion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Léon the lion... Regent and Regina... Interesting name choices...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Léon... He died?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes. Actually he was killed. My dad killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why did he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I'm not sure why he did it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's tough not to get charmed when she looks at you with those innocent eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina... What's the matter? What's on your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">*giggle* I'll tell you Maya... But just you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Umm... Well... *mumble* *mumble*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? REALLY!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">And then... *mumble* *mumble*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh my! That's incredible Regina!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon Nick. There's no reason to pout!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry about me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina told me that someone professed their love to her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-P-P-Professed their love!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not only that! It was Maximillion Galactica!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder how many people have stolen one of his hearts anyways...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">And then, on the exact same day, another person professed their love for her as well!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Someone named Trilo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Apparently he is a tenor who sings in the circus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Haven't met him yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina seems to be quite the hit with the men in the circus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She must have some sort of strange power over them!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're not kidding. Two people in one day! Even I want to profess my love for her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Me too! She's so cute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">*giggle*</line>
<line speaker="Regina">This silk hat is Max's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">It's beautiful isn't it? I thought up the idea for wearing the hat.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yep. He took my sketch to the hat shop... And they made a custom hat for him based off the sketch. There is only one of these silk hats in the entire world! Isn't that cool?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Maya... You're a spirit channeler?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep! I'm still training though.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">That sounds like fun! I think you should join us at the circus!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? As a spirit channeler?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yeah! You'd be a big hit!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? She says I'd be a big hit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she's just being nice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">It's Max!! Hey... Where is Max now anyways?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Nope.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's been arrested. He was charged with the murder of your father.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's OK! Nick and I will help him!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Max isn't the guy is he? I mean... The criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course he's not!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I'm worried about so many things right now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">*giggle*</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Cool! This lady's got a whip! She's an animal tamer, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Sort of...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Two women with whips... That's my cue to shut up and act like a good boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">Alright! I look so cute in this picture! Don't you think I look cute? Don't ya? Don't ya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You sure do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No objections here!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">After practice was over, Dad went right back to his room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">His room?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes. That door right over there leads to the Ringmaster's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I dunno why, but he went off to his room in a hurry. I wonder what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Ringmaster's room... It's probably a good idea to check it out for myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this? What can you tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Umm... I'm not really good at figuring out hard things.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? You too? I understand exactly what you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I never expected Maya to make a new friend in a strange place like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I've already given my heart to another man. So I'm not interested in enrolling in your dating service.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I just wanted to know if you knew this person.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Ahh! This is my silk hat! It's the only one of its kind in the world. It's one of my most prized possessions. This silk hat proves that I was somewhere else... Where did they find this? Huh, sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They found it at the murder scene.</line>
<line speaker="Max">AHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! I... I... I don't know nothing about nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eww... Max is so pathetic like this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Max must be really confused...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">That's... That's the Ringmaster. ... It's a shame what happened... He was going to be like a father to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Ahhh... My sweetie pie. She must be really lonely with me all cooped up in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, she was laughing and rolling around with her tiger...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">She is my special someone. And I am her special someone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh-huh... Very complex...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this person?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Unfortunately I don't take on apprentices. I mean, just look at the face on this one... It's not what I'd call fabulous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's awfully harsh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Max isn't here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must be in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... I wanted to see a magic trick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He should be back in a little bit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile, you're on candid camera.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. I wonder if he is bored? He doesn't even try to glance over this way...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've gotten affidavits from most of the performers at this circus. They are certainly a strange bunch of characters.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, not stranger than you I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... That was cold...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm sorry. I was just messing around.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This silk hat really does look like it can fly!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It does have a feather on it. Maybe that's why you think it can take off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right! Nick, I bet you could wear a hat like this! This is like one of those hats a famous detective would wear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... With a head as big as yours, you'd probably bust a hole in the* <thought>[sic]</thought> it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter what the crime, we always meet the same detective at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sometimes it seems like he's the only detective on the force. That would make Gumshoe really elite, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something tells me that no matter how you look at it, he's anything but elite...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, if she wasn't so mean, I think she and I would get along...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but that's the problem... She is so mean. And that whip... That thing hurts. It really hurts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It is kinda cool though. I wouldn't mind having a whip myself. I bet that cracking the whip on you once or twice would be just what the doctor ordered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Why me!? W-What did I do!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina is sooo cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to admit that her smile does have a sort of hypnotic power.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you believe that she's an animal tamer? That's sooo cool! I'd like to try animal taming someday. Nick! Nick! Lie down! Roll over!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Once this case is solved, I'll roll over for you as many times as you want!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">YAY!!! Remember, you promised, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everyone loved the Ringmaster...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I'm told. Why would anyone want to kill such a beloved man of the big top?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Motive will surely be a point of contention tomorrow in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You can count on that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This was the Ringmaster's room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. This room belonged to the victim. Which means this must be where Max met the Ringmaster last night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that you mention it, that is what he said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder what... Hmm... That's an intresting* <thought>[sic]</thought> poster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! It's a poster of Max! I want it! I want it! Nick! I want it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanna get outta here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Look at all the photos lined up on the wall...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's like a guided tour of the circus' history.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is so cool! It seems like there were so many happy memories. Maybe we should do this sort of thing at our office? Wa can put up pictures of all the clients who have been found not guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the clients who were found guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... We'll just pretend like they don't exist. How's that? ... Nick! Now you've got me thinking about losing cases! Why'd you do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All of these frames look the same.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They almost look like... Thank You cards. It looks like every year the Ringmaster made donations to charity... To the Robot Clown Research Center...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... You're kidding right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? They may be a perfectly reputable charity in the field of advanced tomfoolery!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look at all the cute trophies!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed. Just look at all the awards this circus has won...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like... "All County Quiz Champions"... "Ringmaster's Association Mini Golf Master"... "Beer Belly Balloon Bounce Champ"... "Pet Grooming Grand Prix"... Wow. The Ringmaster was multi-talented in ways I could have never imagined...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a lot of posters here don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So many posters that they aren't likely to miss one, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... We're supposed to be the honest ones around here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... But... You didn't even notice that I took one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Arghhh... She already swiped one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh! Heh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're incorrigible, you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at all the stars on this poster... This must have been the poster they used to promote their public appearances.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Posters are the way to go aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We should make posters to promote our law firm. "Spine tingling legal action! Mind numbing legalese! You will say 'wow'!" Or perhaps, "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> Don't miss out on a stunning life or death courtroom thrill ride!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With those taglines, our law firm would sink faster than the Titanic...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You may not know this, but they call this a "tailcoat".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And they call this "the face of someone who already knew that..." Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A scrap of white paper is sticking out of the coat pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Where? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Calm down, Maya. You can't just go rummaging through people's coats!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahhh... You always make me feel like I'm doing something wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is where the Ringmaster applied his makeup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite a collection of the most understated colors. Shocking Pink for example.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This one says it is "100% All Natural Organic Mascara."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And this one says "Sensitive enough for a baby, strong enough for a mime."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The Ringmaster must have been really concerned about skin care... Very metrosexual.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is strange... Everything else looks nice, but this desk looks old and cheap.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a really big photo on the desk... It's a picture of Regina and her father, the Ringmaster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He really loved her didn't he? Regina was lucky to have such a wonderful father.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a table for guests... There are some papers scattered on top.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Look at this! Max's salary is written on this piece of paper. YIKES!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't know a magician... This salary is incredible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She looks like she's about ready to pass out from shock...</thought> How much is it!? How much is it!? T-T-THAT MUCH!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Incredible, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can say that again. <thought>This must be the paper they used to negotiate Max's salary... The Ringmaster signed and dated it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Max definitely got a raise... But this document is dated a week ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was the table he used when visitors came to see him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eww... There's mud caked on the table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone with terrible manners must have put their shoes up on the table!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't even think about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wasn't! How uncouth do you think I am anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Hey Nick! Look over there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's someone over there! Ex-Excuse me!</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello.</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! He sure is a quiet one! Excuse me!!</line>
<line speaker="???">Wha... Ha... Huh? M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. You work at the circus don't you?</line>
<line speaker="???">N-No. I'm just your everyday average Joe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An average Joe who just happens to hang out at the circus? I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="???">Y-Yes I am. I've got nothing to do with what's going on here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's lying. Like any regular person would hang around the circus... Dressed like that!</thought> I'm an attorney. My name is Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm a spirit medium. My name is Maya.</line>
<line speaker="???">Well... I... Um... Just happened to be... Umm... Passing by...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't suppose you happen to be some kind of carny?</line>
<line speaker="???">Not a c-c-carny... I-I'm a p-performer. Actually, I'm a v-v-v-ventriloquist.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ventriloquist?</line>
<line speaker="???">He-he-he-he-he-he-he... I-I-I'm Benjamin Wo-Wo-Wo-Woodman...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're* <thought>[sic]</thought> last name is Woodman? *snicker*</line>
<line speaker="???">Y-Yes... T-T-That's right... But e-everyone c-c-calls me B-B-B-B-B-Ben.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah... Yes yes yes... That's your alias, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe they call it a stage name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Uh... Yes? You mean... Me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the murder. I'd like to talk to you about the details, if I may.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">R-Really... I'm just a regular normal guy... I don't k-k-now... A-a-a-a...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This guy's so nervous, he's creeping me out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick. Cheer up! Just try and smile!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Would you mind telling us something about Max? Maximillion Galactica. </line>
<line speaker="Ben">Ma-Ma-Ma-Max? H-H-H-He's... N-N-N-Not... V-Very... N-N-Nice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did he just say that Max is "Not Very Nice"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ben">O... O... O... Oww... My... H-H-Head... Hurts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. I hope he is OK. It sounds like he just popped a gasket...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ben, so you're a ventriloquist?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I-I-I-I'm... J-J-J-Just A-A... R-R-R-Regular... G-G-Guy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You already told us that you were a ventriloquist!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Oh... Y-Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't yell at him! You can't do that!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't help it! He's making me nervous!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ben, do you mind showing me some of your skills as a ventriloquist?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">W-W-Well... I-I-I... R-R-R-Right... N-N-Now... M-M-My... P-P-P...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-A-A-A-Ah... I-I-I-I-I W-W-W-W-Why... <thought>Urk!! He's contagious!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Would you mind taking a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Um... Umm... Uh... I-I-I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I guess we won't need you to look at this after all.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Ahh, that guy. His name is Ben, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You don't know him?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I dunno... He didn't really catch my eye. He's friends with Trilo right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... We're the ones asking the questions around here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Which poster is cooler? This one or the Steel Samurai poster?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not a big fan of either one of them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess putting a poster of a magician in a law office is kinda strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No stranger than a poster of a hunk of junk carrying around a spear!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looking at this really makes you think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No matter how great a medium I become, there is no way I could make this kind of money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it's money you're after?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You only live once, right? Well, then you might as well live it fabulously!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Being a ventriloquist sounds like an interesting job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet it's fun once you get good at it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe I should give it a try then! Here I go! "Hello e-e-everyone... I-I-I'm Phoenix Wright." "No matter what the lie or who the liar, I'll expose them for what they are!" What's the verdict?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You might want to practice not moving your lips so much.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-Yeah... Maybe I should sign up for some expert training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't you have another type of training to attend to, young lady...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hello...?</line>
<line speaker="???">KABLAMMO! CONGRATULATIONS! YOU'RE THE BIG WEINER! The one millionth visitor to the room of one Mr. Moe Curls, AKA ME!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Earplugs... Must... Find... Earplugs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">To celebrate this momentous occasion, would you care for an organic grape? Just one! Did you get my joke right there!? Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I welched on giving you more than one!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">No no no! If it was funny, it is your duty as a human being to laugh!! People who don't laugh are usually last-seen in Lan-sing. Catch my drift? Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is like some Faustian nightmare...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon! It was funny! Clowns are always funny in my book!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In my book, they're just funny lookin'.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You sure do have a great taste in clothes girlie! Look at that garb! You look just like Gretta Garb... OH! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* I'm goin' home...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! Nick! You can't!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I can excuse a bad joke or two... But this stooge keeps laughing at his own jokes! That's what I object to!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">OK OK... I get it. But you have to admit he is kinda funny...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argghhh... No, I do not have to admit that, because he isn't!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I look awfully snazzy in these costumes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Did you just use the word "snazzy" in a sentence?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I sure did. These are haute couture from the best international clown designers. At least, that's what they said on the TV shopping channel I use... I like having a big collection so I can match my costume to my mood... And my carrot.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You know, I only own one T-shirt. The rest are all clown costumes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Snazzy dresser!? More like spazzy dresser if you ask me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a hole in the ceiling... Why is there a hole in the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Umm... I was riding a pogo stick, and I guess I just overdid it a little...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Overdid it a little"...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">What can I say, sometimes things get a bit crazy in one's college days...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Carrots are one of my trademark props.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yep! I saw you use them! You must believe in a carrot and no stick approach. You put the carrot out in front for motivation, but I guess the trick is gauging what flavor you want each day...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly! You were really paying attention, weren't you!? You know, I eat about 5 of those carrots every single day. If you eat that many, you've gotta change up the taste every now and again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't understand any of that, nor do I ever want to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe, you've got quite the collection of pajamas... They really scream out to you.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You think they're loud, huh? I kinda thought they were refined... You know, a bit too adult for me to use on stage... That's why I used them as pajamas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second... He sleeps in clown costumes!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Take a look at my desk. Aren't I the most studious clown you've ever seen? Every free moment I have, I spend it studying or reading.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The classic "Pull My Finger" or "Clown Car Maintenance and Repair".. Not to mention the bestseller "Jean-Luc de Laduc's Guide To Obnoxious French Pierrots"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... They all seem to cover rather basic topics though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe he is just trying to cover all of his bases?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly! I want to be a renaissance clown!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad he didn't buy "How To Be A Funny Clown"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Us clowns really take our work seriously. I try to hone my craft day and night, with the latest in jester technology. Unicycles. Trampolines. Balancing Balls. Accordions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like you've put quite a bit of wear and tear on that equipment...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... The theme of my act as a clown is... "How many ways can a fat funny guy fall down?" I don't care what I break or how I break it, as long as it ends with me on my bum!! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this? A banana peel? *slips*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh my! Oh my! What a wonderful fall girlie! You should remember that when you see a banana peel, get ready to fall down! That is one of the basic tenants of clownsmanship.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ow ow ow ow ow...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Every night, I fall down 100 times to practice the proper banana peel breakfall. WHOA! *slip* WHOA! *slip* WHOA! *slip*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. He really is a pro, huh Nick!? His falls are totally different than my slip!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Could you please tell us more about the Berry Big Circus?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's a Berry Big story... You sure you got that kind of time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the hits just keep on comin'... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">This circus has been in business for 20 years. We all performed under the guidance of the Ringmaster, Russell Berry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Twenty years!? Wow!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Working in the circus is never easy, especially nowadays... With movies, TV, and bowling, there is just too much competition.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... But... I LOVE THE CIRCUS!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I love it too... That is why I've been here for 20 years. We work hard to keep the show running. No one sends in the clowns on us!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! He just made a joke! Laugh!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Har! Har! Har! Har! Har! Har!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The Ringmaster was a real big shot in the circus world. A real class act. Even when there were no customers, Russell would use his own money to pay me. Because he knew that I had a family to care for... He was happy to take care of his employees.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">How could anyone do that to such a wonderful man...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Wiggidty-wiggidty-wiggidty WHAT?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry Moe. Nick was born without a sense of humor.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Don't worry about it... How can you fault someone for being born that way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's talk about the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ahh... Let's see... It must've taken place around 10 PM last night. After rehearsals were finished, I was tuckered out, so I came back here. After I went to bed... That's when I caught a peek of it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Caught a peek...?"</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is what Detective Gumshoe was talking about... Moe was the eyewitness to the crime!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">The Ringmaster was truly ahead of his time. He would always add new elements to the show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">New elements...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">When you've been a performer for a long time, your act starts getting a bit stale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I realize that even my act can get a bit long in the tooth... Sometimes my jokes can be a bit... Umm... Old-fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"A bit long in the tooth?"</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But that make-believer takes things too far!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Make-believer?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The magician!! The one that thinks he's all high and mighty!! He had the gall to say to me, "You're one of those funny types, right?" What does he mean "one of those"!? Well the joke's on him now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On him...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yep! He got on everyone's nerves!! The day of the murder... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Nope. No way! Just forget I said anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet he's still hiding something about Max...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you saw the crime. Do you mind telling me what you saw?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well, the police told me that I can't share my story with others. "Don't say a word!!" I'm just gonna have to let these lips stay zipped!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not fair!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I guess you're right... Maybe I can tell you a few details. But only if you can get old stiff lips here to make with the funny...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stiff lips? Wait... Do you mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You can do it!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*achem* *achem*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just getting ready. OK... Do you know why I, Phoenix Wright, am a great lawyer? Because I'm Wright all the time!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">At least his expectations are low.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I wouldn't let him quit his day job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Geesh, cut a guy some slack. At least it was funnier than Chuckles over here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">It wasn't the greatest joke I've heard, but you did try, so I'll tell you what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry he's incapable of being funny, Moe.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That night... Once I had tucked myself into bed, I heard this amazing noise. It was incredibly loud. It sounded like a giant "THUMP"! Once I heard it, I jumped out of bed. That's when I saw... Without question. Without a doubt. It was that magician!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's all I saw... But it just proves how terrible that man actually is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He knows more about Max than he is letting on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">RUSSELL!! How could anyone do this to you... I... I... *sobs*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Moe's taking this really hard...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's that uppity faker's uppity top hat! They found this at the scene of the crime, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I've been told...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Unbelievable. That jerk killed the Ringmaster!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It really is a shame what happened to the Ringmaster, huh Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems that the Ringmaster was truly a great man...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hmph! If he thinks he can kill the Ringmaster, it's only just that he should die too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Moe!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Sorry. I crossed the line. But he truly is a disgusting human being.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why do you hate him so much?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Let me tell you this one story... The morning before the murder, something terrible happened. Max clonked Ben right over the head, as hard as he could.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ben? <thought>The ventriloquist with the speech impediment?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">You should go to the cafeteria and investigate for yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The cafeteria?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Let's just say there's Gotti be something interesting there... Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's the Ringmaster's daughter, Regina. Ever since she was a little girl, she's been watching the circus performances. Cuter than a little puppy Maltese, that Regina. If only my Larina was that cute...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larina?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ah... Larina is my daughter. She lives with her mother now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's true what they say about the tears of a clown...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">I've been friends with Russell since even before the circus began. He was so selfless. He always thought about others before thinking of himself. I'll find a way to return the favor... He always took such good care of me. I wish I would have thanked him more than I did...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ah, Ben... How's he doing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's a ventriloquist isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's right! Boy was I surprised when they told me his secret! He's got a second mouth where his belly button should be!! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Just kidding...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ben wouldn't tell me a single thing about the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ahh... That's a simple problem to solve. He won't talk if he doesn't have his puppet Trilo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trilo...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">If Ben doesn't have his ventriloquist's puppet, you'll barely get a word outta him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Master and puppet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Whenever I see my own pose, I am reminded of my Italian heritage...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahhhh... I see... It must be because you have one of those "Roman Noses"... Roamin' all over your face.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">...!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I didn't cross the line there did I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You went so far past it, you'll need a map to get back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this? Anything come to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ahh... You want some advice on your development as a comedian, right? I see... Well... This is what you do... When you tell a joke, imagine everyone's wearing underwear and dancing the lambada...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I think that's enough advice for now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! He was giving you good advice! Don't be so close-minded!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">This isn't very funny... How am I supposed to know about people who aren't in the circus!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah! Thank you!! Umm... This is an atlas!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Oh... I kill myself. Really. I'm dying here... CORONARY! CORONARY!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now he's just laughing to hear his own voice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Moe is a really nice guy, don't you think Nick? He taught us all about the inner workings of the circus.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. It definitely made me look at things in a new light.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And he's got such a great sense of humor. It tickles your funny bone, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well... I can't argue that some people might find it funny... But the only thing it tickles on me is my desire for high quality earplugs...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">That's Moe! He's such a funny clown! He's been a good friend to my dad for a really long time now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He was good friends with the Ringmaster?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">My dad always said... "When it comes to who I can entrust the circus to, it's definitely Moe."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Yep! That clown is one lovable stooge. Don't you think so, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... No comment...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eww... This place is gross.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be because of last night. They didn't have time to clean up after dinner because of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That reminds me... What was it that Moe said?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He said that yesterday morning Max "clonked" Ben over the head here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He also said that, "There's Gotti be something interesting there." Nick? What's "Gotti be interesting?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't ask...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The kitchen is over here. Everyone must have taken turns cooking. There's a duty list posted here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wouldn't mind trying my hand at cooking for this many people. Maya's Killer Hamburger... You'd try it, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Keep Our Cafeteria Clean!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't seem like anyone ever read this sign, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe they should make it easier to understand... "Clean it or die!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that would definitely make them clean up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, a bulletin board... For... Umm... Bulletins. It doesn't look like there are any useful clues posted here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boring... Maybe we should leave a juicy tidbit for someone to read!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Juicy?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know... Like a fake clue! Hmm... Maybe something like... "Message from the Killer!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Give it up Maya... You know Gumshoe would take it all seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is strange... There's nothing on top of this stand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look here... Max is written on it. It must be his VIP table.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't a bit small to be a VIP table? You won't be putting a ten course meal on this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, he could still eat hamburgers, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are dirty dishes all over the place... It must have been too hectic last night to clean up.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know I can't stand a mess Nick! I think you and I should clean this place up for them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Why do we have to clean up...!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">One, because I hate dirty cafeterias. Two, because one bears repeating.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... This is a crime scene! We can't clean it up! We have to preserve it for evidence!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Arrrggghh... You know I really hate dirty cafeterias!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not as much as I hate cleaning dirty cafeterias!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like they've left it exactly as it was on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They didn't seem too worried about cleaning up the dishes, did they? Hmm... Looking at all these dishes is making me hungry! Let's go get a burger at the snack stand outside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Once we're finished with the case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Alright! Then let's get this over with Nick!! Here we go!! Whoahh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where's the mute button when you need it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chair's been knocked over.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what it looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It almost looks as if someone knocked it over in a struggle, or used it for self defense...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Or maybe Regent just likes to eat his dinner in the cafeteria?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this? ...Must be a juice bottle or something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahhh... Watch out Nick! Broken glass on the floor is dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... A broken bottle just lying in the middle of the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think it means anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... "There's Gotti be something interesting there."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we're going to have to go back and meet with him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Him?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh! It's my two sweeties! Welcome to the Detention Center!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...*sigh* Did he just call me his sweetie!? AGAIN!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">What's on today's agenda? What can I help you with?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we've gathered quite a few clues...</line>
<line speaker="Max">WON-DER-FUL-LY FAN-TAB-U-LOSO!! I mean fabulous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's why we came to meet with you again.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Wh-Wh-What's w-w-wrong!? Quit making such a scary face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK then Max... Let's make this "absolutely fabulous"!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We heard a lot about you at the circus, Max.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Ahhh, you just mean from the dinosaurs? How were those Jurassic geriatrics?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max, you aren't very popular with the other performers, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Yes yes yes. Sweetie, that's what they call jealousy. J-E-A-L-O-U-S-Y. They are absolutely jealous of my absolutely fabulous self! People who really understand can see the obvious differences between us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People who really understand?</line>
<line speaker="Max">For instance, my sweetie pie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, so Regina understands him huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">I plan on getting married to her. She is truly my sweetie pie princess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! That's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Max">It's already in the works.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's strange. Regina never said anything about marrying this joker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You met with the Ringmaster on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Yes. I was with him around 10 PM. Once I was done with practice. I went to his room right after we finished.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They found the Ringmaster's body in the plaza in front of the lodging house.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Yeah, I head* <thought>[sic]</thought> about that... He needed to step out for a bit, so I waited in his room for him to return.</line>
<line speaker="Russell">"Sorry Max. I have something I must attend to right now. Do you mind waiting for me right here?"</line>
<line speaker="Max">"It's pretty cold outside. Where's your coat?"</line>
<line speaker="Russell">"It's alright. I'll be right back. It should only take about 10 minutes."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I waited for him. But he never came back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did he go to the plaza where the body was discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Possibly. The snow had tapered off a bit, but it was still very cold outside. But I have no idea what he went off to do...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Maximillion Galactica! No matter when you see me, you get shivers don't you? The silk hat... The cloak... The white roses on my chest... They're my symbols... You know I had to cut the number of symbols to three?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really? You had quite a few to begin with then, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Well, I thought that you could never have too many symbols... Sunglasses... Beauty mark... Soft pillows for lips... A beard... Buck teeth... I gave all sorts of symbols a shot. But if I forget one when I put on my makeup, everyone would forget who I am!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's awful... Especially for a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask what you do with such an exorbitant salary?</line>
<line speaker="Max">We've already covered this point. I'm paying off my father's debt.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How could he possibly have such a large amount of debt?</line>
<line speaker="Max">For example, say you rented a video... And perhaps you forgot about it, for say... a short period of about 10 years. You'd would* <thought>[sic]</thought> have the biggest late fee known to man... It's kinda like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... Now I can see how you can get that much debt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That makes sense now. Wait a minute... That doesn't make any sense!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">U-Uh-huh... This woman, huh? Well... My type of woman is a gentle sweetie...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like you are describing Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, he's definitely not describing Franziska!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">Just between you and I... He's* <thought>[sic]</thought> wasn't a bad guy at all. I can say that for sure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... That's the first time I've ever heard you say something nice about someone, Max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He must have really been a nice guy.</line>
<line speaker="Max">I can't believe a guy with that ugly mug is after my sweetie pie princess! Especially after she has eluded my charms for such a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There isn't much you can do about that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Hmph. You haven't even been truly in love, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Max">When you are truly in love with someone... You'd be jealous of their mirror because it traps their image inside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awww... Don't you think that's sweet of him, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I'm gonna get back with my sweetie pie! Then I'm gonna turn that dumb puppet into a toy glider!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I guess you two haven't worked out your differences yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Last night, you met with the Ringmaster, correct? To negotiate your salary, and such?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Exactly... We reached an agreement about the salary from my 6 month old contract.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the truth? The whole truth?</line>
<line speaker="Max">What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just went to his office to negotiate your new salary?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I hate lies and I hate liars even more! What are you insinuating!? Do you have any proof that I did something other than negotiate my fee last night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">Geebus...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Sweetie, you must have some wax build up in your ears. You haven't listened to me at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You're still not listening are you? I said that I HATE LIES!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It seems this evidence isn't enough to make him confess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">You want to try again? It doesn't bother me at all!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Th-Tha-That's!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was on the table in the Ringmaster's room. You weren't lying when you said that you received quite a raise...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Is there a problem with being well compensated?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not with the compensation... Just with the date. This is dated a week ago.</line>
<line speaker="Max">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Max! You finished your contract negotiations a week ago!</line>
<line speaker="Max">F-Fa-Fab-Fabulous!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">... Alright. I'll tell you the truth. That night... The Ringmaster called me to his room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He called you? Why did he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Sorry sweetie... That's private.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Ringmaster called him... I wonder if there was some sort of problem?</thought> Um... Max? Perhaps you could share with me what you two spoke about?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Well... Not if I don't have to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't this why the Ringmaster called you into his room that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't this why you were called to the Ringmaster's room that night?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Wh-Where did you get that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cafeteria... But you already knew that didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Max">...! O-Of course...</line>
<line speaker="Max">It fell and broke on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's still hiding something else.</thought> Max.</line>
<line speaker="Max">What is it my sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It didn't fall and break on the floor. You used this bottle to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">B-Ben...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You nailed him over the head with this bottle, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Max">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you got called to the Ringmaster's room that night.</line>
<line speaker="Max">F-F-F-FAAAABBBUUULLOUS! You might as well be a magician!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">Will you give up on this... Please... Sweetie...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Max">If you don't shape up, I'm gonna beat you over the head with that bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did I do? Hmm... I must be on the wrong track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Max">I already told you! It fell to the floor and broke.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He won't tell me the truth!</thought> ... Max.</line>
<line speaker="Max">What is it my sweetie?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">B-B-Ben... H-He...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had a run-in with Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I didn't do anything to Ben. I-I didn't get in a fight with him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah-ha! So you're admitting that you did have a fight with someone!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Wh-Why are you looking at me all funny!? No one said anything like that!! Do you have any proof that we got into a knockdown drag out brawl?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This proves it.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Whe-where did you get that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it obvious that I found it in the cafeteria, Max? You busted Ben over the head with this bottle, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Max">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's how the bottle broke. And that's why you were called to the Ringmaster's room.</line>
<line speaker="Max">F-F-F-FAAAABBBUUULOUSSS! ABSOLUTELY F-F-F-FAAAABBBUUULOUSSS!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">You just don't quit! You know Ben, don't you? What reason in the world would I have for getting into a fight with him? I've hardly ever said a word to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... It fits in with the chain of events.</line>
<line speaker="Max">You are so belligerent... If that's the case, how about you show me some proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Max">Don't look at me like that! This isn't easy for me you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How 'bout it Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">How 'bout what? What do you expect me to do with this? Lemme guess... You're showing me that so I can make it disappear for you... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no no no... PLEASE DON'T MAKE IT DISAPPEAR!! <thought>Hmm... I gotta try again! The Ringmaster called him... I wonder if there was some sort of problem?</thought> Um... Max? Perhaps you could share with me what you two spoke about?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Well... Not if I don't have to...</line>
<line speaker="Max">The truth is... Yesterday morning during breakfast, we had a run in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you had a fight with Ben the ventriloquist?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You could put it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why did you fight with him? Ben seems like such a quiet man.</line>
<line speaker="Max">We fought about my sweetie pie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean Regina?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That ill-bred creep told my sweetie pie princess that he was in love with her! Would you put up with that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Ill-bred"!! Are you talking about the same Ben!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Told her he was in love with her"!! Are you sure this is the Ben we are talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">All I can say is that he made me mad and I had to tap him on his hard head! That's when the Ringmaster called me and I realized that it was my chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your chance?</line>
<line speaker="Max">That's when I went to his room and I laid it all out on the table. I asked him to "Let me marry my sweetie pie!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">The Ringmaster told me that it "sounds good to me!" That's why my sweetie pie is MY sweetie pie! And no one else's!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Max">Since Ben was causing me so much trouble, I realized I had to shut him up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Shut him up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... What do you mean by "shut him up"?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You don't know, do you my sweeties? Unless Ben and Trilo are together, Trilo can't say a word.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trilo...?</line>
<line speaker="Max">The puppet. The ventriloquist's puppet. His real name is Trilo Quist.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... A puppet doesn't talk.</line>
<line speaker="Max">I know! That's why I hid it! Before the police came and took me away of course... If that puppet started flapping off at the balsa, I'd be screwed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You hid him? You mean the ventriloquist's puppet?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You are so smart sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Where did you hide him?</line>
<line speaker="Max">What? Sweetie... You aren't thinking of trying to add him to my defense are you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Ben does seem awfully lonely without his puppet.</line>
<line speaker="Max">FABULOUS! That should have taught him a lesson! OK... I hid Trilo in the Ringmaster's room. You don't mind going there and getting Trilo for me, do you my sweets?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No problem! None at all! Thank you Max!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">You know I can't stand to see my sweeties in a jam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then don't go hiding puppets!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Ben's not here anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I wanted to ask him something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's cold out... He's probably in the tent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Nick? I wonder if we've been making any progress...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be so negative... Of course we are making progress.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... Everyone loved the Ringmaster... And there's no sign of footprints on the scene... There's still a lot of mysteries left to be solved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And now Regina isn't here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not seeing how that's related...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The seats are so far away from the ring...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But they make up for it with the amount of people that can see a show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Nick... Do you think that if every person in the audience screamed all at once, the vibration they'd create could cause the big top to collapse?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm glad I don't pay you to come up with this stuff...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Look! That's where Max makes his grand appearance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's "grand" alright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I want to try entering court like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How'd I know that she'd say that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! Those lights are huge! If they fell from the ceiling, you'd be going to the circus in the sky... Life is so fragile, isn't it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It can be snuffed out in an instant by falling gargantuan lights.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's so fragile that I've decided to eat as much good food as I can before I die. Like hamburgers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently you didn't notice the big sign that said "closed" by the snack stand.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Awww... It's closed!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks the same as always... A great big mess. Considering how messy it is, I bet they wouldn't notice if another poster went missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Will you just stop it you poster pilferer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm just kidding! You know I already got one of these posters!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean stole one of those posters!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Uh... Let's focus on what Max told us. He said that he hid Trilo somewhere in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Trilo... Ohh! The ventriloquist's puppet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look at all the cute trophies!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed. Just look at all the awards this circus has won...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like... "All County Quiz Champions"... "Ringmaster's Association Mini Golf Master"... "Beer Belly Balloon Bounce Champ"... "Pet Grooming Grand Prix"... Wow. The Ringmaster was multi-talented in ways I could have never imagined...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... There's something shoved under the bookshelf! This... is...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Trilo! That's Ben's puppet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you're right. We'll give it back to him later.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why do I have to carry this thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">This punk, huh? Trilo is such a wooden, cheeky excuse for a puppet! I can't believe that this thing is what I'm up against for Regina's love! Ahh... My sweetie pie... Love only me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...What? You're up against what for Regina's love!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whatever. Let's hurry up and give this thing back to Ben.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Hey Ben!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">A... Umm... Uhh... H-H-Hello.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hello to you too! It's awfully cold today don't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Y-Ye-Ye... Uhh... I-I d-do indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't you think it's cold Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't see how talking about the weather is helping our case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell us what you know about the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I-I-I-I... Uhhh... I-I-I-I uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know anything at all?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I d-d-d-don't k-now a-a-a-a t-t-thing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">W-W-Well... I-I-I-I don't k-k-know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been in the circus for a long time, haven't you Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Y-Y-Yes... Ab-Ab-About f-f-four years...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I gotta admit, I'm kinda interested in this place as well. Moe is so funny, and Max is so amazing... Not to mention Regina being the cutest little thing I have ever seen!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...Regina? I... Umm... I... D-D-D-Don't R-R-Really... L-L-L-Like... H-Her... T-T-Too... M-Much...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... That's odd... Max said something about a confession of love...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh... Ben... This is yours isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Y-Y-Yes!! T-That's mine!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Here ya go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright Maya... Let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's that time isn't it? See ya around, Ben!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">O-O-O-OK...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Nick... Where are we going next?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... Maybe we should go talk to the clown once again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who said that?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What's your problem anyways? Don't you know how to properly greet someone!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ben? Is that you Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! I would never...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">It was me! Yeah me! Down here!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... You're... Trilo!?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That is Mr. Quist to you sir! Learn some manners before you just blurt out my name! Now try speaking to me again, but this time with some proper respect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not again... *sigh*</thought> Mr. Quist... Is that better?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">No! Look at me when I am talking to you, you 8-bit excuse for an attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Trilo! We talked about insulting people! You promised!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">But he was mocking me! Being mean to bullies was not included in the deal!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I'm sorry Trilo...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What just happened? Trilo is still a puppet right? A ventriloquist's puppet!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hey! Who do you think you are, calling me a puppet!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell us what you know about the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You talkin' to me? I said you talkin' to me? Don't look at him when you're talkin' to me!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Trilo Quist. You behave young man!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Shut up Woody! What murder are you talking about? You mean the one where they off'ed the old man?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">No need to make such a fuss about things! That old mutt paid us all peanuts!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Trilo... You can't say things like that! I didn't raise you to be that kind of puppet!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't you have nerve pills or something to take right now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These two are really an odd couple, aren't they Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">OK! OK! I'll talk... Gramps got clobbered over the head!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Let me lay it all out for you... The pay sucks... The clown sucks... And my partner has his hand up my pants.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your partner... You mean Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Yeah... The creepy old guy who never finds it in himself to leave me alone... Tell him to "BACK OFF" for me will ya? He's just another one of the dorks around here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... My...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">But I'll be fair... In this cesspool of human garbage masquerading as circus performers... I found my Madonna.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Madonna?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Regina. My lovely Regina. She is stunning... Right? Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... I'm not sure if I would go that far...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You'll have to excuse him... He does not understand of what he speaks. I, on, the other hand, am an appreciator of true beauty. Hence why I shall marry her!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ma-Ma-Ma-Marry!?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">The Ringmaster got knocked upside his cheap head by that flying fraud!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Max Galactica? Why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Trilo! Straighten up!! Don't accuse people like that!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Straighten up!? I'm made of wood!! Besides, you were there! You know what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were there...?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hehe! If you're that interested, then I'll let you in on the facts!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You... You're going to marry... Regina?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's right! She doesn't quite realize the joy that awaits her, does she?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But she did seem a bit worried about things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... She...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I don't care! It is my choice not hers! We're getting hitched!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I know you think that... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...But what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I gave her a special gift... I gave her the wonderful gift of song...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You gave her a song?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Well, I am a renowned tenor! You'll be happy to know that I've decided to grace you with one of my songs! Mi mi mi mi mi mi mi! "I want you to touch me! I want you to kiss me! I want you to..." The rest is private!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Umm... The melody is pretty good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But those lyrics... I think they need a little work.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Who asked you!? I'm the artist here!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Umm... Uhh... Thanks... Now that Trilo's here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Now that Trilo's here..." Does that mean you can talk normally now?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hey! Buttface!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">AHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You must be looking forward to tomorrow, aren't you Mr. Ambulance Chaser!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhh...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You know... It's time to get rid of that pesky magician once and for all!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tri... Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Enough jibba jabba! Let's get to court already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh... Hey! Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's a witness for tomorrow's trial...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... What in the world happened with Ben and Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite a pair, those two. What did that puppet see anyways</line>
<line speaker="???">Oooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh no... Now what!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oooo-Ooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahhhhh... Yeowwwwwwwww... Ahhhhhhhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-T-That monkey... ... AHHHH! My badge!! That monkey stole it!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHHHAAATTT!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hehehehehe! Mr. Attorney, that face was so cute. You looked so completely dumbfounded!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You!! That monkey!!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hey... No need to get angry... OK?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-B-But!! My attorney's badge!!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Don't worry... I'll help you out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK... If you say so... <thought>If I don't get my badge back, how can I flash it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Regina">By the way... The monkey's name is Money. Money the monkey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">His name is Monke... Money?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The monkey... Is called Money?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the rich ape just stole my attorney's badge. Mind if I get that back?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I'll see what I can do... Even I have Money problems.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Whenever Money sees something shiny, he takes it back home.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Haha... That's pretty funny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess I'll just have to find out where Money disappeared to...</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I think that's your best bet. You should probably ask Uncle Moe... He might know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Well... Money isn't exactly someone I am on friendly terms with.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">He's not really the kind of animal I work with... Even if he does need taming.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Go to Moe's... Hmm... I guess it is time that I revisit that kooky clown...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you mind telling us a bit about Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Ben...? You mean the guy that is always hanging around with Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean "hanging around"?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Well, he was there when Trilo told me that he was in love with me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo told you he was in love with you?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Yes he did. Kinda cute, don't ya think? He's so smart, and he's such a wonderful singer... I love him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... What about Ben?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">What about Ben? He's got nothing to do with me loving Trilo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like sand through the hourglass, so are the Days of the Circus...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regina, you were proposed to, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Proposed to? Nope... That won't be for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Really? That's strange, isn't it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Max and Trilo both said otherwise. They said they asked for her hand in marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh, but Max only talked to the Ringmaster about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I forgot about that. He asked the Ringmaster for her hand, not Regina directly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So I guess Trilo hasn't asked her directly yet.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">What!? He's going to propose to me!? I'm so confused... How about you Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Who do you think I should go for? Max or Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... Wait... You do realize that Trilo is... a... puppet?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Uh? I don't care that he's a bit stiff...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">NICK! YOU CAN'T SHOW HER THAT PICTURE!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch... Yeah, that would be a bit insensitive of me.</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Huh? Show me! Show me! Show me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know how Max flies in the sky like he does?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">I do know! Want me to tell ya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know!?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Uh-huh. *giggle* But you have to keep it secret!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Regina">So here's how it works... *mumble* *mumble*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! That's incredible!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, don't pout Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Regina">Hehe... We were just teasing you! I don't know a thing about magic!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry we tricked you Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Detective Gumshoe took off already.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. Just leave him alone for a while, OK Maya? I'm sure he just got lonely and headed back to the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something's covered up by this tarp... An old sign perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look out! They've got the killer trapped behind that tarp!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? It wasn't funny? You know it wouldn't have hurt you to look even a little bit surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew! She didn't notice that I was too scared to talk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the condenser for the air conditioner. It hasn't been used in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? How'd you figure that out!? You're not making things up now are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold your horses! It was easy to figure out! It was snowing before the murder, right? Well, look at the condenser. The snow is still piled on top of it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Nick! I'm impressed. Maybe you should be a P.I. instead of an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This safety light was on at the time of the murder, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what they say. <thought>There were performers in the lodging house, so it makes sense that it was on. I bet the killer was worried that someone would spot them during the crime...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Ringmaster's body was found here. I heard that the way he fell over made him look like he was carrying a wooden box... But what in the world really happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh my! If it isn't "Mr. Wright All The Time"!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*ugh*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's all Wright to be wrong every now and again, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See Nick! It just took awhile for the joke to find its audience!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">So what can I do for you? Did you remember a good joke you wanted to tell me? Pull up a chair, or maybe just pull my finger, and let me have it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're going to get the same sound effect either way, aren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">How'd you know I put a whopee* <thought>[sic]</thought> cushion on the chair!? You really know what it takes to be a clown, don't you? Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, about Regina...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Regina is such a pure, innocent child...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's such a cutie, too.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">She was born and raised in the circus you know? But that means she doesn't really know much about the world outside the Big Top.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like Pearly...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">For her, every child's "dream" of the circus is her everyday reality.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She lives in a dream world...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Everyday she sees dancing wild animals, men flying in the air, and one very funny clown. The funny thing is, that all seems normal to her because it is her everyday life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that explains why she thinks she can marry a ventriloquist's puppet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">Don't ask me if her reality is a good thing or a bad thing though... "A clown sees life simply, without complications."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you ever heard of a monkey named Money?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ahhh! Yes! Money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He stole my Attorney's Badge!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Money does love shiny objects... It makes sense that he'd swipe your badge. But under no circumstances can you chase after him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh? Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! I know!! You don't want to get involved in any monkey business, right?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">EXACTLY! BRAVO!! BRAVO!! Enough joking around though... Money isn't considered a member of Regina's family.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then who does he belong to?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I'll be happy to take you to where his owner is staying...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean right now?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Of course. Shall we go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, should we go with him now, or wait a while?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll go after we talk some more, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yay! You want to hear me talk some more, huh? Your wish is my command!! I'll give ya the full repertoire of 1001 jokes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Woohoo!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't "Woohoo!!" that!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*huff* *huff*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">This is it... What's wrong, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... can't... breathe...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Don't be such a wimp! You only had to climb two flights of stairs!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*pant* *pant*</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Anyways... This is the place. Acro's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Acro?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He's an acrobat... It seems like he's not around today...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh... That's a big pile of junk over in the corner...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I don't think it'd be wrong to assume that Phoenix's stuff is over there too... Just be careful to make sure you've got the Wright stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks Moe! See you later!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Moe must have gone off somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as long as he isn't off writing new jokes...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, that reminds me Nick... You have to get your Attorney's Badge back by tomorrow, or we're in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know. I know. <thought>I'm gonna have to try and find out where that monkey hid it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can see the Big Top from the window here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There is no snow on top of the Big Top... Kinda weird don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The inside of the tent is warm so any snow that lands on top probably melts.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess you're right. The snow probably just slides right off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Money must use this to swing around on...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go ahead Nick. I know you want to ride on it too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe later...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... The net's ripped. Money must be prone to breaking things... He's hardcore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... The net looks fine to me. You really think that he plays basketball?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think so... Monkeys live life above the rim you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You're joking right? You think the monkey has got proverbial "game"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course. That monkey doesn't fake the funk on a nasty dunk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, a prehensile tail might be an unfair advantage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hehe... It's a monkey calendar!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoever's in this room must really love monkeys.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe a little too much... Wow... I just realized that the year is almost over. Amazing how time flies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been one wild year. Especially the last part...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we still got one last person to help this year... Max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This bed is incredibly well made. It's almost like a maid made it up. Even the laundry on top of the bed is folded perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, there's nothing unusual about that at all. It's how things are supposed to be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can't a man respect another man for doing something said man cannot do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... He's got a barbell. Look around... Everything he's got is for upper body training. Wait a second... These are the same machines I see on TV all the time!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't have this one! This barbell here is a new model!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't overdo it Maya. You don't want to end up a muscle woman.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Holy cow! There's a fork... And a mirror... Everything's shiny!! There's even a really cheap looking knockoff wristwatch!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this! It's a trophy! And it's really heavy!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I found it! Your badge! It's right here!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks! You really saved me! ... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter? Did you find something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Check this out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's a ring...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something engraved on it... "From T to R"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I think it's about time we wrap up our investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think we'll win in court tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows... Even I can't imagine what kind of testimony will come out tomorrow. <thought>I'm guessing Moe will be a witness in court tomorrow... Moe and maybe the puppet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry Nick. No matter what, we've still got a magician on our side!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's good, because we might need some magic tomorrow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think I have enough evidence yet... I should investigate and gather some more clues before I try again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh! I've made too many mistakes!</thought></line>
</xml>