<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew, what a day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is no time for relaxing, Nick! Say, you think WP's got a chance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that really depends on the people we found out about in today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The director and producer...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, what are we doing here then!? Let's get to the studios!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think we should do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what do I... huh!? Why don't we do what you just said!? We gotta get the scoop on this director and producer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Then there's no point hanging out here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what I've been saying! Let's get to those studios pronto!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. We don't have enough information to make a case yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's exactly the same thing you said yesterday! Just admit it: you don't have a clue what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's not enough information!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, see this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You... really like showing that off, don't you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, you still have that! Great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we couldn't get into the scene of the murder without it. And its owner isn't missing it in his detention cell...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor old WP...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, what if this really was Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's hard to say. We don't really know anyone else it could be. I seriously doubt it was that old windbag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Mr. Powers is... lying?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He really doesn't seem the type, does he. <thought>Curiouser and curiouser...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish I had my own Samurai Spear! You'd by my own personal pincushion, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me!? Why me!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, I don't know how that will help us figure this out.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh, Mr. Wright! Thank you for earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all. We got lucky, to tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can say that again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, WP! Do you have any leads that might get us going in the right direction?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Hmm... S-sorry, but no.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Be sure to tell us anything that comes to mind, no matter how small.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't rely on getting lucky again tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes... *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do, er, "fanboys" sneak into the studios often?</line>
<line speaker="Will">No, not that I know of. That security lady's pretty strict with them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, in today's testimony, didn't she say they were often hanging around?</line>
<line speaker="Will">The kids really, really love the Steel Samurai. They sneak past when she's not looking, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was the director present at the morning run-through?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes, yes he was. He was directing how the Steel Samurai and the Evil Magistrate should move.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why didn't you tell us that before!?</line>
<line speaker="Will">W-well, just, the studio asked us to keep quiet...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That has nothing to do with this! I hate to repeat myself, but Nick here is a newbie lawyer! Fresh off the bar! When he loses, he's going to lose big!</line>
<line speaker="Will">I... I see. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whose side is she on!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You aren't hiding anything else from us, are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Will">N-no, I sure hope not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found this cardkey in your dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh, that's mine, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can people outside the studios get these cards?</line>
<line speaker="Will">I don't think so. Even I have to return the card. Once the show's done filming, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding this photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This really, truly, absolutely isn't you, right?</line>
<line speaker="Will">R-right. *sniff* I was sleeping in my dressing room the whole time, honest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But who else could have worn it!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your costume was in your dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes. I guess they snuck in and took it while I was asleep.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But who!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Regarding the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it heavy, that spear?</line>
<line speaker="Will">It's pretty hefty, yeah. I don't think the average person would be able to swing it around effectively.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... that's the spear that broke or something during the morning run-through?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh yes, I goofed on a round kick, you see... I broke the spear. The security lady fixed it for me right away though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">With duct tape. We heard.</line>
<line speaker="Will">E-excuse me. Thank you for showing me that, whatever it is. I wish I could think of some way I could help you... S-sorry. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No one's here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, now that they have Ms. Oldbag in custody. I guess they don't have anyone else to replace her...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hey! In the guard station! Look! She left her donuts! ... ... What? I wasn't going to eat them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The computer that runs the studio security cameras. Huh? It looks like it's been turned off for the day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security guard station. Ms. Oldbag must like junk food. There's a mountain of it on the desk in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The main entrance to the studios. They probably have a police officer on patrol out there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. It looks like Detective Gumshoe isn't here today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. He's probably up to his neck in paperwork after the commotion at today's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, Nick... Remember that "Studio Two" we heard about at the trial today? It was down that path with the fallen tree, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I think that's what they said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe the director and the rest of them are there today? Now's our chance, Nick! Let's check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm bushed. Maybe I'll sit down here for a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is exactly why I don't want to get old, ever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey! I'm still young! I'm just tired!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, when you start having to say "I'm still young," you know it's all over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But... but I AM still young!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the trial, they said Studio Two was down this path. The monkey head is in the way, but we should be able to get by it without a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This monkey head is real heavy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it did knock that tree over when it fell.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Both of these, the monkey head and the tree, fell the day of the murder, didn't they.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's what Detective Gumshoe said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The studio mascot. Apparently it's a monkey of some kind. I've never seen a monkey with a nose like that before!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why don't they put his head back on? Maybe we should ask that assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure we really want her fixing anything. And you'd probably need a crane to move that thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Probably so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's the security camera that automatically takes pictures of people here. It took two pictures on the day of the murder, before the actual time of death. One of them was the Steel Samurai. The other was a grade school boy. It doesn't seem to be switched on today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The entrance to Studio One. This is the studio where they found Jack Hammer's body.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It says "Welcome."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They let people in here when they're not filming, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Let's come here some day! Whaddya say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, if that security lady lets us in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... don't really want to be in here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... It is a murder scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I want to go someplace else. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh*...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, look at that camera! That must cost a ton!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! So don't touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, smile, Nick, you're a star!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-stop that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's for reflecting light. They call it a reflecting screen or something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Where's your enthusiasm for all things entertainment?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, lighting is fine, but I'd want to be the director. Or maybe the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she's being serious...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like a backdrop for a stage. This must be used in the Steel Samurai show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! That's the mountain, Neo Fujiyama!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't the Steel Samurai take place in Olde Tokyo? Can you even see Mt. Fuji from there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not Olde Tokyo, Nick! "Neo" Olde Tokyo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This... is Studio Two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't really look much like a "studio," does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that it does not.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... There's a trailer over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks pretty sturdy for a movie set trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are we sure this is a studio?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An incinerator. Apparently they just put this one in. It's already covered in soot. They must not clean it much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like two people ate here. There's nothing left on the plates.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, so they ate t-bone steaks too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it with steaks around here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! There's always room for steak! But... something does seem out of place...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... don't know. It just feels "odd."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a big "2" painted here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Probably because this is Studio Two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably... Though it doesn't look anything like a studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A light van for moving staff and equipment around. They've kept it in pretty good shape. Looks like it'd run fine.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, let's go for a drive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure... if I had a license.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You don't have a driver's license!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, look, I have this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why are you showing me your attorney's badge, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There're some flowers here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, so pretty! They're taking good care of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't get to [sic] close. That fence looks dangerous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These look like materials for making a movie set.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They've been sitting here for quite some time. This might as well be a junkyard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On closer inspection, this trailer looks like it's been here for a while. I don't think this is part of some temporary film set.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Let's go inside!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You think it's okay...? Oh well. It's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... shucks.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, it's that assistant girl. Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Hi... WP's lawyers, right? I heard about the trial! Great job, guys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Oh hoh hoh. Don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Is it true they caught the security lady!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! Oh... oh hoh hoh!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Actually, she just called me. She told me to cover up that drain...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean that one? <thought>Wow, what a mess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">I... I know... I'm not so good with handiwork. Some assistant, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but you do work on the props, and the backdrops, right?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">R-right. Just... lots of times they end up looking worse than they did before I fixed them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh? Oh! Well, I'm sure these things happen. Nothing to worry yourself about!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">You're right! I won't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Personally, I think she should worry at least a little bit more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">Um, if you'll excuse me, I have to go to the guard station. I'm supposed to fill in for Ms. Oldbag.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! See you later, then!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Good luck with your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, the fanboy they were talking about in the trial today... He came in through that drain?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it seems. I guess they covered it up in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... Hey, Nick! If that drain's covered, the boy won't be able to get in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah. I think that was the idea...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I feel kinda sorry for him, though. Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, you want to rip the grate off?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really, Nick? We can!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa... she's serious? Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah, I think we should leave it on. They only just repaired it. And if we take it off, that assistant will get yelled at by you-know-who.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow! I didn't expect her to take it that hard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess some things are just made to be broken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! You know, Nick, you're pretty swell sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sometimes...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hiii-ya! There. That should make the kids happy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The things we do...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The drain grate is off. And I know who did it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now the kids'll be able to come in again. Doesn't it make you feel great to do a good deed like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Must be nice to live so free of guilt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The remains of yesterday's lunch are scattered around. Everyone was probably too shocked to clean up. There's a t-bone on one of the plates, minus the steak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door to the dressing room. It's not locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Let's go in! Maybe there'll be something else to steal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey! We're not thieves!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we did take that cardkey...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-we borrowed that! There's a difference.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... cola, candy, chips, gum... Huh. It's so... normal. I was expecting some cool theme snacks or something. Popcorn, at least!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-wait! Look! "Samurai Soda"! Nick! Try this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Be my guest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay! Oh, too bad, it's sold out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is where the Steel Samurai costume was, on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what Mr. Powers says, at least. I guess they snuck in and took it while he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Nick, what if Mr. Powers hadn't been sleeping? I wonder what the killer was planning on doing then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh... <thought>She's got a point!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's an array of cosmetics here. According to Maya, that wig was used in some old TV show...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Samurai Boogey-Woogey," Nick! Get with the picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, explain to me how you can identify a show just by seeing a wig!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I, um, kinda like samurai movies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Kinda"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some regular suits in among the costumes here. Those must be Mr. Powers's personal clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like someone was sleeping here. Maybe Powers did take a nap here, like he said.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Powers's bag. I wonder what's inside? Hey! Supermarket tabloids? Wow. I'm kind of shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Leave those alone! <thought>Wolf Men Found On Mars...? I'll have to buy that issue!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bunch of snacks on the table. They must give these to the employees. Some tea and cookies...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait... Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">These snacks... they've passed the expiration date!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Then don't eat them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*grumble* <thought>They're snacks! They're meant to be eaten!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's locked. I guess he doesn't open his window much. It is kind of dusty outside.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh... hello.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ho hoh! You look a little out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">It's the clothes, isn't it? I thought my camo vest might do the trick... Kind of an "alternative guard fashion" thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security guard station. I can see the computer that runs the security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, please don't touch anything in there. The security lady would knock the stuffing out of me if she knew.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how are the studios doing?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">There's police wandering around everywhere, it's terrible. They won't even let me clean up. Don't want me "disturbing evidence." I haven't even cleaned up our lunch plates from the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean those plates with the steak bones left over on them in the employee area?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yeah. Can you believe it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do kids sneak in here a lot?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Well... I don't think there's that many of them, but I do see one in particular a bunch. He's always gawking at the sets, or snapping pictures. You should see Old Windbag's eyes flash when she sees him. She has a bit of trouble catching him though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard something at the trial today. They said that the director and producer were here the day of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, sorry... I was in the prop storage room, so I didn't see them. I guess they were here, though. The studio head seemed pretty eager to keep us quiet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So they were trying to protect the director?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">More the producer, really. The producer's our real star here. She saved these studios from the brink of disaster and kept them running. I don't think we'd still be in business if it weren't for that producer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The producer, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">Wow, they gave a lawyer one of those cardkeys?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I'm sort of borrowing it.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I see. You better be careful not to lose that. They're very strict about those cardkeys here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess they're pretty good about keeping these out of outsider's hands.</thought> Thanks, I'll be careful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">That's Mr. Powers. Why is he dragging his leg like that? What is this, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like she didn't know about this photo or the injury that morning.</thought> Uh... Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, you work with the props, right? About that murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">You mean the Samurai Spear? Yeah, it's a prop, but it's still pretty heavy. I hate having to carry that thing around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So you'd have to be pretty strong to use that as a weapon, it sounds like. Why is Mr. Powers the only person I can think of!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Penny">Umm... Not really sure what that is. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="???">WTF? Who are j00 d00dz!? LMAO!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh!? W-we... Wait, you first! Who are you!? You look pretty suspicious to me!</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Whatever, l4m3rs! How can j00 not know the great Sal Manella!? I make teh L33T SH0WZ! The Steel Samurai? Mine! RTFC! <thought>Read The Film Credits!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-really!? You're THE Sal Manella!? I'm so sorry! I, just, you looked so... Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Manella">No no, quite alright. Really. It's fine. ROFL! ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">You know, on closer inspection... Mmm... Yeah... Hot! Hot! Hot! *slobber* Hey, do j00 do a lot of "cosplay," coz that costume r0x0rz!... *drool*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Rocksores!? Wh-wh-what... Hey! You're drooling!</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Huh? Mmph! LOL! Buffer overrun! *pant* You've triggered my CR34T1V3 P0W3RZ! Yes... yes, it's coming to me! "Pink Princess"! The sequel to the Steel Samurai... "Pink Princess: Warrior of Little Olde Tokyo!" ROFL... LMAO!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-"Pink Princess"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why's it gotta be "Little" Olde Tokyo!? Why can't it have a cool name, like "Neo Olde Tokyo"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, we really need to talk about "cool"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bunch of snacks on the table. They must give these to the employees.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hey! Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-the snacks! There was twice this much here before!</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Ah. I, uh, I ate them. They were past their expiration date anyway. ROFL!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's biting her lip and staring at me with tears welling in her eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice anything unusual on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, I know who j00 d00dz are. That security lady told j00 about us, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">It was a pretty regular day. We had a run-through for an action scene in the morning. Then a meeting from lunchtime in the Studio Two trailer. Heh. I was so busy I didn't even get a chance to eat lunch!&#160;:(</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A t-bone steak, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah... sux0rz! I hate missing out on food...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... what does "Sucksores" mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No idea...</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Anyway, I was in a meeting from noon till after 4:00. With the producer, and some bigwigs from the network.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mr. Hammer's time of death was estimated at 2:30 PM. If he's telling the truth, that meeting gives him an alibi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the producer who was at the meeting with you...</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, you mean Dee Vasquez? She's a genius. M4d sk1llz, all the way. Scary, though. *sweats* She brought these studios back from the brink of destruction. She's the one who made it possible for me to make the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You had a meeting with her on the day of the murder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, we were together from noon to 4:00 PM, the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who exactly are these "bigwigs" people keep mentioning?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, the boss over at the network, and some sponsors. Also a few production guys. They piled into a limousine and got here right around noon. Major tension! *sweats*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Were all of them with you the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, unfortunately. They're all gray-haired geezers... *scowl*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... sounds like they'd all be reliable witnesses.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">... T-this is WP, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Well, look, he's obviously dragging his foot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right. The director would know about the injury; he was there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">I try not to pay much attention to things that don't interest me. LOL.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-why are you staring at me like that...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This place is deserted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek! N-N-Nick! W-w-what was that noise!? It sounded like it came from inside the trailer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone must be inside...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-Hello? ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No answer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty suspicious, if you ask me, Nick! Let's go in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure we should be barging in... ...Huh. It's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Don't we have a key?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. But there's probably one in the guard station at the main gate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then what are we waiting for? Let's borrow it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If they'll let us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trailer door. It's locked. The key is probably in the security guard station. I doubt they'd let us borrow it.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah hah! You again!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">How rude, acting like you've seen a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... certainly got back to your post quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh the police took me away, they did. They pulled out a spare Steel Samurai costume! Told me to "put it on." Can you imagine? How could I, a sweet little old lady, wear a giant suit like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers is pretty tall...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">As soon as they saw there was no way I could wear it, they let me go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that would rule out her being the murderer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway! Know this, whippersnapper! This old lady NEVER forgets a slight or insult! And you won't get any information out of me! My lips are sealed!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You sure are talking a lot for someone with sealed lips.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Starting now! One, two, three, mmmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This lady's too much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security guard station. I can see the computer that runs the security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! No touching!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I'd better investigate there later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, about that kid you said you saw...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">If I see him again, I'm taking him down!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Look at her eyes! She's serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have a feeling she's not going to respond well to anything I show her now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! H-hey! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll bet he came in right through that drain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, um, kiddy-o! What's yer name, sport?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm not a kid, so don't talk to me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh!? But you... You are a kid! What a rude little brat. That's no way to talk to an adult!</line>
<line speaker="???">I don't see no adults here! Hippie fashion chick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-hippie fashion...? Nick... I think I'm being mocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You got to hand it to Maya, she's pretty sharp. And pretty mad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">I'm Cody! Cody Hackins. Call me "kiddy-o" again and I'll cut you down where you stand, evildoer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The drain where the fanboy came in. He didn't waste any time coming in, either. Talk about cause and effect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're a fan of the Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">How dare you utter that name, evildoer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean? We're on the Steel Samurai's side!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">H-hah! Hah hah! You can't fool me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay... then what's the last line said by the innkeeper in Episode 8?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hah! Easy! "Like some fries with that?"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph... not bad, kiddy-o.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What are they doing!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">Evildoers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, you heard anything about the incident the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You were here, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see anything...?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">He... he...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">He... always... The Steel Samurai always wins! Always! Yeah, I saw 'em! I saw everything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">But... but no way am I telling you losers!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wha--!? Wait...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Lemme go!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... He's gone. Huh? Something fell off the table when he bumped into it on his way out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A... bottle? Why was this sitting there, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, what was that kid saying?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He "saw everything"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Where's that old windbag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Odd of her to leave her post...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag"><thought>H-hey!!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! That was her!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag"><thought>S-stop! Whippersnapper!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah. Sounds like she's chasing after that boy.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Natch!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh oh, she tripped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya sure looks happy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey, Nick. Now's our chance! Let's check out the guard station!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Oh! This is it, Nick! The "Trailer Key"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The key to that trailer in Studio Two!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'll be borrowing this, right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security guard station. Ms. Oldbag must like junk food. There's a mountain of it on the desk in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if the key we borrowed from the guard station will work? ... It opened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great! Let's go, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems eager all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you first, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, not THAT eager.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trailer door. It's unlocked.</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek! S-someone's in here!</line>
<line speaker="???">Names.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-our n-names? Um, w-we're WP's lawyers, and, um...</line>
<line speaker="???">I see. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-and who might you...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Dee Vasquez. The producer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dee Vasquez... She's quite beautiful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Another old movie poster. "'The Singing Samurai' starring Jack Hammer." What the hell do samurai sing about? Chopping off heads?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. My. God. That movie was the best! It's about a samurai who sings his way to fame and fortune! Mr. Hammer was a very accomplished singer, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Singing samurai stars... What's next? Ninja ballet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"'Samurai Summer' starring Jack Hammer." This poster's quite old.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! It's been years since I saw that show! It was one of those typical summer romance stories... but it was great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A typical summer romance... with a samurai on a horse?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster. "'Dynamite Samurai' starring Jack Hammer." I guess Mr. Hammer used to be quite the star.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is where they had that meeting. There are documents and paper cups scattered around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing in here that could be a clue. Just some paper cups and crumpled documents.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like they were designing a set to use for the Steel Samurai show. They've got some figures for how much the set costs... I can't believe they spend that much money on those sets!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The glass is frosted. I can't see outside. This far into October, the dimming daylight makes it feel like winter's coming.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering if you could tell me about the day of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Script.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Script. I'm looking for a script.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A s-script?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">"The Steel Samurai, Episode 13." I need it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... could we ask you a bit about the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I need to read it. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>We're getting nowhere fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, w-we'd really like to ask you about the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">It's on TV. Every week. That's all I have to say about that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! She's telling us to go watch TV!? The nerve of her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, don't get mad at me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the director... Sal Manella, was it? What, er, exactly is his role here...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Perhaps I didn't make myself clear? I'm looking for a script. I can't be bothered with anything else. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick? Are all people in the entertainment business this... weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's starting to look like it.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I'm not interested.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's get out of here. Isn't there someplace else we have to check?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">If you see Manella, give him this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-why do we have to do your errands...!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... I don't think I like her. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't cry. She'll take it as a sign of weakness. Alright. We'll give it to him if we see him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here. I got this from the producer...</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Huh? "Bring the script for Episode 13"? Episode 13... where did I put that one? ... I must have left it somewhere... *sweats* U-uh oh... My ass is p0wned if I don't find it... *shakes*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... It might be quicker to just look in all the places where he's likely to have been.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're back at the scene of the crime. Let's find what we need and get out of here quick, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Look! That's the chair the director sits in! I've always wanted to sit in one of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The director...!</thought> Maya... Take a look around that chair for me, would you? Remember that script the director was talking about? Didn't he say he'd left it somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahah! Found it, Nick! The script!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We found your script.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">W00t! THX! S-still... I dunno... That woman is to be ph34red when you bring something to her late... Say, um, j00 think j00 d00dz could take it down there for me? THX!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is that producer really that scary?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, she's certainly not NORMAL...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, we found it! Your script!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Umm... uh... You're not going to talk to us?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Quiet. I'm reading.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Just you hold on! What's the big idea!? Who do you think you are anyway!? And, and do you even know who we are!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Powers's lawyers?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm.... right.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Am I a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no, it's just, well, no, but...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... You wanted to know about the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes. Anything you could tell us would be a big help.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... You know there was a meeting here at noon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. With the director and the people from the network...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Correct. Now, listen closely. None of the people in this trailer that afternoon went to Studio One. It was impossible for us to leave.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Impossible? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The path was blocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... path?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the murder, the path that leads here was blocked?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">You saw Mr. Monkey on the way here, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-"Mr. Monkey"?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The monkey with the broken head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right, that... <thought>What an original name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Its head fell over in the wind on the day of the murder. They didn't start moving the head out of the way until after 3:00. It was after 4:00 by the time the path was unblocked. Capsice? Everyone in this trailer was stuck here until the path was cleared. Stuck in this trailer. Stuck until after 4:00. Hammer died at 2:30. Thus, none of us could have gone to Studio One.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">It's true. A crane came just after 3:00 to move the head. We called some people in to clear the way. I'm sure they'd corroborate my story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but wait! What if the head fell over after 2:30? Then you could have gone to Studio One!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">2:30... the time of death. ... Very well. Come.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... That's "Mr. Monkey." When it wasn't broken, it announced the time... in "ooks." One "ook" per hour. Ook ook ook ook. Always with the ooking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It IS a monkey, after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Check its head. The clock inside stopped when it broke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Nick, it's stopped at 2:15.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">2:15...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">That's right. This path was blocked from 2:15 till after 4:00. Therefore, we're innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Hammer died in Studio One at 2:30...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">See? Good bye.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do we do, Nick? There isn't anyone besides WP who could have killed Hammer! It's over... We're finished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It sure doesn't look good. Guess we should head back to the office and plan our strategy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really want to take a break, but we have work to do! Still, it's kind of sad to see so many empty benches... Kind of like if you threw a party, and nobody came.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the path that goes to Studio Two. The mascot's head fell right on the path on the day of the murder. The path was completely blocked between 2:00 and 4:00.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. There's a clock and a speaker in the monkey's head. It would usually tell the time by "ook"ing. The clock is stopped at 2:15 now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now what... We're fresh out of clues. Everyone's alibi is water-tight. We don't even have any promising leads. Things are looking pretty grim.</line>
<line speaker="???">It's a little early for giving up, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">You've got one lead...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia! It's you! What took you so long!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sorry, Phoenix. Maya has trouble calling me unless she's really in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! Oh, wait. I guess that means we're really in trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'd say so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you mean, we have one lead...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The boy, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, I saw 'em. I saw everything!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">But...but no way am I telling you losers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno. He didn't sound like he was going to help us at all.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sure you can find some way of bringing him over to your side. Either way, we should get back to the studios. That boy is our last hope, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks, now I'm more worried than I was before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">My poor plant! It looks so... so sluggish! Have you been watering it properly, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well, Maya has actually... I think maybe she's giving it too much.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That child! Sorry, Charley.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The plant's name is... Charley?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of an old movie that Mia liked. Oh, hey! Mia, what's the name of this movie?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That movie...? Oh! I'd sure like to see that one again! It's, um... What was it, again? S-sorry, it's right on the tip of my tongue...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let me guess... it's a suspense thriller?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what's the best thing to do from here?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We need to get to the studio and talk to that boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, do you have any ideas about who might have done this?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We don't have enough information to make a case yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where have I heard that phrase before? So THAT's where Maya got it from...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Showing me that isn't going to do any good. You know what they say, "Dead men don't tell tales."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You sure are talking enough!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess Mr. Powers is in questioning...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh well. Let's try again another day, Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... puff... huff... puff... huff... puff... huff... Huff... puff... huff... puff... huff... puff... huff...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... puff... huff... puff... whih... whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's been chasing that boy this whole time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... puff... when... when I ca... catch him... I... huff</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like she hasn't had any luck catching him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... puff... I...  I got a hostage now, whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "hostage"...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... what happened to the boy?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I-if I see him a-again, I'll... huff! L-lay him flat! Huff... puff...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">My, what a violent old lady...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I met with the director just now...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Eh? Hah... my heart, it don't feel so good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is she okay!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">B-before I go, I'd like to v-visit the place where poor H-Hammer died...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... she was saying she wanted to visit the studio where he died.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this about a "hostage"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... huff... W-when that boy was running away... ...he dropped this, a-and ran! Huff... huff... H-he'll come back... huff... huff... for this one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's kind of hard to understand her with all that huffing and puffing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! That "hostage" might be what we need! Cody might talk to us if we gave him that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good idea!</thought> Ms. Oldbag! Might I...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">No! I'm catching that brat if it's the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Do you have anything you might trade with her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A trade, hmm... I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">H-hey... that... huff... That's a card... huff... Studio One?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. A cardkey to Studio One.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... puff... I... I could visit poor Hammer... I'd like to visit... huff... he died... whew. I was his... his fan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't have your own card, Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Studio One isn't my turf. Huff... huff... You'll let me borrow... borrow it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I give her the cardkey, then I won't be able to get into Studio One...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, we have our own investigating to do there.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... huff... puff. Poo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was that last bit a breath, or a pout...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I... I told you who I s-saw! Huff! Huff... it... it was Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, at least she's consistent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag? I'm borrowing this... just so you know.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh... o-okay... huff. J-just be sure to... huff... give it b-back... puff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's not as demanding when she's exhausted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Huff... huff... puff... ... huff... puff... haaah! ... Huff.. huff... puff... huff... puff... huff... hooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's too busy catching her breath to tell me anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why don't you let her borrow it, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it can't hurt. Here you go, Ms. Oldbag.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Listen to me, sonny. I don't like having debts to no whippersnappers. You take this, and we're even. Deal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...? A Steel Samurai trading card?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That sneaky kid dropped it! I figure it's pretty important to him, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, I may have a use for this. <thought>This must be the "hostage" she was talking about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Right. I'm off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There she goes, hobbling off toward the studio...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Welcome"... I wonder if the murder will make this place famous, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A classic director's chair. I'm surprised they don't have an extra large one for Mr. Manella.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A collection of expensive film equipment. I can't even begin to imagine how much just one of these costs. If we broke one, we'd go bankrupt for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A panel for reflecting light. They call it a "reflecting board" or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A stage backdrop. This is "Neo Fujiyama," according to Maya. It looks incredibly fake, but I guess the kids don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A perfectly normal stepladder. I've never actually used one. I don't like heights. I'm a firm belever that humankind was made to keep both feet on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like two people ate here. There's nothing left on the plates.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a big "2" painted here. Probably because this is Studio Two? Probably... Though it doesn't look anything like a studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A light van for moving staff and equipment around. They've kept it in pretty good shape. Looks like it'd run fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nameless flowers bloom in solitude. They probably have a proper name... But it is not for me to know. Not now, nor ever till the end of my days. ... I need a vacation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These look like materials for making a movie set. They've been sitting here for quite some time. This might as well be a junkyard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door is unlocked. We could probably just walk right in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Another old movie poster. "'The Singing Samurai' starring Jack Hammer." What the hell do samurai sing about? Chopping off heads?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's a samurai musical set in ancient Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A s-samurai musical? Is that even a genre!? Well, I'm impressed. You know your stuff, Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, Maya's the real fan. I just picked a little up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"'Samurai Summer' starring Jack Hammer." This poster looks like it's been hanging here for years.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is one of Maya's favorite movies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe we should replace the poster in the office with this one?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That... would be kind of sad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Hey, you! W-wait a sec!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Phoenix... Was that the boy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. His name's "Cody Hackins."</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think he ran into the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like one of those electric-powered bicycles. I dunno about these. I mean, what's the point?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It makes it a lot easier to go up hills!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where have I heard that line before...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door to the dressing room. It's not locked.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is where Cody ran... Let's go in and see if we can get him to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be the storage room. That's where they keep all the film equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... cola, candy, chips, gum... Huh. It's so... normal. I was expecting some cool theme snacks, or something. Popcorn, at least!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Look at this! "Spaghetti in a Soda Can"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-spaghetti? Wouldn't just the sauce come out and the noodles all stay stuck inside?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"Best when slammed." I guess they want you to drink it in one gulp...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Slamming spaghetti. Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's sure to be in here somewhere... Found you!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dammit! He's getting away!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Come back! ... There. He's back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How did she...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hey there. Would you mind helping us out? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... I-I'm Cody.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hello, Cody. I'm Mia. Mia Fey. Nice to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I'm Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Who asked?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, you can take it from here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not so sure I'm qualified...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's an array of cosmetics here. According to Maya, that wig was used in some old TV show...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You don't know "Samurai Boogey-Woogey"!? You're even lamer than I thought!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does everybody but me know about this show!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers's bag.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now, Phoenix, it's not polite to look through other people's belongings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, don't look at me! <thought>Tell that to your sister!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a box of snacks on the table, and some cans of soda. They're all empty. I'm glad Maya isn't here to see this. She'd be devastated.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sorry? What was that about Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-oh, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai's so cool. I think he's the, um, the "bomb."</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hah! What would a lamer like you know about the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, watch that attitude!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, you really should't yell like that. He's only a kid.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah! Don't yell like that I'm only a kid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, do you know anything about what happened here? Could you tell me, please?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I don't know nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... looks like a little persuasion's necessary. Maybe a bribe...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hey, it's the Steel Samurai. Huh? Why's he dragging his foot like that? Where'd you get this, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">The Samurai Spear! That's totally cool. I wish I had one, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This kid and Maya would get along great.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody... This look familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hey! My UR!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"You are"... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">"U.R." You know, "ultra rare"! That card's really hard to get! Man, for a grown-up, you sure are dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll give you this... IF you help me.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">But that's my card! By offering me something I already own, you're in effect eschewing the very basis of our consumer society, namely the principle of fair trade! Man, for a grown-up, you sure are dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-what do they teach these kids in school these days!? Quantum physics!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">Whatever, I don't need that card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I got a double. Just keep it. It's yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What!? After I went through all that trouble...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">If you want to trade, find me a REALLY rare card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Really rare"!? You mean there's something rarer than "Ultra Rare"!?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Ultra Rare Premium cards are way rarer than plain Ultra Rare cards! Come ON! Man, for a grown-up, you sure are dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Premium... rare... why do I feel like we're talking about steaks?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">What's that? Bo-ring! Man, how can one person be so lame!? If you were a superhero you'd be Lame-o-man!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, hi.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello. What brings you here?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, well, I had to arrange some stuff... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">The, um, girl with you. Doesn't she seem a little different? Like, is she even the same person as before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, nope! She's the same as always.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Same as always.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Okay... whatever you say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you seen that boy since then?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Nope. You missed it, though. The security lady was chasing around after the boy so fast I thought she'd collapse. Of course, he got away in the end. Boy, was she mad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, we saw them. How's the old windbag doing?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">She was squeezing donuts through her clenched fists back at the guard station.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Some people take their jobs a little too seriously.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are all the posters on the wall here of Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes. It's really a terrible loss for the studios.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... his popularity had been waning recently, right?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">That's true. Then again, after what happened...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After WHAT happened?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Y-you mean, you don't know about Hammer...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, what?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I-I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, now you have to tell me. What happened with Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I-I'm sorry. I'm probably not the one who should tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. Why do I get the feeling something's being covered up here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Hey, that's a Steel Samurai trading card. I collect those, actually. I'm one card away from a complete set!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A complete set?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yeah, a set of one of each card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">... Wait...Waitwaitwaitwait!!! That's it!!! That's the card I need! You don't know how long I've been looking for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I don't care what kind of girl you might think I am, I need that card! P-please! I beg you! Please trade with me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-trade with you?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, trade cards! Look, I'll even trade you an Ultra Rare Premium card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trade me a... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, it's a good deal for your Ultra Rare! Please!!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Can't you see she's desperate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-what's everybody getting so excited about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... no, I can't. See, this card isn't really even mine.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">!!! I... I see. O-of course. Of course it wouldn't be yours. Of course you couldn't trade it with me. Of course I won't ever get that card, ever. Of course I don't even really deserve that card.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, do something! She's blacking out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-o-okay, okay! I'll trade!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Umm... Sorry. I'm really Not sure what that is.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Really!? Th-thanks!!! Then this is for you.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yaa-hoo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And there she goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Doesn't doing good things like that make you feel great?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Yeah, it does.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See this card?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, so... Wait! That's it!!! That's the last Ultra Rare Premium card I need! C'mon give it to me, please! You gotta give it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, I've never seen him so... eager.</thought> R-right! Okay! How about a trade?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You're on! I'll give you a "Samurai Spear" and throw in an "Evil Magistrate" to boot!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no no... not that kind of trade. I don't want cards. I want information.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Huh? You sure? Fine by me!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Okay, Phoenix. Let's hear what he has to say. If he knows something that could help us, we can have him take the stand tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you like the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">He's so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You're judging him by his looks! You have to look at his actions, at his life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm being lectured on life by a grade schooler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">You like him too, don'tcha?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Oh, me? Y-yeah! I, um, love the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">So, tell me what your favorite thing about the Steel Samurai is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right... <thought>C'mon, think of something!</thought> I really like his, um, his kind nature. What a guy!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Totally! He looks so tough, but inside, he's as gentle as a kitten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">So, what else do you like about him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell me I have to keep this act up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well... <thought>I've never even seen a full episode of that dumb show.</thought> A-actually, I'm kind of a fan of Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Whoa! That's totally hard-core!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're calling ME hard-core?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">So, what else do you like about him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell me I have to keep this act up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Got to think of something...</thought> I like it when he, uh, he vanquishes his foes!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah! Whizzam! The Steel Samurai always wins! Always! Check this out! It's my fan album!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the...? It's all pictures of the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I go to every live performance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Those stupid publicity stunts where they beat each other up in public...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">I always take a picture when the Steel Samurai lands the final blow! Whizzam! I got 'em all! I never missed one! A perfect collection! Check it out! My new digital camera!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wow, that's very impressive. The newest model, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You bet, lady! I just got it for my birthday. My album has a name, wanna hear it? "The Steel Samurai: Path To Glory." The Steel Samurai always wins! Always! Hey, if you want this, you can have it, lady.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Really? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, I took these with a digital camera. I got all the data at home so I can always make another one.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, then I'm happy to accept! Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's with people always giving stuff to Mia? What a life!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you like the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Well, yeah! Duh! He's so strong!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You're judging him by his looks! You have to look at his actions, at his life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm being lectured on life by a grade schooler...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were here on the day of the... incident, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see anything unusual?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Cody.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Cody, he needs to know because he's fighting for justice. Isn't that the Steel Samurai's motto? "For great justice"? You have to help us fight for great justice, too.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I... I saw... I saw everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, well... We might get some useful information out of him yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for this.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hey, I gave that to the nice lady, not you, loser! No looking at that, okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Believe me, I wasn't going to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody... I need to ask you something very important. What did you see on the day of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... I got here that day around 2:00... I had to come in through the woods out back so that old lady wouldn't see me. I got kinda lost, though. I was in there for maybe a half hour or so. Then I finally got to the studio. After that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What is it, Cody?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Th-the Steel Samurai killed the bad guy! He used his Samurai Spear! Just like always! One shot, one kill! It happened so fast... I got scared. I went home after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I see. It must have been hard for you.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Man, you say those nice things but it's so obvious you aren't speaking from the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... right.</thought> Mia?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we can say for sure this means the Steel Samurai did it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">True enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the director has an alibi, so it wasn't him.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... the only person left who it could have been is Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... I have to admit, it's kind of a shock. But if you put this boy on the witness stand, your client will be "guilty" for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not call him then...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I think that would be wise. Best to leave this one alone.</line>
<line speaker="???">Not so fast, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I heard everything! This boy here's a key witness! And he's under police protection, starting now! C'mon, son. You've got a rendezvous with me down at the precinct!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">No! I ain't going! Waah!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... That didn't go so well. We're back to zero leads. And now we have a serious handicap in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what're we going to do, Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, hmm... I... really need to be going. Don't worry, Phoenix. I'm sure you'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa whoa whoa! C-come to the trial tomorrow, please! I need you there!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, can I ask you something? Do you really believe that Mr. Powers is innocent?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course he is!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... That's all I wanted to hear. Excellent. I'll see you in court, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I never expected things to go this badly for Powers's case... I'm not sure we can win this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix? If you don't believe him, who will!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, she's mad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh well... I'll see you in court tomorrow then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Great! Thanks, Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">See you soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>