<xml>
<title>Turnabout Sisters</title>

<line speaker="Cellular">Brrring... Brrrrring...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello? This is Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hey Maya, it's me.</line>
<line speaker="???">Mia! What's up? You haven't called in a while.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sorry, I've been so busy. How you been?</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, LONELY. And it's all YOUR fault. Nah, I'm just teasing. I've been great! I'm finally getting used to having my own place.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's good to hear. Actually, I'm calling because I have a favor to ask.</line>
<line speaker="???">I know, I know. You want me to hold evidence for you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Sharp as always! There's a lot of buzz about the upcoming trial... I just don't feel safe keeping the evidence here.</line>
<line speaker="???">I gotcha. So, what is it this time?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's... a clock.</line>
<line speaker="???">A clock?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yeah, it's made to look like that statue, "The Thinker." And it tells you the time! I thought you might like it. You always liked toys.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! I'm not a little girl anymore, Sis!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now, now. You know I'm only teasing. Ah, I should probably tell you, the clock isn't talking right now.</line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? It's not working? That's lame!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I had to take the clockwork out. Sorry. I put some papers inside it instead.</line>
<line speaker="???">Papers? Is that the evidence, then? Hmm, well... there's a possibility that it might turn out that way, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Can you come by the office tonight, say 9:00, to pick it up? I'll be in a pretrial meeting until then.</line>
<line speaker="???">Okay, Sis, but I expect dinner! Something good! Like... burgers! I could really go for a good burger.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Okay, okay. We'll hit the usual joint.</line>
<line speaker="???">Alright! It's a deal! Okay, Sis, see you soon!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yep. I'll be waiting, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="???">Now, Miss Fey, I'll take what's mine... the papers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry, but I can't give you what I don't have.</line>
<line speaker="???">Miss Fey, you are a poor liar. Why, I see it right over there... That must be "The Thinker" that swallowed those papers.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">How could you know...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ho hoh. You are not cogniferous of my background? Gathering information is my business, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I... I should have been more careful.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ho hoh. My dear Miss Fey... I am so very sorry. But I am afraid I must ask you for one more thing. Your eternal silence... Farewell, Miss Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh oh, I'm late. Huh, that's strange. The chief must have gone home already. She said her sister was coming over so we should all go out for dinner... ... What's that smell...? Blood...? Mia! <thought>Maybe she's in her office!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I smell blood... and that can't be good! I have to check and see if Mia... the Chief's okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That smell... Blood!</line>
<line speaker="???">... *sob* Sis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone's there!</thought> ...! Chief? Chief...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The strange girl dropped out cold. I left her lying on the office sofa. I went back to the chief where she lay under the window. Her body was still warm... I could feel it when I held her shoulder. Then, all too quickly, it began to fade... Until finally she was cold.</thought> Chief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some shards of glass are scattered on the floor. They seem to be the remains of a glass light stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The chief's chair. A simple, functional design. Feels pretty good to sit in, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Chief... It's hard seeing her like this, but if there are any clues here... She was struck on the head with a blunt object. She probably died instantly. "The Thinker" lying next to her must have been the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... there are some glass shards near the chief's body. Must be pieces of the glass light stand lying broken in the back of the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing else that seems like a clue here... Hmm...? A piece of paper! It must have fallen from Mia's hand! What could it be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's painful to look... but I have to, for Mia's sake. Looks like she was hit in the head with a blunt weapon. She probably died instantly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! A word is written in blood on this scrap of paper! "Maya"...? Did Mia write this? This piece of paper is a receipt from a department store, dated yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think that's enough snooping around for now. I'd better call the police... and find out what that girl was doing here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's encrusted with dried blood. How ironic that this became the murder weapon... again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a large building right across from the office. The "Gatewater Hotel." A nice, luxurious place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All the chief's important documents are packed in here. This is where she filed her case records and recent rulings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Surprisingly, the chief was never good with machines. About all she used this PC for was e-mail. She picked up this ancient model at some garage sale for practically nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A perfectly normal office desk. The chief had a very particular policy about office décor: "Spend big on stuff the clients use, but keep your own stuff simple."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Fey &amp; Co. ledger book. Everything is written in the chief's ultra-neat handwriting. It's a small office, but it makes a good bit of money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! I'd better call the police! ...? That's funny... A few of the screws on the receiver are missing... It looks like someone was halfway through taking it apart.</line>
<line speaker="???">Police!? Please, come quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what was that!? Someone screaming from outside the window!?</thought> ...! She's staring right at me! She's holding a phone in her hand...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The phone receiver is missing a few screws. I'd better not use it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>That girl just now... where'd she go!? I put her right there on that sofa...! Uh oh... I hope she didn't run on me.</thought> Yipes! <thought>Don't scare me like that...</thought> Umm... Excuse me but, who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's okay. I work here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maya... Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Maya"...? So Mia was writing this girl's name! Maybe I should show her the receipt? I never thought there'd be a use for evidence like this outside the courtroom!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You couldn't cram more legal books in here, even if you wanted to. Few can gaze upon the shelves without feeling insignificant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door to the chief's office. It's slightly open. I'd better not touch the door knob.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A large painting. I guess you'd call this "modern art." I, on the other hand, call it a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The reception desk. I usually sit here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This sofa is for clients. It's leather... a real luxury model.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A small writing desk cluttered with office supplies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She seems to be in shock. I don't want to disturb her, but I have to know...</thought> Um... excuse me? Can you tell me what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I came in... The room was dark. And Sis... Sis...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she was already dead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're the chief's...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sister. I'm her younger sister.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you were here... visiting? This late at night?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes. She said she wanted me to keep some evidence for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes... I-it was that clock... It was "The Thinker."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about "The Thinker"...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! The Th-Thinker... That was... Oh, Sis! *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm, probably shouldn't have asked her about the murder weapon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was lying next to the chief.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know. I saw it there too. I thought they might be pieces of the light stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Maybe. <thought>Never heard of a glass light stand before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Before Mia died, she wrote a message with her own blood. She wrote it on the back of this receipt.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! Th-th-that's MY name! W-why!? Why would she write my name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please, just calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-why would Sis write my name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Now I've done it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better hurry up and call the police!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry, I've never seen that before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! The police! <thought>Sounds like they're coming this way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright, I'm Detective Dick Gumshoe, see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gumshoe...? What an odd name.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We received a report from the building across the way, see. Got a person saying they saw a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It must have been that woman I saw.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, I don't want either of you moving one inch, 'kay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great. Just great. Maya... Wait, she wouldn't have... nah.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoaaaaaaaaaaaah! Scuze me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This word "Maya" here mean anything to you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Um... that... That's my name...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">WHAAAAT!? The victim drew this here note in her own blood, see? With her dying breath, she wrote down the killer's name!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">K-killer...? I'm not--</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Case closed! You're coming down to the precinct, ma'am.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's younger sister, Maya, was arrested on the spot. I was taken in for questioning and didn't get out until the next morning. My eyes were heavy... but I couldn't sleep. I sat around, waiting for visiting hours to begin at the detention center. I had to talk to Maya as soon as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, they have poor Maya locked up like a criminal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! It's you! The lawyer... G-good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning! <thought>She looks so tired...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... Are you going to be my attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's what I wanted to talk to you about...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better give it to her straight...</thought> It's up to you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Up... to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I don't think this is something I should decide. After all, you're the one in trouble here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... They're never going to believe me... are they? Even you, when you found me in the office. You looked at me like I had done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First things first, I better get her cheered up...</thought> Yeah, of course I will! Cheer up!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-really...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa! Did I say the wrong thing? She looks sadder now!</thought> Um... what... what's wrong? You don't think I can do it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... No... no one could! Who would believe me? Even you, when you found me in the office. You looked at me like I had done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe if I joke a bit she'll cheer up...</thought> Hah hah! No way, Jose! Just kidding...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Eh heh. Whoops. That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? M-Maya...? Was that a... chuckle?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? N-no! ... It wasn't very believable, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not really...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'm sorry! I just thought, since you'd made a joke... Please, don't mind me! You're doing just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who's trying to cheer up who here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I knew it. No one will believe me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even you-- when you found me in the office. You looked at me like I had done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Did I look at her like that?</thought> No, no! I never thought...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-it's okay. I understand. ... And... I've also heard about you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heard...? Heard what about me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... was talking to my sister on the phone the other day...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"Today was my junior partner's first time in court."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Really? How'd that go?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"It was quite the scene! Honestly, I was on edge the whole time. It's been a while..."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hah! So, he crashed and burned?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"...He's a genius. One of those 'strike fear into the hearts of evil' types... The only thing he's lacking is... experience."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh, sounds like it was fun! Well, I know who to go to if I ever get into trouble now!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"I don't know, Maya. I think you might want to wait... give him three more years. That is, unless you want to be found guilty."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what she said!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean to trouble you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's okay. It's true, I guess. But... at the same time, I can't just sit and watch! When I think of the person who did this to Mia...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I know...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile for the camera...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He hasn't moved an inch. A real pro, this guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something I've been wanting to ask you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with that outfit?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, this? This is what all acolytes wear. It's my uniform, you could say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-acolytes? Like people in religious training? What is it you do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! It's nothing strange, really! I'm a spirit medium. ...In training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A s-spirit medium!? <thought>I'm pretty sure that qualifies as strange.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! Let's see... that morning, I got a call from my sister. She wanted me to hold onto a piece of evidence for an upcoming trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes. That clock shaped like "The Thinker."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The one Larry made...</thought> How could that have been evidence in a case?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, right, she said something about that... ... I remember! Do you want to hear it in her own voice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-her own voice!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes. I'm pretty sure our conversation is on my cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You recorded it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! I forgot how to delete those things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about the day of the murder? Sorry... I know it must be hard.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, it's okay. All I've been doing the last few hours is talking about it. I've kind of gotten used to it... Let's see... that morning, I got a call from my sister. She wanted me to hold onto a piece of evidence for an upcoming trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's "The Thinker" clock that Larry made. It practically qualifies as a serial murderer by now.</thought> So then, when did you arrive at the office?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was right around 9:00. The lights were off and... I could smell blood. Th-then I found her. My sister...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Maya. That's all I need to hear for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you say you have a conversation with your sister on your cell phone? Let's hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Oh! I just remembered: that detective took my cell phone. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. <thought>Of course...</thought> Next time I see Detective Gumshoe I'll ask him for it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll write you a note so you don't forget, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're an acolyte. A, er, medium-in-training.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right. The Fey family, especially the women, have always been very sensitive to the spirit world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second, you said the "Fey Family"? So, Mia was into this stuff too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! She left the mountain to "follow her career," she said. Her powers were first-class, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I had no idea.</thought> Hmm... Wait...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're a real, honest-to-goodness spirit medium? With E.S.P. and all that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes. ...In training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, can't you contact Mia's spirit, then? We can just ask her who killed her!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! I-I'm sorry... I'm still in training. I couldn't do something on that level...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I thought that would be too easy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you about the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Sis... *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Better not ask her about this now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was lying next to the chief's body...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I saw that too. They said they thought these were pieces of a broken light stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that seems about right. <thought>Though I'd never heard of a glass light stand before this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember that receipt?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-you mean the one with my name on it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any idea why she...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Absolutely none! Um... Do you trust me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I trust you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why? Don't you think I did it, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I don't. <thought>It's just a hunch, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That detective thinks I did it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't think you'd believe me. You're just like the detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry... I don't like lying just to make people feel better. But it doesn't mean that I've decided you did it! <thought>She seemed so lost at the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you about your cell phone...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That detective took it when they brought me in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, Gumshoe took it... I'll have to try to get it back next time I see him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry... I've never seen that before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... I was wondering, could I ask you a favor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is the address of a famous lawyer. My sister gave me this a long time ago. She said if I was ever in trouble, I should call him. And, well, I'm in trouble. Do you think you could go ask him to represent me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure, why not? I'll go ask.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you so much! I have no one else to turn to...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Say, what about your parents...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I see. Don't worry, leave it to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you! The trial's tomorrow... at 10:00.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what!? Tomorrow!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if this guy refuses!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry... I think this is the kind of thing you should really do yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...You're right. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Actually, I asked the police to contact him, and they tried calling a few times. Nobody could get a hold of him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They couldn't find him?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I have no one left to ask!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Say, what about your parents...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-okay! Don't worry, I'll go ask him for you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-you will? Thank you so much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just worried what will happen if I can't find him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They told me that if I don't find one, the state will pick an attorney to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When will that happen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They're giving me until 4:00 this afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And visiting hours are almost up... I'd better hurry!</thought> Right, I'll be back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The office is filled with police officers. They're all busily searching for clues...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! You there! This is a crime scene, pal! No trespassing! Umm... Sorry, don't I know you from somewhere? Wait, you're that Butz guy, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, Phoenix Wright. <thought>How could anyone mistake me for Larry!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, guess I got the wrong name, Mr. Wright. Sorry 'bout that. That Butz guy, he was a killer! And you're no killer! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He WAS proven innocent...</thought> Umm... right. And you were...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Gumshoe, wasn't it? Dick Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="???">Right! At your service. Hang on! That's Detective Gumshoe to you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Suedeshoes, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="???">That's me! Don't step on my blue suede shoes... Wait! That's a song, pal! My name's Dick Gumshoe... W-wait! That's Detective Gumshoe to you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Gumtree, was it? Detective Gumtree?</line>
<line speaker="???">G-Gumtree...? Gum doesn't grow on trees, pal! And I'm the one in charge here so don't push your luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever you say, Detective...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, get the name right. And don't go calling me "Dick"...</line>
<line speaker="Police">Hey, Dick! Get over here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-yes, sir! B-be right there! Umm... ahem! You're her lawyer, right, pal? If you got business here, you'd better do it quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew! He thinks I'm Maya's lawyer...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a horrendous amount of legal books here. Scarier still is that Mia probably read all of these.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's favorite potted plant. I remember it had this bizarre name no one could ever remember.</line>
<line speaker="???">"Cordyline stricta," pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who was that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. Perfectly clean, as always. The only thing it's missing is... Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An old movie poster. Apparently, this was the first movie that made Mia cry when she saw it. I'll have to check it out one of these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sky is blue, and so am I... There's that hotel, right across the way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About Ms. Fey... did you do an autopsy?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm? You want to know the results, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now don't you look at me like that, pal! It's no use! She might have been your boss, but that doesn't mean you get any special treatment. Alright, alright. You can see the report, but that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Mia's death was instantaneous.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal. She was... a beautiful person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You knew her, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure. All of us down at the precinct knew Ms. Fey. Much as it pains me to say this, she was a darn good lawyer. Hey, what are you looking at? I just got a little dust in my eye, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, about Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! I'm looking forward to the trial! Sorry, pal, but this is one trial you aren't going to win!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The city's put Prosecutor Edgeworth on the prosecution!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sure you know what that means, you being a lawyer and all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal! Mr. Miles Edgeworth himself! Wait... you do know him, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know him. He's a feared prosecutor. He doesn't feel pain, he doesn't feel remorse. He won't stop until he gets his "guilty" verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, don't talk about him that way. You make him barely sound human! Still, I'm afraid this pretty much decides the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, Edgeworth is on this one... He hasn't lost a case since he became prosecutor at the incredibly young age of 20. Of course, there are rumors of back-alley deals and forged evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoa! And you call yourself a lawyer, pal!? About four years ago, this Edgeworth guy became a prosecutor at the age of 20! Everyone says he's a genius. Surprised you don't know him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course I know him... I was just playing dumb. He's a cold, heartless machine who'll do anything to get a "guilty" verdict! There are rumors of back-alley deals and forged evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I know for sure is that Edgeworth hates crime with an almost abnormal passion. I never imagined I'd be facing him so soon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering, do you know anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That statue? That's the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? He thinks the clock is just a statue, too... I'm starting to wish I'd never seen this thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was broken glass at the crime scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm? Oh, that? Seems like a glass stand next to the victim fell over. The glass shards were pieces of the broken stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a piece of paper next to the victim, wasn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. The one with the killer's name written on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure that Mia wrote it herself?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Given the condition of the writing, it's hard to say if it's her handwriting or not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So there's no proof that Mia wrote it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering... did you see Maya Fey's cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh that? I have that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could give it back?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure! I mean, wait a second, pal! Tricky lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh, he's on to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... if I tell him why I want it there's no way he'll give it to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, it's just... You know, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nope. I know nothing, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That cell phone has a lot of numbers on it... like her boyfriend's... A cell phone holds all a little girl's sweetest and spiciest secrets!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Urk? Y-you're trying to confuse me! Sorry, pal. I already checked all the numbers in memory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Impressive! You're quite the detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh huh. Oh, here, you can have the phone back. There weren't any suspicious call records in there, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, I can't be straight with this guy... but what should I tell him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, um... T-that carrying strap on the cell phone...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This? Hmm... it says "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo"... "The Steel Samurai"... that action hero on TV?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you see that strap is a collector's item... She... was worried it might get lost if it went down to the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That what she said?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um. Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Okay, pal. I wrote down all the numbers she called anyway. Here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems he didn't notice the recorded conversation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't mention it, pal. When it comes to dealing with lawyers, "fight fair and square," is our motto!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know how I feel, seeing everything written up like this... It makes Mia's death seem so... routine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems he didn't notice the recorded conversation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm? What's that? Sorry, pal, but I got no info for the likes of you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You all done, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, yes, thank you. I'll be heading out now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, wait. One more thing I wanted to mention to you. I don't suppose you're planning on talking to that witness. Anyway, you'd better not! No influencing the witness with your lawyerly ways, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Come to think of it, I had completely forgotten about her...</thought> The... witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, Miss April May. I'm sorry 'bout this... But I can't tell you anything about her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, you just told me her name. Miss May, huh?</thought> So you've sent her home already, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ahah! You're trying your lawyerly tricks on me now! She's not to go outside her room until the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So... she's still in the hotel across the way.</thought> I guess I should know better than to try to get a detective to leak information.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got that right, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Time to pay a visit to Miss May!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>According to the receptionist, the big boss is "out". She couldn't say when he'd be back. It must be hard to keep track of everything when you're a famous lawyer... Not to mention run an office like this. I guess I'll just have to come back later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Expensive-looking mahogany bookshelves, filled with expensive-looking books. Hmm... funny... they don't look like they've ever been read.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A solid mahogany desk. The wood's been polished to a deep luster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That painting has been bugging me ever since I stepped in here. The oil paint is so thick it's practically giving me a stuffed nose. I'm sure the price is nothing to sneeze at either, for that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An expensive potted plant. No idea what kind of plant it is, but it's probably the most expensive one available.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A table for clients. Hmm... an elegant ebony case, and if I'm not mistaken, that lighter's made of solid gold. Even I can tell someone here's got money to burn.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! What is it? Did you meet the lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry. I haven't seen him yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. I'd better go see if I can find this elite lawyer she's talking about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about your family?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I only had my sister. My father died when I was very young. And I don't know where my mother is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't know...? So she could still be alive?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">The women in my family have been mediums for generations. They say that E.S.P. runs in our blood. About fifteen years ago, our family was involved in an... incident. There was a man, and he... he... He ruined our mother's life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Ruined"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">After that, she disappeared. Several years after that, my sister announced she would "become a lawyer" and she left the mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... So, you live by yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes. I've gotten used to it. Oh, also... I had to become independent, or I would lose my E.S.P.!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel bad for her, all by herself up on that mountain...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, who was this man who, um, "ruined" your mother?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">About 15 years ago... there was an unusual murder case. It made quite a stir, everyone was talking about it, apparently. The police were running out of leads, and they were getting desperate...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... they didn't use a spirit medium, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The police convinced my mother to try to contact the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... So, what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The case was solved... we thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "thought"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The man my mother helped the police capture was innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The police's consultation with a medium had all been carried out in secret, of course. But... A man found out about it and leaked it to the press. He told all the papers that my mother was a fraud, and the media jumped on it big time. She... my mother... became the laughing stock of the nation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... White...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me? White?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was his name. My sister told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">White? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I got your cell phone back.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Say... Can I listen to my sister's voice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Maya's eyes closed... She listened to every word with such intensity... Before long, tears began to roll down her cheeks.</thought> ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="April">Well! Hello there, handsome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... hi. <thought>Smooth, Wright, real smooth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">You're the lawyer, aren't you? The detective told me... He said, "Don't say nothing to that lawyer, pal!" Tee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Memo to self: thank Detective Gumshoe for making my job harder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Gee! This is all like something out of a movie! It's all so exciting I can hardly contain myself! Ooh! Let me go freshen up so I can look the part of the beautiful eyewitness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I pity the lawyer that has to cross-examine this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A simple bed. It's been recently made. Nothing eye-catching here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The flowers are fake, as expected. I know sunflowers and tulips, but that's about the extent of my floral knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah. A still-scene painting. Wait, should that be "still life"? Whatever. One of those is hanging on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bottle and two glasses are on the table. Somebody must be staying with her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The late summer sunlight streams through the window. There's the Fey &amp; Co. Law Offices building, of course. You can see the inside of the room pretty clearly from here. I think it would be a little difficult to recognize a face from this distance, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's a screwdriver stuck in this drawer. I wonder what's inside? Let's take a look...</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Hey! H-h-hey!!! What are you doing!? No touching! Oooh. Bad boy! Y-you really shouldn't pry around in other people's rooms, now. You wouldn't want to make me upset, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Upset!? I thought she was going to explode for a second there! I wonder what could be inside the drawer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... what's inside I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">*cough* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could tell me something? I need you to describe what you observed at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="April">Ooh. "Observe," "incident"! You sound just like a lawyer in the movies! I like a man with a big... vocabulary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... *gulp* Better not encourage her.</thought> Er... you know that thing that occur... um... happened the other day? The bad thing? What did you see when it happened? I don't suppose you could tell me about it? Pretty please?</line>
<line speaker="April">Let me see... Um, well... Dream on! If you want to know, you'll just have to come to the court tomorrow, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, could you... just who exactly are you?</line>
<line speaker="April">Oooh, Mr. Lawyer! Are you hitting on me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-n-no! Hey! I'm just doing my job here!</line>
<line speaker="April">Tee hee! You know, you're cute when you blush.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Believe me, this is the first time in my life I've blushed this much...</thought> Umm... eh heh. Right... can you just tell me what it is you do?</line>
<line speaker="April">Well... No! Tee hee! And you had your little hopes up, didn't you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see there are two glasses on the table. Is someone staying here with you?</line>
<line speaker="April">Oooh! What amazing powers of observation! You must be one of those famous detectives, like on television!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, no, not me, I'm, er, just a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="April">Say, Mr. Big Detective, why don't you go look for clues... in the garbage? Hmm? Miss May doesn't like nosey little lawyers... Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="April">Excuse me, but I'm a witness? Police witness? You understand? How could I possibly give you any information in good conscience, hmm? Me... "the witness"! It's just like the movie!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... seems like Mr. Grossberg is out. Well, maybe I should just wait here for him to come back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">*Ah-HHHHEM!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If that wasn't the most over-the-top clearing of the throat I've ever heard!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah hah! So, you're the one they say has been looking for me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... y-yes, that's me! <thought>He looks even... grander than I imagined!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm...? That badge on your collar...? Ah, so you're a lawyer, are you now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, well... yes.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">And what do you want? I'm not particularly busy these days... Please, proceed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not busy...? Then how come no one could get in touch with you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm? Something the matter? You came to see the one-and-only Marvin Grossberg, did you not? Well, here I am, boy! What do you want? Out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... w-well, sir, actually it's about Maya. Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...! Ah... yes. Maya Fey. Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm? Why the strange reaction?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">A-cha-cha. I'm really quite busy here, son. I can't go taking cases on a day's notice! No, it's quite impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a second! How did you know the trial was tomorrow!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Urk? Ahem! A-anyway... I'm afraid it's entirely impossible for me to represent her. Sorry. End of discussion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's going on!? He refused me before I even got a chance to ask him! What do I tell Maya...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>Looks like Detective Gumshoe has gone home. The police are still keeping themselves busy in the chief's office. No one has time to talk to me. Guess I'll head out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's favorite potted plant. I guess I'll have to water it now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Maya's not here. She must be in questioning. They probably won't let her out for a while. Maybe I'd better go talk to that lawyer again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you just refuse like that! Please, tell me why you won't take the case!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm? Eh, ahem! Well, you see it's just... I'm busy, you see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the client is Mia Fey's sister!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... ahem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia trusted you... She knew  her sister would be in good hands.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, yes, of course I know that. However! I'm sorry but, I must refuse. Sorry. Good-bye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Creep. Fine. I don't have time to argue with you anyway. I'll go look elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">*grumble*... Think not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Did you say something?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I think not, I said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I'm terribly, terribly sorry. But I'm afraid that no lawyer worth their salt will take on this particular case. Terribly sorry, m'boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I... I cannot say. ... I beg your pardon, but could you leave? Now? I've nothing more to discuss with you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's going on here!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you know Mia Fey...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... She... worked here. A long time ago. Quite the apprentice, that one. Learned my techniques in the blink of an eye! She left one day, quite suddenly... She had a mission, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "mission"?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You could see it in her eyes. She followed it with a burning passion. Never looked back, that one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... quite a painting.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ahah! You noticed! It's my pride and joy! Impressive, isn't it? Well? ISN'T IT? The color of the sky! The hue of the sea! The weave of the straw hat! It's worth at least three million. I have no intention of parting with it, of course. No, I won't sell it! Not even to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't interested...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It's not for sale!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not buying! <thought>Geez!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Very sorry, but I've got nothing to say regarding this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hiya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! You're back! Did you find the lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... well... <thought>What do I tell her?</thought> Well, see... <thought>Just be honest!</thought> I... I really don't think you should use that guy. He... didn't seem healthy. He was all skin and bones!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... What really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't mean... He refused to help?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urp.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I see. I've been abandoned, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>4:00 PM. Time's up. What should I do? Do I just leave her and go home...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's nothing left here for me to do... She'll be better off with a state-appointed lawyer.</thought> I think I'd better get home now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good-bye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a few days later when I found out how the story ended. The result of the trial was in the newspaper. "Guilty." I'll probably never meet her again. Did I make the right choice? Will I ever know? Mia... if you can hear me, please, tell me! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not! I can't let that happen! I'm not leaving here until she takes me as her lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've made up my mind! I'm going to defend you whether you want me to or not!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">! Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? Well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>No one is as sad as a person without any friends. I know... I've been there. A long time ago. Why did I become a lawyer in the first place...? Because someone has to look out for the people who have no one on their side.</thought> Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You aren't the culprit! Someone else is!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-how do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, um, I have a hunch... <thought>Given the evidence, it would be easy to assume that Maya was the killer. But there's something about this whole thing that smells... fishy. That witness's strange behavior... was that all an act? And the way that lawyer refused to help out Maya... But more than all that, she has no one left to help her! Nothing is more sad, or more lonely than that. I know... I've been there. A long, long time ago. Why did I become a lawyer in the first place...? Because someone has to look out for the people who have no one on their side.</thought> Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To be honest, I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Is this girl sitting in front of me the killer? All the evidence seems to say "yes." But there's something about this whole thing that smells... fishy. That witness's strange behavior... was that all an act? And the way that lawyer refused to help out Maya... But more than all that, she has no one left to help her! Nothing is more sad, or more lonely than that. I know... I've been there. A long, long time ago. Why did I become a lawyer in the first place...? Because someone has to look out for the people who have no one on their side.</thought> There's only one thing I know for certain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I won't abandon you. You can count on me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... That's so kind of you... *sniff*... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well! Let's fight this one and get you out of here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-right! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew, she smiled at last. She looks like an entirely different person!</thought> One last question... You are innocent, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! And I trust you... So you trust me, too, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a deal. <thought>So, what next... There's something that's been bugging me... Just what was inside that strange woman's drawer? It was when I tried to look into the drawer that she got all defensive. There has to be something in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Good afternoon, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, I beg your pardon, sir! I am the bellboy of this establishment, at your service, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">I've just come up to deliver room service, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... do you know where Miss May might be?</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah. I believe our guest Miss May is currently using the, er, facilities...? If you've no need of anything, I'll be taking my leave. Please, stay as long as you like. Enjoy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... Wait... no! Hey! ... <thought>Why does it seem like every time I come here, I end up embarrassing myself? Wait... now's my chance to snoop around a bit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Ah, I almost forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gah! Y-you came back quick!</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Might I ask you to inform Miss May that there is a message for her? Please tell her that Mr. White, of Bluecorp phoned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. Sure. <thought>Mr. White... of Bluecorp? Where have I heard that name?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">White... That was his name. My sister told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"White" was the name of the guy who ruined Mia and Maya's mother! Could it be a coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a screwdriver sticking out of that half-open drawer. Now's my chance to see what's inside! ...! What do we have here! A... wiretap? Hmm! What would a woman like her be doing with a thing like this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is definitely something suspicious about this "Miss May"! Why would she have something like this in her hotel room? There's a story behind all this, I know it! Alright... I'll be using this bit of evidence in tomorrow's trial, that's for sure. For Maya's sake... I'll get to this woman's bottom! Wait... I mean ... you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="April">Oh, bellboy...? Still there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, time to scram! I look forward to tangoing with you tomorrow, Miss May! In court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>