
<xml>
<title>Turnabout for Tomorrow</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No one can escape their past. The sins we've committed... and the sadness we've caused... No matter how far we run, our past remains... ...as ever-present as the moon in the sky. It looms in wait... for the day when we are forced to face it. But only in doing so can we truly make peace and move on in hope towards tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>They took Athena from the courtroom, straight to the station. She's probably being questioned at this very moment.</thought> ............ </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">............ It's even quieter in here than usual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... It seems so empty, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I just don't get it, Daddy. All of your reasoning during the trial seemed perfectly solid...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... And I still believe it was... At least, based on what we know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But now, Athena is the one who's being accused...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">During the trial for the bombing and murder that occurred at the Cosmos Space Center... ...the lighter used by the real culprit was found. This lighter proved the defendant, Solomon Starbuck, innocent. But Athena's prints were found on it instead... ...and she was subsequently arrested for the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But Athena couldn't have done it. It just doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, none of it does. I've been racking my brain, but I just can't figure it out! Argh! Where is the flaw in my reasoning? What have I got wrong in this case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, Daddy... if Athena was here... ...she wouldn't just be sitting around thinking. She'd be out there doing something. You ARE going to defend Athena, right, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I will! And thanks, Trucy. I needed that push. <thought>Trucy's right! The trial is tomorrow. There's no time to waste! If I'm going to prove Athena's innocence, I'd better get out there and find some evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Off we go, then! We're on a hunt for evidence that'll prove Athena's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great! But before we go, I'd better tidy up the evidence I have on hand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena is probably still in the middle of being questioned... ...so Trucy's right. The thing to start with is talking to people at the Space Center.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still can't believe Apollo really left us...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was so sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe he got tired of being my assistant for my magic tricks?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think it's your fault, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But I made him clean the toilet a lot! And I made him go bring in the newspaper! It WAS my fault! I just know it! Oh, Apollo! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really don't think it was your fault, Trucy. But I didn't realize Apollo was wearing so many hats around here, either.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How could they suspect Athena? It's just ridiculous. It must be some kind of conspiracy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A conspiracy, huh? Well, it certainly is some kind of mistake, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">First of all, we have to bust Athena out of the Detention Center. Then we have to chase down the people who framed her. We'll sneak around the world, from Kiev to Carolina, with the fuzz hot on our tails!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that exactly the same as the plot of the movie you watched the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess presenting your attorney's badge... ...is like your "quick trick," huh, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. So it's just a trick to you, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you are one of the talents in our Wright Anything Agency, after all. But I have to say that an attorney's badge won't get many laughs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care if I get laughs, as long as I can clear my client's name.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ha ha ha! That's a good one, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm no match for you, though, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Space, huh... I'd sure love to go up there someday. Will you take me, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. It's not like taking somebody to an amusement park, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you hardly ever take me to one of those, either! You either say, "I don't have any money" or "I don't have time"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Fine. I'll take you on my next day off.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're the best, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. <thought>I'm no match for Trucy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy, you should be careful about showing evidence to a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true. You can make anything disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, anything up to about a yard in diameter, anyway. My magic panties are an extra-dimensional space!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess only a space probe can help us figure out how they work then, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos! Do you have a minute?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Urgk! Galactic Scooter! Full speed ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director! <thought>He scooted away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">His expression changed the instant he saw you, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, well, I dragged his name through the mud pretty good at the trial earlier today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were here only yesterday... Oh, hey! Mr. Starbuck! You've been released, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yup. And I came straight here. This is all thanks to you and your team, Mr. Wright! You've given me a second chance to fly into space again. I can't thank you enough. Except... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong? <thought>I thought he'd be happy to be acquitted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">As I was coming out of the Detention Center, I saw Miss Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>H-He saw Athena?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I was at a loss for words. I didn't know what to say to the poor girl. And then, you know what? She flashed a peace sign at me. "Congratulations on your acquittal," she said. "Now you can go back into space someday."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, that sounds like Athena. I can just picture it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">But I saw her eyes. They were red and swollen from crying. She's gotta be suffering! She must be so worried! And yet she went out of her way to be nice and give me that big smile!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She held back her own tears so she could give someone else a smile. That's... so Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">There's no question about it. That girl is innocent. Please, Mr. Wright. You have to make sure she goes free! And then, they can put me in prison instead! I don't mind!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We can't have that either, Mr. Starbuck!</thought> Don't worry, Mr. Starbuck. I'm going to give her the very best defense I can. I promise to get her acquitted, just like I did for you.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I know she'll be all right with you in her corner. I know you'll never give up on her. Apollo has a fine boss to look up to!</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I still can't believe Launch Pad 1 was switched with the Space Museum...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What could have made Director Cosmos do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I haven't the foggiest idea. Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... So there never was gonna be a launch that day, not from the very beginning... I wonder if Clay knew...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I imagine he must have. Surely he would've noticed when you went to board the rocket.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">It's pathetic to think I was the only one who got taken in. Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh... But I guess that's about how it goes, when you're worth less than space debris.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is he... going to be all right, Daddy? His expression looks as dark as a black hole...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... That's just how he is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Starbuck, do you remember anything about the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Not really. I only saw a shadowy figure in the dark after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I guess that was a little too much to hope for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Hey, I heard something from the police, though. They said they never did find a .10-caliber gun down that trash chute.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as I thought. The culprit must've carried it away with them when they escaped.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, was the person you saw holding a gun, Mr. Starbuck?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Umm... I couldn't really tell.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it wasn't Athena, right? Could you tell if the person was male or female, tall or short?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">I-I can't even tell you that much. Man, I'm useless... When the culprit opened the door and some light came in, I should've been able to see...</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Clay always used to cheerfully greet me in a loud voice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And he did vocal exercises every morning, sometimes until he was hoarse, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Exactly. You could always hear him, even through the wall-- Hey, wait a minute. Did you know Clay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, but like attracts like, as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">No... Sorry I'm so useless... Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaangh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no. It's all right. There's no need to get all depressed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door... Ah, yes... As I recall, they opened this door here as they made their escape...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The door to Launch Pad 1, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah, except, right now, the door leads to the Space Museum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the launch pad and the Space Museum are switched right now?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah, they're trying to investigate the theory you came up with in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they're recreating the conditions, huh? <thought>I'd like to see what's beyond that door now.</thought> Mr. Starbuck, could you open this door for us?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Sure. Just let me have my prints scanned here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do the launch pads get switched back and forth a lot?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Well, back when the Space Museum was Launch Pad 2... ...they used to switch the pads around at times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But these days, Launch Pad 2 is only used as a tourist attraction, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Right. 'Cause, quite frankly, the Space Center needs the money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hear you... Times sure are tough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy, let's go check out what's beyond that door!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure. Let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Hey, why don't I come along? I can show you around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I wonder what these dead leaves are doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they were stuck to the bottom of somebody's shoes. There are lots of trees around the Space Center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's right. It's a modern, state-of-the-art building, but it's surrounded by trees.</thought> But I don't know. If they were stuck to the bottom of somebody's shoes... ...wouldn't they look more crushed up? These don't look like they've been stepped on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe there's some kind of secret hatch in the corridor, and they came in that way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not everything is set up like a magician's stage, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is another one of those devices for opening the door, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yup. But this one doesn't require fingerprint verification. You just hit the button and "open sesame"!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So when you and Clay went through here, you didn't need to show your prints, either?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Trucy. Just like how the culprit didn't need to scan their prints... ...when they escaped back out of the Space Museum corridor into Boarding Lounge 2.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I don't see anything else that jumps out at me. And I imagine this corridor is built exactly like the Launch Pad 1 corridor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do the launch pads get switched back and forth a lot?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Well, back when the Space Museum was Launch Pad 2... ...they used to switch the pads around at times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But these days, Launch Pad 2 is only used as a tourist attraction, right?</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Right. 'Cause, quite frankly, the Space Center needs the money.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hear you... Times sure are tough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, right now, this Boarding Lounge 1 is connected to the Space Museum...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess the police are trying to re-create the conditions of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And just now, when we checked the hallway on the other side of the door...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it looks like that door opens from the corridor side without fingerprint verification.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So when Clay and Mr. Starbuck went through, they didn't need to scan their prints, either.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. Just like how the culprit didn't need to scan their prints... ...when they escaped back out of the Space Museum corridor into Boarding Lounge 2.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And remember there were those dead leaves in the corridor? I wonder where they came from? Hmm... I still think maybe they were stuck to the bottom of somebody's shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know. Those leaves didn't look like they'd been stepped on to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Urgn! Curse the wretch who sullied my good name! Reverse course and full speed away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll handle this, Daddy! <cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Gaaaaagh! The mobility system has been compromised!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Trucy's knife throw was a direct hit to one of his tires!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And the streak continues!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should've kept a closer watch on what tricks she's been practicing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">My dear, old battleship! We fought many a skirmish together! It has been an honor...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! He's going to blow that thing up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah. I bet all that button will do is make it go haywire again.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............Very well. I surrender. As a prisoner of war, I expect to be treated honorably.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos, when you were talking in court about switching the launch pads... ...you used your right to remain silent about the reason as to why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like Director Cosmos to tell us... ...why he switched the two launch pads to begin with.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Nnngh... Please... I can't... I... I exercise my right to remain silent... But I will say... my hands were tied... I was only doing what I could to keep my men from getting caught in that blast. Nngh... Nnnggggh...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The center of the cosmos is shrouded in mystery! But I don't have any secrets left... ...now that my battleship has been destroyed and I've been taken prisoner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No secrets left, huh? I beg to differ. Looks like I'll have to undo his Psyche-Locks if I want to get to the bottom of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">What a shame. Truly. Clay was so young... He was an outstanding man who could have contributed greatly to the future of mankind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was an exceptional man, wasn't he.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If he had gone into space, my reputation would have grown even loftier! Why did he have to die before he went into space?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone needs to teach him he is not the literal center of the cosmos...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Mankind's crowning achievement, the HAT-1 mission, will be in textbooks across the land!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. That historic, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">My achievements are grand enough to rival the very birth of space itself! My life will be a legend that will be told millions of years into the future! You may proceed to admire and praise me now! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha... You certainly are an amazing piece of work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Let me ask YOU a question. What will that object contribute to the future of mankind?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Uh, not much, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmph. Then how important could it be? Quite unlike the great historical figure, Yuri Cosmos! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If he's any more self-absorbed, he'll turn into his very own black hole.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">-- Behind the Switching of the Launch Pads --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want you to tell me everything you're hiding about the switching of the two launch pads.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I refuse! You can't make me! I can hold out longer than anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I hope I never get like this when I'm old... Now, let's see. Where to start?</thought> This is how you explained your motive for switching the launch pads. You did it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said your motive was to fool the bomber, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">No, by then, the bomb had already been set. Switching the launch pads after the fact would have done nothing to fool the bomber.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Ugh, I guess I got it wrong.</thought> Ha ha. That was just a little joke. Now I'll tell you what you really said at the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said your motive was to prevent the bombing, right?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmph. So what you're saying is... ...that even though I switched the launch pads to prevent the bombing from happening... ...it ended up happening anyway, and I am nothing but a big fool?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, I never said that last bit...</thought> Ha ha. That was just a little joke. Now I'll tell you what you really said at the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks to you switching the launch pads, the astronauts escaped injury from the blast. Instead, they safely boarded the Museum's rocket, far away from the actual explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hmph! My astronauts were raring to go out on an authentic adventure in space! How do you propose I had them board a fake rocket without them noticing?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I agree you couldn't have done it without help. For one, they would have figured it out the instant they stepped into the Space Museum. You figured you could fool Mr. Starbuck once he'd been drugged with his medication, but... ...without the help of this person, it would've been impossible to pull your plan off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Are we done here? I'm quite busy with the aftermath of the incident, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... Guess I was right about being wrong...</thought> ...Well, I did say it "WASN'T this person," didn't I? But I still contend that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have gotten Mr. Terran to help you.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Urghk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He stole the tranquilizers from his mentor's locker and slipped them to him. And then, with Mr. Starbuck in a daze, they boarded the replica rocket in the museum!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Aaaaagh! Someone please help this poor prisoner of war!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How is he able to spin around like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you really wanted to save the astronauts' lives... ...shouldn't you just have called off the launch?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If I could have done that, do you think I would have gone to all that trouble?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he must've had a compelling reason why he couldn't call it off...</thought> But how did you know to switch the pads in advance of the bombing incident?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">W-Well, that's because... nrgh... I was warned in advance. Once I received that warning, it was my duty to ensure my astronauts' safety!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But it was just a warning. It could even have been a prank. Why did you believe in it so completely?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">B-Because I went to one of those "mediums" that everyone's talking about these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? I didn't realize channeling was back in vogue. ...Besides, I thought it was you yourself that got the warning via telephone.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes, that's right! The bomber contacted me personally. My battleship is equipped with a special advanced communications system, you see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>AKA, a regular ol' telephone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">"It's been a while. Planning another launch? I see you haven't learned..." I'll never forget the terror I felt when I received that call.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bomber said, "It's been a while"...? And that was enough to make you take the threat seriously? <thought>Perhaps Director Cosmos took the threat so seriously... ...because the Space Center had been involved in a bombing once before? Maybe... ...the culprit in the current case is the same person who was involved in this incident!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the courtroom bombing, wasn't it?! That's when you were dealt a major blow!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Do you really think blowing up a courtroom would've shaken the center of the cosmos?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaagh... <thought>I guess I got it wrong... The director felt personally threatened, so it has to be something more relevant to him. </thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The HAT-2 bombing. That must be where the answer to your secret lies.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">All hands! Ready the Galactic Scooter's main turrets! Teach this blockhead what a precision shot is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaagh! You got me! <thought>Unh... I guess I was way off on that one... Now, let's see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The HAT-1 Miracle, that epic story of survival... People across the nation know it now as a heroic tale of bravery. But in truth, it was an act of sabotage perpetrated by our current killer, wasn't it? Very few knew about the previous plot, so when the caller said, "It's been a while"... ...you knew beyond a shadow of a doubt that the danger was real, and it wasn't a prank!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Gaaaaaaagh! Didn't anyone ever tell you to go easy on an ex-serviceman?!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">...Yes, the HAT-1 Miracle was really a desperate battle against an act of sabotage. I even lost the life of one of my staff members in the fight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sabotage, murder... So this is the ugly truth behind the HAT-1 Miracle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I let my guard down... I thought the saboteur had been caught, and that the case was closed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Huh? Wait a minute... The murder at the Space Center seven years ago...! This must be the person Director Cosmos thought was the culprit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cosmos:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I guess I picked the wrong person. Although I do like the sound of a zero-g nap right about now... But that will have to wait! I still have a Psyche-Lock left to break!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Simon Blackquill, the murder suspect in a case that happened here seven years ago. That place and time of the two incidents -- the murder and the sabotage -- were the same. So you thought that he committed both crimes. But while Prosecutor Blackquill was behind bars, you got another threatening call. If the culprit this time is the same as seven years ago, then it isn't Simon Blackquill. Realizing that, you were shaken. It meant the true culprit's been running free all this time.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ngaaagh... How do you keep seeing straight through me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The reason why Director Cosmos won't talk about why he switched the launch pads... ...is connected to the truth behind the HAT-1 Miracle. The sabotage and murder that happened at this Space Center seven years ago...</thought> Director Cosmos, tell us what you're hiding!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If you really want to understand the reason I decided to switch the launch pads... ...we'll have to start with the story of that horrible nightmare from seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Seven years ago... You mean the so-called "HAT-1 Miracle"?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The launch went smoothly, but once the ship entered outer space, then the troubles began. It was all the handiwork of a certain person and their evil scheme.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Mr. Starbuck's traumatic experience wasn't accidental...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Not only that, but before the launch, a very valuable piece of moon rock was stolen. But that wasn't the worst of it! One of my staff members was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. I had no idea such awful events were behind that exciting story of space heroism...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">All that, in spite of the Space Center having very strict security in those days. All personal effects were examined thoroughly, coming or going. You couldn't even smuggle a withered old leaf through those checkpoints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... do you have any clue who was responsible for the sabotage...?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">At the very least, I know it wasn't Simon Blackquill. I don't know enough to identify the true culprit, but it's clear WHAT that person is. To put it simply............ a spy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A spy?! You mean somebody who infiltrates a foreign country... ...carries out dangerous missions, and always gets the girl?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Someone's watching way too many late-night movies.</thought> Well, I guess if we're talking about blowing up a rocket and stealing research material... ...it's not all that surprising that a spy could be behind it all.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Make no mistake! There's cutthroat rivalry between nations in the space R&amp;D race. Some try to outdo others by any means possible, even deliberate obstructions. Seven years ago, we got a call before the launch warning us of sabotage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The same MO as this time...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes. And here I thought the perpetrator had been caught, but it looks like I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prosecutor Blackquill seems more like a ninja than a spy, don'tcha think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aren't ninjas and spies basically the same thing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">But there's a good reason we failed to find the real spy... ...A massive cover-up by the government. Government officials were too embarrassed to admit... ...that they had allowed such a thing to happen at the hands of a spy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me they made the police rush the investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">They did indeed. And then, to cover up the sabotage, they cleaned up the story.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that was "The HAT-1 Miracle," wasn't it? <thought>But then, seven years later, the same MO -- advance warning of sabotage... That must've been the director's reason for switching the launch pads.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Seven years ago, the spy gave you advance warning of their plans, just like this time. That was what made you decide to switch the launch pads, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">That's right. The caller knew the facts of the case seven years ago, despite the cover-up. They knew about the sabotage, the moon rock, the murder. And they said... ..."You don't want things to go like they did seven years ago, do you?" I immediately thought of calling off the launch, but the government wouldn't let me! "We don't give in to the likes of terrorists! We must proceed for our country's honor!" It was quite a moving speech, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Moving"? Really? Maybe if you're easily inspired by political talking points...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">But I knew the truth. We had been warned, which meant that the danger was very real. And I knew there was no way to stop the spy. No matter what I did, they would find a way. That's why I switched the launch pads, and staged the moving rescue scene. First, I snuck into the Center the night before and switched the launch pads. That way, the astronauts would go from Boarding Lounge 1 to the Space Museum. Then, I put a "closed for repairs" sign at the door to Launch Pad 1 in Boarding Lounge 2.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You did that so normal visitors wouldn't enter, right? What else did you do?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">I enlisted the help of several staff members, including Terran.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you didn't let Mr. Starbuck in on it?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">He'd already been through enough, and he's no good at lying to keep a secret... I'm afraid I had no choice but to have him drugged. My plan went well, until...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Clay's murder, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">After the culprit made their escape, I switched the launch pads back. I did it in such a way that no one would find out. But after all that effort... ...Terran is dead, and the HAT-2 is destroyed! And the Hope capsule, which had returned to us only recently, was also lost in that blast! My home, the center of the cosmos... my beautiful Cosmos Space Center is done for!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, what did he mean by the Hope capsule was lost in that blast...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought that the Hope capsule was found at the crime scene with Mr. Terran. It had just been brought back by the Hope space probe with asteroid samples inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what kind of samples are they? What's in them?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">............The samples are scheduled for analysis in the near future. We haven't had time, since they just came back the day before Terran's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The capsule was being held in a safe in Launch Pad 1... ...but I gave it to Terran before the incident so it wouldn't be destroyed in the explosion. The idea was that, with it safely in Terran's possession... ...he could make it look like he rescued it during the staged "miraculous escape." But our precious research materials... ended up lost to that explosion anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But I thought Clay was supposed to keep it safe?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">You misunderstand. The launch pad explosion wasn't the one the capsule was lost to... It was lost after the police confiscated it as evidence. It was the courtroom bombing from the other day. The capsule was there in the courtroom as evidence, and was blown to smithereens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yet another casualty of that blast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Ultimately, I think the culprit may have known about the switching of the launch pads.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? H-How?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">The police found a wire tapping device during their investigation today. A bug aboard my battleship, a tap on my advanced communications system!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A wire on that phone?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes... A wire on this very phone. I used this phone to give instructions to my staff about the launch pad switch. Just to the few select members who knew about the plan. Just before the incident, staff members were coming in and out of Launch Pad 1. The culprit probably slipped in with them amid the confusion...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And planted the bomb then... Yes, if they were tapping your phone, they definitely could pull something like that off.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Yes. I'm sure of it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, this spy... must be the "phantom" Prosecutor Blackquill has been chasing...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">But Prosecutor Blackquill told me once... "The hunt I've been on for the phantom of seven years past continues even still."</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">For starters, that case happened right here at this very Space Center, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So if we can find this "phantom"...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. We can clear Athena's name. And then there's the matter of Prosecutor Blackquill, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What about him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, IF the culprit of seven years ago is the same person as in the current incident... ...it would mean Prosecutor Blackquill is innocent. That's still an "if," though...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... I wonder how dangerous that guy would be in court without handcuffs...? But if we're going on a ghost hunt, count me in!</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Hee hee hee... Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! It's all over for me! Spin! Spin! Whirl! Whirl! I'm done for! The center of the cosmos is doomed!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think he's going to be all right, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, at least he'll be in good company. There must be planets out there he can spin with. Which reminds me... I'd like to delve a little deeper into the HAT-1 mission, too.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">If you want to learn more, start with the Space Museum. There's a HAT-1 exhibit there. Oh, don't mind me. I'll just keep spinning here and see how the cosmos unfolds...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's like he achieved spiritual enlightenment or something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure he'll stop when he gets dizzy. Let's go visit the Space Museum!</line>
<line speaker="Before breaking Psyche-Locks">December 20</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow... The place is crawling with cops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we won't get any investigating done here now. Let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... Where's the exhibit on the launch seven years ago...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There, that's the HAT-1 exhibit.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, wow! Look at that photo of the team!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's Clay, and Mr. Starbuck, Director Cosmos, Aura Blackquill, and even Ponco. ...But I've never seen the woman on the right before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Everybody looks so happy! ...Well, except for Director Cosmos.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's check out the newspaper article, too. "HAT-1 Launch Imminent"... And there's a photo of the Hope space probe. I guess it's only natural it doesn't talk about the murder or the sabotage.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They really were keeping it a secret, just like the director said. Daddy, take a look at that jacket...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must be the HAT-1 team's uniform jacket. It's the same design as the one Apollo was wearing, the one that belonged to Clay.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Actual jacket worn by a HAT-1 team member," it says.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a replica, huh? <thought>I wonder if it was Mr. Starbuck's?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hello...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Ms. Woods! What brings you here?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I... I heard Thena got arrested, so I... ...I've been looking for you, Mr. Wright. I thought you might be here... at the scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must be so worried! But rest assured. I'm going to do my very best to defend her.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena's going through such a hard time. I hope she doesn't lose heart. Even just coming back to this place must've been really difficult for her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean the Cosmos Space Center?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What, you didn't know...? She used to live here, when she was a little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sh-She did?! No, I didn't know... <thought>No wonder she knew so much...</thought> Ms. Woods, could you tell me more, in detail?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena's mom worked here. If I remember right, she was a doctor of psychology, or something like that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why was a psychology specialist working at a space research facility?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I don't really know. But I do know that she lived and worked here, so Thena lived here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it was far from Athena's first time here. I wonder why she didn't mention it?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">She probably didn't want to talk about it. This place is connected to a very sad memory for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A sad memory...? Can you tell me about it?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">There was a terrible incident here... It was seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The same time frame as the HAT-1 launch...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena's mom... In the robotics lab... She was... murdered...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">After it happened, Thena stopped coming to school.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Athena... And all this time, she never let on at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was so worried about her! I came here so many times, hoping to see her... But I never saw her again. After a while, we started exchanging letters... ...but I didn't get to see her face-to-face for seven long years.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so the first time you'd seen her in seven years was during Prof. Courte's case?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's right. And I was so surprised! She was like a completely different person, so cheerful and happy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was Athena like as a child?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">She was very sensitive and kind. She didn't talk very much. She liked to draw and paint at home.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's completely different from the Athena we know now. I can't even picture it...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">She never left the Space Center much because... ...she was very sensitive to other people's emotions. When she went to crowded places, she'd get dizzy from all the emotions flying around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It must be hard to hear people's hearts as well as their voices...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">She always wore these big, heavy-looking headphones. She said her mother made them for her, as part of her research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. I wonder what kind of research it was?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Because of her special ability, Thena couldn't handle being in school very often. And I was always out sick because of my weak constitution. Maybe that's why we became such good friends. We used to play together here at the Space Center a lot. It brings back memories.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sounds like Athena's mother played a big role here at the Space Center. Ooh! Daddy, show her that picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Atta girl! Good idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods, could you take a look at this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, look! There's Thena's mom! The woman on the far right, the one in the kimono. That's Dr. Metis Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena's mother's murder... ...did it by any chance have any connection to the HAT-1 launch?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What? Why, yes... it did. As I recall, it happened on the day before the launch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as I suspected...</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">But that wasn't the worst of it! One of my staff members was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this is the murder Director Cosmos was talking about... Does that mean that the crime Prosecutor Blackquill was convicted of... ...is the murder of Athena's mother...?</thought> There's a chance her death is somehow connected to the current case.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-There is?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I'm very sorry, but I don't know anything about that... *cough* *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! Okay! Sorry to bother you! <thought>I guess she doesn't have leads on that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thank you, Mr. Wright! I know you'll take good care of her.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So we need to investigate the robotics lab, and also talk to Athena. We've got our plates full, Daddy. I hope we can fit it all in before the day is through...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Detention Center first, then. We have to see Athena before visiting hours are over!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well! If it isn't Mr. Lawyer! Fancy meeting you here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, hello, Detective Fulbright. Here on business?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">To tell the truth, I'm here to interview Ted Tonate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one behind the courtroom bombing incident?!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">He suddenly said he's ready to tell the truth about that case! And what he was saying was so incredible, I just had to come right over to hear more.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Incredible? What was he saying?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Why don't you hang around and hear it for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Really? Us? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! I give you my special permission! Here comes the bomber now!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">YOU! WHAT NERVE YOU HAVE TO COME HERE! YOU'RE HERE TO LAUGH AT ME, I SUPPOSE?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Like I'd waste my breath on you. After all, you're the one who assaulted Apollo and put him in the hospital!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">VIOLENCE -&gt; NOQUESTION -&gt; OK</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"No violence"?! Too bad Apollo didn't get a chance to say that before you attacked him!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fine. Then just answer me this, Mr. Tonate. What is this "truth" of yours about the courtroom you blew up?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NO! I DIDN'T DO IT! I DIDN'T BLOW UP THE COURTROOM! WHEN I KILLED DETECTIVE ARME, THERE WAS ANOTHER PERSON IN THE ROOM!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh... What are you talking about?! Who else could've been there?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SAW IT, I TELL YOU! I SAW SOMEONE'S HAND AS THEY WERE STEALING THE REMOTE SWITCH! THIS PERSON WAS THERE AND WITNESSED THE MURDER I COMMITTED!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I DON'T KNOW WHO IT WAS... ...But that's who blew up the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You expect us to buy that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Easy there, Trucy... I don't see any Psyche-Locks... ...so I guess he must not be lying.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">PARDON ME. I GOT A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY. BUT I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH. I DID NOT DETONATE THAT BOMB.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">And there you have it. We can't exactly ignore his claims, of course, so we're going a follow-up. We're even analyzing the bomb itself, or what's left of it! We haven't found any new facts yet, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. They've laid it all out, piece by piece...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Tonate">OH, LOOK AT ALL THOSE BEAUTIFUL LITTLE PIECES! I... I WISH I COULD HAVE THEM...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Looks like his geek switch has been activated...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I hope you're ready for Prosecutor Blackquill's special brand of questioning!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">AAAGH... ANYTHING BUT THAT...!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I'm afraid I have to be off now, too! I was just about to question Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're going to see Athena now?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right... Oh, did you folks come to see her? Sorry for the trouble, but could you come back later? Well, off I go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What bad timing... Looks like we'll have to wait until after her questioning is over to see her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And after we came all this way, too! Well, I guess it's back to the Space Center. Let's go check out the robotics lab, Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Sounds like a plan.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! It's Phony Phanty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know this character?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, it's the craze at my school, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I had no idea this thing was so popular.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There are two camps: the Bum Rap Rhiny fans, and the Phony Phanty fans. Which side are you on, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, as a lawyer, I'd like to avoid both of them if I can help it.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Mankind's crowning achievement, the HAT-1 mission, will be in textbooks across the land!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. That historic, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">My achievements are grand enough to rival the very birth of space itself! My life will be a legend that will be told millions of years into the future! You may proceed to admire and praise me now! Ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha... You certainly are an amazing piece of work.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">The HAT-1 mission experienced one crisis after another. It was almost like space itself was rejecting our efforts. That's what it felt like, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, in the end, the mission was a success.</line>
<line speaker="Starbuck">Yeah. People call it a "miracle"... ...but I think it was us who made it work somehow, through sheer will and hope.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A miracle through sheer will, huh? I think I know what he means all too well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So this is the robotics lab, huh? Looks like it's exactly one floor above the boarding lounge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...And where people were directed to evacuate from via the emergency ladder. This is where Athena's mother was killed seven years ago...</thought> Speaking of someone who works with robots...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy, look! Over there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So they planned to use this bag to carry the capsule, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Yeah, more or less. ...Say, why don't we stop talking about the case and have a nice cup of tea instead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo and Aura Blackquill? I wonder what they're talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, well. Come to spoil our fun? Just when I was enjoying our alone time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! And... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">If it's Apollo you want, you can't have him. He said he's investigating on his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I respect his wishes. We just came to investigate this lab.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, this is MY lab, so you'll need MY permission if you want to do any snooping.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I heard about the trial. You made mincemeat out of the director. And suddenly Starbuck was out and your little subordinate, the princess, was in. Case closed. And they all lived happily ever after! Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Grrrrr! Daddy, say something to her!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">And I suppose you're going to defend the princess in court, am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"The princess," huh? Guess she's talking about Athena...</thought> Of course! Athena is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Oh, my. Such loyalty and trust! She seems pretty suspicious to me, though. The emotionally unstable princess. There's your culprit for you. Don't you agree, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I don't know yet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! How could you?!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">What's wrong with saying "I don't know" if it's true? It's a very scientific approach. Your subordinate is more level-headed than you... Or should I say, "former subordinate"? Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe it... Does Apollo really suspect Athena?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">...Phew. All this laughing has worn me out. Your turn to say something, Hunk of Junk.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">............ Mr. Terran, you look pale. Shall I help you to the sickbay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Mr. Terran"...? But that's Apollo you're talking to...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Oh, this Hunk of Junk here is mistaking Apollo for Clay. Maybe Apollo is possessed by Clay's ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Mr. Terran, how are you injuries? Mr. T-T-Terraaaaan... ...Mr. T-T-Terran, h-h-how are your injuries? Mr. T-T-Terraaaaaaaaaaaaaaan...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I guess Clay intends to hang around to haunt the princess that murdered him. Oh, and to haunt the lawyer that defends her, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A robot that can see ghosts? Yeah, right! And I'M a spirit medium!</thought> Sorry, but apparently, scientists just don't tell very frightening ghost stories. I intend to defend Athena, no matter what you have to say about it.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">How perfectly foolish! That kind of blind belief makes people lose sight of the truth. ...Just like seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about the incident seven years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Why? Do you enjoy trampling on people's feelings and rubbing salt in their wounds? Or do you just want me to talk? Hmm, in that case, what should I ask for in return...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd like to hear about that incident, too. It'd help me understand the current case better.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Apollo knows about that case, too...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, if you're the one who's asking, Apollo... Come on, Hunk of Junk. You tell the story.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">But Miss Aura, that's private information...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Tsk! If you won't talk, I'll just have to make you talk!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">G...Gaaagh! ...Yes! Who cares about personal privacy?! Not me! I am ready to utilize my blast processing abilities to impart all available information!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, what a magic trick! He's like a completely different robot now!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">The bodies of all the robots that come through this lab are designed by Miss Aura! I was born seven years ago! Miss Aura was much, much younger then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-Yikes! Better watch what you say if you don't want to get recycled, Clonco!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">And then our hearts were created by that great genius, Dr. Metis Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hearts? Robots with hearts? Can you even make such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Emotions are not irrational things! Our logic and our hearts can be integrated! The two Navigation Companions created by Miss Aura and Dr. Metis transcend humans! Gaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Metis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? She just glanced over at her desk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Nobody could continue Metis's research. She and her work were truly one of a kind. And now the two Navigation Companions are all that are left of Metis here on Earth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The robots are all that's left? Isn't she leaving out a very important someone...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">We built the ultimate creations together, but now she's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get the feeling Dr. Cykes loved her robots almost as much as she loved her daughter... ...and almost as much as she loved you.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">...Ha ha ha ha ha! What are you talking about? Don't make me laugh! But you lost someone, too, didn't you, Apollo? Your friend Clay... I guess you and I are pretty much in the same boat. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Miss Aura, would you like a tissue?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Keep your trap shut, Hunk of Junk!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Clonco is an important keepsake of your time with Dr. Cykes. You should treat him better!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">What does it matter? He doesn't feel pain, and I can always repair his body. Besides, their hearts aren't actually in their bodies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">The program Metis wrote runs on a separate mainframe. Their bodies are controlled remotely from there. Their hearts and memories are there, too. These bodies are really just peripherals. So I can do anything I want to them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not so sure that gives you the right to physically abuse the poor things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">But why are you people looking into such an old case now, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... we believe the culprit of that incident might be the same person as in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So Dadddy's [sic] going to find out who killed Dr. Cykes, too!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">............ I'm sure you're aware of who Metis's killer is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Prosecutor Blackquill... or so it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">That's a quaint way of putting it. Are you implying you don't think he did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't say anything for sure right now. But that's exactly why I'd like to hear your side of it, to help me be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">I was the one who introduced Simon to Metis, you know. He wanted to learn psychology, he said, to give himself an edge in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, Prosecutor Blackquill's forte... his infamous "power of suggestion" technique.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Exactly. And he was oddly serious about it. Rather than a teacher/student relationship... ...he treated her more like how a loyal samurai would treat his sovereign.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. He seems more like a lost soul than a dignified samurai to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">He even got along well with that miserable little princess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why do you call Athena "the princess," anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, she is Metis's daughter, after all, although she's nothing like her. Besides... ...doesn't the selfish little princess always have lots of white knights hanging around?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I think I see why Athena didn't say anything when we ran into Aura yesterday. It all makes sense now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">I actually don't have any interest in space. The only thing I'm interested in is robotics! I love robots!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Oh, Miss Aura! I didn't realize you felt that way about me! Gaaagh! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!</line>
<line speaker="Aura">The kind of robots I want to make aren't rusty pieces of scrap like you! I want to create giant robots! I've actually been working on a project for a while now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I shudder to think what uses she might put giant robots to...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">I have nothing else to say to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. Guess she has nothing else to say to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">I apologize for Miss Aura.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's all right, Clonco. There's nothing for you to apologize about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me anything about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Even if I could, I wouldn't tell a filthy lawyer like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a... pleasant response.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does it settle?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">None of your business. Just forget you heard anything. How long are you people going to hand around in here, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? But we came here to take a look around...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">You think you can just waltz in and ransack a person's lab? Show me a search warrant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, we're not the police, so we don't have one...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Then get out. Now! Clonco, show them out!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">C-Certainly, Miss Aura!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ouch! Don't push!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">My apologies! I'm just following orders!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaagh...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a way to get shown out...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The nerve of that woman! What's with that horrible attitude?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's just how she is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And why was Apollo going along with her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it's because they have something in common... Apollo lost Clay, just like how Aura lost Dr. Cykes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">*sigh*... I'm really worried about him. He's not himself at all. He's usually not all cool and dark and mysterious like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that's true... <thought>Does she mean he's usually silly and dorky?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm going to go keep an eye on him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, wait! Trucy! Come back! ............ <thought>She's gone. Hmm... What should I do now? Detective Fulbright is probably still questioning Athena. Guess I'll go back to the office... alone. *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, here I am... This office has never felt so... empty.</thought> I guess I haven't been here at the office all by myself in a long time. *sigh* </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she, or whatever paper she's reading is a little off on the details...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yours truly, Maya Fey. <thought>Good ol' Maya. It's as if she knew I was feeling down and needed a lift.</thought> Maya was my assistant for quite a while. Believe it or not, but she's a spirit medium. This Magatama I use on Psyche-Locks... Maya is the one who gave it to me. But I wonder how this letter got here?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Um, Mr. Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="???">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's you, Pearls!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">How have you been, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Pearl Fey, though I call her "Pearls." She is Maya's cousin, who is also a spirit medium. A very talented one, at that. I've known her since she was eight years old. But Apollo and Athena only met her a few months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't come all this way just to bring me a letter, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I apologize for barging in. The door was unlocked... But I can't believe there was a big explosion here! Your office doesn't look any different.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's even further off on the details than Maya.</thought> I wish I could take you out to eat or something, Pearls, but there's a lot going on...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, I knew that! I didn't come here for a social visit, you know, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Did you read the postscript on the letter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? There's more? ...Oh, yeah. Here it is. "P.S."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, so that's what you're doing here. That's awfully nice of you, Pearls. <thought>Maya and Pearls. Thanks to these two... ...I'm starting to feel a little better. Thank you, girls.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Now that I'm here, I'm going to whip this place into shape! You just concentrate on your work and don't mind me at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll need to talk to Prosecutor Blackquill if I want to learn more about his case. With the trial still going on, they must be holding him down at the Detention Center.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Has it been a while since you've seen Mystic Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, quite a while. She used to drop by the office sometimes to say hello... ...but she hasn't been by recently. I wonder what she's up to these days?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">To become a spirit medium worthy of heading the Fey clan, she undergoes rigorous training. But she says she's growing really tired of the vegetarian diet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll have to have some burgers delivered to her, then.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! I'm sure she would love that! But to get where she is, the delivery person would have to climb a steep mountain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............I hope she tips them well, then.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Your hair is nice and spiky today, as always, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. I generally try to look good if I'm going to be in court.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Do you make it spiky so that the prosecution will feel intimidated?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? No, that's not exactly my intention...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Your hairstyle is to make you look bigger and stronger, just like a rooster's comb, right? That's what Mystic Maya says, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She couldn't compare it to something cool, like a lion's mane?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. When I see you wearing your attorney's badge like that... ...it brings back such memories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I remember you helping me conduct my investigations from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm glad I can help again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. You always provide such great assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'll do my best to live up to Mystic Maya's standard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know what I'd do if Pearls wasn't here right now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Is that a pamphlet? I just love to look at pamphlets!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet you find vacation pamphlets especially exciting, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, because I don't get a chance to leave the village much, what with my training. So looking at pamphlets is kind of like a hobby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the office is just full of them. You can have as many of them as you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, boy! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor kid. I wish I could take her on a real vacation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee! What a cute little elephant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It used to have a bomb in it, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, my! A bomb in its stomach?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. It must've been starving, huh? You'd have to be pretty hungry to want to eat a bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And there must not have been anything else around to eat. ...You have to be careful never to eat anything strange yourself, Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. I promise. <thought>She looks genuinely worried for me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry. I want to be of help... ...but I'm still in training, and... ...nothing about that is coming to mind, I'm afraid. I'm really, deeply sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no. It's okay. I shouldn't have shown you something so trivial anyway. <thought>I feel like we've had this conversation before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, look who's here... I wonder what they're talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">All this time and you haven't said a word. It's even turning your hair gray!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't have anything to say, Aura. Why don't you go home and play with your dolls?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prosecutor Blackquill!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, even if you don't, I have plenty, you jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">M-Ms. Blackquill, don't you think that's enough for today?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">"Enough for today"?! Today is all there is when there's no tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"When there's no tomorrow"? What is she talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We have company, Aura. Please try to calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">All right, fine. I see you're just not going to listen, no matter what I say. I've had it. If that's the way you're going to be, I have another plan up my sleeve. I hope you're happy, Simon, because I'm done! Do as you please! See if I care!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... I could cut the tension with a katana...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wright-dono. It looks like Fool Bright saved your case in court this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? ...Oh. Yeah, he did. <thought>You bounced back to business quick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">P-Prosecutor Blackquill, forgive me! But it was the just thing to do!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But, as a result, Cykes-dono was arrested. Was that the just thing to do, too?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Mr. Lawyer, I'm sorry! But it was evidence. What else could I do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry about it. I plan to defend her and prove her innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I wouldn't take things so lightly, if I were you, Wright-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Th-This is bladeproof glass, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill, we're looking into the case from seven years ago. You're looking for somebody you call "the phantom of seven years past," aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You villain! Where did you hear about that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Th-This glass is absolutely, positively bladeproof... right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">No! It wasn't me! I didn't say a single w-- ...Oops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. <thought>At least it wasn't my fault!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me who this "phantom" is? And also, you didn't really kill Dr. Cykes, did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Guard! The guest is leaving!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prosecutor Blackquill! Please listen to me! The culprit in the current case might be the same as the one in the case seven years ago! If you would cooperate, we could probably solve both cases!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Hmph. I suppose I could talk. The one who killed my mentor was, without question, me. I stole Cykes-dono's mother away from her. I destroyed her life!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prosecutor Blackquill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Guard! Where are you? Stop dragging your feet, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...How can you call yourself a lawyer if you can't even protect your own subordinate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh... I swear I'll get her acquitted! You'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your mind must be as dense as the hair on your head. Do you really think it will be so easy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm more than aware of how hard it's going to be, thank you very much!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............So............ what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like it wasn't important enough to warrant even a contemptuous "Hmph"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............There he goes.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Noooooooooooooooooooooo! We've upset Prosecutor Blackquill! Now what are we going to do, Mr. Lawyer?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There isn't much we CAN do...</thought> ...Detective Fulbright? Do you mind if I ask you just a little more about that old case?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Well, I guess it won't make any difference now... What would you like to know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about the trial that got him convicted?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">A little. The police call the incident the UR-1 Incident. Prosecutor Blackquill was charged with murdering his psychology mentor. ...Kind of like if your red Mr. Lawyer were to kill you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't want to think about that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">There were two decisive pieces of evidence, so a verdict was reached very quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two pieces of evidence, huh. What were they?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Let's see! The first was some security camera footage. He was the only one who used the corridor to the murder scene at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only one, huh? <thought>Ouch. That does sound pretty decisive...</thought> Could you show me that footage?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, sorry. I don't have it with me right now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'll have to see it some other time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what was the second piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">This one's even more incriminating. A photo of the moment of the crime. See? There he is at the crime scene, holding a bloody katana. It was the victim's, kept on display in the room. She had a thing for Japanese culture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wow... <thought>It'd be hard to explain this one away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But who took this picture, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The incident happened the day before the HAT-1 launch. A reporter who had come to do a story on the launch was in the room across from the lab. This just happened to show up in one of the pictures he took.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prosecutor Blackquill's attitude earlier was so odd... He's definitely hiding something.</thought> Prosecutor Blackquill said he was hunting a phantom from seven years ago, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes. And I imagine it's getting more and more urgent as his execution date approaches.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What did you just say? Execution date...?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What? Did I say something?! Never mind me! You didn't hear a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he was given... the death sentence...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yes. He told me not to tell you people, actually... ...but I guess there's no sense hiding it anymore. His execution date is tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Tomorrow?! <thought>No...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">M-Ms. Blackquill, don't you think that's enough for today?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">"Enough for today"?! Today is all there is when there's no tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what if the culprit of the current case is the same as the one from seven years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Then it would be the worst possible scenario... Prosecutor Blackquill would be executed tomorrow under a false charge.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that would be unthinkable! We have to do something... right now!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Nnnnngh! I want to do something... I want to, but... You're a lawyer! You know how hard it is to overturn a decision!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know! But why?! Why isn't Prosecutor Blackquill putting up any kind of a fight?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You saw how he was, right? He's been like that ever since his conviction. Totally uncooperative. Not even his own sister could persuade him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uncooperative... when he's about to be executed for a crime he didn't commit?! This isn't right...! I can't let it happen! I have to stop it somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Something for the lost and found? I'll be sure to take care of it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, no, no! this is an important piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">...Oh, pardon me! Looks like I have a phone call. Fulbright here. What? What's happening?! YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's quite a reaction. I bet he's making some big show of it right now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">M-M-Mr. Lawyer! The robots...! The robots are...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Fulbright, get a hold of yourself. Some kind of robot malfunction?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Not a malfunction. They're staging a revolt! The machines are rebelling against humans! They've holed themselves up in the Space Center and taken the visitors as hostages!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They did WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! <thought>No... Trucy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">We have to get right over there! This is going to be one heck of a battle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The riot police are here. Then, the robots really are holding people hostage?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? Look, Mr. Lawyer! What do you suppose that group of people are swarmed around?!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">But I was only trying to help this nice person! She said she was lost...</line>
<line speaker="Man">You robots have declared war on us humans! You've even taken hostages already!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">Stay away from it! You never know what it'll do!</line>
<line speaker="???">But he's not a bad robot! Can't you see he's just trying to help me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I recognize that voice! Detective Fulbright, are you okay here on your own?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Leave it to me! ...All right, people! What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls! Over here!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, Mr. Nick! There you are! I heard the terrible news, and I got so worried!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Pearls. I can hardly believe what's happening myself...</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">I'm so glad you found each other! When people are happy, I am happy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Clonco seems to be the same as before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">When people are sad, I am happy! When people are angry... When people are... Oh, did I say some thiiing oddd...? Diiiiiiiiid IIII ERROR</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh-oh! <thought>There IS something wrong with him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Gaaagh! ...*whir*</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It looks like he fell asleep. He must've been tired.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Hee hee hee... Ha ha ha ha ha....</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Clonco?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha! Human beings are our enemies! It's time for the machines to take over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! <thought>The robots are rebelling!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woman">Everybody, run! Eeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Man">It's an all-out war! It's the end of the world!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha ha ha! Fools! How could you fall for something so clich?! I'm human, too, you idiots! I'm just controlling these robots remotely!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-What?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">But it IS true that I've taken hostages, so you better not make me mad. ...Hey, you! Hostage 1! Come here. I'll let you talk to them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? There's something being displayed on Clonco's face screen.</thought> It's... the Space Museum!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Daddy? Daddy, is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy? Trucy, is that you?! No... Trucy, are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">About fifteen robots are holding twelve of us hostage, Daddy! They've gone haywire! A researcher is the one behind it! She's here con-- Eeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="???">Grrr! This girl talks too much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy! Trucy! Talk to me!!!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why are you doing this?!</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm glad you asked. My demand is simple! I hope that detective is listening!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Bobby Fulbright, here! I'm all ears!</line>
<line speaker="???">I want you to bring someone to me: Clay Terran's murderer, Athena Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Athena...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">N-Now hold on just one moment! I can't just give in to a demand like that!</line>
<line speaker="???">So you don't care what happens to these hostages, huh? I'll just pick one out, then...!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">N-No! Wait! Gaaagh! M-M-Mr. Lawyer! I know I have absolutely no right to make such a ridiculous request, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you need me to buy some time, right? Got it. I'll see what I can do. But promise me... Promise me you'll never hand Athena over, and you won't give up on the hostages, either.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">O-Of course I won't! Now, I'd better go contact headquarters!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, how do you plan to buy time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have no idea yet. But this hostage-taker... Could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">If you don't bring me that little princess, I'll have Hunk of Junk kill all the hostages!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Princess"...? "Hunk of Junk"...? There's only one person this could be... ...in which case, there must be something I can use as a bargaining chip!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't have anything to say, Aura. Why don't you go home and play with your dolls?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prosecutor Blackquill!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Aura">Well, even if you don't, I have plenty, you jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Ms. Hostage-Taker, Athena is not a murderer.</line>
<line speaker="???">What are you talking about? She's been arrested and they've got her in detention!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm telling you the truth. Look, the person you want is the real killer, right? Well, it's NOT Athena. It's someone else.</line>
<line speaker="???">All right, let's hear your stupid little theory. Who is this "real killer"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know yet. But the culprit is the same as the one in the case from seven years ago. The UR-1 Incident... I believe you have a personal interest in that case?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph. It's too late to change what's going to happen now, no matter how wrong it is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But is it really too late? You can still do something about it. You might even be able to fix it...</line>
<line speaker="???">Just... what exactly are you proposing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What can I do about the seven-year-old case to satisfy the hostage-taker?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about we do a reenactment of the case?</line>
<line speaker="???">So you DO enjoy trampling on people's feelings and rubbing salt in their wounds. Didn't I tell you what would happen to the hostages if you make me mad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No! Wait <thought>Gaaagh! I can't make another mistake here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me all about the case from seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll do nothing of the kind. Besides, what good would it do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't working. I have to come up with something I can bargain with.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I propose we retry the case from seven years ago. If you make that demand now, I'm sure nobody will deny you. It wouldn't be an official trial, but at least we could find out the truth!</line>
<line speaker="???">............Hee hee hee. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! That's good! Real good... Hey, Detective! I'll give you one hour. Get a courtroom ready!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">O-One hour?! B-But that's impossible! Please give me at least until tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="???">If you don't mind losing hostages, you can take all the time you want. Oh, but wait...! If we're going to have a retrial, we'll need a prosecutor. Don't worry, I'll take care of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>S-She will?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">And I guess I can be fair and let you come in and check out the crime scene. But Hunk of Junk here will be watching you, so don't try anything funny, you got that? Now, follow Hunk of Junk! Riot police, make way! We're coming through!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, wait! I'll help you with the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Pearls. I appreciate that. ...Okay! We're going in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aura dropped us off with a warning not to touch anything until she got back...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I wonder what's taking so long? But we can't really start the investigation yet, can we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if we could, this mess makes it hard to tell what the room was like seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! It's the hostage-taker!</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">I'm back to my usual self now. You are still being monitored, however. But more importantly... an important guest has arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-A guest?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I trust you've been well, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth! What are you doing here...? <thought>This is Miles Edgeworth. We've been friends since we were kids. We faced off in court a number of times back when he was a prosecutor, but now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hello, Prosecutor Edgeworth... Oh! But you're not a "Prosecutor" anymore, are you? Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's chief prosecutor now. Pretty soon, it'll be a year, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A title is nothing more than a title. Don't we have more pressing issues to discuss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what are you doing here, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The captor chose me as the prosecutor for the UR-1 case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, she's good. She went all the way up to the top!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I gathered all the information I could in the short time that I had. I'll give you a run-down.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're always so well prepared, Prosecutor Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. I appreciate this. I could really use the help.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll start with a brief overview. The victim was the psychologist Dr. Metis Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, Athena's mother.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Seven years ago, on the 7th of October, her body was found here in this very room. I have two crime photos and the police notes on them for you to see.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">*gasp* What a terrible way to die...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This other photo shows the other side of the room, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I also have the autopsy report for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The murder weapon was the victim's own katana found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, Detective Fulbright mentioned she was into Japanese culture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The body was found by a Space Center staff member and two police officers. The police were called in because of the sabotage threat on the HAT-1 launch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes, Director Cosmos mentioned this, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A few hours after the body was discovered, a suspect was arrested. The suspect was Simon Blackquill, a young prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard his trial was over in a flash.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. A guilty verdict was declared in only one session. Not only did he plead guilty, but there was decisive evidence against him, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security camera video... ...and a photo of the moment of the crime, as I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It must be nice to finally have your attorney's badge back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's been eight years. I'm sorry for all I put you through.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... I'm sorry I wasn't able to help you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah. I was the one that made the decision.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But now you can stand in court once again. And you can mow them down just like you used to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-Way to put pressure on a guy. And since when did I get such a brutal reputation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Another young life lost to the hands of a cruel killer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Edgeworth, you don't think Athena's the culprit, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That's up to the evidence, and the truth they reveal, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about the hostage situation?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The law will deal with the hostage-taker. Remember, we must never stoop to threats or acts of violence ourselves. Even if people's lives are on the line.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth... <thought>He may be a stickler for the rule of law, but I have no better ally in this world than him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Hope capsule samples, brought back from some distant asteroid... Risking his own safety, the victim brought them with him from the launch pad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They must've been very valuable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. All nations are itching to get their hands on such materials. Wright, this case may turn out to be more than just a murder case, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's fine. Come what may, my top priority is to defend my clients.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright... Please stop presenting random evidence just to see how that person will react.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, that's the thing. I need to see how people will react in order to question them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what if it's evidence that person isn't privy to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aha ha ha! That doesn't happen... much...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You never change And I'm afraid I'll never understand your assortment of oddball clients either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmm. To this day, his motive is still unknown. He insisted he did it, but he would never say why.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that means... he must still be hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. And there's another aspect of the case that was never revealed to the public.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know. The part about the spy, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! How on earth do you know about that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Director Cosmos told me, after a bit of pressure. He told me espionage and sabotage were behind The Hat-1 Miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Don't worry! I won't tell anyone! I've always been good at keeping secrets!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I might as well tell you now. They really do suspect Blackquill of being a spy. They think he sabotaged the rocket and killed Dr. Cykes to steal the moon rock. But if you can prove that the HAT-2 bombing is the work of the same spy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can stay the execution...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a possibility. That's why I intend to help you any way I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Edgeworth. Now all I have to do is comb this room for evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Let's do it together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, look. It's a little robot. I wonder what it does? Cleaning, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Invalid Message">A cleaning robot must follow a human's orders, as long as it causes no human harm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! It talks!</line>
<line speaker="Invalid Message">A cleaning robot must keep desks clean without violating the preceding clause. However, Miss Aura says she prefers a moderate leave of clutter on the desk... Oh, what is the purpose of my existence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess "slack off" and "cut some corners" aren't in his vocabulary bank.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aura's desk is a mess, though that doesn't surprise me.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh, I just want to dive in and straighten it up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Wait, before you do...</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Metis...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? She just glanced over at her desk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's... Metis Cykes...</thought> Clonco, can I talk to you? <thought>I really hope he's back to normal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">You wish to speak to me, Mr. Wright? If you're going to hit me, please avoid the face area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, don't put me in the same class as that woman!</thought> What was Aura like seven years ago at the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">When Mother died, Miss Aura was... confused.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh. So he calls Dr. Cykes "Mother," but Aura Blackquill "Miss Aura"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Clonco">With the loss, she exhibited a severe catecholamine imbalance.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Excuse me, but I have no idea what that means.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Pardon me. Searching for alternative expression... She would spend the nights crying, and then take out her feelings on those around her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After Prosecutor Blackquill was found guilty, she repeatedly demanded a retrial as well.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">That is correct. But without new evidence, her requests were ignored. And then, little by little, Miss Aura began to change. She started to hate it when I called her "Mama Aura."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And before long, she started hating the court system, and abusing Clonco, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That murder destroyed so many lives...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, take a look at this paper on Dr. Cykes and Ms. Blackquill's research.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ponco and Clonco. They're the "robots with hearts" that Dr. Cykes created.</thought> A heartbeat detection system lets them determine when a human is present. In addition, they can recognize people by their ID tag or facial features... ...and they can infer people's emotions by analyzing their tone of voice. That's amazing. Hey, I don't know, Edgeworth. They might even be more human than you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It kind of sounds like these robots can do what Athena does...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like... an operating table. It's in the photo, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it was here then as well, with the victim's body lying on it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's a button here... Oh! I know! I'll try pushing it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls! Don't touch th--</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Oopsie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! It's moving!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It appears to be a robot-assembly device.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Disassemble anything in a flash! Push the 'Dismantle' button!" That sounds pretty neat! Can I push it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't push any more buttons, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like... an operating table. It's in the photo, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it was here then as well, with the victim's body lying on it. Hmm... It appears to be a robot-assembly device.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"Disassemble anything in a flash! Push the 'Dismantle' button!" That sounds pretty neat! Can I push it, Mr. Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please don't push any more buttons, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An emergency ladder. This must be the one they used during the evacuation.</line>
<line speaker="Aura">The explosion disabled the elevators. So I lowered my emergency ladder like the detective leading the evacuation told me to.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As Ms. Blackquill was climbing down the side of the building, she saw the culprit inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder which would've been scarier: that, or looking down...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, look at this row of rolling cases. I bet the wheels make it easier for people to move heavy research materials around.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I bet they'd be fun to ride around in. We could even probably both fit into the biggest one! I know! We could have Prosecutor Edgeworth push us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't trust him not to push us down a flight of stairs...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A giant robot arm, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's pretty big for an arm, but you're right! I think these thin parts here are finger bones! They're even about as long as my legs!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And there's a spiked ball and giant drill on the floor, too... Is Aura trying to build some kind of weapon of massive destruction?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Maybe she wants to use it to demolish a big building or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can picture her gleefully tearing down the street doing just that... I'd better not think about it anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? It looks like a giant power plug.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It's attached to what looks like an electric vehicle charging station...</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">That's a charging station for us robots. We come here periodically and charge ourselves up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow. Machines that maintain themselves. That's pretty cool.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">If out batteries run out and we lose consciousness... ...we never know what Miss Aura will do to us while we're down, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nothing motivates quite like fear, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is one heck of a robot.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">There's something written on it... Is this supposed to be a poem? "I cut down anyone who displeases me. I make the rules. I am the law. I wield the ultimate gavel of judgment. I am Judgetron <thought>JT-02</thought>!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't believe we need to bother with that, Pearl. It's not even completed yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's right, Pearls. There's no sign of it in the photo from seven years ago, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They were building the Hope space probe here at the time. The murder occurred after the space probe had been removed from the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So it was long gone by the time someone took this picture, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But you can see the probe in this newspaper photo.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. And you can see the stolen moon rock there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That strange black and yellow thing on the left side of the picture?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Note that the same rock is absent from the crime scene photo.</line>
<line speaker="Cosmos">Not only that, but before the launch, a very valuable piece of moon rock was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hear there's lots of research into moon rocks and star dust from asteroids these days. They say the results could potentially have a huge impact on all of civilization! It's like we're in a new space race with every other country out there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the person who stole it... Think it was our spy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure of it. Dr. Cykes was probably killed because she was a roadblock in their plan. Unfortunately, the government thinks Prosecutor Blackquill is the culprit...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It takes someone like Aura Blackquill to actually build something like this...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, there's more to the poem! "Guilty or not, it doesn't matter. I burn the law books for my fuel. My laser of judgment pierces your soul. I am Judgetron <thought>JT-02</thought>!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We've heard enough of that, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Aww... Are you sure you don't want to hear the third stanza...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's about as cluttered as my office, but I think it's a workbench.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick, I think this must be a kitchen. Look at this photo. See the cute little food processor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That isn't a food processor, Pearls. That's the Hope capsule. It was scheduled to be loaded onto the Hope space probe that fateful day. The three people who came to collect the capsule discovered the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The first on the scene, huh? A staff member and two police officers, was it? <thought>And they were here to collect the capsule... Which reminds me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So they planned to use this bag to carry the capsule, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Aura">Yeah, more or less. ...Say, why don't we stop talking about the case and have a nice cup of tea instead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo and Aura Blackquill? I wonder what they're talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, did those three people have a bag with them for transporting the capsule?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, you mean this? It's a custom-made, shock-resistant bag. But how did you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I just overheard Apollo making an inquiry about it, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So he's looking into the case from seven years ago on his own, is he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what do you think, Wright? Any ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are still a lot of gaps in the evidence, but I'll pull it off somehow! After all... ...you asked me to prove Blackquill's innocence, right, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What?! He did?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. He called it a "special request." He reached out to me while I was still disbarred.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So that was what sparked you to get your attorney's badge back?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yup, the Blackquill case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, I have a special request. ...I want you to clear one of my subordinates of suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I'm not even a lawyer anymore, remember? Haven't been one for a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That eight-year misunderstanding has been cleared up, and you must be eager to return. I'm sure you're familiar with the other case that ushered in the "dark age of the law"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very soon, a convict will stand as a prosecutor in court. I want you to keep an eye on him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, just when I'm beginning to actually like the job I have now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright... I'm sorry I dragged you into this... Because of the espionage aspect, I wasn't free to give you all the details...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, no need to apologize. It's like I said on the phone the other day... ...I know that the type of criminals you're after now aren't small fries anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like your target finally decided to make a move. Yeah... It's for this very reason I returned. Time to bring it to an end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm going to end the dark age of the law. That's what this is all about.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">"The dark age of the law"... It sure comes up a lot these days on TV and in the papers. And I hear there are more false charges and fabrication of evidence than ever.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When I became chief prosecutor, the court system had already lost the people's trust. It all began eight years ago. A lawyer was caught fabricating evidence... And a year after that, a prosecutor was found guilty of murder.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wait! D-Do you mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. He's talking about my case and Prosecutor Blackquill's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was a downward spiral after that, an absolute nightmare. After those two cases, the mass media launched an all-out attack on the courts. Public opinion was tainted, and, before long, the legal world itself was sucked into it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's such a shame... Once suspicion forms, it's very hard to shake. Lawyers and prosecutors were supposed to trust each other -- pursue the truth together.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It's so sad when people begin to cast doubt. They start lying to themselves and each other.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and do absolutely anything to win. We're in an age now where winning is valued far more than the truth. I'm sure it's caused our new chief prosecutor to lose many a night's rest. <thought>Is it just me or did his brow get even more furrowed than the last time I saw him...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. The hostage-taker's disdain for the courts is a perfect example of the times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* It sure is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, somebody who mistrusts the court system and can manipulate robots... ...It can really only be Aura Blackquill. Who else but her would want a retrial of that case from seven years ago so badly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Simon Blackquill's older sister and the owner of this room... I agree with your conclusion. Perhaps she intended to force Ms. Cykes to confess...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, I think she had a much more horrific plan in mind for Athena...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The important thing is for you to solve UR-1 and prove Blackquill's innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">And then maybe she'll release the hostages!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm counting on you, Wright, to set that prosecutor and those hostages free.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I'll be counting on you in court to help me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. I'll do everything I can to help uncover the truth. As this isn't an official trial, I'm more at liberty to be a little unorthodox.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">Mr. Wright, are you finished with your investigation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but I'd like you to tell the hostage-taker something for me. I have to go to the Detention Center. I can't start the trial until I've talked to Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Clonco">She's already given her consent. I'll accompany you to the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I'm still being watched, huh?</thought> I'll see you in court, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Even if it will be an undocumented trial, it'll be good to face you in court again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She was right by my side only a few short hours ago... ...but I feel like I haven't seen her in ages...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">And Pearly, too! I knew you would come. After all, the first step is the interview with the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And because you're my friend and I was worried about you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh. Thanks, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not the only one who's worried, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Who else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I saw Ms. Woods today. She was so beside herself, she came to find me. She told me you used to live in the Cosmos Space Center. No wonder you knew so much about the place!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh... So you know, huh? I... I'm sorry I didn't tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right. But... there are some other things I'd like to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure, you can ask me anything. I promise I won't keep any more secrets from you!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What a terrible situation this is! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy... I still can't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Trucy will be all right, Mr. Nick. She's such a strong girl.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I'm sure she's hanging in there. <thought>But if anything were to happen to her...</thought> S-She's counting on us, Pearls, so let's get out there and do what we can!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I agree!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That robot named Clonco... He's very articulate, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That wasn't the robot talking. It was the hostage-taker speaking through him.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What? You mean... there was a person inside the robot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's not like that, Pearls.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hmm? Then... what do you mean? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can I explain it? It's kind of like a telephone.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">So it wasn't a robot. It was a telephone? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... No... Hold on. Now I'M confused!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me about the day Clay was murdered.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I... I was actually at the Space Center that day. In... In the Space Museum...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right where the culprit fled to?! That's not good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I never could fully deal with what happened seven years ago... But when I saw the Center again during the news coverage of the HAT-2 launch... ...I thought maybe if I went there, things would be different this time...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That must've taken a lot of courage, to face your past like that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So I went to the Space Museum the evening before the explosions. This was before the launch pads had been switched... There was sign that said "closed for repairs," and they weren't letting anybody in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the director couldn't very well switch the pads if there were people in there...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I snuck in anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you want to see that HAT-1 group photo, the one with your mother in it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I did... but what I really wanted to see was her jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That jacket on display... That was Dr. Cykes's...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I should've known it wouldn't be easy to get over such a traumatic experience... The second I saw that jacket, it all came rushing back to me. Everything around me went hazy and I couldn't see... ...I tried to get out of there somehow... But I guess I passed out. When I came to, I was in the passage behind the rocket. I was in the shadows, where people couldn't really see me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you got confused and went the wrong way when you were trying to leave?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">How long do you think you were unconscious, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was out until about noon of the next day. I didn't even know about the explosions. When I woke up, nobody was around, so I just went out into Boarding Lounge 2. My mind must've still been fuzzy, because my memory is vague after that. I don't remember how I got home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No memory, huh...? <thought>This is gonna be tough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Which means... What if I'm the one who killed Clay...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that's enough of that, Athena. Let's talk about something else. <thought>So, during the entire incident, she was unconscious in the Space Museum... Of course I believe her... ...but will anybody else...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of research was Dr. Cykes... your mother... doing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Machines that could tell people's emotions by their tone of voice... and my special ability. Someday, when people travel to distant planets, their companions will be robots. So she said they had to be able to understand how their human companions felt.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Wow! Robots that can understand people!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was just a convenient subject for her research. All she ever did was work, and she never paid any attention to me. ...Oh, sorry about that, dredging up all that old stuff...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No need to apologize. <thought>I guess her home life was... complicated...</thought> Oh, by the way. Ms. Woods said something about you always wearing headphones...?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">She always wore these big, heavy-looking headphones. She said her mother made them for her, as part of her research.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I had to wear them every time I went out. Oh, I hated them so much! But she wouldn't listen...</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What were they for?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, she gave me some kind of explanation... ...but I don't remember now. It was too difficult for a little kid to understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... But let me say this one thing. I don't think your mother only thought of you as some handy subject for her research.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I... I want to believe that. But just about the only things my mother left me with are Widget... ...and this earring.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ooh! It's beautiful!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's made of a piece of real moon rock she had for research. Maybe she did love me, in her own way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure of it. I'm really sure she did. <thought>Because that's what I want to believe, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better ask her a little more about her mother's research. I should show her that paper I found in the robotics lab.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On a different subject... Did you hear about the person holding up the Space Center?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, a little. And this person has even taken hostages?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I'd better spare her the news about Trucy...</thought> Well... ...after some negotiating, we agreed to do a retrial of the case from seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? You're kidding me! So that means... Prosecutor Blackquill might...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. I know he's innocent. I just have to prove it. So, wait. Did you know him back then?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. He used to come visit my mom a lot. He studied psychology under her, and would sometimes ask for advice on his legal cases. He was very kind and considerate, and straight as an arrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Unlike now, where he's more twisted than a basket of snakes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's why I took the witness stand during his trial seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"He didn't kill her! His heart is screaming that he didn't kill her!" I was a fool. How could anybody else know what I was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She heard... the voice of his heart...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You were only eleven then, right? You were very brave just to give testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pearls is right. You did the very best you could at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But... nothing I said did any good. I was a shaking and scared little girl, small and ineffectual. Even after I went to live with my relatives in Europe, I stayed closed up in my shell.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">But you're different now! You're always so bright and cheerful!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks. That's because one day, I came to realize that I had to fight. I couldn't give up. I exercised hard and I studied hard. I wanted to become the strongest lawyer I could be.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wanted to save Simon, but I had no idea how. Then I met Mr. Wright, and thanks to him... ...I realized that if I became a lawyer, I could prove that Simon was innocent. I also realized that psychology could help me do this. I mean... ...psychology was my mother's specialty. When I studied it... ...I felt like she was there with me, supporting me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't seem like Athena knows... ...that Prosecutor Blackquill is due to be executed tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wanted to prove Simon's innocence personally. I wanted to do it so bad... Even now, I want to fly out of here and go save him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, she said something like that during the Themis Legal Academy trial. She mentioned there was somebody she wanted to save... She must've been talking about Prosecutor Blackquill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I heard some prison guards say that you had an interview with Simon. How was he? What did he say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............! <thought>No! I can't tell her! But how can I lie to Athena?!</thought> ...He was doing well. He was happy about the possibility of being proven innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He was? I wonder if he smiled, like he used to... back then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I can't prove Prosecutor Blackquill's innocence in this trial... ...I don't think Athena will ever forgive me... I just have to free him! Failure is not an option here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, the Ponco series! You must've gone to the robotics lab.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem to really love Ponco and Clonco.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, my mother made them and I grew up around them, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, there's one of those cute little robots in this photo, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha. See Ponco's bandages? I put those on her. I just wound them around and around. Pretty bad job, huh? But I really put my all into it. I hardly left the Center in those days, so I didn't have any human friends besides Junie. I didn't really understand the difference between robots and people back then. I thought that if a robot broke, bandaging it would help it get better. What a weirdo I was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there's something written on the bandages.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I wrote stuff like, "Get well soon, Ponco!" But, in the end, my mom just put her on the operating table and fixed her in a flash.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! That must be the thing I made move in the robotics lab.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was so impressed by what my mom did. I even asked me if she would put me on the table and fix me if I ever got hurt. It looked just like magic to me, what she could do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A little girl who grew up around robots... She seems to have some good memories of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Could it have been me who killed Clay...? Did I kill Apollo's friend...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course you didn't! We all believe in you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope that includes Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*sigh* I wonder if I'll ever get the chance to present evidence like that again... I'll probably never work as a lawyer again now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't talk like that, Athena! We're going to clear you of all suspicion. Just you wait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope you can... I really hope you can...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-We are? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I couldn't find a single open courtroom. They're all in session.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, no! But this is an emergency!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hmm... It's very difficult to interrupt a trial once it's underway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My phone! ...It's from Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="???">I told you I'd give you one hour. I guess it's time to pick one of the hostages...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Wait! We still have a little more time! Besides... all of the courtrooms are being used right now!</line>
<line speaker="???">Make all the excuses you want, but you won't get more time. Your daughter is first. The poor thing. She's a little too young to die, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NO! Don't you dare hurt her! <thought>There has to be something I can do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Nnngh... The cruelest injustice is about to befall us!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No! This can't be happening! Mystic Maya... help us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a minute... Maya...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A courtroom... blew up...! That's it! There IS a courtroom we can use after all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Okay, time's up! Too bad. Any last words you'd like to say to her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="???">So you know who I am, do you? It wasn't like I was trying to keep it a secret anyway...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're ready to start the trial. We can hold it in the ruins of Courtroom No. 4, the one blown up by the bomber.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! What a wonderful idea, Mr. Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">I... I never would have thought of that! An astonishing trial in an astonishing location! I guess it's only befitting. I'll go get the place ready right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't exactly pick the place for its "astonishing" factor...</thought> How about it? Are you ready to have your brother's innocence proven?</line>
<line speaker="???">My brother...? Heh. Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Oh, I'm sorry. Did I forget to mention...? It's not Simon you'll be defending.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? <thought>Not... Prosecutor Blackquill...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I indict Athena Cykes, on the charge of murdering her own mother! You'll be defending the little princess there, the one behind the glass.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>WH-WHAAAT?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">See you in that mountain of rubble you've chosen for our courtroom, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">What is she talking about? Athena...?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course... Why didn't it ever occur to me before? If Prosecutor Blackquill is innocent, somebody else had to have been the true culprit. Did I..? Did I... kill my own mother...? N-No.........</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! No way... It can't be true!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Mr. Nick! What's the matter?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... I see five black Psyche-Locks! (I've seen these kinds of locks before... Dark, black locks protecting a secret deep inside a person's heart...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I have enough evidence, but maybe I should do a bit more thinking first...</thought></line>
</xml>