<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Edgeworth, your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution will show the court that at 2:30 PM on October 15, the defendant, Mr. Will Powers, killed fellow actor Jack Hammer at Studio One of Global Studios. It is impossible for anyone else to have committed this heinous crime. The evidence presented during the trial will all point to this fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I see. Very well, I would like to move on to your testimony. Mr. Edgeworth, the prosecution may call its first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First, I would like to call a familiar face, Detective Gumshoe, to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective, if you would briefly describe this case to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes sir! I'll explain with the guidemap here. To understand this case, it's important to grasp the layout of the studios, see? This here is the Employee Area. The actors did a run-through of their action scenes during the morning here. This is the main gate to the studios. The security lady that works at the studios was here at 1:00 PM on that day. Past the security station there is a gate, see? Past that are the studios. And here it is... Studio One. This is the scene of the murder, where the body was found! Now, on the day of the murder, October 15, there were only three people here. The victim, Jack Hammer, the defendant, Will Powers, and a young woman, the production assistant. All the production staff were in the Employee Area until noon. Then after lunch, the victim, Jack Hammer, went to Studio One. Right after that, at 1:00 PM, the security lady got to the guard station. Now, jump ahead to later that day... 5:00 PM. The production staff came to Studio One to perform a rehearsal. Needless to say, the rehearsal was cancelled... The time of death was 2:30 PM. The "Samurai Spear" found lodged in the victim's chest was the murder weapon. That's the case, in brief. Anyone like to hear that again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... should I listen to that whole thing again...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, could you describe that one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I shoulda known it would be you, pal! Fine. Once more for the mentally-challenged lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, yeah. Live it up while you can, Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I can probably remember that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the murder weapon was a "spear"? How... medieval!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. This case is quite simple if you ask one question: And that question is: "What did the security lady at the guard station see?"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's call this security officer to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness declare her name?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">... Hmm? My, aren't you a handsome fellow! I'm afraid I'm a bit flustered!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-your name, please!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, dearie! No need for you to be embarrassed! Just call me "grandma."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">YOUR NAME, PLEASE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Seems Edgeworth has a bit of trouble getting his witnesses to say their names...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wendy Oldbag, dearie. So just call me "grandma." It's practically my name! So even when I was young I was an Oldbag, but not really that was just my name dearie. Still how the other children would make fun of me and just because of my name can you believe it? But there was this boy, the captain of the chess club in junior high, and when he called me an old bag well I just cried and cried because I had a crush on him you see--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-objection! I... object to the witness's talkativeness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection sustained! The witness will refrain from rambling on the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was just getting to the good part, dearie!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps we can get to the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, the witness was stationed at the main gate on the day of the murder, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yessey I was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And to get to the scene of the murder, someone would have to pass by you?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You know your stuff, dearie!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... You may begin your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She sure is one hell of an Oldbag...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">On the day of the murder, I arrived at the guard station at 1:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You saw the defendant, then? Hmm... Very well. Let's begin the cross-examination. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">On the day of the murder, I arrived at the guard station at 1:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So up until that time, anyone who wanted to could go into the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, there wasn't a security guard at the gate, no. But the main gate was locked, dearie. You'd need an employee cardkey to get in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... the cardkey that I have. So, what she's saying is no one who wasn't supposed to be there could get in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was there anyone at the studios when you arrived at the guard station?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Poor old Hammer and the rest had been doing a run-through there since the morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "run-through"...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They were working out a scene between the Steel Samurai and the Evil Magistrate. They got the basics figured out by noon, and were to use the afternoon for practice. Rehearsal was supposed to start at 5:00. That's why poor old Hammer went to Studio One in the afternoon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Powers was in his dressing room sleeping... when he was supposed to be practicing! Talk about a laid-back hero...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If there was a run-through in the morning, why did you only get there after noon?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I, well, I had some errands to run that morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of "errands"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, well, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Answer the question!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Actually... I was watching poor Hammer and Powers. Observing, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-observing? Weren't you supposed to be at the guard station?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Whippersnapper! I told you I locked the gate, didn't I? I did my job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not sure your boss would see it that way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway! I always watch Hammer's run-throughts. Always! Never missed one in all my years.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I want to see a Steel Samurai run-through too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could quit being a spirit medium and take up guard duty.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not a bad idea...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, it was 1:00 when I got to the guard station.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see the victim then?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Did I see poor old Hammer? Nope. He'd already gone to the studio before I got back to the guard station.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell us what happened next.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was at the main gate from then until 5:00!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were watching there the WHOLE time? No breaks? Not even a second?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">O-of course! I am a professional, you know! Our are you criticizing how I do my job!? Whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's just, after seeing you eating those donuts in the guard station yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I can watch the gate and eat donuts at the same time! Snipperwhapper!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Snipperwhapper"...? Old windbag is losing it, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you raise an objection?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the witness was on duty through the afternoon, the whole time. Very well. What did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Now, the murder happened at 2:30 PM, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh hoh hoh. I have my ways! That over-dressed young detective told me. I fed him some donuts and he talked and talked... If you ask me, that detective isn't cut out for his job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Detective Gumshoe, getting chewed out by a security guard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Interesting to me, because a certain man walked right by me at 2:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">2:00? You're sure?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Sure as spit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, who was the man!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Really, you should try not to get so excited at your age. You might strain something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Now, now, don't get your skivvies all in a bunch. I'll tell you who it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was Powers! That man right there, and he was heading toward the studio!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you saw Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's what I said! Got wax in your ears, sonny?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, this is your chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, time to pull out the secret weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'll say it again! It was him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Doesn't she seem like she's enjoying this a little too much?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Windbags love gossiping about other people's misfortunes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ugh. Can't she get her kicks somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me get this straight, old bag! Er, Ms. Oldbag! You've been saying since yesterday that you "saw Mr. Powers," correct? But you're talking about the man in this photo, aren't you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">J-just a moment, Mr. Wright. Let me see that photo! ... What is this, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">None other than the Steel Samurai, defender of Neo Olde Tokyo. Ms. Oldbag! Is this the "Mr. Powers" that you saw!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Of course! Didn't your momma teach you any sense, sonny? Anyone can plainly see that's Powers! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, yeah. ... Umm... well. I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, Mr. Powers does play the role of the Steel Samurai! But that doesn't mean Mr. Powers IS the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...! I... I know that! I wasn't born yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No one in this court is accusing you of that, Ms... er, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's having trouble calling her "Oldbag" apparently...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, you do not have proof that the person in this photo is Mr. Will Powers, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Humph! Nosy old man! Of course I have proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even Edgeworth is surprised!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution would like to ask the old... the witness. Please make known all the information in your possession ahead of time!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">How was I to know everyone would be so nosy! You should be ashamed, all of you! Anyway, I showed that photo to the young detective. He told me "this isn't any good as evidence, pal." He didn't even give it a second look!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, old windbag has left even Edgeworth speechless. She's good!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear about your proof, then.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I never say anything I don't mean, mind you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. So he had sprained his ankle...? Very well. Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's got to be hiding something... I'll press her until she squeals.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I never say anything I don't mean, mind you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I haven't said anything yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I'll have you know I'm not pointing fingers at anyone behind their backs! Everything I've said is on the straight and narrow! The up and up! Youth today! Always whining about each other, pointing fingers this way and that! It's enough to make an old lady want to cry...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright! Please, for all our sakes, try not to upset the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think Edgeworth has met his match...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That morning, during the run-through of the action scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was present at the run-through?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, let's see... There was Powers, he's the Steel Samurai... Then poor old Hammer, the Evil Magistrate. And... me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what exactly were you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Observing! Just... observing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, she was off moving backdrops around and such.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she didn't see the run-through, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I saw Powers trip and fall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Trip and fall"...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes! And to think, he's supposed to be the Steel Samurai! What a laugh! So Powers sprained his ankle. I helped make it better for him, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... helped make it better?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I kissed it where it hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">L-let's just skip over that part, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where was the assistant then?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, her? She was cleaning up backdrops, I think. She didn't know about Powers's ankle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You may continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He broke one of the props, it was a big mess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He broke a prop?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Sure did! His own Samurai Spear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His Samurai Spear... the murder weapon!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Luckily I was there with my duct tape to fix it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This strikes me as a significant detail... I'd better write this down in the Court Record.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Apparently, he sprained his ankle pretty bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was Mr. Power's [sic] ankle badly sprained?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Not so bad that he couldn't walk around. He went to his dressing room to rest up after lunch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thus the nap...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, I saw him dragging his foot when he walked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dragging his foot... okay.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You can see he's dragging his leg! See? Clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure? <thought>Let's take a look at that picture again... Hmm... so he was walking strangely because he was injured...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It does look like he was dragging his foot.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">See! And you didn't trust me! Whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's how I knew it was Powers. Happy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, you can't look at this and say it's Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, but only Mr. Powers would have been dragging his leg!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He has a point. It does seem quite likely that it was Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's got to be more to this. I'd better keep pressing her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? Find any glaring contradictions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she seems pretty sure that was Powers in that photo... I guess I'll just press her and see if I can shake her conviction...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think we've heard enough! Haven't we, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, there is one thing that bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which is?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where is this "Steel Samurai" costume now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... hmm. Actually, well... We couldn't find it. We're looking, though.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyway, that's not important! The witness did see the Steel Samurai, yes. And it is clear that the person in the Steel Samurai suit was Mr. Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Are you sure you're sure, Your Honor?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold it right there! We keep talking possibilities, but we have to agree that this photo shows the Steel Samurai! Nowhere in this photo can we see Mr. Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The defense has a point. I also wonder if someone else not caught on camera could have killed Mr. Hammer. We have to consider that possibility, also.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then allow me to remove that doubt from your mind, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'll wait and see where this goes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose, since there weren't any additional crew members at the studios that day... It's quite likely that it was the defendant inside that costume. I see no problem with this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Most perceptive, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He still doesn't seem that convinced to me... I hope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness continue her testimony, please?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">No need to ask twice!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The time of poor Hammer's death was 2:30 PM, true?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So, if no one else went to the studio... Then it would have to be this "Steel Samurai" who did it. Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The time of poor Hammer's death was 2:30 PM, true?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Eh? Didn't I just explain? I gave donuts to the young detective. And the, after some rubbish about it being a "secret, pal" he told me everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I see Detective Gumshoe shares his fellow officer's fondness for donuts.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The only person I saw go to the studio before then was Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you absolutely sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, quite, quite, sonny. Nobody suspicious lookin' passed by at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nobody suspicious lookin'... Right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">No one else went there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about before you got to the guard station?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">You mean before 1:00? Why, everyone was in the Employee Area before then. And I locked the main gate so no one could get in. Not to mention...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">If they had, I would have seen them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness has answered the question! Anyone going into the studio had to pass by the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's right, sonny! You let 'em have it, Edgey-boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>E-Edgey-boy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Old windbag sure has balls! Or... well, you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Old windbags have a way of skipping over important details, after all... Or, for that matter, entirely forgetting them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How convenient.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something for you to look forward to, perhaps?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on! Look at this photograph one more time. This photo was taken by the camera at the gate for the studios, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yesiree, sonny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, whenever anyone passes by here, it automatically takes a picture?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">And here I thought you didn't know your head from a hole in the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... Anyway! It's also true that the computer in the guard station records all security cam data.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ooh! You know, if you wanted to work at the studio, we might have an opening.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That very computer printed out this photo. Note that on the back of the photo are printed the words: [Oct 15, 2:00 PM, Photo #2]</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Even I know that means it was taken at 2:00 PM on October the 15th! Really, sonny!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I knew that too. The issure here is the bit at the end where it says: "Photo #2"...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">"Photo #2"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The computer only held data for one photo on that day. Don't you think that's odd? Shouldn't this photo be "Photo #1" if it really was the ONLY photo!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Please tell the court what you mean by this, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, that's what I want to ask the witness. This evidence shows that not one, but two people went to the studio that day. Yet there is only data for one of the photos! Who could have erased the data for the other photo? Only someone with access... the security lady herself!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Eh!? You watch your mouth, whippersnapper! The only person I saw that day was Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the camera on the gate fired twice! That means two people went by!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Umm... well, yes... that's what it would seem to mean...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can the witness explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Umm... ahem. I-I don't understand these new-fangled computer things... Umm... E-Edgey-boy! Help!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh!? B-believe me, I want to, but I don't know what this means either.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Humph! Some help you are! You're a whippersnapper too! ... ... Whippersnapper...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something the matter, Ms. Oldbag?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ah! That's right! I... I just remembered something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me guess... Someone else passed by the gate... someone other than the Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Er... well, yes, I suppose you could put it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*sigh* I see. Your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Every day, after I finish my guard duties, I have one other important job to do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-Ms. Oldbag! This is the first I've heard of this!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, of course, sonny! I've only just remembered it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right... anyway, Mr. Wright, please begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I'd say this was a turn for the unexpected, but I kind of expected this...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Every day, after I finish my guard duties, I have one other important job to do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Another "job"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">T-that's right. I check all the people that passed by the main gate that day. I look closely at every one of the photos that security camera takes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you backup all of the security camera data?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, they keep telling me too, yes. But those computers are just so frustrating.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I go through the photos recorded on the security computer and check them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How many photos are there, usually?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">On a day when we're open to the public, we get more than 500 people. But on filming days or rehearsal days... well, we don't have much money. We never get more than 50, and that's a big day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you backup all of the security camera data?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, they keep telling me too, yes. But those computers are just so frustrating.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I throw out any photos that aren't suspicious lookin', you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How exactly do you determine what isn't "suspicious lookin'"?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, you can tell by looking at their faces. For the most part.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-for the most part? This is a murder trial, Ms. Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, I didn't touch that suspicious lookin' Will Powers's photo, did I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she's missing the point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Come to think of it, now I remember throwing out one photo that day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Come to think of it"? Couldn't she think of that a little earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Classic old windbag maneuver, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Might be a useful tactic to remember for use in my future career as a windbag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let's find out more about this "erased" photo.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, who in the heck was in that photo you erased!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Humph. A fanboy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-fanboy?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Steel Samurai fanboys. Real freaks, if you ask me. They get information about the rehearsals from gosh-knows-where. They're always hanging about. One was there that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait a second! Didn't you just say no one else could get in!? "I locked the main gate so no one could get in"... Those were your words!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well! If you must know, there's a drain that goes into the Employee Area. The grate has been loose for a while. It leads outside, and well, that's where they come in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They come in through the drain?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I told you they were freaks. Oh, and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They're kids. Children. Whippersnappers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">K-kids!? So, on the photo that you erased...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It was a boy. Probably 2nd or 3rd grade.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order! Let me get this straight. You saw two people pass by the gate on their way to the studios that day? One was the Steel Samurai, dragging his leg. The other was a boy who looked to be in about 2nd or 3rd grade?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh yes, well we see his type there every day. Can't stop 'em. Can't catch 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A boy in 2nd or 3rd grade? Hmm... I assume it would be hard, if not impossible for a young boy to wield the Samurai Spear?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Impossible, I'd think. It's quite heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Right! As I said, I didn't pay him much mind. That's why I erased the data.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick? What's going on? I mean, the boy was there, that makes him a suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and they're already trying to "un-suspect" him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd like to take a five minute recess. I want the defense and the prosecution to consider this new information... And no forgetting vital information this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. WP?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Tell me straight: were you really in your dressing room? You didn't go to the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Will">I-I didn't go to the studio! I was s-sleeping, honest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So who was the "Steel Samurai" in that security photo?</line>
<line speaker="Will">How should I know? The Steel Samurai costume was off in the corner of the dressing room. Anyone could have walked in and taken it, really.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? You should take better care of that stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Will">I couldn't imagine anyone would want to steal a Steel Samurai costume! So... where does this leave me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It doesn't look good...</line>
<line speaker="Will">*sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're the only likely suspect, right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! W-what are we going to do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First, we play for more time. We'll start targeting someone else that could conceivably have done this!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! And it'll take them so long to shoot us down that we can get another day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... but if we pick the wrong person, we might lose on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Will">You... don't sound very optimistic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not optimistic at all, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. It's time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. Let's go. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Will">What does that mean... Please don't sigh like that! *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene for the trial of Mr. Will Powers. Mr. Edgeworth, will you present the prosecution's thoughts on this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution's thoughts are simple. Nothing has changed. The other person who went to the studios was a boy of roughly 10 years of age. The photo we do have may not be hard evidence... But there is still no one else that could have committed this crime! I call for a verdict of "guilty" for the defendant, Mr. Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Mr. Wright, your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense disagrees with the prosecution's claim. There IS another person who could have committed this crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Interesting... Let us hear who you have in mind! However... Be aware that this court does not look kindly on accusing the innocent. If you accuse someone who is obviously innocent, you will be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. Great. As if the stakes weren't high enough.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, who was this person other than Mr. Powers that could have committed murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the assistant! The Steel Samurai costume was in his dressing room. She stole it, and in doing so she became the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you're saying the Steel Samurai in the picture is really the assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's correct, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're serious, you've got guts, Mr. Wright. Remember the photo? Wasn't the Steel Samurai a little lame!? He was dragging his foot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. <thought>Uh oh. Bad feeling time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Remember the testimony concerning Powers's injury!!!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Powers and poor Hammer were at the run-through. Oh, and me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about the assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, her? She was cleaning up backdrops, I think. She didn't know about Powers's ankle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The assistant knew nothing of Mr. Power's injury! She could look the Steel Samurai look with that costume... But she couldn't walk the the Steel Samurai walk! She wouldn't have limped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That kind of takes the legs out from under that case...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I'm afraid I have to penalize you, as I warned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nobody knows... the trouble I've seen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">May we move on, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... this fight isn't over yet!</thought> If you would, Your Honor, one more chance, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the grade-school boy! ... ... ... Why isn't anyone saying anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bah! Are you seriously suggesting the boy did it, Mr. Wright!? "Grade-school boy kills veteran action star with spear!" For one thing, it was the Steel Samurai holding the murder weapon. Would you care to explain just how the boy was involved?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... maybe that was a dumb move on my part.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Maybe"? "Maybe"!? How about "absolutely," Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I'm afraid I have to penalize you, as I warned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nobody knows... the trouble I've seen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">May we move on, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... this fight isn't over yet!</thought> If you would, Your Honor, one more chance, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was the security lady! Wendy Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-who!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai is dragging his leg in this picture. That means whoever was in the suit knew about that morning's injury. Maybe because... they had been watching the action scene run-through! There was only one person other than Powers and Hammer who knew about the injury. The security lady, Oldbag!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-what!? Whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I-is this true, Oldbag!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oldbag!? That's Ms. Oldbag to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag was standing guard alone at the main gate. She was by herself... in other words, she has no alibi! She could have briefly left her post to steal the the Steel Samurai costume... Then slipped into Studio One, the scene of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-why would she go through the trouble of wearing the Steel Samurai costume!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Simple, Your Honor. She knew the camera at the gate would take her picture. If she was in his costume, she could point the finger at Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! Excellent deductive reasoning, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ohhh yeah, right here! Sherlock Holmes II, baby!</thought> ...? <thought>That's odd. Isn't this the part where Edgeworth pounces...? Doesn't he usually jump up with an objection and some new damning evidence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth? Does the prosecution have an opinion on this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... The prosecution has no meaningful objections at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-w-what!? What's that supposed to mean!? Oh, so you all think I did it? Is that it!? Edgey-boy! Don't just sit there, do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's my move? Maybe now's my chance to take this the whole way?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess this does kind of make it look like she's the killer. Funny, I feel bad for her all of a sudden.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It's true that the witness could conceivably have committed this crime. Yet we must not forget that the victim was an action hero. As formidable as her personality may be, I doubt she'd be strong enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh! If he removes her from consideration, that means Mr. Powers is it! Sorry, windbag... but I don't have a choice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The very same reasoning that makes Mr. Powers a suspect in this case... can be used to cast doubt on Ms. Oldbag's actions on that day!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">B-but why would I do something so horrible to poor Hammer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You forget that Mr. Powers lacks a clear motive, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That did it. Now windbag is one of the suspects. No hard feelings... I hope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Wait just a minute! What about the other person who went to the studio!? The boy! The one whose photo I erased!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's only a grade schooler though, as you said. 2nd or 3rd grade, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Th-that doesn't matter! When I was that age, I could pin my old man in 10 seconds, tops!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your thoughts, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That boy is not the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!? How can you be so sure! Oh, or is it be nice to the kids and mean to your elders day? Whippersnapper!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">P-proof!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed? Then let's see this proof, Mr. Wright. You have proof that shows the boy could not have committed this murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scene of the murder, as we all know, was Studio One. However, you need a cardkey to enter Studio One! How could a boy with no formal relation to the studios have a cardkey!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The murder weapon was the Samurai Spear. That very spear is shown here in this photo. How could the boy have taken the spear? It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I can't see how that has anything to do with this matter, Mr. Wright? Mr. Wright. There aren't that many pieces of evidence in the Court Record. Please try not to pick the wrong ones!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sorry, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll ask again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! Well, would the witness care to comment on this?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Mrph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The windbag... speechless. This has got to be a first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! This court will suspend proceedings on the current trial for today. Mr. Edgeworth, please find out more about your witness, Ms. Windy... what was her name?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something "Oldbag," Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then the prosecution will look further into this Oldbag before we continue! That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">W-wait a second! I'm not going to just sit here while you run off barking up the wrong tree... me! I'm talking!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, great, stop the presses! The windbag wants to talk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Oldbag! What is this all about? Have you omitted something from your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Actually, if you must know, there's something I was told not to talk about.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-not to talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By whom!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? You mean it wasn't Edgeworth who told her not to talk...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-well, testify!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Global Studios wanted me to keep quiet about something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Oldbag! This is crucial information! Why did you keep this from the court until now!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Ain't you been listening? They told me to shut my trap, and I always do what I'm told.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, this isn't a bad dream, Your Honor. Witness the power of the Oldbag...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... Your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Global Studios wanted me to keep quiet about something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you were told not to talk?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That's right! By the studio and TV bigwigs, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't I hear about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Don't be too hard on yourself, sonny. We were all in on it.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">There were... some other people at the studios on the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-who were these people!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, the director and the producer, for starters...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... director?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should have known something was fishy! How could they have done a run-through of their action scene without a director? Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, well, I was surprised no one asked about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, where were these people?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The director was in the Employee Area all morning for the run-through. He joined the producer around lunchtime and they had a meeting after that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, in the Studio Two trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Studio Two...!? <thought>There was a Studio Two...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, if you look at the guidemap... Here it is. You go through the gate and all the way to the left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The path where the monkey's head was fallen over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright... Would you like to continue the cross-examination...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I've already asked all my questions, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">They said they had "nothing to do with it," see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Oldbag! This is a trial for murder!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I know that, silly! Still, they were pretty convincing about having nothing to do with it. And... they gave me a little bonus on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So, you got your "bonus" and you still talked... Hmm. I think I've asked all the questions I have to ask...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there's no harm in getting as much info as I can!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">So they told me to just pretend they "hadn't been at the studios that day."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So they were actually in the studio!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, the whole day. When they heard about the murder, they beat it before the cops came.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*grumble* <thought>I'll kill this woman, I swear it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel sorry for Edgeworth, almost. She really left him hanging on this one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But if you're going to go accusing me, I'm not letting them get away scot free!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Them"...? W-who were these people!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, the director and the producer, for starters...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The... director?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We should have known something was fishy! How could they have done a run-through of their action scene without a director? Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes, well, I was surprised no one asked about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, where were these people?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The director was in the Employee Area all morning for the run-through. He joined the producer around lunchtime and they had a meeting after that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Where!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, in the Studio Two trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Studio Two...!? <thought>There was a Studio Two...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Well, if you look at the guidemap... Here it is. You go through the gate and all the way to the left.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The path where the monkey's head was fallen over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright... Would you like to continue the cross-examination...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I've already asked all my questions, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I guess pressing her was the right thing to do! For an old windbag, she sure likes keeping secrets... Let's get as much information as we can!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. We have learned there were others at Global Studios on the day in question. The director and the producer and, er, some bigwigs, were all present. Yet, as we stand here, they have not been questioned! I hold that it is impossible to declare a verdict on the defendant, Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The court acknowledges the defense's point. The prosecution will gather more information about the witness, Ms. Oldbag... and more information about these other people we have just been told of!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I understand, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This ends the day's proceedings in the trial of Mr. Will Powers. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Will">Th-thank you so much, Mr. Wright. I was right to ask you to defend me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, really, it's nothing. *grin* Oh, or should I... *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll be going down to the studios to do some more investigation. We have to find out more about this director and producer. They'll be turning up in the next trial as witnesses for certain. So now's my chance to get material for the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, Nick... Have we figured out just who it was in that Steel Samurai costume? Could it really have been old windbag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think, Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Will">I don't think it was her, really.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Neither do I, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yeah, I know! Look, I was just buying time back there. Someone had to be the bad guy for a bit to take the pressure off Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor old windbag... I feel kinda sorry for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, she wasn't winning any points in there, with or without my accusation. Okay, let's get down to the studios.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! We'll be back to visit you soon...</line>
<line speaker="Will">Th-thanks. Thanks, guys. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court see no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for mis-interpretation of the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>W-what!? I see plenty of room! Its still wide open... no?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court find the defendant, Mr. Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>