<xml>
<title>Turnabout Succession</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was how we first met. ...Seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew, OK. It's been a long time since I've felt like such a rookie. Got to try and relax.</thought> Ah, good morning, Mr. Enigmar.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">I'm... sorry to have sprung this on you so suddenly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I received the files from your previous attorney only yesterday. Honestly, I'm not entirely sure I'm prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">...I understand I am asking the impossible of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well, you haven't really told me what happened yet! All we did... was play cards.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">And that was enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, it wasn't. Trust me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ooh! Morning, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ah, I'm so glad you came.</line>
<line speaker="???">You OK, Daddy? They picking on you?</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. I am fine, as always. This old boy is here to help me, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's "young man" to you.</thought> Good morning. That's a cute outfit you have on.</line>
<line speaker="???">Thanks! My first show's today, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sure it is! <thought>What the heck is she talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Oh... Old boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Me? <thought>Look what he's started.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Um, uh... Here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="???">I dunno! I just got it over there in the hall. They told me to give it to the "old boy in the blue suit with the spiky hair". They said it was really important!</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">...What's this? A memo for you or some such?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Not from the looks of it. <thought>What is this? Looks like a page from someone's diary.</thought> I'll give it a read later.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Well, how do you feel about the trial today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll get through it. Somehow. Incidentally... the prosecutor today is a new guy, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ah... An easy win, then, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're calling him a "true thoroughbred in the history of the prosecutor's office". ...Of course, there's one of those every year.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">...The switching of attorneys just before the trial... ...I know it is a difficult situation I put you in. But... allow me to say one thing, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">They will not be able to pronounce me guilty today. So, do your best, but do not worry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First time a defendant's ever given me a pep speech...</thought> I'll do what I can.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. I see you do not understand. You see, it will be impossible for them to declare a verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Impossible?</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">Yes. Isn't that right, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yup! You bet, Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My first look at the case was only yesterday. And the information I was given was a tad bit lacking, to be honest. Still, I'll do what I can. ...For their sake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">I believe the curtains will be lifting any time now. I am in your capable hands, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My client is Shadi Enigmar. Known to the world as Zak Gramarye. A wildly popular magician, star of Troupe Gramarye. His mentor, Magnifi Gramarye, was a rare breed of magician. He single-handedly ushered in a golden age of stage magic... until he was shot dead. And Zak Gramarye is the suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Each attorney's badge has a number engraved on the back. No two numbers are the same. So if you drop it, people will know it was you. Better make sure I don't lose mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Shadi Enigmar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="???">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the prosecution ready?</line>
<line speaker="???">I was just thinking, is this what all the fuss is about? Bit of a buzz-kill, really.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Buzz-kill"...? Is this some new kind of crime?</line>
<line speaker="???">One of the worst. This is a trial, ja? Where are the sweaty palms? The pounding hearts? A Gavinners concert's got ten times the thrill this gig's got.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who... were you, again?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Klavier. Klavier Gavin. I came... to get the party started. Legally, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Gavin? Defense Attorney Kristoph Gavin's...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, figures my bro's more famous in this part of town.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Klavier Gavin... Lead singer for the megahit band, the Gavinners. You're out of your league, rock-boy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I know what you're thinking: "You're out of your league, rock-boy."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">True, my debut single, "13 Years Hard Time for Love", went platinum overnight... ...but that's just a hobby to me compared to this, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Talkative, aren't you? I like your affected Euro-rock accent, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm just getting warmed up, Herr Attorney Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you would be so kind as to fill us in on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Achtung, baby. Time to call on the opening act. ...What was his name again? Ah yes... Detective Gumshoe! Hit it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And you are?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you were the one who called me up here... sir. Name's Dick Gumshoe. I'm a homicide detective down at the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe... Long time no see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Today's the day, pal. Today, I win, and you lose! I got confidence in my testimony today, see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What, you normally lack confidence in your testimony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Detective, this is my stage. Can the antics.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All this "hey you"-ing and such. And I could care less about your history together.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well, Detective Gumshoe, if you would. Please tell us about the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It happened six days back, in a room at the General Hospital! The facts are as simple as they come. Here's the crime scene. The victim was a patient, asleep in a hospital bed. The killer comes in, puts a pistol to his forehead, and bam. Lights out. ...Them's the facts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Not so long ago, the victim, Magnifi Gramarye was a famous man. He had the entire country under his "magical spell", as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah yes, the great magician. He retired years ago, though. Say the name "Magnifi" to one of my generation... and you'd be lucky to get a blank stare.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, though I'm sure the youngsters today know his disciples even better. I daresay Troupe Gramarye has made quite a name for themselves.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyhow, the retired Magnifi's been in the hospital for the last year. Hmm, what was it? A mall-ignorant tutor or something. Doing something to his liver, I think. Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "malignant tumor", perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In other words, he had liver cancer. He had only three months left to live, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The facts do seem simple enough. But... something's not right.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The victim was already climbing a three-month stairway to heaven. ...Why not wait for him to knock-knock-knock on heaven's door? Why shoot him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't have put it quite so lyrically, but it's true. Why make the effort to commit murder when the victim was about to die?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Incidentally, the victim had a serious case of diabetes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Diabetes?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In fact, he was about to "shoot up" with insulin... ...when he was shot with a pistol. The syringe was found at the crime scene. Chronic diabetes... and cancer. As much as it pains me to say it... ...the victim was clearly at the end of his life.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I always hated getting shots. I guess Magnifi was giving himself the insulin shots... There's no way I could do that... *shudder* ...! Wait! If Magnifi used this to inject his insulin... ...why are there no traces of it having been used? Hmm... Something to keep in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe the question before us is clear, then. Why did the killer have to shoot this dying man? What reason could he have had?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Very well, Detective. Perhaps you can enlighten us as to the circumstances of the shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually... the victim kind of ordered the defendant to do him in.A few days before it happened, the victim sent a letter "ordering" his own murder.The defendant did what was asked of him, and shot the old man in the forehead!The bullet was fired from the pistol found at the scene, no doubt about it.And the pistol definitely belonged to the old man, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaat!? You're saying the victim ordered his own shooting?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Those are the facts. I have here the letter in question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very unusual, indeed! Although, could such a thing as a letter really cause one to pull a trigger, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe the answer to that question can be found at the end of the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... "You cannot refuse, and we both know the reason why." Detective Gumshoe, can you explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Unfortunately, even the defendant won't say a peep about that bit, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One thing bothers me about this. Why didn't he just say "11"? Why have him come at "11:05" without some specific reason...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The devil is in the details, Herr Attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Was there some reason?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As it turns out, there was. Every night, for a half hour, starting at 11:00... ...the victim, Magnifi Gramarye, was given an IV.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An IV...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There it is in the picture, off to the side of the bed.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">At 11:00, a doctor would come to set up the IV. Thirty minutes later, he would come back for the empty bag. This happened every night, without fail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that was the only time they could meet without the chance of an untimely interruption. ...During his IV.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, shall we begin? ...Mr. Wright, your cross-examination, if you would!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this "reason he couldn't refuse", I wonder? He could have at least mentioned it to me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually... the victim kind of ordered the defendant to do him in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just because he got the letter doesn't mean he went through with it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? I disagree. The victim was, indeed, shot in the forehead, after all. Just as he had commanded.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It could be a set-up. But let's not be in such a hurry. Maybe we should let the witness talk for a change.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Thanks, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Fine. I can play it slow as well as I can play it fast. On with the testimony, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A few days before it happened, the victim sent a letter "ordering" his own murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And this letter was sent by the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There it is! Gotcha! You're all mine this time, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I had the handwriting checked out, of course. It's the victim's, no mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ha ha ha ha ha! Score one for the boys!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't "lose". I was just ascertaining the facts. ...So why am I so annoyed?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... a letter ordering your own death? Things aren't what they used to be, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure this is exactly "commonplace", even now, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...So anyway, guess I'll keep going while I'm ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The defendant did what was asked of him, and shot the old man in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...How can you be so sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you gotta learn to stop relying on people to do your thinking for you, pal. Learn to think for yourself! Get that noggin cranking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You fail to grasp the concept of "questioning", detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">First, we got this letter. It says "shoot... in the forehead" loud and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see that. But I still wouldn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, maybe you need to grow yourself a backbone, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You fail to grasp the concept of "shooting people is bad", detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We also found the defendant's pistol at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Traces of gunpowder residue shows that it had been fired recently.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, Mr. Wright? As far as I can tell from looking at this photo... ...there seems to be no issue with the prosecution's claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The photo... Maybe there's something in there I can use. So they're saying the defendant "shot the victim in the forehead"? I think there's a hole in the prosecution's argument! Clearly, Mr. Enigmar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, nothing in this picture suggests he didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, I see. That is unfortunate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, let's pay it no mind and carry on, shall we? I like a fast tempo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, I still got stuff to talk about, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Everyone's so eager to move on. So of course, I want to slow down. ...Is there really not a single clue in this picture?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Back to the testimony, if you would, detective.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">People don't normally commit murder just because their teacher told them to. Which means the defendant didn't fire that pistol!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...This is your position, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is the sort of occasion when my brother would present some "evidence".</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did you have some evidence you wanted to show us? Something proving it wasn't the defendant who shot the old man?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... ......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Penalty for excessive perspiration, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But it's a cold sweat, Your Honor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looking at this photo, another possibility occurs to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does the letter tell us? That the defendant had a "reason he couldn't refuse" his teacher's wishes.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Bingo, pal! That's why the defendant popped him one in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? The defense disagrees. You see, the defendant had another choice he could make.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What, and you can prove that with this photo!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I can prove he had a choice, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"The defendant might have fired, like he was ordered. But he didn't shoot the victim's forehead." Well, let's hear what you're thinking, Mr. Wright. If he didn't shoot the victim's forehead, what did the defendant shoot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... I see! Which is to say... ...I have no idea what you're talking about. Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defendant had a choice other than shooting the victim in the forehead? ...Perhaps I might suggest one. He could have shot this attorney in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... I see. Which is to say... ...I still don't see. Still, when in doubt, give a penalty, I always say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. Time to think this one through again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The clown doll...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a closer look. See? It's been shot in the forehead, too.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...! There's a hole in its forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and a hole in the prosecution's claim!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hah! And I suppose you have a reason as to why he'd shoot the clown doll?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't just shoot the doll. He shot the doll's forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">His "forehead"...? Aah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's read the "orders" once more, shall we? "...You will shoot, one shot, square in the forehead." ...Which is exactly what he did. He shot the clown doll square in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense has raised an intriguing possibility. That hole in the clown's forehead... It definitely looks like it was shot! Bailiff! Send someone to investigate this matter!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I admit, I'm impressed. But I expected nothing less. Still, this doesn't mean he didn't shoot the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Perhaps he did have to shoot a forehead, as ordered. But the letter says nothing about whose forehead... This was the only way he had to follow his orders without taking a life!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. The bullet hole in the clown doll's forehead does demand an explanation. It might very well be a clue. Yet Prosecutor Gavin is right. It alone does not prove the defendant's innocence. You cannot say for sure the defendant didn't shoot the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So sorry, Mr. Wright. How sad it is to see the mighty fall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...How sad it is to see the novice's overconfidence. He doesn't realize just how big this little "hole" is going to get.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Detective Gumshoe. Please take this new-found fact into account as you continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... it might have been the clown's forehead he shot.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, so he practiced first on the doll, then shot him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He "practiced" in the middle of the hospital? Anyone could have come in at any moment!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but no one did come, did they, pal? Besides, it's what I woulda done. "Always look before you shoot," I say.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Might I suggest we move on? This is getting us nowhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Patience. We'll get there sooner than you think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please continue with your testimony, detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The bullet was fired from the pistol found at the scene, no doubt about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean this pistol, the one in the crime scene photo?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...That's the one! It's a funny-looking gun so there's no mistaking it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We compared the bullet taken from the victim's skull with a bullet fired from this gun. The rifling marks on the bullets were a perfect match.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you verified the murder weapon, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet we did!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The court would like to see the pistol in question.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, sir! Here she is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well. This truly is a "blast" from the past.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a stage pistol for magic shows, see. But it can fire real bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It looks so much bigger in real life than on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but it can only hold one round. ...By the way, the pistol's firing chamber is empty. ...And it shows traces of having been fired recently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... were any fingerprints found on the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Unfortunately, no. Of course, the defendant is known for wearing gloves. We might say that a lack of fingerprints is, in fact, a "fingerprint" of its own.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! Intriguing point, well made!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa whoa whoa! Not well made! Not intriguing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, the court accepts this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...My grandchild would get a kick out of seeing this. ...But now it's time to return to our testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And the pistol definitely belonged to the old man, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Why are you so certain?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What pile of sand has your head been stuck in all this time, pal? You never heard of "Zak &amp; Valant's Quick-Draw Shootem"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">One of the defendant's specialties. Zak and Valant stand on either side of a girl! Then, they shoot! But the bullets don't hit her! Instead, they hit everything else on stage!!! This was one of the pistols they used in their show. Got a great design, huh? The kids love it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Many boys and girls joined the police because of that pistol, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You know, that would explain a lot about the police force.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Troupe Gramarye stopped doing that act a while ago. The old man held on to that pistol ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The court would like to see the pistol in question.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, sir! Here she is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well. This truly is a "blast" from the past.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's a stage pistol for magic shows, see. But it can fire real bullets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. It looks so much bigger in real life than on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but it can only hold one round. ...By the way, the pistol's firing chamber is empty. ...And it shows traces of having been fired recently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... were any fingerprints found on the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Unfortunately, no. Of course, the defendant is known for wearing gloves. We might say that a lack of fingerprints is, in fact, a "fingerprint" of its own.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha! Intriguing point, well made!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa whoa whoa! Not well made! Not intriguing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, the court accepts this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...My grandchild would get a kick out of seeing this. ...But now it's time to return to our testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So what if he shot the clown? He still shot the victim, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So let me get this straight. You're saying my client first shot the clown, then shot the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Not a bad summary, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>More of a confirmation than a summary, but whatever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That was really more of a confirmation than a summary. But our defense attorney seems pleased enough with himself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do these people ever miss a chance to mock me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, now that Mr. Wright's gotten that out of his system... ...shall we continue with the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I didn't have time to gather all the details before coming in here. This testimony might be my only source of information. Better pay attention... and read this letter carefully.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you look closely, you can see how the pistol's made to bend here. It's a one-shot model, and I guess this bend is where you load it. So... this is the famous Gramarye Golden Sun. They say kids used to love pretending they had one of those. I wonder if they pretended to miss their targets, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trickiest cases often seem the simplest. Prosecutor Gavin, you missed the bullet hole in the clown's forehead. If you hadn't missed that, you might have come to a very different conclusion. ...Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah, but like I just said, pal... ...after he shot the clown in the forehead, he went and...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Did nothing of the sort to the victim. The pistol proves he could not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The murder weapon? How?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite simple, Your Honor. This pistol only holds one bullet at a time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he had shot the clown in the forehead... ...he couldn't have shot the victim, too!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeeeeeeeeeeargh!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Th-That's not a contradiction. Not even close! All he had to do was reload the pistol after the first shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Where did he get the extra bullet? They're not so easy to come by, you know. If you claim the defendant "had one ready"... ...then prove to us how he got it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Urk...! ...... Heh... Ha ha ha... I had a feeling this wasn't over yet. No... this party's just getting started. And I haven't proven anything yet, beyond my good looks, and startling record sales.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And utter lack of humility.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ah... what's this? It seems that the prosecution has another witness prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Like I said, Herr Detective was just the warm-up act.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Ugh.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now that the audience has gotten a taste of what's to come, they're ready.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ready for what?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For my decisive witness, of course. A witness who, you will find, can prove one thing for us: That it was Zak Gramarye who shot the victim in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. We will pause for a 15-minute recess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This might be my lucky break... I'll need that 15 minutes to talk to my client... Zak.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Very impressive, Mr. Wright. I have to say, I expected nothing less.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...We've only just begun. I was hoping you could tell me a bit more about what happened, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I did not think you would believe me if I told you. Better that you discovered the truth for yourself. I was thinking of you, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we need less thinking and more talking! That night in the hospital... What really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, the way your eyes gleam, Mr. Wright... ...you'll scare Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Speaking of which, where is she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">You have seen the problem yourself: the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "one shot in the forehead" one, right?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes, and the reason he speaks of. I could not deny my mentor's wishes... even if it meant my own death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">This is something I will not say... for now, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's this "for now" business?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">I have done many things in my life, some well, some poorly. But this is a cross we must bear alone to our graves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."We"?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">You wanted to know about the night of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finally... This guy sure likes to take his time getting to the important stuff.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Of course, I had no intention of shooting my mentor. I snuck into his room that night at the appointed time. And found there upon his bedside table two pistols.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..."Two"?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes. The one I had used on stage... ...and the one that had been used by my partner, Valant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, for the "Zak &amp; Valant's Quick-Draw" thing?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">My mentor... had the look of one sleeping. I stood by his bedside, hearing only the light sound of his breathing. ...Then I took the pistol into my hand. I cannot deny that my resolve faltered then, for a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "faltered"...? You mean you thought about shooting him?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Recall there was a reason I could not refuse his request. His last such request... though not his first.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... there were other requests you "couldn't refuse" before?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">To be honest, I've not always been steadfast... and I fear I've brought pain upon Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Was Magnifi coercing his disciples somehow? Just what was going on in Troupe Gramarye...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yet... in the end, I did not shoot him. Instead, I turned and shot the clown! I took the pistol I had fired and placed it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In your pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I believe if you examine the bullet in the clown's head... ...you will find it to be different than the one in my mentor. The... What were those called?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Rifling marks".</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes. Well, that is all I have to tell you... concerning the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Concerning the case"...? You mean, there's something else you can tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Heh... Ha ha ha! You are a fascinating man, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Thanks?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Yes... there is something. My mentor... his eyes opened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!? Magnifi Gramarye...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">The old devil. He was not asleep, you see. ...Of course, the gunshot would have woken him anyway. And there we had our last discussion as mentor and pupil. It was not a long discussion. Maybe five, ten minutes or so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you talk about...?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ha ha. Mr. Wright. ...Did I not just tell you? It does not concern this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Zak Gramarye... He seems pretty steadfast to me... or maybe just stubborn.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Mr. Wright! Your presence is requested in the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Once again, I am in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right. Let's get back in there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">During our recess, a bullet was found in and dug out from the clown's head.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! This is news! And the rifling marks...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There wasn't time to do a detailed analysis. Though they did find the weapon type matches the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, that's not very conclusive, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is why I'm about to call my very decisive witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your "decisive witness"? How many times have I heard those words... ...though they often turn out to be far less decisive than you think.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Oh, don't worry on my account. I'm quite confident this witness will do the job. After all, he is intimately acquainted with the players in our little production... ...being the other half of Troupe Gramarye's famous duo... "Zak &amp; Valant"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Valant Gramarye... So, we get to meet the Great Magnifi's other disciple!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps we'll start by asking your name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Valant Gramarye... Magician.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Er, and you're the "decisive witness", are you? You can prove your fellow student... your partner's guilt?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">"Fate"... the grand illusion, filled with traps and tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait! The shooting took place in that hospital after 11 o'clock at night! If you're a "witness", does that mean you were there that late?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">If one were to deduce this logically, the conclusion is... yes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... OK. <thought>I always get the characters, don't I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I have an interesting fact for you. You see, several days before the crime... ...my witness received this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That... looks very familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait... That's the same letter Zak Gramarye received!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yes. Or perhaps I should say "ta da"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! And what does it say? Surely not the same thing!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you should see for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, it's practically the same! The court accepts this into evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most unusual... Exactly what was going on with you folks? What exactly was your "Troupe Gramarye" up to?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...By which you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm just having trouble envisioning a man who would ask his students to kill him. Both of them, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's just my opinion, Herr Judge. But from these letters, I'd say he was coercing them, not asking them.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">We walked the magician's path together, and in so doing, shared much of our lives. When people are so close, there is strain... a warping of relations, you might say. ...Yet this has nothing to do with the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>By which you mean you're not going to tell us. ...Which makes me wonder even more about this "reason they couldn't refuse".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, let's get on with the testimony for starters. The defendant, Zak Gramarye stands accused. Tell us why.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Oh, I'll do more than that. "For where he walks, the red roses rise singing hymns to the miracle that is magic!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fascinating. Though, I hardly need to remind you... ...that the evidence could just as clearly point to you as the suspect. The letter, the murder weapon... ...and now, the two bullets found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In fact, the only difference seems to be the designated time...</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! As every magician knows... timing is everything.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes... And now it's time to get this party fired up! </line>
<line speaker="Valant">That night, I visited the hospital room at the time Magnifi requested.The smell of gunpowder hung in the room... and my mentor had taken his final bow.I did not imagine my fellow student might have received the same instructions!Yet a deal with the dead is still a deal. Death's sweet kiss... I gave to the clown.Then I informed the doctor and the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you were the one who reported the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed. I would think... ...this fact alone would clear my name of suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not jump to any conclusions!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, the cross-examination generally comes before the conclusions in this court. But, if your testimony proves to be true... ...then the defendant, Zak Gramarye, is guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And if it wasn't Zak Gramarye, then the killer was you, Valant! And no disappearing act will get you out of that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">That night, I visited the hospital room at the time Magnifi requested.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Which, according to the letter, was 11:20 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Indeed. In magic, timing is everything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Consider, the illusion of teleportation. If I were to appear on stage before my stunt double has left, how would that look? Why, it would reveal the very secrets of my magic!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now that you've revealed the very secrets of your magic for all of us, let's move on. You went at the designated time... and what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The smell of gunpowder hung in the room... and my mentor had taken his final bow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you weren't worried for your own safety at all? I mean, you smelled gunpowder, yes? What if the shooter was still nearby?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I... I did not consider this, to be honest. It is forbidden for a magician to have a good imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Uh, really? <thought>Isn't magic all about illusions and imagination?</thought> How about this: you were the shooter, which is why you weren't afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">N-Now you are the one imagining! It is forbidden for a lawyer to have a good imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will refrain from pausing so suspiciously before responding. ...My forbidden imagination is starting to imagine things.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I did not imagine my fellow student might have received the same instructions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Which brings us back to this "reason" neither of you could refuse.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">So it does. And my partner, he did not refuse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Magnifi wrote the same thing to you. Why could you "refuse" if Zak couldn't?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Because I have a will of steel! Of course... ...I also do this trick where I bend steel bars. So perhaps steel isn't all so strong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So which is it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Mind if I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Yet a deal with the dead is still a deal. Death's sweet kiss... I gave to the clown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were two bullet holes at the scene: one in the victim, and one in the clown. You're saying the one who shot the clown... was you?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">No doubt my partner Zak has said much the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, because whoever didn't shoot the clown committed murder. I'd better dig around here a bit more... and see what I turn up.</thought> Mr. Valant... Let me ask about something else concerning the crime scene, namely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to shoot a pistol, you need a bullet. Where was the bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I entered the room, and took the pistol in my hand. The bullet was already loaded, ready to fire at any time. A magician is always prepared, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prepared for...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">One never knows when a miracle will be called for. A magician always has seven doves in his pocket, and a white rabbit up each sleeve!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Clearly, we're dealing with professionals here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is this bullet that was loaded in the pistol really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a loaded bullet, we wouldn't have a murder. It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where exactly was the pistol when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Atop a small bedside table, it was. As if to say, "Here I am, take me into your hand, pull my trigger. Shoot him."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim clearly wanted to be shot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... why?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps he wanted to go out... with a bang? ...Yet we will never hear the truth from his lips, so all we can do... is guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the location of the pistol all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a murder weapon, there would be no murder! It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How many pistols were there when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...By which you mean what, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two pistols were used in the "Zak &amp; Valant Quick-Draw Shootem", correct? One for each of you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You are well informed, yet... ...only one of my "old friends" sat in the hospital room that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did Zak tell me back in the lobby...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Of course, I had no intention of shooting my mentor. I snuck into his room that night at the appointed time. And found there upon his bedside table two pistols. I took the pistol I had fired and placed it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no problem with that statement. Only one pistol is visible in the photograph of the crime scene, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... So you picked up that pistol and fired it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed I did. Allakazam... Allakazing... Allakaboom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the number of pistols really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The number of pistols is quite important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">The pistol was already loaded. I merely had to pull the trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the pistol was already loaded, something doesn't make sense. Why weren't the victim's fingerprints on it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You should know that we of the Troupe Gramarye are capable of many things. One of these being the levitation of iron balls... without touching them.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There's no magic involved here. The shooter was just methodical, is all. He simply wiped everything of fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Can't really do much with fingerprints that weren't there. Maybe I should ask about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where exactly was the pistol when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Atop a small bedside table, it was. As if to say, "Here I am, take me into your hand, pull my trigger. Shoot him."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim clearly wanted to be shot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... why?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps he wanted to go out... with a bang? ...Yet we will never hear the truth from his lips, so all we can do... is guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the location of the pistol all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a murder weapon, there would be no murder! It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How many pistols were there when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...By which you mean what, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two pistols were used in the "Zak &amp; Valant Quick-Draw Shootem", correct? One for each of you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You are well informed, yet... ...only one of my "old friends" sat in the hospital room that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did Zak tell me back in the lobby...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Of course, I had no intention of shooting my mentor. I snuck into his room that night at the appointed time. And found there upon his bedside table two pistols. I took the pistol I had fired and placed it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no problem with that statement. Only one pistol is visible in the photograph of the crime scene, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... So you picked up that pistol and fired it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed I did. Allakazam... Allakazing... Allakaboom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the number of pistols really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The number of pistols is quite important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...On second thought, let's run with this testimony for a while longer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I took up the pistol from the small table and shot the clown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you do that? I would think calling the police would come first.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Then you know nothing of the relationship between a master and his disciple! If your master says die, you die. Do you understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you're going to die?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Certainly not! ...It was but an example! In any case, I wanted to fulfill my obligation. A final courtesy to a great mentor, perhaps. Or, perhaps not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Perhaps I'm totally confused. Maybe I should ask about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to shoot a pistol, you need a bullet. Where was the bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I entered the room, and took the pistol in my hand. The bullet was already loaded, ready to fire at any time. A magician is always prepared, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prepared for...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">One never knows when a miracle will be called for. A magician always has seven doves in his pocket, and a white rabbit up each sleeve!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Clearly, we're dealing with professionals here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is this bullet that was loaded in the pistol really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a loaded bullet, we wouldn't have a murder. It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How many pistols were there when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...By which you mean what, precisely?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Two pistols were used in the "Zak &amp; Valant Quick-Draw Shootem", correct? One for each of you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">You are well informed, yet... ...only one of my "old friends" sat in the hospital room that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did Zak tell me back in the lobby...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Zak">Of course, I had no intention of shooting my mentor. I snuck into his room that night at the appointed time. And found there upon his bedside table two pistols. I took the pistol I had fired and placed it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no problem with that statement. Only one pistol is visible in the photograph of the crime scene, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... So you picked up that pistol and fired it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed I did. Allakazam... Allakazing... Allakaboom.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the number of pistols really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The number of pistols is quite important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...On second thought, let's run with this testimony for a while longer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Only one pistol was in the hospital room that night. With it, I shot the clown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you took the only pistol there, and fired it?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that pistol was this one, which was left at the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Good show! I see you, too, are a magician of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And you're an idiot of sorts... Do you have any idea what you just said...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see the fire in your eyes as you glare at the witness. So how about heating up this trial a bit? These slow ballads bore me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I've got a hunch, but maybe that's all it is. Maybe I should ask about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In order to shoot a pistol, you need a bullet. Where was the bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I entered the room, and took the pistol in my hand. The bullet was already loaded, ready to fire at any time. A magician is always prepared, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prepared for...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">One never knows when a miracle will be called for. A magician always has seven doves in his pocket, and a white rabbit up each sleeve!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Clearly, we're dealing with professionals here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is this bullet that was loaded in the pistol really so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a loaded bullet, we wouldn't have a murder. It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where exactly was the pistol when you entered the room?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Atop a small bedside table, it was. As if to say, "Here I am, take me into your hand, pull my trigger. Shoot him."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim clearly wanted to be shot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... why?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps he wanted to go out... with a bang? ...Yet we will never hear the truth from his lips, so all we can do... is guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Is the location of the pistol all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Without a murder weapon, there would be no murder! It's very important, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please add this detail to your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Actually, let me ask about something else.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness may continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What can I do, but obey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...On second thought, let's run with this testimony for a while longer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Valant">Then I informed the doctor and the police.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you informed the police... What did you do then?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What do you suppose I did? Used my magic to levitate my mentor's corpse, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know, that's why I'm asking. Now please answer the question and skip the sarcasm.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">After I made my report, I called the doctor, and we returned to the room. While we waited for the police to arrive, we discussed... stomach medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We've confirmed this with the doctor. It all checks out. He praised Mr. Valant's knowledge of stomach medicine, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Ah, it is an honor I do not deserve. But, I accept.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Both of Magnifi's students received the same letter. Both admit to having gone to the hospital that night. Two bullets were fired... and one of them killed Magnifi! Time to find the cracks in his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the defendant, Zak Gramarye, when he entered the room... ...there were two pistols on that table.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Two...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One of those pistols he used to shoot the clown in the forehead. Then he left with it in his pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course, this is what he would say. Unlike the hapless clown, we must assume our defendant has some brains in his head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, what about what Mr. Valant has told us? You see, there's something about his testimony that doesn't make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...What might that be? I told you, I took the pistol that was there, and shot the clown...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's your story, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the rifling marks tell a very different story, Mr. Valant. Recall what Prosecutor Gavin told us!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We compared the bullet taken from the victim's skull with a bullet fired from this gun. The rifling marks on the bullets were a perfect match.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Valant, if you fired this pistol... ...then YOU shot the victim in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Well, this is all rather sudden...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Heh heh heh heh... What have I done?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I owe the court an apology. ...Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry for what!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You see, I was unaware that two of these unique pistols were crafted. The analysis of the rifling marks only proved the type of gun that fired them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... But that's not what you told us before! You said you'd verified the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is why I'm apologizing to you now. Quite sincerely, I might add. ...Would you hold me accountable for a mistake made in my youth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was just this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I am still young. And, I might add, it wasn't really my fault. If the defendant had only admitted he took one pistol from the scene of the crime... ...we would not be having this pleasant discussion now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Valant Gramarye?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were presented to this court as a "decisive witness". But you've proven to be more "divisive" than "decisive".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You'll see, in time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The testimony so far has merely been a review of the "facts". The proof... comes next.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Care to elaborate, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">When Mr. Valant entered the hospital room, the victim had already been shot. As his next testimony will prove! Herr Wright, the real fight is about to begin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Bring it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will now testify to the court. Help us determine who shot what!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">I arrived in the hospital room at the appointed time, which is to say 11:20 PM.After discovering the body, I fulfilled my obligation... then called in the doctor.The doctor examined the body before the police arrived...He was quite clear about the time of death: 11:10 PM.And the one in the room at the time was my partner... not me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Those times are rather close, you have to admit. You're talking about an alibi established over a matter of minutes. To use a 10-minute discrepancy as the basis of your alibi...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Is easy to explain in this situation, Herr Judge. For example... ...take our debut hit single, "13 Years Hard Time For Love". Cue to the song, press the play button, and it will play for 2 minutes, 15 seconds. Do it a hundred times, the result is the same.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Their debut single was only 2 minutes and 15 seconds long? What a rip-off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Magic is a world of utmost precision! Hocus pocus... requires admirable focus. And in the time of death determined by the doctor there is an incontrovertible truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The prosecution warns us that we're dealing with rather precise times. And we can expect the cross-examination to require the same level of precision.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I would hope the defense refrains from its customarily broad, sweeping accusations. ...Lest we blur the focus this case so clearly demands.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Point taken. Baseless remarks will result in a penalty. Carry on, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Carry on... Right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">I arrived in the hospital room at the appointed time, which is to say 11:20 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">11:20 PM... Can you prove that's when you arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Alas, such a feat may be beyond even the Great Valant. For there was no one in that room but Magnifi, and he was departed, after a fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I have here defendant Zak Gramarye's sworn deposition. "I snuck into his room that night at the appointed time. It was 10 minutes before I left the room... and the victim was still alive."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The time indicated by this letter to Zak was 11:05 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Exactly. Which means the witness could not have entered that room before 11:15! ...Because his partner was still in the middle of his crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see someone did their arithmetic homework.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You see, the defendant himself has corroborated the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Does that all make sense?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any problem with that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If you say so. Let's continue, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The only problem I see here is the glaring contradiction in that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Was that a question?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... I guess it was?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You have been warned, Herr Wright. ...Baseless remarks will be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well put, Prosecutor Gavin! Oh, and Mr. Wright? Here's my answer to your question!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">After discovering the body, I fulfilled my obligation... then called in the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You walk in on a murder, and the first thing you do is shoot the clown?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...The disciple does what the disciple must. My mentor's request, without reason, had caused for me a surfeit of sorrow. For what would I, Valant, be now without him? "May the soul of Magnifi the Great find greater peace above." This I muttered to myself as I pulled that lonely trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In any case, I believe this is nothing more than what we have already learned. I'm still waiting for one of those "Wright moments", Herr Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May I remind you that baseless remarks will earn penalties. Proceed with that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>What a pain this is turning out to be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">The doctor examined the body before the police arrived...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did the doctor say anything concerning the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Why yes... I believe he screamed, "My God! He's been shot in the head!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It doesn't take a doctor to notice that. I believe I would have said much the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And I would have penned the requiem that arose in my soul at that horrid sight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What ever happened to good old-fashioned investigation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In any case, I believe this is nothing more than what we have already learned. I'm still waiting for one of those "Wright moments", Herr Attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">May I remind you that baseless remarks will earn penalties. Proceed with that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>What a pain this is turning out to be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">He was quite clear about the time of death: 11:10 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think I'm stepping out on a limb to say I have some doubts about this. How could the doctor be so precise with the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We do usually only get an "estimated" time of death, true. I'm not sure I've heard of a "verified" time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Magic revels in making the complex appear simple, but reality is the opposite. What appears complex, in this case, is a simple matter of subtraction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see another person has done their arithmetic homework!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The point here... is the IV the victim was taking. It's quite visible in the photograph of the scene. Recall what we heard earlier about the victim, Magnifi Gramarye's schedule. Every night at 11:00, Magnifi took an IV drip for thirty minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can see the IV bag right there, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now, look a little closer. Follow the tube down from the bag to the end...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...! The needle's been removed!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Doubtlessly, it fell out when he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would seem to be the case!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...When the needle comes out, the IV no longer drips.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! You could just measure the remaining IV liquid...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Precisely. The IV liquid functions, for our purposes, as an hourglass of sorts. This is how the doctor determined the time of death. From the amount remaining in the bag, it was determined that... ...the IV had "stopped 10 minutes after administration began".</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...And so it was. When I, Valant, entered that room... ...10 minutes had passed since that horrible crime was committed! And this is proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Did that seem important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, seeing how it is the biggest clue we have to the time of death... ...I'd say it's very important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Agreed! It would be hard to imagine a more precise way to determine the time. Behold the power of arithmetic! Very well. The witness will add this detail to his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any problem with that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If you say so. Let's continue, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How could the doctor be so precise with the time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We do usually only get an "estimated" time of death, true. I'm not sure I've heard of a "verified" time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Magic revels in making the complex appear simple, but reality is the opposite. What appears complex, in this case, is a simple matter of subtraction.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The point here... is the IV the victim was taking. The IV liquid functions, for our purposes, as an hourglass. You see the IV needle fell out of the victim's arm the moment he was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! You could just measure the remaining IV liquid...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...This is how the doctor determined the time of death. From the amount remaining in the bag it was determined that... ...the IV had "stopped 10 minutes after administration began".</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...And so it was. When I, Valant, entered that room... ...10 minutes had passed since that horrible crime was committed! And this is proof.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. Did that seem important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, seeing how it is the biggest clue we have to the time of death... ...I'd say it's very important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Agreed! It would be hard to imagine a more precise way to determine the time. Behold the power of arithmetic! Very well. The witness will add this detail to his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any problem with that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If you say so. Let's continue, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And he knew this by the amount of IV liquid left?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed. Apparently, doctors, as well as magicians, have a few tricks up their sleeves.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The impact of the shot caused the IV needle to drop, telling us the time of death. ...The deceased's final message to this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I left this "alibi" go through... ...I'm finished. There has to be a hole in this somewhere. Heck, I'll take a pinprick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">The water of life springs not eternal... The remaining IV liquid proves my innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice the IV yourself, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">When first I entered that room, the stench of gunpowder assailed me. Next, the mark of death upon my mentor's forehead! And then, his left arm did I spy, a rose, drooping and wilted. Its thorn, the discarded IV needle.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Knocked from the vein by the force of the shot. Luckily for you. If that IV had not been there, why... you might be a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Indubitably so. I might say it's thanks to my lucky color.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your... lucky color?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Indeed. Even today I wear it proudly 'pon my suspect self. For it always, without fail, brings me luck. Why, when "Zak &amp; Valant" won their first Magician's Grand Prix... Yes! The very one held by the Association of International Magicians! I was adorned in this attire then, too! And our trophy: a bust. Ah, what a day that was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*groan* This is one trip down memory lane no one needs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Valant">My lucky color, yes indeed! And that IV, too... ...I say, I think 'twas hued especially for me, Valant!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does seem to be the case, indeed. ...Well, Mr. Wright? Any thoughts on this testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Valant sure looks happy with himself. ...OK, how about this "lucky color" testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any problem with that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If you say so. Let's continue, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It certainly sounds like your lucky color's brought you plenty of luck. But not this time. Mr. Valant... your lucky color's betrayed you.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honor! The witness's testimony just now clearly contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Whaaat!? Please recall my warning at the beginning of this cross-examination, Mr. Wright. Baseless accusations will be duly penalized! I do hope this latest accusation is well-based.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Don't worry, I've got all your bases right here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Let's hear the defense's claim. Where is your evidence that contradicts what Mr. Valant has told us?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... pity. That didn't "do it" for me, as the kids are fond of saying nowadays. Perhaps you can explain it in such a way that it would.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I don't know whether it's the sort of evidence to "do it" for anyone but...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Do" yourself a favor and stop flailing around for excuses! ...Before you "do" yourself in! ...And "do" try to straighten your spine. All that bending over is bad for your posture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've got something that should make you sit up straight.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Darn... I was so close on that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Now that we're all upstanding citizens again, back to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">And the one in the room at the time was my partner... not me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You entered that hospital room at 11:20 PM. The time given by the defendant, Zak Gramarye, was 11:05 PM. ...You didn't run into him at the hospital that night?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Hmm. This is why I never perform with amateurs, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Picture if you will the night-time hospital. Outside, only the pale light of the moon. If two dressed as we were to meet in such circumstances... ...I daresay that would ruin the mood completely!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... The mood isn't in question here.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe the witness is saying they didn't meet, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">For what is magic, if not the study of beauty? Us meeting was not only out of the question, it was an impossibility!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>For what is magic, if not the study of how to make absolutely no sense at all? That said... was there a contradiction in there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't see any problem with that testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If you say so. Let's continue, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Sometimes the most magical thing of all... is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The only problem I see here is the glaring contradiction in that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Was that a question?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... I guess it was?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You have been warned, Herr Wright. ...Baseless remarks will be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well put, Prosecutor Gavin! Oh, and Mr. Wright? Here's my answer to your question!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>An alibi over a matter of minutes. Precise is right! Hmm. And pressing with impunity will earn me a nice penalty, too. Better focus on one thing... this "time of death".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...The crime scene tells all, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The photo of the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...All this talk of color has me yearning for black and white, clear-cut simplicity. ...Tell us, Herr Wright, just where is the contradiction in this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...My pleasure. And, I assure you, it's quite simple. ...But I can't promise anything in black and white.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Let's hear what Mr. Wright has to say. What in this photo contradicts the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Contrary to Mr. Wright's promises, this seems pretty black and white to me.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Agreed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... how's that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're wrong. That black and white enough for you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Ugh. Thank you sir, may I have another... Valant's "lucky color" is the color of his clothes, right? What contradicts that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Valant Gramarye! Let's get one thing straight about your "lucky color". ...It's "yellow", yes?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Kind of takes the mystery out of it, but yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something wrong with yellow, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, there is. Decisively wrong, in fact. Take another look at the photo of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Confusion, doubt... tell us, what do your elderly eyes spy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even my elderly eyes can see a problem here, Mr. Valant. Look at that IV bag!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ack! Wh-What is this...!? What foul mag... ick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It would be hard to call the IV liquid "yellow". And I'm afraid, no magic was involved in the taking of this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Ah... Alla... Allakaz... Allakanooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! What does this mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This... This is some kind of mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Prosecutor Gavin... Your witness's mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The greener they are, the harder they fall... I suppose there's no substitute for experience.</thought> Valant Gramarye, as you reminded us several times... ...your lucky color is yellow. But the IV is clearly not.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This contradiction can mean only one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And to think... You almost had me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see your true colors now, "ace attorney" Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something you'd like to tell us, Prosecutor Gavin? As far as this court can tell, the witness's testimony does contradict the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha... Yes, a contradiction. One that I shall be pleased to hand right back to Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How? Because the witness has made no mistakes! I agree, at a glance, the IV liquid does appear a sort of greenish-yellow. But I assure you, the liquid itself is quite yellow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yellow liquid...? How can you say that? As far as I can tell from this photo, it's green...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, but what color is the IV bag itself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bag? You mean the plastic bag on the hook?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It looks like a... I want to say "light blue"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Precisely. ...Figured it out yet? Put a yellow liquid in a blue bag and...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You get green.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This, incidentally, is the liquid's true color!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see! Your explanation does have the ring of truth to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As I thought... There's no substitute for experience, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You may tell a good tale. But. You've just proven something rather grave. For you, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">G-Grave?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The liquid in the IV is yellow, yes. ...But how did this witness know that?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's quite unnatural when you think about it. You... did think about it, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ah... Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense requests an explanation from the witness! At the scene of the crime, the IV liquid appears to be green! ...So let me ask! How did the witness know the IV liquid was actually yellow!?</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Allakazooooooooooomg!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Mr. Wright! You will explain this at once! The witness clearly knew the color of the IV liquid... ...so I'm sure it means something, but what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I can think of only one possibility, Your Honor. The witness, Valant Gramarye... ...has testified that the IV liquid was yellow because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a reason the IV liquid looked yellow to the witness! ...I bet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Erm, Mr. Wright? That "I bet" at the end there... it worries me. Am I right in the assumption that you "hope" there's a reason. Not "know"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Perhaps. Yes. Definitely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then allow me to crush that hope as gentle and gentlemanly as I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One more chance, please... <thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...From the facts before us, the answer is clear. The witness knew that the IV liquid was yellow. ...Why? Because he'd seen it before. But not inside the blue bag we see in the photo. He saw the liquid by itself, in a clear, colorless bag.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose he would have had to. But I'm still not clear as to what all this means.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ask yourself, why would he know, if he didn't work at a hospital? ...That's where you'll find your meaning, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm afraid I find nothing. So what if he knew the IV liquid's color? Leave the getting excited over absolutely nothing to our teenybopper fans, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The IV liquid is the only evidence "proving" the time of death. A 30-minute hourglass, with 20 minutes worth of sand remaining. Your claim, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I remember it well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However... ...there's a critical difference between an hourglass and an IV bag.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-W-Wait! I know!!! An hourglass uses sand, but an IV bag uses liquid... ...I'm right, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As much as it pains me to say this, Your Honor, no. Unlike the sands through an hourglass, IV liquid enters the patient's body. At which point, like magic, it disappears. However! What if the amount of IV liquid had increased? You couldn't tell, could you? After all, there's no way of knowing how much went in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let me get this straight, Herr Wright. You're saying the witness watered down the victim's IV bag!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not with water... but with IV liquid. That's how you knew the IV liquid was yellow!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Now wait. Wait. I said wait!!! How might an amateur such as myself assay to perform such a task?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm an amateur, too, but I can pour water into a cup.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm afraid there's quite a big difference between a cup and an IV bag. Quite. Can you prove our witness is capable of such a feat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... He has a point, amateurs. I, at least, would have some difficulty pouring IV liquid into that bag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You don't need to be an expert to see the look on the witness's face! He added liquid to that IV to throw off the time of death!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I tire of these fairy tales lacking evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Any solid evidence to bring us back down to earth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Valant Gramarye. I'm afraid your "magic" won't serve you well in a life of crime.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Might I ask what you're strongly suggesting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Magic relies on props. And props... become evidence. Our witness was certainly able to increase the amount of IV liquid in the bag. All he had to do was work a little magic. And the prop was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm afraid Mr. Wright is attempting to water down this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why add water, when you could add a penalty?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Unnk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Why indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go so well. I wonder if there was something at the scene... Something he could have used to add more IV liquid.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once again, Mr. Wright, if you would be so kind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim's syringe...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's the perfect prop for the "Magically Increasing IV" trick! And easy enough for an amateur to use.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Wh-What kind of evidence is that!? The syringe was clean! Not a trace of liquid in it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And don't you find that odd, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim had the syringe to administer his insulin shots... ...There should have been traces of insulin left inside!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Valant Gramarye? As you pointed out yourself, the IV liquid makes the perfect clock... ...one that you could manipulate at will!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Allak... Allakazzzzzzzaaaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I do believe... well, with this being his first... ...that the burden of this trial has been a bit too much to bear for Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Valant used this to manipulate the time of death, washed it, and left the scene. ...Which is why it shows no signs of use.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that, while there is a doubt as to the amount of IV liquid in that bag... ...the time of death cannot be proven. ...And that brings our trial to a close for today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well. Maybe I can squeeze an extra day out of this... I can do a little much-needed investigation work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see there are no objections, court is adjour--</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Heh. Heh heh heh! ...Truly, there's no substitute for experience. Nothing blinds one to the truth so effectively.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A word to the wise: Underestimate the young, and they'll sweep your feet out from under you. In a way you never, ever expected. ...You see, I know exactly what you're thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? <thought>What's he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You say the witness used the syringe to manipulate the level of the IV liquid. But there is no proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no proof he didn't do it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Yes, quite true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? He's admitting it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nor was this witness quite as decisive as I'd hoped. This, I admit. After all, why linger in the past, when the future holds so much?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... have something in mind, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Proof, Herr Judge. I have another way to prove my case. ...With evidence, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This... is the victim, Magnifi Gramarye's diary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Diary...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">After going into the hospital, Magnifi began writing his memoirs, it seems. The story of his birth, his startling debut... and of meeting his disciples. It seems he intended for the last chapter to end, quite appropriately, with his death.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait... That book doesn't say what the reason was, does it? The reason why his disciples couldn't refuse his last request?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Sadly, it does not. What's important here... is on the last page. Apparently, the victim wrote in his journal that night. Even after the IV had begun at 11:00 PM. ...Let's read it, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This does appear to have been written just before his death. The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Read the very last part with particular care. "This journal may end here or it may go on... but not long. That depends on his hand." Of course, by "his"... ...he refers to our defendant, Zak Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That would make sense, yes. He was the first scheduled visitor, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But look at what he said before that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"This journal may end here or it may go on." ..."It may go on"! Magnifi Gramarye intended to write again! That is... ...if Zak Gramarye didn't pull the trigger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see the defense understands the meaning of this. The victim's diary does not "go on"... It ends! Because Magnifi's life was brought to an end by the defendant, Zak Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! ...Prosecutor Gavin! Are you certain that Magnifi Gramarye wrote this!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...There is no mistaking his handwriting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this does seem to be significant. According to this, Magnifi did intend to continue his diary. Yet, if his diary ended here, which plainly, it did...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Then the one who pulled the trigger was the first visitor. ...Zak Gramarye. Well, how do you like me now, Herr Wright? Still too "green" for your tastes? Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... <thought>He's right about the diary being pretty clear. Still I find it hard to believe... ...that he'd overlook such an obvious problem with his precious evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? The witness's testimony we heard was lacking... ...but put together with this evidence, it seems quite sufficient for a case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...If the diary is accepted like this, the trial's over. Hmm. Maybe it's time for me to show them something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the last page. The diary ends here. ...! Huh?  What's this? It looks like... a page was ripped out? Well now, isn't that interesting?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't like anything about this situation... ...But the judge is already getting twitchy with his gavel. So I'd better show them something quick... or else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm left with no choice but to show my own evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What!? You have some evidence that overturns this diary!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hmm... ...It's not to [sic] late to rethink this and avoid more... embarrassment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please show us your evidence, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Incidentally, don't even think of showing us this diary I've just shown the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now that we've come this far, I hope you have something a little more... decisive. Show us evidence that proves the victim continued writing his diary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Alright. I'd be happy to. The decisive evidence proving that the diary didn't end with this page is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This evidence... You're saying this is "decisive"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We don't need proof that he "might" have continued his diary. We need proof that he did continue that diary! If such a thing exists, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Time to get cozy with the Court Record... I know I've got the evidence in here somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">First... take a close look at this diary. ...Note that a page has clearly been ripped out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this...!? ...I hadn't noticed that at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's why we're still here talking about this...</thought> As it just so happens... ...I have here what I believe to be the missing page.</line>
<line speaker="Valant">...Allaka-I-don't-believe-it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looking at this page... It's hard to imagine that the first visitor that night shot Magnifi Gramarye. That's the defense's position.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Wait. Let me see that! What in sam hill...? Why, this is the continuation of the victim's diary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Note the torn edge of the page. It's a perfect match with the torn remains of the last page in Magnifi's diary!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">Quite... remarkable...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Would you care to explain what all this means, Herr Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The diary continued after his first visitor came. Which means that the victim was still alive after Zak Gramarye left! Leaving no one to take his life but the second visitor! Valant Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">No... Nooooo...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The handwriting, too, matches that on the other pages. This is, without a doubt, the genuine article! Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Valant">But, but wait! This is... That's impossible! That old man couldn't have written that...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Finally. You just couldn't resist, could you, Herr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Resist what? Presenting solid evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Herr Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Might I request we put the current cross-examination on hold? The prosecution would like to call a new witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But, Prosecutor Gavin! This evidence overturns the current witness's...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I ask only to put it on hold! Please. My new witness has a very, very important piece of testimony to give. ...Five minutes. No more. I promise... Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well, if you put it that way... Mr. Wright, what's your take on this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... Well, Your Honor. Judging from his enthusiasm... ...we'll have to hear this new testimony sooner or later anyway. ...So it might as well be sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Then, though this is highly, highly irregular... ...we will put the current cross-examination on hold. The witness may step down. ...Now, Prosecutor Gavin! Please bring this surprise witness to the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I had a bad feeling just then. That ripped-out page was too obvious... ...He must have known. And I should've known it was a bad sign all around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Holding trial with no audience is a first, even for me, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I beg the court's understanding. But I had to make a judiciary deal with the witness to secure his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A judiciary "deal"...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The details of his testimony may have some "legal ramifications", shall we say. I thought it best to contain the information to this room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. And you are the witness, I gather...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah... Y-Yes. Yes, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...State your name and occupation for the record.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Erm... My name's Drew Misham. I'm... a painter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A painter? And you are somehow related to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">No, well. Not per se...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I have one simple question for this witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Mister... Misham, was it? Do you know what this is?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Oh... yeah. I know it well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...How's that possible? Have you seen this diary page somewhere before?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Oh, yeah. I mean... I made it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... what? You "made" it!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Yes. You might call it one of my "works".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The regional prosecutor's office received a tip-off yesterday. "Illegal evidence has been prepared for the trial of Zak Gramarye."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Illegal... evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I initiated an investigation, and found this witness. A painter to the world at large, Drew Misham has another side, you might say. He is skilled in making perfect reproductions of certain things... ...Forgeries, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Forgeries...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well! So, we are to understand that this page here is...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A fake. Prepared by a certain defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> I didn't "prepare" this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ah, the attorney speaks. Something about this page, I presume. But what is he saying? It makes no sense! ...After all it was you who presented this evidence to us, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Witness! Er, Mr. Misham, was it? Who requested this forgery!? Who was your client!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">That... I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Most of my clients prefer to remain anonymous, even to me. I make the items they want, and receive my payment. That's the extent of my contact with them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...! There's no proof this is a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Drew">It's a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Drew">To avoid just this sort of problem... I always put a special mark on my "works". I can say, without a doubt, this is mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Wright. You have just presented illegal evidence to this court. My court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...It was careless of me. ...That's all I can say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh... Old boy! Um, uh... Here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I dunno! I just got it over there in the hall. They told me to give it to the "old boy in the blue suit with the spiky hair". They said it was really important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was all a trap. A fatal trap...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have an explanation for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I did, would the court hear it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Probably not. Forging evidence is a serious crime. And presenting it in court, a serious mistake. A fatal mistake, for an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Fatal, too, perhaps, for your client, I fear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Tell me, what kind of defendant relies on forged evidence...? The answer is quite clear. A guilty one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honor, wait! I understand that presenting forged evidence in court is a serious crime. But you cannot hold my client responsible for actions I undertook as an individual...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I am sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Another close call, I dare say. If the prosecutor's office hadn't received that hot tip... ...everything would have gone the way you wanted it to, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I even gave you a chance. Too bad you decided not to think before embarrassing yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see no need for further discussion on this matter. Special witness dismissed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The ripped-out page... Now I see that everything has been a set-up. All so I would present forged evidence to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">...Mr. Attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Could I... ask your name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Mr. Wright... I have seen and studied many people, but none like you. I'll remember you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Though I deeply regret having to declare a verdict in this way... This trial is over.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have the right to find a new attorney and make an appeal. However, this court must...</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Ah, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Mr. Zak?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">There is one thing I wish to make clear. Today, in this courtroom... ...you cannot declare me "guilty". ...It is impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm afraid the defendant is quite mistaken. I most certainly have the authority to declare a verdict on you.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">Except... tell me, how do you plan on announcing your verdict... ...when your defendant does not exist?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Doesn't exist"...? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Zak">I am talking... about this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Enigmar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defendant's escaped! Find him! Quick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Close all exits from the building! On the double! He must not be allowed to escape!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Shadi Enigmar...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>