
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Academy</title>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. My butterflies have butterflies in their stomach.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what's it like to have your very own case for the first time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My heart hasn't raced this fast since I ran that full marathon last year.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it keeps up, you might get a lawyer's high -- you know like a runner's high?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Relax, everyone's nervous their first time.</line>
<line speaker="Means">So my fears weren't unfounded. After all, today's prosecutor is so terribly brutal... ...and willing to use any means necessary to win a conviction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's that the-end-justifies-the-means concept again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Now that it has come to this... ...we have no choice but to fight fire with fire. The end justifies the means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I wish he'd stop saying that.</thought> That's your method, Professor. I'm going to defend Juniper in my own way.</line>
<line speaker="Means">But, Ms. Cykes. Just yesterday you told me...</line>
<line speaker="Means">As a lawyer, what is it that you treasure beyond all else?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh! That's an easy one, Professor! Seeking justice for my clients!</line>
<line speaker="Means">But if this trial proceeds in the same manner and ends in the same way as the mock trial... ...would you not lose everything you've worked so hard to gain?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I'll just have to make sure that doesn't happen, then, won't I!</line>
<line speaker="Means">My, but aren't you a stubborn one. Well, I suppose you will have to learn of your own inefficacy the hard way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Grrrrrrr...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Forgive me, Prof. Means, but can we just leave it at that?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Oh, dear, please forgive me. It's just, I wish to protect Juniper by any means I can.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I do, too, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, if you would excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! Thanks to him, I'm feeling even more pressure than before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't let it get to you, Athena. And don't forget to keep smiling.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll be fine! And I haven't forgotten what Mr. Wright said! "The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles."</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to begin. I'll show you to the courtroom if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo, I'm counting on you to support Athena this time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, Mr. Wright! Leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's right. I have Apollo to back me up. Junie's fate rests in my hands. I won't rest until she walks free!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Athena Cykes, d-defense team leader, is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That didn't sound very confident. You sure you're okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll... I'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know, I know. As usual, you want me to deliver the opening statement. Agh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This case is crystal clear. I see no need to explicate it any further. ...Now, summon the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Is there something the matter? Please do share, Your Baldness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whatever gave you that idea?! Bailiff, please call our first witness!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>And now we don't even get an opening statement...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Detective Fulbright... He and Prosecutor Blackquill have become quite the team.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Oh, right! The case brief! Leave it to me! Yes, let the detective in charge, everyone's favorite friend of justice, explain!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was THAT just now...? It's like he and Blackquill are totally in sync.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't think they're capable of mind melding, if that's what you're thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, Detective Fulbright. Would you please explain the case to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Prof. Courte's body was discovered on October 24th at approximately 2:30 PM. She was murdered with this awl I have here! The victim's blood and the defendant's prints were both discovered on it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">EEEK!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that bird can deliver evidence, too? Blackquill has trained him well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe Blackquill should train it not to mess up people's hair while he's at it.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Moving right along! The body was discovered on the outdoor stage, although no blood was found there! However, we detected traces of a massive amount of blood in the third floor art room. In short, the murder took place in the art room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the body had been moved from the art room to the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Precisely! And there is one more piece of irrefutable evidence! A recording made by a tape recorder that a school paper reporter hid in the art room! It captured a female voice screaming, "You're a goner!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this?! You have such a recording?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Must be from that tape recorder Myriam mentioned.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But why is this the first we've heard of a death threat at the moment of the murder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Shhhhhh! Silence, please! I would like to play the tape for you now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It is quite hard to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But the voice does sound female...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The noise and low volume of the voice have made voiceprint analysis all but impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, you haven't identified the voice as belonging to the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Not so fast. After all, voiceprint analysis isn't everything! The victim was killed at night, then discovered in the afternoon the next day. The question is... when was the body moved!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Oh, oh! I know! It could've been moved in the middle of the night when no one was around!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Sorry, but no! The campus was full of students that morning. However, no one reported seeing a body. That means the body was moved sometime before the mock trial when all the students... ...and faculty were gathered in the Lecture Hall and the rest of the campus was empty! It was during this time Hugh O'Conner, one of the mock trial participants, found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So the prosecution heard about Hugh seeing the body...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait a moment. If all of the students and faculty were gathered in the Lecture Hall... ...then there wouldn't have been anyone who could've moved the body!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! Have no fear, for there is always an exception.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An exception?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">The three mock trial participants were standing by in individual dressing rooms. They were the only ones who had free access to the deserted campus before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Then that would mean...! ...What would that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Those three students were the only ones who could've moved the body! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't like where this is headed, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Me neither...</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">And by those three, I mean... ...Hugh O'Conner, Robin Newman, and Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I knew it... <thought>Please, Detective Fulbright... Don't say what I think you're about to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">In justice we trust! I take it EVERYONE understands now! The voice believed to be that of the murderer was female! And out of the three people who could've moved the body, just one is a girl. That leaves the defendant Juniper Woods as the only possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Impressive. He has you on the ropes even before any cross-examinations.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>You could at least pretend to be upset for me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A splendid job, Fool Bright. That could not be any clearer. Feel free to anticipate a salary raise next month.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha ha! I don't do this for the money. It's all about justice! In justice we trust!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Not only a halfwit, but a perennial stick-in-the-mud you are.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I guess neither the carrot nor the stick works on Detective Fulbright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Bailiff, please bring our next witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... our first witness... is a cardboard box?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">......... Kaaahk! Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss...! Stealth mode deactivated!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! The box has hands!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Smile, Your Honor. Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What the dickens?! I've just had my picture taken!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Myriam Scuttlebutt. Senior at the legal academy. I'm a reporter on the judge course. Juniper's been a bad, bad girl. I'll tell you all about her crime, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Umm, might I ask whether you could come out of that box?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">How will I get any more scoops if I blow my cover? So, the answer is no. After all, covert action is an undercover reporter's bread and butter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But testimony from a faceless witness is highly irregular.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A former ninja I met in the clink said that exposing those who work in the shadows... ...is to pass the death sentence upon them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! I had never thought of it that way. Very well, if it would spare a life, I'll make a special exception this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>A former ninja in prison? Holy shinto! How can the judge believe this load of crock?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, your testimony please. Oh, but take care not to reveal your face.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">The murder happened exactly like Juniper's mock trial script.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The murder is just like her script?! Could such a thing be true?!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Compare her script with the murder case and crime scene photos. Then you'll see!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is so simple, even an ape posing as a decrepit old judge could understand. Only the victim and the defendant were privy to the script. Ergo, the defendant is the killer. Furthermore, in the art room where the crime supposedly occurred, this witness's script... ...along with an envelope on which "Use" was written were found. This proves that the accused's script had been rejected the day before the mock trial. She pressed the victim to use her script, an argument ensued, and then the fatal stabbing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*gulp* <thought>That makes perfect sense. What now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Blackquill has all his ducks lined up in a row. He's really on a roll now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. He's like a pit bull once it sinks its teeth into you.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">How dare she! My script had it all! A bum rap and phony evidence! Grudges and betrayals!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I trust the defense is ready to cross-examine the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No problem! I-I mean, yes I'm ready... I think... <thought>Time to find a hole in her testimony, and unbox the truth! I've seen it done over and over. I know I can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">The murder happened exactly like Juniper's mock trial script.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! Don't sweat the details! That kind of stress will give you wrinkles!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. Blackquill really turned that one around on you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, whose side are you on?! Hurry up and think of a clever comeback!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, easy there, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now you listen to me. The two cases do, indeed, have their differences. For one, the stage hadn't yet been erected in the mock trial script. And in the actual case, there were signs indicating the victim's wrists had been bound. But such differences pale in comparison to the host of similarities. In any event, replicating the crime without knowledge of the script is an impossibility.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmmm... <thought>Looks like I won't be passing this off as a coincidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! What a total burn! Try again, why dontcha, Pawn of Woods?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Up until the mock trial began, only Prof. Courte and Juniper knew the script's contents.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! I don't think so. I mean, I tried any number of times.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Shame on you, Myriam!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">But that crafty she-devil Juniper has eyes in the back of her head! What chance does your average person have if an undercover reporter like me failed?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Interesting point. Still...</thought> Ms. Scuttlebutt, won't you get in trouble later for admitting to such underhanded tactics?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Why, you...! I plead entrapment!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>How is you blurting out your own crime entrapment?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk... But you haven't scooped me yet! They were all set to use Juniper's script...</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">But Prof. Courte's sudden decision not to use the script sparked Juniper's murderous rage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. There in the art room where the heinous crime took place... ...an envelope marked "Use" and Myriam Scuttlebutt's script were found. Evidently, the script that was going to be used belonged to the girl in the box over there.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! It's only natural that my script would be accepted and hers rejected. I introduced all sorts of brand-new concepts, including bribery and fake evidence! It was a cutting-edge script portraying a courtroom battle in the dark age of the law!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I can't help but feel Prof. Courte went out of her way NOT to use it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">But Juniper... She used some devious, underhanded tactics to get her script chosen. That's why her script, and not my masterpiece, was used in the mock trial! How's that for an explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Juniper has to be the killer. She has a motive and the murder is just like her script.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. If he's so weary, he should try hmph-ing less. I bet that'd save some energy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is no time for jokes, Apollo! He just called me a canary!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't let him get to you. At least canaries pick up on things quickly, just like you.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I shan't repeat myself, so listen carefully, Cykes-dono. Hugh O'Conner discovered the body before the mock trial even began. How could one stage the body as it is in the script before anyone knew its contents?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gah... That's right...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you even fathom the intricacies that go into staging a crime scene? No, I think not. You have the rudimentary mind of an elementary school child.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Elementary school?!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">"Reporter's Testimony Throws Attorney Athena Cykes for Loop!" The perfect caption!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How marvelous! A photo in the newspaper is just the thing to boost your brand.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>In a school paper? Seriously?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Anyone can see the similarities between the script and this case. But that doesn't mean Junie's the killer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know it's frustrating, Athena, but we don't have much to go on at this point. All you can do is relentlessly press the witness and hope you find a hole.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, got it! <thought>Press relentlessly! Right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Now do you see how clear-cut my case is? Take it now, and in that fair, desperate mind of yours... ...etch it deep so you may never forget!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No... Nooooooooooooooo! <thought>Even my arguments get thrown back in my face. It wasn't supposed to be like this. What am I going to do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Athena. You should just about have all the answers you've been looking for now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about it this way: If the killer knew the details of the mock trial... ...would they really commit the crime in the exact same way?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't follow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Try to place yourself in the killer's shoes. I bet you'll discover an inconsistency if you do.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Ah! I get it! Thanks, Apollo! Ms. Scuttlebutt! Just so we're clear, you're claiming... ...that the killer INTENTIONALLY made the crime scene just as it was in the script... ...and that it is beyond the shadow of a doubt NOT a coincidence. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">No duh! After all, it's just more evidence of Juniper's evil she-devil ways.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Scuttlebutt:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Our client made the crime scene look just like the script, something known only to her? That would be not just foolhardy, but completely irrational!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Ms. Cykes. Please tell this court what you mean by "irrational."</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It wouldn't make any sense for Junie to mimic her own script on purpose because it would...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Intentionally making the crime scene look like the script... ...would expose the secret script for all to see!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">So?! Juniper's a ruthless she-devil! She'd easily do that and a lot more to achieve her evil designs!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Does the defense care to offer a counter-argument?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I'm good. Moving right along...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Just one moment. Here in court, we have a special gift for intentionally evasive lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I want a refuuuund! <thought>Ugh. There's something obviously wrong with this whole set-up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Here's the thing. The mock trial details were kept secret. In short, there was no way our client could've known what was in the script!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course I didn't forget! Our client wrote--! Er... whoops.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">To say that the script's own author didn't know the details is quite a stretch, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>Ugh. I think I need to find an explanation that actually makes sense.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The murder scene was the same as it was in the mock trial script. That in and of itself is irrational!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk! What's wrong with them being the same?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Ms. Cykes. Care to explain what you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, let's say for argument's sake, that Ms. Woods is the killer. If so, then... ...what reason would she have to intentionally make the actual murder mimic her own script?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">That's easy! She was admitting that she was the-- Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. If she had really done that... ...it would've been like proclaiming to the world that she was the killer! So, what we ACTUALLY have here is evidence of someone trying to frame our client!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk... Kaaahk kahk-kahk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The body was found on the day of the mock trial, in short, the day the details were revealed. So it would be completely inconceivable for the murder to go exactly like the script!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk! Don't let it go to your head just yet!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">E-Enough with the stupid sword metaphors, already!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There is a perfectly good reason for the inconsistency of which you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Reason? What reason?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Must I spell out everything? Hmph, you are what people today call "high maintenance." The accused had intended to stop the mock trial. And in that event... ...nary a soul would have been the wiser to the similarities of the case and script.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What?! Ms. Scuttlebutt saw the body, too?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Precisely. And with the discovery of the body, the mock trial ought to have been canceled.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, so you didn't call the police?!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Nope! I kept it secret for my big scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I made her pay long and hard penance for her sin. Did I not, my little box top?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! Compared to the work of a war correspondent, the sheer terror of that was-- Aaaaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jeez, I wonder what the Twisted Samurai did to her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Block off all the holes in her box... ...and spin her like a top while Detective Fulbright cackled in delight?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That sounds more nauseating than scary.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough jabbering. Witness! Continue your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss, sss... Sure, Mr. Samurai. I'm ready to finish off that she-devil!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I snuck into Juniper's dressing room while everyone was in the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kaaahk! Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Athena! You haven't even started your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know, but her testimony points to her as being a potential suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I don't think Prosecutor Blackquill is-- No, wait, I bet he's already thought of that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The witness left the Lecture Hall to sneak into Ms. Woods's room before the mock trial. That means she, too, could have moved the victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kaaaaaahk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The prosecution's claim no longer has any ground to stand on! Heeeeeelp!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, now, no need to ruffle your own feathers so. When you squeak like a little brat, it agitates Taka. Do you want him to peck your eyes out?</line>
<line speaker="Widget">No, thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You listen here. The witness has a perfectly good alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Oh, yeah, I do! Around the estimated time of death... ...I was at undercover reporter class. It's right near my home!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Undercover reporter class?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The proverbial rug has been pulled from under you. The witness could not be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense must look before leaping -- or at least make sure the rug's secured to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I tried to warn you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oooh...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, there ends the cross-examination. Let's allow the witness to step down.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? N-No, wait a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The defense has no right to cross-examine the witness after that little spectacle. For whatever a man is sowing, this he will also reap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. <thought>Why can't he say, "You reap what you sow"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, if the cross-examination is over, I suppose the witness may go home. Perhaps spend some time in her lovely box and recover from today's stressful events.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Don't you worry about me, Your Honor! There's no rest for the wicked... or journalists, either! My third eye's always eyeing a scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's always eyeing a scoop...?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Well, back to the trenches! Buh-bye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's... just one thing I'd like to ask. Did you take a picture of the victim's body, and if not, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I, well... that is... No... I-I didn't take one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's strange... Why wouldn't you take a picture if you're always eyeing a scoop?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you or didn't you really see the victim's body?!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! Er... it's not like I, uh... actually SAW it, saw it, but...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What the devil?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you hear that, Your Honor? The witness didn't actually see the body! That completely overturns the prosecution's claim that the witness was led to it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Justice-dono! You dare bare steel at me again?!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Scuttlebutt:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What exactly am I looking at here?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! It's a crucial moment forever frozen in time by my third eye. A photo clearly showing Juniper Woods! Kaaaaaahk!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Why did you not tell me of this?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. It's a shocking scoop I was saving for just the right moment. And that would be now, right here in court. Surprise! Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss. Kaaaaaaaaaaaahk! What'd I do, what'd I do?! All journalists keep their scoops secret until the right moment!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's pretty brave hiding it from Blackquill like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or pretty stupid. ...Well, this is an unexpected turn.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, Athena? About this picture... See how it only shows the back of the subject?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah! So, then...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, who knows whether this photo Juniper in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Then I... tripped and fell. Caught my knee on my own box.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She stayed under the box, even while running after someone? Sounds difficult...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Recall that the body was already there, for Hugh O'Conner had already seen it. She was trying to show someone the body because she wanted to stop the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The defense has a point there. Very well, you may proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! It seems Justice-dono has saved your pretty little hide, missy. ...For now, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Whew. Guess I pulled that off somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Apollo. You're a lifesaver.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Incidentally, my compliments to the witness for her very fine box.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss, sss! It's primo cardboard, lovingly selected from among many-- Kahk!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tell another lie or hide another fact from me... ...and I shall put it to the torch!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk... Kaaaaaahk! P-P-Please, anything but that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think it would be more eco-friendly to recycle it, but that's just me. All right, Ms. Cykes. You may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I snuck into Juniper's dressing room while everyone was in the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Because if I got a big scoop on Juniper, club membership would go through the roof! Right now, the Newspaper Club only has one member, me. The club's history once I'm gone. So, the Themis Herald's brand recognition is a matter of life and death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Her means may be questionable, but her motive is surprisingly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Extra, extra! "Students seeking the Thrills and Chills of Exposé Journalism, Report to the Clubroom!" This has been a paid advertisement. Anyway, where was I...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Huh. Never took Myriam for such a go-getter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Juniper had changed into her stage costume. I asked her, "What are you doing?"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">How should I know? But if you don't believe me, take a look at this photo! I captured this critical moment like the gonzo journalistic pro that I am.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But, this only shows the back of whoever was fleeing.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">You expect me to shoot her face when she's running away from me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess you're right, but... <thought>This doesn't seem to be getting me anywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">At any rate, as this photo shows, Juniper was in her stage costume.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">When suddenly, she fled into the hallway, as if she wanted me to follow her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Call it a journalist's instinct! I see something fishy, I go after it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you never did catch up to her, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss! A true undercover journalist gets up and dusts herself off when she stumbles!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That reminds me. Didn't you fall during the chase? When you tripped on your box?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! A true undercover journalist is always ready to stumble over a great story!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure are a lot of holes in your story. Or is that just the Scuttlebutt brand of journalism?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk! A true undercover journalist always prevails against her adversaries!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I followed her all the way to Prof. Courte's body! She led me right to it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The accused had employed her self-penned script as a manual for murder. Ergo, she had to stop the mock trial before the script's details became public. And that accounts for her desperate attempt to lead our carton cretin here to the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I'm positive it was Juniper because she was wearing the costume that she had made!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! It's only as simple and clear-cut as a good piece of journalism should be!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... <thought>Sure it's simple, but I'd hardly call it clear-cut.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">That's why I chased her, sss, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She keeps saying that it was Junie, but she didn't even actually see the body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but Blackquill's assertion takes that into account.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, even if I press her on never seeing the body... ...I won't be able to overturn this testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, whoever it was that was fleeing, Myriam never did see their face. So, I'm wondering why she thought it was Juniper. Try thinking along that line and see what you can come up with.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Scuttlebutt's sole basis for identifying our client as the figure in this photo... ...is the fact that it shows someone in Ms. Woods's stage costume.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. Well, it IS Juniper's costume. So that must be Juniper in it. It's clear-cut.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, that's where you're completely mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is a design drawing of our client's stage costume.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my, what a wonderful creation! The constellations are extraordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm glad you noticed, because those stars are precisely what's important here. In the drawing, there are constellations all over the outside of the costume. But there's not a single star on the costume in the photo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Oh, then that means... Uh... What exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, there were no other blue costumes at the scene. Which leads me to believe... ...that the figure in the photo was wearing our client's costume inside out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But why would Ms. Woods make a mistake like that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it's not really a matter of why... ...but rather, who made the mistake of putting it on inside out.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk... W-Wait, you're not suggesting...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. I'm glad you're catching on. The costume's designer wouldn't put her own costume on inside out!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk! Kaaaaaaaaaahk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, Ms. Scuttlebutt, but... ...doesn't believing you had a scoop when you really didn't make you a failure as a reporter?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">A f-failure as a r-reporter?! Kahk-kahk-kahk. Kaaahk kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk! Ack! ...Ah!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why hello, Ms. Scuttlebutt! So nice to meet the woman beneath the box!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk-kahk! Y-- You didn't see nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ms. Juniper Woods!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What were you doing on the morning of the mock trial?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was in my dressing room, *cough* painting my costume in fluorescent paint.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fluorescent... paint?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">My design drawing shows twinkling stars on the costume. *cough* *cough* I was going to make the costume shimmer like that by painting the inside fluorescent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fluor... what was that again? Fluoride? Did your costume have cavities?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Not fluoride -- fluorescent, as in glowing. The paint would make it glow in the dark. *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, yes, so you applied that to the inside of the costume. And then?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I let it dry for a while because I heard it takes a long time. So I put the costume on my mannequin inside out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Inside out...? So, then...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is a photograph of the inside-out costume taken in the dark. As you can see, there is a heavy layer of paint over the entire inside surface. If someone were to properly don this costume in this state... ...the wet paint would get all over their body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Why, yes! I believe it would!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. Ergo, the costume was worn the way it was, not by anyone's mistake... ...but because this was the way it was on the mannequin -- inside out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Figures he would have a photo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. Did we just fall into his trap?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I bet Blackquill had it all planned out. Still, I think you should give this photo a nice, long look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, please tell me you found something that doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Check out the chest area. It kinda looks like a hand print to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right! But Junie would know better than to touch it while the paint was still wet.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Evidence? That shouldn't be a problem, right? After all, you've come this far.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just because I've come this far, that doesn't mean I've thought everything through, though...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! You mean you've just been bluffing?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What did you expect me to do?! I'm sick of losing to this guy! But you're right... There's only one thing left to do at this point! And that's to present some evidence! Pronto!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............A showdown, is it? I gladly accept!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The fluorescent paint must have stuck to the hands of whoever touched the costume. And that paint should glow in dark places... So, I just need to carefully check every last piece of evidence!</thought> This piece of evidence shows who touched the costume!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems Prosecutor Blackquill is not too pleased with your off-target evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Let's ask him what he thinks. Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I thought. My initial suspicion was correct.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gah hah! <thought>Now I'M speechless...</thought> Please! I think I've got it this time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A school newspaper?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Take a look at the photo where the lights are dimmed and the spotlight is on Ms. Woods. Observe Mr. Newman's hand in that photo as he stands at the prosecutor's bench. As you can see, it's glowing, just like Ms. Woods's fluorescent paint.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It is glowing -- quite brightly I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But why would he put fluorescent paint on his hand for the mock trial, you may ask? The answer is he wouldn't -- not on purpose. It got there when he put the costume on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...? I mean, oh! That means...! ......What again?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It means the figure photographed in the costume was not our client Juniper Woods. It was her classmate, Robin Newman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...To think you were actually able to prove that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, you never know what's going to happen next. That's the thrill of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... So, then... ...does that mean that Robin is our man...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Well... That's certainly how it looks...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Very well, Robin Newman it is! He is here in the gallery, I trust? Show yourself! I challenge you to a duel!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the witness please state his name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">IIIIIIIIIII'M ROBIIIIIIIN NEWMAAAAAAAAN!!! I want to become a great artist! I practice day and night!!! YEAAAAAAH! NOOOOOO! That's not it! Art's gotta be sincere, maaaaaan!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, for occupation, should we put down ...budding artist?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">NOOOOOO! Themis Legal Academy! Senior! PROSECUTOR COOOURSE! This brace is proof of my masculinity! I've been training to be a prosecutor for 18 years!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*ahem* I assume you will be cleaning up the pottery you smashed before you leave today.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">.........Aaaaaaaaagh! AWWW, MAAAAAAAAAN!!! Aaaaaaaaagh! Aaagh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems the witness has finally settled down.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I guess nothing fazes the judge after all these years.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may proceed with your testimony, Mr. Newman. Specifically, the court wishes to hear why you had fluorescent paint on your hand.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I went to see Juniper in her dressing room! BUT SHE WASN'T THERE!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Newman does seem particularly agitated, but...</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Agh! ...Arrrgh! Aaaaaaaaagh! Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not again. What's his problem?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sensed it the moment Robin took the stand. ...The discord in his heart!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you think he might be hiding something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Probably! You ready, Mr. Newman? Let's see what the Mood Matrix can do for you!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I went to see Juniper in her waiting room!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">BUT SHE WASN'T THERE!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">When I walked by that frilly costume, I was like, whoaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The mannequin it was on! IT WAS ABOUT TO FALL OVER!!!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I got the paint on me when I caught it!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I never put it on! That's just STUUUPID!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He had to catch the mannequin as it suddenly started to fall over?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even I can guess this one. The most natural response would be surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Apollo's right, so maybe I should try focusing on some other emotion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">When you mentioned the stage costume... ...I sensed a sudden, powerful feeling of joy. Would you care to explain, Mr. Newman?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">W-W-Wait?! WHAAAAAAT?! Wh-Why would a frilly scarf-thing and a long skirt make me feel like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but you seem awfully interested in that costume for some reason. You didn't happen to put it on, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">L-Like I'd be into that kinda thing! I'm a dude! I'm into braces, not dresses!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't think... Robin likes girls' clothes... do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, come on! Isn't it obvious?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're enjoying this a bit too much, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">NO WAY, MAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAN! The mannequin came falling toward me, so I stuck out my hands to stop it! End of story!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's a new piece of information! Time to run an update! <thought>Hmm... Even after that update, something just doesn't feel right here. Do I have anything that could prove his statement contradicts what really happened?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">No way, maaaaaan! The only contradiction that thing shows... ...is your existeeeeeeeeeeeeence!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! <thought>I-I object to that statement! Okay, so... Maybe I should compare when he caught the mannequin against the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You said the mannequin came falling toward you, so you stuck your hands out to stop it. If so, then then fingers of your hands would've been pointing outward like this. But that's not what the handprints show. In fact, this looks more like just your thumbs and the base of your palms.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Wh-Why in the world would I leave such weird handprints?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know why! You left them when you went to adjust the scarf after putting it on. Just like the model in the drawing!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">WHOOOOOOA!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't you admit it, Mr. Newman? You DID put the stage costume on, didn't you? And you really DO like frilly clothes, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Fine! I admit to putting the costume on! BUUUUUUT! I DON'T LIKE GIRLY CLOTHES, MAAAN!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes! New information to plug in! Time for another update!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I snuck in, knowing the costume was in there!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">My heart was pounding, even though I'm a guy.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Then I saw it! It was even more amazing than I'd imagined!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I was like, WHOAAA! I'm a guy, but I got all excited!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">It's true! I did put on girly clothes!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">But it was strictly for artistic purposes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hopefully, we can figure out what Robin's hiding based on this new information.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just hope it's not more than we bargained for, although that usually seems to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There! Another emotion that doesn't fit.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">So what?! You're really starting to get on my nerves, maaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman, you got excited when you put the costume on... ...but you also felt sad.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Who cares if I felt sad?! It's no big deaaaaaal!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, Mr. Newman, out with it! Why did you feel sad?! You're hiding something, aren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh! Nooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're not fooling anyone anymore. Now, tell us why you were sad!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">OKAAAAAY, FIIINE! If you're gonna be that way, I'll tell you!!! The reason I felt sad is... is... is...!!! No matter how much I dress up, I'll never be as pretty as Juniper!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, no offense, but for one thing, he's a guy -- and a real hothead at that.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">NOOOOOOOOOOOO! THAT'S NOT IIIIIIIIIIT! I totally owned those girly clothes! I should've been totally pretty!!! BUT! BUT! THERE'S SOMETHING THAT KEEPS GETTING IN MY WAAAAAAY!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow! That's a whole lot of anger and raw emotion right there! His heart is crying out in pain -- his emotions are out of control!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Out-of-control emotions...! We saw those during the Nine-Tales [sic] Vale incident. So, all we have to do is find the source of his uncontrollable anger, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. Help me look for a conflict between his statements and the images we see. If we can find that we can wrestle him away from whatever's tormenting him. <thought>Mr. Newman said that there's something "getting in the way" of him being pretty. Something that doesn't go with girly clothes... But what could it be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">FINE! I'LL TESTIFY, MAAAAAAN!!!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I snuck in, knowing the costume was in there!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">My heart was pounding, even though I'm a guy.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">It's true! I felt a powerful feeling when I saw that long frilly scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I admit it! I wore girly clothes!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I felt like a diva when I pulled the hood over my head!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">It felt so right I was totally dressed up like a girl!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, we're looking for the source of his anger?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. The conflict in his testimony will most likely arise from his emotional repression.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's compare the images to his testimony! We might find the problem that way!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman, you feel a great deal of anger toward your brace, don't you? Is that what you feel is holding you back from being as pretty as you think you should be?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Huh? Wh-Wh-Wh-WHAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman! The truth is, you really want to take that brace off, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">No way maaan! This is a symbol of masculinity! I could never take it off!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it that you can't take it off, or that you don't want to take it off?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Aw, maaaaaaaaaaaan! I shoulda kept my big mouth shut!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... <thought>This is really weird. He exhibits intense anger toward his brace, which he calls a "symbol of masculinity"... ...but he can't take it off, even when dressing like a girl. And why is he so interested in girls' clothes in the first place? I have a feeling we're on the verge of uncovering an earth-shattering secret.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena? You okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It seems Robin is still hiding a secret. A big one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bigger than the fact that he likes to wear girls' clothes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, at least I think so.&#160;! <thought>No, it can't be! I just thought of something, but it's totally insane!</thought> Mr. Newman!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm on to your little secret. And if I'm correct, it's not very little at all. It's huge! This sounds completely insane, but it's the only possibility left.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman! You like to dress like a girl!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">That's right! And I'm never gonna change! I'll show you how real men cross-dress!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You will? <thought>Now???</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, we already know he likes to cross-dress. This line of discussion is a dead end.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But if he really likes to dress like a girl, you'd think he'd want to... ...take that "symbol of masculinity" off when he does it. Wait, could this mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You don't like girls, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">What?! Whaaaaaat?! WHAT GAVE YOU THAT IDEA?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh... Then, what? You like girls?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I-I-I! I refuse to answer thaaaat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, you're not asking just of curiosity, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? N-No, of course not! <thought>Better try something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman, or should I say... Ms. Newman... You are and have always been a girl!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Have you lost the plot, Athena?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I'm completely serious. I don't have any direct evidence. But that's what Robin's heart is shouting out, loud and clear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh. Ooh hoo hoo. Ooooooh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've seen plenty of witnesses in my day... ...but if he's a she, then she's the most convincing actress I have ever encountered. Therefore, let me pronounce my verdict. Robin Newman is without question... a man!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ooh. Ooh hoo hoo. Ooooooh. Ooh hoo hoo.........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You are now truly Justice-dono's equal in one area. You are just as equally insane! Never in the history of this planet has there been a finer specimen of the masculine spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ahhhhhhh! The brace! It's...!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ms. Cykes... No, allow me to call you "Athena." I wanted to keep this a secret at all costs! But noooo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-- No waaaaaaaaaaaay!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gnnnaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! .........S-Surely this must be some kind of jest?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eh heh heh, nope, it's for real. I'm a girl, body and soul. If you don't believe me, I'll give you a P-E-E-K.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">As if! Ah ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What an amazing transformation.</thought> Well, all the discord is gone. The image is now complete!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I was raised as a boy since I was little, and I studied law just as my parents wanted. But now, this living lie that had me pinned to the ground, it's...! Aaaaaagh! *huff* *puff* It's been blown to smithereens by you, Athena! Now I can stop pretending I want to be a prosecutor! I'm gonna be an artist! Yaaaaaaaaaaaay!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! What a shocking development. He really DID turn out to be she!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eek! Why's everyone looking at me like that?! Tee hee! I feel like a movie star or something! But no paparazzi please! I value my privacy, O-K-A-Y? RAAAAAAAAAWH! No pics or you'll regret it, maaaaaaaaaan!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Am I just imagining things, or is Robin even more hyper now than when she was a he?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know. Maybe it's because she finally got her troubles off her chest, literally.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is all well and good, but does he being a she actually change anything?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The fact that the witness is a girl does change things. Because there is now a piece of evidence that we must re-evaluate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, let's see what the defense has for us now. What piece of evidence must we reconsider now that we know that the witness is a girl?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Please do explain.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor. You see, I feel that if you have a sharp eye and an open mind... ...you can discover something completely new in the most obvious of places!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yet, the defense's statement reflects anything but those two admirable traits.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeek! <thought>Guess that won't fly! But I know we have some sort of evidence that could be seen differently based on sex.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is what I'd like the court to reconsider.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, the tape recorder -- the one that recorded the threat, "You're a goner!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. And we have already established that it's a female voice in the recording. Of all the students who could've moved the body before the mock was to start... ...our client was the only female if you exclude Ms. Scuttlebutt because of her alibi. And that is why the tape recorder made our client the prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... So then...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! The witness just revealed that she's a girl! Therefore! If we are using the voice in this recording as the basis for hurling accusations... ...this witness must be labeled a suspect, too!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh... Oh, noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow... Talk about a sudden turn of events. You've done it. You've found a hole in one of the prosecution's key pieces of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... But, wow, that was a lot of work for a single one.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eek! That's not nice, Athena! How can you accuse me of being a killer? I mean, I'm just a weak, innocent little girl! Just thinking about murder makes me--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">How can you say that?! I'm not an accessory to any crime, Mr. Birdman!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing could be more simple. All anyone had to do was watch the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But Athena, the murder took place before the mock trial even began.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oof, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe Prosecutor Blackquill wishes to penalize you, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeowch! <thought>What is this, Athena the Piñata Day?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've got it! All anyone has to do is write their own script! In a completely stream-of-thought, devil-may-care way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not even going to ask how such a Frankenstein could resemble the actual script!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo! <thought>Oh, well, if at first you don't succeed...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sorry, Junie, but... You're not going to like this.</thought> Our client may have leaked the script's details to someone.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...What the devil?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">And I know I shouldn't have, but... I revised the script to favor the prosecution. But Prof. Courte noticed it immediately and changed it back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Woods did not want Hugh O'Conner to win the mock trial. That's why I believe she leaked the details to the witness, Robin Newman.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I get it. If Robin won, Hugh wouldn't be able to confess to Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. Junie was probably trying to keep their friendship from becoming awkward.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">B-A-D Athena... YOU DON'T HAVE ANY EVIDEEEEEEEENCE!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Actually, we might have just the thing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, one of Robin's lines I read when we were reenacting the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Here's a shot of the crime scene. Ironically, it was Prof. Courte who posed as the corpse. Herr Forehead, how did the mock trial participants react to this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Newman was surprised by what Prof. Courte was wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Robin said, "Oh, the green sweat suit."</line>
<line speaker="Newman">S-U-R-E, I might have said that. But... SO WHHAAATTT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, think of it this way, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yeah. Uh, which way, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If I told you that I'd be wearing a blue suit today... ...but then showed up wearing what I've got on now, what would you say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... "Oh, the red suit." Ah! <thought>I-I think I've got it...!</thought> Your Honor! We have evidence proving that Ms. Newman knew the contents of the script. The defense moves to present said evidence to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Ms. Cykes. Present away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This evidence proves that Ms. Newman had prior knowledge of the script's contents.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I don't understand! Why are you just making stuff up? Oh, Athena! Shame on Y-O-U!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's R-I-G-H-T!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-O-R-R-Y!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh my gawd, you two! That was so C-U-T-E!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, thank you! Erhm, but I'm afraid I must award Ms. Cykes a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>When Robin commented about the body in the mock trial... ...it was like she was saying Prof. Courte was wearing the sweat suit she always wore. That's not something you'd expect her to say, unless...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The mock trial's script?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Newman, during the mock trial, you were shown a photo of the victim's body... ...and reportedly, you reacted by saying, "Oh, the green sweat suit."</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Oh, um... Yes, I said that. What's your point?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You seemed to have some issue with the green sweat suit, and I think I know why. The proof is in the script, specifically on the "Things to Prepare" page. "Sweat suit: Victim's outfit will be a red one from the prosecutor course."</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You were surprised because the sweat suit in the photo was green. But, if you didn't know about the script's content... Then that shouldn't have surprised you!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">...N-- Noooooooooooooooooo! I thought we were friends, Athena! How could I have been so bliiiiiiiiind!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In light of her privileged knowledge, I move to declare Ms. Newman a suspect, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Note...? What note?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The professor and Juniper were working together to prepare for the mock trial. But only one copy of the script was made to prevent it from being leaked. But that gets kind of inconvenient, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're not seriously going to suggest...!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Eek! But it's the truth! Prof. Courte did do exactly what you're thinking! She didn't write down any of the proceedings or the truth behind the case... But she did write a note to herself about the props and details about the victim's B-O-D-Y!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Is this really true, Ms. Newman?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">If you don't believe me, send the police over to my house! Tell them to check the pictures on my camera. I thought it might give me an advantage... ...so I took a picture of the note!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........I'd say she's telling the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>...Wait a sec!</thought> If there's a note with details about the body, then that means... ...there are others who could have made the murder look like our client's script!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I believe you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apparently, this case isn't as clear-cut as Prosecutor Blackquill would have us believe. This new revelation blasts a big fat hole in the prosecution's case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-hoooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The battle is still young. And my blade is now fully drawn. Between it and my next witness, your life will be forfeit. So, put away your wooden sword... ...and show me what you are truly capable of if you wish to live!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>You want it? Don't worry, I'm gonna bring it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">......... I already said I want nothing to do with this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How juvenile. It is not a matter of what you want, for you WILL cooperate, Hugh O'Conner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill. Why have you called this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You will recall that they day before the mock trial -- in short, the day of the murder... ...the accused testified that she left for home at around 6:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. My notes here do confirm that fact.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. Our client wasn't at school at the estimated time of death, so she couldn't be--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...I've no intention of saying anything more. Now, if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hold! I am not through with you yet.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. It seems the rogue prosecutor has it out for me.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Leave, and we just might discuss you-know-what.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Ack! N-No, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>One little statement and Mr. Cool loses it? What's that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I changed my mind. ...I'll stay and testify.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Are you sure, Mr. O'Conner?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. The word of a genius is as good as gold. Let's get on with this. Hugh O'Conner. A senior at Themis Legal Academy, lawyer course. How's that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">J-Just fine. Your testimony, then... If you please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're up against the top of the class now. I'd be careful if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know Junie would never lie like that! That pompous schoolboy won't know what hit him!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">To get mentally prepared for the mock trial, I meditated at the archery range till 7:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That is quite enough. Well done, Golden Boy.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The final bell rings at 7:00 PM, at which point, the campus is a desolate place. Now, you will recall the tape recorder. We know the time of the voice recording. It was 7:10 PM, the day before the mock trial. That was the dark hour of this heinous crime.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Do you have any proof of that?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">As its final bell, this school plays a special broadcast when the clock strikes seven. The female voice on the tape appears ten minutes after that broadcast. The killer waited until the school was empty to spring her devious and deadly trap.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, when the witness saw the defendant, that would've been...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. It was five minutes after the voice was captured on tape in the art room. Ergo, we know that the accused was still in the main building, even after the killing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the time of the murder and the time of when the body was moved...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Great... Another inconvenient testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">To get mentally prepared for the mock trial, I meditated at the archery range till 7:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Don't tell me you're going to start pestering me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No need to play dumb with me. All the girls want to know about my private life.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wha--?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will remind the defense this is a court of law, not a pick-up spot.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It seems miss fancy-pants lawyer is smitten with the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">If you must know, I never go a day without meditating. Satisfied now, stalker girl?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's it! You'd better take that--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, whoa, there, tiger. Just take a deep breath and relax.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I'll just continue my testimony now, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">At around, 7:15, I went to the main building before going home. That's when I saw Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You and Prof. Courte were busy preparing for the mock trial together yesterday, right? Was that the last time you saw her?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Yes. I left school at around 6:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...No, wrong. I don't know what she was doing, but Juniper was definitely at school after 7:00 PM. But I suppose neither side can prove one way or the other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. <thought>But if Junie was there, that means she's lying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Truth be told, I only saw her for the briefest of moments.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">We didn't say much as we passed by each other. She seemed her usual self.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The final bell had already rung. They get mad when you stand around chatting. Then again, we're not like you people, talking endlessly in those annoyingly loud voices.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Normally, I'd shout, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" right about now, but I'll take this one for the team.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Anyway, I think that's about all I have to say.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Oh, let me add I never went to the art room. There was no reason for me to be there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The lawyer course I'm in is supervised by Prof. Means. Plus, I'm not a member of Prof. Courte's Art Club, so why would I even go there?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What about art class?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Nice try, but Seniors don't take art class.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, then let me ask you--</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Wait. I just remembered something important!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I scored only 100% on all the art tests I took through Junior year. ...That's it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Riiight... Always happy to indulge in some ego-stroking. Anyway, what to ask next...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please tell the court what you were dong on October 23rd, the day before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. That's an easy one -- nothing in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing at all? You didn't help with the preparations?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You don't get it, do you? I was merely playing the role assigned to me. I left the preparations and the like to others. My job was to be mentally prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie put her heart and soul into getting things ready, while he just sat on his behind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Just to reiterate, I spent most of the 23rd meditating at the archery range. I didn't talk to anyone until the school closed at 7:00 PM. I supposed a few Archery Club members did come and go while I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you didn't talk to anyone? Not a single soul?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's right. I didn't say a word to anyone till the final bell at 7:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see... This is crucial information. Please add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I don't know if you're bluffing, but if you are, you have a pretty good poker face.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I didn't talk to anyone until the final bell. I'd been meditating alone at the archery range."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would an honor student like you ignore the last bell?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I wouldn't say I ignored it. I was simply running a little late.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you remember exactly how late?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You're a stickler for details, lady. But if I had to say, it was maybe about ten, fifteen minutes. If you think that's important, I'll add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was hoping you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The final bell had rung ten, fifteen minutes earlier. No biggie."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually, never mind. I've got all the info I need.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. My, don't we seem confident.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The final bell had rung ten, fifteen minutes earlier. No biggie.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, shame on YOU! Pressing me for no reason...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrr...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, people do run late sometimes. Like you on the day this whole case began.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears we have a culprit in the case of "The Pot Calling The Kettle Black."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Et tu, Your Honor...?! <thought>Hmmm... Now what? Ask another question?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you stop by the art room, or as it's now known, the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can you prove it?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But let me ask you, can YOU prove that I did?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But I will ask how often do you visit there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hardly ever. There's no reason for me to be there, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no reason for you to be there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Is there an echo in here? If something's bothering you, I'll just add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How considerate. Thank you for noticing. Let's add your statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Oh, let me add I never went to the art room. There was no reason for me to be there."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please tell the court what you were dong on October 23rd, the day before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. That's an easy one -- nothing in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing at all? You didn't help with the preparations?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You don't get it, do you? I was merely playing the role assigned to me. I left the preparations and the like to others. My job was to be mentally prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie put her heart and soul into getting things ready, while he just sat on his behind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Just to reiterate, I spent most of the 23rd meditating at the archery range. I didn't talk to anyone until the school closed at 7:00 PM. I supposed a few Archery Club members did come and go while I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you didn't talk to anyone? Not a single soul?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's right. I didn't say a word to anyone till the final bell at 7:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see... This is crucial information. Please add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I don't know if you're bluffing, but if you are, you have a pretty good poker face.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I didn't talk to anyone until the final bell. I'd been meditating alone at the archery range."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually, never mind. I've got all the info I need.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. My, don't we seem confident.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I didn't talk to anyone until the final bell. I'd been meditating alone at the archery range.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Well, I did exchange a few greetings. But what does that matter?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So, he didn't have any conversations? The entire day? Me thinks that claim needs a little more scrutiny. But what should I do? Is there anything I should ask about in more detail?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you stop by the art room, or as it's now known, the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can you prove it?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But let me ask you, can YOU prove that I did?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But I will ask how often do you visit there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hardly ever. There's no reason for me to be there, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no reason for you to be there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Is there an echo in here? If something's bothering you, I'll just add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How considerate. Thank you for noticing. Let's add your statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Oh, let me add I never went to the art room. There was no reason for me to be there."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would an honor student like you ignore the last bell?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I wouldn't say I ignored it. I was simply running a little late.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you remember exactly how late?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You're a stickler for details, lady. But if I had to say, it was maybe about ten, fifteen minutes. If you think that's important, I'll add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was hoping you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The final bell had rung ten, fifteen minutes earlier. No biggie."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Actually, never mind. I've got all the info I need.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. My, don't we seem confident.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's it. Anything else you'd like to ask?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I expected as much. So, go ahead, ask away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm, Mr. O'Conner, I want to ask you...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you stop by the art room, or as it's now known, the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">No, I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can you prove it?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But let me ask you, can YOU prove that I did?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As much as I'd like to say I could, I can't. But I will ask how often do you visit there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hardly ever. There's no reason for me to be there, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no reason for you to be there?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Is there an echo in here? If something's bothering you, I'll just add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How considerate. Thank you for noticing. Let's add your statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Oh, let me add I never went to the art room. There was no reason for me to be there."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would an honor student like you ignore the last bell?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I wouldn't say I ignored it. I was simply running a little late.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you remember exactly how late?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You're a stickler for details, lady. But if I had to say, it was maybe about ten, fifteen minutes. If you think that's important, I'll add it to my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was hoping you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The final bell had rung ten, fifteen minutes earlier. No biggie."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please tell the court what you were dong on October 23rd, the day before the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. That's an easy one -- nothing in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing at all? You didn't help with the preparations?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">You don't get it, do you? I was merely playing the role assigned to me. I left the preparations and the like to others. My job was to be mentally prepared.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie put her heart and soul into getting things ready, while he just sat on his behind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Just to reiterate, I spent most of the 23rd meditating at the archery range. I didn't talk to anyone until the school closed at 7:00 PM. I supposed a few Archery Club members did come and go while I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you didn't talk to anyone? Not a single soul?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's right. I didn't say a word to anyone till the final bell at 7:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see... This is crucial information. Please add it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I don't know if you're bluffing, but if you are, you have a pretty good poker face.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I didn't talk to anyone until the final bell. I'd been meditating alone at the archery range."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, is that the confidence and composure that comes from being a genius?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, it doesn't matter who's on the stand. Our job is still the same.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sure, but if Junie was really still at school after 6:00 PM... Ugh. I didn't spot any inconsistencies in Hugh's testimony, either. What am I supposed to do now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, you didn't talk to anybody on October 23rd? Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I already told you, my word is as good as gold.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, then how do you explain this? And don't spare any details.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Sorry, never seen that before.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is the victim's planner. She recorded all of her plans in great detail. Take a look at this page here. It reads, "23rd - Meet with Hugh" and "Important." Don't you find that... interesting?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Wha-?! Where'd you get that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The keyword here is "important." You say you were at the archery range all day. But you also said a few students came and went while you were there. That doesn't sound like a great place for an important talk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the entire campus was buzzing with activity before the mock trial. Where could they have possibly had a private conversation?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought about that, too. But the situation changes after the last bell.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this, now?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The witness stayed after the last bell... ...in order to have a private talk with the victim. Am I right, Mr. O'Conner?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">This is insane!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I don't have any direct evidence. However, the witness was meditating until after the last bell. And he attempted to conceal his private meeting with the victim!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. First Robin, now me? Who are you going to accuse next? You're just another unscrupulous attorney looking to get ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't let him get to you. He's definitely hiding something. I mean, he was supposed to meet with the victim around her estimated time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I had my suspicions about Robin, but... ...Hugh seems just as guilty! These three are the only possible suspects, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. O'Conner, answer me this! Did you meet with Prof. Courte that day?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">..................... Sorry, Mr. Jailbird Prosecutor. I don't mean to steal your thunder, but I've something to say.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If it will save me some trouble, then by all means, speak away.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">If you would recall, Ms. Cykes, the voice on the tape recorder was female. Knowing that, I'd like you to explain how I could possibly be a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh... <thought>He has a point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph, impressive. Golden Boy here does shine gold, indeed. Care to take the reins? You're more than capable of prosecuting this case.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Sorry, but I'm studying to be a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What a pity. To think such genius is to be wasted on mere lawyering. At last, your moment is here, Cykes-dono. Time to refute Golden Boy's statement... ...and prove that you're the young prodigy worthy of the badge on your lapel!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uuuurgh! <thought>Could he lay any more pressure on...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The voice is unmistakably female, so there's no point in arguing about that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... You're right. In which case...! <thought>To whom does the voice on the tape really belong to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The voice on the tape is that of this witness!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">But I'm a man with a man's voice. All you have to do is open your eyes and ears.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Agh... But th-that's different...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See, Your Honor, I have him squirming on the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but it would have been nice if it had been due to a fact relevant to your rebuttal.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arghh! <thought>Now I'M the one squirming at my stand... The voice is definitely female. That much we know. In that case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the voice is female, it must belong to our client Juniper Woods!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, now. Finally seen the light, have we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">So, you're going to explain how Juniper is guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait... Oh, oops! Your Honor, let's pretend I never said that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How about you at least pretend to take ownership of your statements.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uuugh! <thought>If it wasn't Junie's voice, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The voice on the tape belongs to the victim. That's the only thing that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... <thought>Yeah, that is a problem.</thought> You're a goner... You're a goner... You're a goner...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're a goner... You a goner... Hew a corner... Hue o conner? ...Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, Athena, you're scaring me here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">YOU'RE scared? I'm terrified for even coming up with this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With what?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Blackquill! You wanted to know if I am worthy of my badge. Well, I'm about to show you why, despite my age, I'm able to proudly wear this at all!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh? Then can I take it you won't be changing your argument? Still, it stands that it's a bit odd for the victim to be the one yelling, "You're a goner!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I agree, if that's what the victim was saying. But it's not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I assume you have something to back up your assertion, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Not exactly... But you don't have to add fuel to his fire, Your Honor!</thought> If it is indeed Prof. Courte's voice on the tape, then she was shouting because she was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"You're a goner!" was a threat directed at the witness!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">And what possible reason would she have to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, well, she was at that rebellious age. You know how students can be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim was neither a student nor at a rebellious age. She was a professor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo! <thought>How could I forget such a basic fact?! You're a goner... You a goner... Hew a corner... Wait! Maybe...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">"You're a goner" was a threat the witness shouted at the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">As has been mentioned countless times, the voice in the recording is female. How the devil do you reckon it belongs to the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right, heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm confused how you could be confused about that, so without further ado, a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No fair! <thought>Two against one! You're a goner... You a goner... Hew a corner... Wait! Maybe...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I would like to call one basic fact into question. Is that shout on the tape really saying, "You're a goner!"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What are you up to now, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Courte's planner says she was supposed to meet with the witness for an important talk. Perhaps our witness, despite being a genius, had done something wrong... And this made Prof. Courte get angry with him during their private meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't see how this changes what we heard on the tape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, if you want to see how it changes things ...then let's try a little experiment. Your Honor, I want you to tell at the witness as if you're mad at him. But... and this important... use his full name!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Okay! Let's see, um... Hugh O'Conner!!!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. What did I do to deserve that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, like that! Now try again, but faster!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hugh Aconner!!! ...Hm? Hue... a coner? Hew... o coner? You... a coner? W-Wait a second! ...No, no, no, this can't be.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Now that you mention it...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>You can do this, Athena! Just give the old guy one more little push...!</thought> The voice on the tape recorder never was "You're a goner!" That's only what we thought we heard, when in fact, it was the witness getting yelled at! The court will note that this is different from the selective hearing men are so good at!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think you're right, but what was that last part again?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Never mind. The important thing is that the voice that was recorded isn't our client's. And since it was the victim scolding the witness, he must now join the list of suspects!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Hrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>E-Evidence? What's he going to pull out now?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Feast your eyes on this photo, and let me see that insolent look vanish from within them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see here... Oh, it's a picture of the defendant and the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The photograph shows professor and student preparing for the mock trial together.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, was this taken in the art room -- the room where the murder occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed it was. But the revelations do not end there. Do you see the clock on the wall? It reads 7:05, a mere five minutes before the voice was recorded on the tape.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WH-WHAAAAAAT!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The accused brutally stabbed the victim to death five minutes after this photo was taken.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems the defendant's culpability in this crime is quite obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie was with Prof. Courte just five minutes before she was murdered? What now? Nothing I say can change that fact...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Understand now? You can believe in your client all wish, but try as you might... ...such misplaced faith will inevitably be cut down before the cruel, steely blade of truth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ngaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Listen, missy. The person you'd like to save more than anyone else in the world? I'd be willing to wager that your defense isn't what they desire.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But...! I became a lawyer so I could--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You still fail to understand? After so much pain and defeat? The courts are not the play yards of little children dressed as lawyers. So before you break your back in failure... ...run along home and grow up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>If he thinks I'm giving up now, he's got another thing coming! I have to find my inner strength if I ever hope to save him. But I can't think of any way to strike back. The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles? That's impossible! How could I smile under these circumstances, even if I forced it?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is badder than bad! Who knew Blackquill had that one waiting in the wings! Why didn't that Twisted Samurai just present it at the beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wait, maybe this was his real plan? Was he just trying to show me how weak and powerless I am?! Maybe he's right, because I really haven't got a clue! Who's the real killer? Who murdered Prof. Constance Courte?</thought> Robin Newman, a girl who had been forced to live a lie as a guy? Or was it Hugh O'Conner, the honor student who had met with Prof. Courte?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There seems to be little reason to debate the defendant's guilt any longer. The time for a verdict has come.</line>
<line speaker="???">Newman:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's the meaning of this? You can't interrupt a judge about to hand down a--</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Tee hee hee. Maybe, but false verdicts are a N-O N-O!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha-?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Newman, please explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Juniper's not the killer. I know because... because I know who the real killer is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You do? You know who the real killer is? <thought>What is she up to now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yup! I know because the real killer is... M-E, me! Tee, hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh......... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">IT WAS ME! I DID IT ALL ALONE. JUST MEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I don't get it. Why is SHE confessing?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ms. Newman WAS witnessed near the stage. There's even a related photo of her. The more I think about it, the more suspicious she seems...</line>
<line speaker="Newman">ROBIN NEWMAN ISN'T THE KIND OF GUY WHO PINS THE BLAME ON FRIENDS... ...JUST SO HE CAN WALK FREEEEEEEEEE!!! GET IT OVER WITH! DECLARE ME GUILTY ALREADYYYYYYYYY!</line>
<line speaker="???">Woods:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Juniper! Wh-What are you doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thank you for all you've done, Thena. But you'll have to forgive me. I can't let my friends take the blame any longer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie! No! Don't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hugh and Robin have done nothing wrong. They have absolutely no connection to this case. The real killer is... is me. I alone am responsible for the entire crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I'm afraid it is true. Forgive me, Thena.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! Will somebody please explain what's going on here?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........Hmph. I see right through your cheap ploy. School rules state that a prior conviction terminates one's eligibility to graduate. A guilty verdict here would make whatever dreams one had go up in a puff of smoke.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I wasn't aware...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Even meek little mice will fight when cornered. A pitiful spectacle, I might add. These vermin are trying to protect each other now that they've nowhere else to run.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Protect each other? Wait... So, was Robin just trying to protect Junie, too? If so, then the real killer is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">O'Conner:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Uh-oh, now it's Hugh's turn...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What... What is wrong with kids these days?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I know what just crossed your mind, Ms. Cykes. You think I'm the killer, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, he really is a genius. He even knows what you're thinking.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I think it's about time I told you the truth. And I'll even get right to the point. It was me. I did it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait............ WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now both potential suspects are claiming to be the real killer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! I... I am so confused right now...!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">If you still have doubts, how about I detail my murder plot? It's absolute genius.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough of this nonsense! This is a court of law, not the set of some high-school drama!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see I have no choice. I'm afraid I'll have to--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hoy! Wait, Your Baldness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm sorry, Prosecutor Blackquill, but I'm in no position to hand down a verdict just yet. I am hoping that the defense and prosecution can come up with some airtight evidence. That is why I am giving you both the rest of the day to continue investigating this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Pinch me, I think I'm dreaming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Fine. Do as you wish!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This brings today's proceedings to a close. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? And how would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">J-Just look at it! It's one huge contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. The defense is simply making another baseless assertion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! <thought>Crash and burn!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All that says to me is you're completely wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aaaaahhh! <thought>I guess that won't fly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've been doing this for far too long to be fooled by such nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh! <thought>And I really tried hard that time, too.</thought> Your Honor, can I at least get credit for trying?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I hereby award Ms. Cykes the court's "Wasted Effort" award.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Where's the love?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mind letting your slightly senior partner help out a little now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...If you insist. <thought>Actually, I could really use the help.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I find this statement suspicious. You should find the answer if you take a good look at the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Thanks, Apollo! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could get used this [sic] more humble version of you, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You okay, Athena? You can tell me if something's bothering you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No, I'm totally fine! <thought>Actually, I'm not anywhere near fine.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The thing with cross-examinations is the answer you need isn't always obvious. You have to dig deep to find clues hidden in the testimony. Really wrestle with it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so it's like grabbing a bull by the horns and wrestling it to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, try not to take it so literally. Just stick with pressing the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Thanks, Apollo! <thought>Okay, let's give it a try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Newman, this emotion is inconsistent with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">What are you talking about?! It's not truuuue!!! My only emotion is testosterone-fueled stubbornessssssss!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! <thought>I wouldn't really call that an emotion!</thought> Wonder where I went wrong? Well, better try that again!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Bring it on! A million times or a billion!!! I DON'T CAAAAAARE!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The source of Mr. Newman's anger... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Nope! You're way off! WAAAY OFFFFFF!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! <thought>No good, huh?</thought> I'm trying to listen carefully, but all his shouting -- it's...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'd better finish this off quick before you rupture an eardrum.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No worries! I'm gonna nail it next time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need prolong this trial any further. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Juniper Woods...</line>
</xml>