<xml>
<title>Turnabout Succession</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This rough sketch is only half-hidden by the oil painting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll never understand artists.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Still, it's impressive. I wouldn't you could hide such a dark sketch under a little paint.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it is called "oil paint" for a reason. I bet it's pretty oily. The paint I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm still waiting for you to get to your point.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So! You're... Vera, right? I'm Trucy! Trucy Wright! That's "Wright" with a "W"! Uh, but not "write", right?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um! We're... on your side! You can tell us anything! ...Please?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Good morning...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>She... She speaks!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm, not bad, not bad. But I think you'd do better with a little smile, you know? You're so pretty! You need to sell yourself, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! Let's... take it easy for starters.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Thank you for taking my case...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okaaaaay... Well, that's a start, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There she goes with the nail polish again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's great, really! It's so cultured!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">............ ...Want to try...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooooh! Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* Girls... <thought>The victim, Drew Misham, was a forger. And a stolen painting was found in his studio. A life of crime, really... ...And maybe one that led to his death.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we will now... er... *cough* Begin the, er, trial of... Vuh... Vuh... Vuh... Vera Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Is the judge OK? His voice is all raspy, and he's looking around all nervous-like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Erm... ahem. The repercussions of today's trial will, most likely, be felt for a long time. ...And may, indeed, alter our legal system forever.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Today is a test of the Jurist System... ...and the first step toward a new order in our courts.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy's secret mission!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The jurists will function like a jury. It is hoped their inclusion will help the courts to better reflect the people's will.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why... aren't there any jurists in the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Three closed-circuit cameras watch this courtroom at all times. The jurists have access to everything that transpires. Jurists! Judge well, and judge cool.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now see here, Prosecutor Gavin! I-I was going to say that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, my apologies, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Jurists! Today, er... Judge today's trial "coolly", if you would be so kind!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The jurists are unbound by the letter of the law. They don't affect the trial with evidence... but by their "feelings". And we're about to find out just what effect they're going to have.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Prosecutor Gavin. The details of the case, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim is the painter Drew Misham. He was killed in his own studio. His coffee... was poisoned. By whom, you ask? By none other than the defendant, Vera Misham.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There wasn't any poison in the coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung... Someone has been doing their homework! Indeed. Poison was not present in the coffee... but on the mug itself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The mug...? Ah, residue was found on the rim, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The autopsy report describes the manner of our victim's death.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to this report... ...the victim's death was caused by "atroquinine" poisoning.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A chemical compound that does not occur naturally. Lethal dosage is a mere 0.002mg. A touch of atroquinine in the body... ...is the touch of the Reaper's scythe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Prosecutor Gavin. You may present your witness.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I have for you today a simple man, for a simple case. ...A man who witnessed the murder in its entirety.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That journalist, no doubt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The witness will state his name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah! Right! Well, for starters, my name's Spark Brushel! My job is... a lone observer of the world!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words, a freelance journalist, right?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ahem! If you don't mind, I'd like to state something here for the record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I dislike conclusions, specifically, the jumping to aspect of conclusions. "Preconceptions Make Park Sandbox of Endless Desert Waste..." end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, you are a journalist. You said so yourself yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Well, that's true, yes. But you must understand, I stand before you today a man with a dream! I'm offering you my testimony in exchange for exclusive rights to the story! "Scoop Turns Mr. Brushel Into THAT Mr. Brushel!" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Let's hear your testimony then, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A "simple case", eh, Gavin? For me, the jury... is still out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I visited the studio around 9:00 that night to do the interview.The first outsider to enter the atelier! "Journalistic History Made", end quote!His daughter brought us coffee right after we started.And you know what happened next. "Star Falls!" end quote.No one else entered the room besides her the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does sound like a simple case. Unless... you were the one who poisoned him!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Wh-Wh-Wh-Whatareyousaying!? Judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Need I remind you, the cameras are rolling today. I felt the need to be a bit dramatic.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You didn't do it, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">M-M-M-M-Medoathinglikethat!? Come on! That's like... "Newsmaker Making the News", end quote. Or even "Contemporary Witch-Hunt", end quote! I know! "Wild Accusations Rock Courtroom", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha. Rock, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prosecutor Gavin sure looks like he's having fun.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm so happy for him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice, your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I visited the studio around 9:00 that night to do the interview.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">9:00 at night? Isn't that a little late for an interview?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">If the great painter Drew Misham says, "come at 9:00"... ...believe you me, I go at 9:00! The first, and as it turned out, last interview with such a prolific painter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Can you tell us what it was like when you arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The first outsider to enter the atelier! "Journalistic History Made", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were the first reporter ever in "Drew Studio"?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Posterity will look back on that night as a turning point in journalistic history! "A Basically Insignificant Step For All Mankind... But A Giant Step For That Brushel Guy", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If no one on the outside ever had access to the studio... ...then it would serve to reason that the deed was done by an "insider".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...By which he means Vera did it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, how did this epoch-making interview go?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">His daughter brought us coffee right after we started.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Would you mind being a little more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oooh wee, let me tell you, I enjoy a cuppa. In fact, it all began when I was in third grade, no wait, fourth grade--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not what I meant!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe I know what Herr Forehead is driving at. This coffee the victim was served... Did anyone other than the victim touch it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right! That! <thought>That's what I was going to say, really.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, now, if you've got a question to ask, you'd best straight up ask it! That's what I tell all the new recruits. Several times, if necessary. "Write for a grade schooler", that's my motto. Which isn't to say I can only write grade school-level stuff, mind you--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Who touched the coffee!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Dunno. I was in the back, looking at the studio's equipment when she served it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">And you know what happened next. "Star Falls!" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this about a star falling?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Star Falls!" huh... It's like an old telegram! "Send Money, Over".</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Zowie! You don't know? That's like a journalism code word. An important personage passes away... a star falls. Get it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But there's no gravity in space, is there? I wouldn't think stars could fall, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Does this matter?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hoo boy! This is good stuff, good stuff! How about "Star Breaks"... Nah... lacks punch. I know, I know! "Star Dies". Nah... lacks imagination. Of course, you could go with "Drew Dies". Straight, to the point. I like it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think we need to hear about something a little more substantial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about when Mr. Misham passed away...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hoo boy, what a scene that was! He puts his coffee mug down with a crash, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, and then?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Then the cold finger of Death touches his spine! Life's flame sputters and fails! So cold was that touch, he could do naught but tremble uncontrollably! ...Actually "life's flame" is a little tired. "Life's river froze over"... Yes! That's a go.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think he's starting his article already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you describe that a little more simply?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, as you can imagine, I was pretty surprised. He hit the floor, as they say. "Artist's Seizure Is Final Performance", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Atroquinine paralyzes the central nervous system. The body arches back like a bow, the limbs tremble, the throat burns--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's quite enough of that! Some of us want to be able to sleep tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yeah? Well I want details, lots of juicy details!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For that you can listen to our last year's hit single. "Atroquinine, My Love", by the Gavinners. Available at all major music outlets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The point here is that the victim died of atroquinine poisoning. Well, Mr. Justice? How did you find that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, as an account of the moment of the victim's death, I'd say it's very important. ...Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court requests the witness add this account to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You'd think the moment of Mr. Misham's death would be important... ...But Mr. Brushel's story really didn't tell us anything we didn't already know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you drank the coffee that Vera served you, too?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course. "When someone serves you coffee, you drink it"... That's what my old boss always used to say. Never did get what he meant by it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you're still alive, which is to say, you didn't die.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course not! "No Point Falling Before You're A Star", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's not exactly what I was getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What were you getting at, then? You know the poison was on the rim, not in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes! There were two cups on the tray she brought. And one of the cups had Drew's signature painted on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. No chance the guest would take that one by mistake, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Was that testimony important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're talking about the coffee the witness drank. I'd say that is important!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please add that to your testimony, Mr. Brushel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Brushel drank the coffee, too... Doesn't look like this is going to lead to much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say Mr. Misham had the coffee, too. But did you actually see him "drink" the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course! "He Who Sees It Wins, But He Who Says It Wins Bigger", end quote. I live in a man-sees-dog-eat-dog-and-writes-about-it world. Yet...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Yet"?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I guess I can't say I "saw" him drink it, really. He had one so-called "sip", if that. "Man Puts Lips To Mug, Drinks?" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. That poison is quite virulent, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">My stomach did a so-called "somersault". Since I'd gulped down that coffee without so much as a second glance at it. Wait, maybe something's there! Some kind of so-called "trick"! Anyone want to venture a guess? For the record?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does this guy have a pause button?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Did you find that testimony valuable?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim drank his coffee, then immediately fell over?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes. You can go to press with that one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! This is a vital piece of information! Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will add this to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Vital! Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The coffee Mr. Misham drank... That has to be important somehow... ...Nah.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Those spasms... That was definitely death by poison.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say it was "definitely death by poison"... How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey, look, I'm a journalist. I've seen a lot of things. And I've had more than my share of experiences with so-called "poisonings". "Man Eats Fishy Fish, Goes Bye-Bye"... end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Food poisoning doesn't count. Hmm. Should I get him to talk about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's just go with what we have for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you drank the coffee that Vera served you, too?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course. "When someone serves you coffee, you drink it"... That's what my old boss always used to say. Never did get what he meant by it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you're still alive, which is to say, you didn't die.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course not! "No Point Falling Before You're A Star", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's not exactly what I was getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What were you getting at, then? You know the poison was on the rim, not in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes! There were two cups on the tray she brought. And one of the cups had Drew's signature painted on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. No chance the guest would take that one by mistake, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Was that testimony important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're talking about the coffee the witness drank. I'd say that is important!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please add that to your testimony, Mr. Brushel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Brushel drank the coffee, too... Doesn't look like this is going to lead to much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say Mr. Misham had the coffee, too. But did you actually see him "drink" the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course! "He Who Sees It Wins, But He Who Says It Wins Bigger", end quote. I live in a man-sees-dog-eat-dog-and-writes-about-it world. Yet...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Yet"?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I guess I can't say I "saw" him drink it, really. He had one so-called "sip", if that. "Man Puts Lips To mug, Drinks?" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. That poison is quite virulent, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">My stomach did a so-called "somersault". Since I'd gulped down that coffee without so much as a second glance at it. Wait, maybe something's there! Some kind of so-called "trick"! Anyone want to venture a guess? For the record?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does this guy have a pause button?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Did you find that testimony valuable?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim drank his coffee, then immediately fell over?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes. You can go to press with that one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! This is a vital piece of information! Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will add this to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Vital! Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The coffee Mr. Misham drank... That has to be important somehow... ...Nah.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I drank the coffee, too, but I'm not dead yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're sure you drank the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes, quite. I gulped it down, felt that sweet scorch in my throat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you say the victim took one sip and fell over. ...And you still kept drinking?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course! "Drink your coffee when it's hot, never when it's not". That's what my old boss used to always say. Never really knew what he meant by it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. Should I get him to talk about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's just go with what we have for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about when Mr. Misham passed away...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hoo boy, what a scene that was! He puts his coffee mug down with a crash, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, and then?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Then the cold finger of Death touches his spine! Life's flame sputters and fails! So cold was that touch, he could do naught but tremble uncontrollably! ...Actually "life's flame" is a little tired. "Life's river froze over"... Yes! That's a go.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think he's starting his article already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you describe that a little more simply?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, as you can imagine, I was pretty surprised. He hit the floor, as they say. "Artist's Seizure Is Final Performance", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Atroquinine paralyzes the central nervous system. The body arches back like a bow, the limbs tremble, the throat burns--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's quite enough of that! Some of us want to be able to sleep tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yeah? Well I want details, lots of juicy details!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For that you can listen to our last year's hit single. "Atroquinine, My Love", by the Gavinners. Available at all major music outlets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The point here is that the victim died of atroquinine poisoning. Well, Mr. Justice? How did you find that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, as an account of the moment of the victim's death, I'd say it's very important. ...Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court requests the witness add this account to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You'd think the moment of Mr. Misham's death would be important... ...But Mr. Brushel's story really didn't tell us anything we didn't already know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say Mr. Misham had the coffee, too. But did you actually see him "drink" the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course! "He Who Sees It Wins, But He Who Says It Wins Bigger", end quote. I live in a man-sees-dog-eat-dog-and-writes-about-it world. Yet...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Yet"?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I guess I can't say I "saw" him drink it, really. He had one so-called "sip", if that. "Man Puts Lips To mug, Drinks?" end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. That poison is quite virulent, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">My stomach did a so-called "somersault". Since I'd gulped down that coffee without so much as a second glance at it. Wait, maybe something's there! Some kind of so-called "trick"! Anyone want to venture a guess? For the record?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does this guy have a pause button?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Did you find that testimony valuable?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim drank his coffee, then immediately fell over?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes. You can go to press with that one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! This is a vital piece of information! Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will add this to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Vital! Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The coffee Mr. Misham drank... That has to be important somehow... ...Nah.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">He had one sip, if that. The next moment, he was on the floor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he either took a sip, or he didn't, and then fell over?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes! Indubitably! Just like that! Wham bam!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Mr. Misham drank the coffee, and fell over immediately... Hmm. I think Brushel's telling the truth, too. Hmm. Should I get him to talk about something else?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's no real need to change the testimony. The problem with the testimony is already pretty obvious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about when Mr. Misham passed away...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hoo boy, what a scene that was! He puts his coffee mug down with a crash, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, and then?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Then the cold finger of Death touches his spine! Life's flame sputters and fails! So cold was that touch, he could do naught but tremble uncontrollably! ...Actually "life's flame" is a little tired. "Life's river froze over"... Yes! That's a go.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think he's starting his article already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you describe that a little more simply?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, as you can imagine, I was pretty surprised. He hit the floor, as they say. "Artist's Seizure Is Final Performance", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Atroquinine paralyzes the central nervous system. The body arches back like a bow, the limbs tremble, the throat burns--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's quite enough of that! Some of us want to be able to sleep tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yeah? Well I want details, lots of juicy details!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For that you can listen to our last year's hit single. "Atroquinine, My Love", by the Gavinners. Available at all major music outlets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The point here is that the victim died of atroquinine poisoning. Well, Mr. Justice? How did you find that testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, as an account of the moment of the victim's death, I'd say it's very important. ...Please add it to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court requests the witness add this account to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You'd think the moment of Mr. Misham's death would be important... ...But Mr. Brushel's story really didn't tell us anything we didn't already know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you drank the coffee that Vera served you, too?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course. "When someone serves you coffee, you drink it"... That's what my old boss always used to say. Never did get what he meant by it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you're still alive, which is to say, you didn't die.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course not! "No Point Falling Before You're A Star", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's not exactly what I was getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What were you getting at, then? You know the poison was on the rim, not in the coffee.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh yes, yes! There were two cups on the tray she brought. And one of the cups had Drew's signature painted on the side.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm. No chance the guest would take that one by mistake, I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Was that testimony important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're talking about the coffee the witness drank. I'd say that is important!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please add that to your testimony, Mr. Brushel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So Brushel drank the coffee, too... Doesn't look like this is going to lead to much...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">No one else entered the room besides her the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you say that for sure?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">For sure? Sure! I'm sure. Drew Studio isn't a big place, kiddo. I'd know it if someone else had come in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if they had been hiding in there from before!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Even if someone had been hiding in the studio... ...they hardly could have poisoned that mug without anyone noticing.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You think I, Spark Brushel, would miss something as obvious as that? Nooooo way.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He sure makes it sound exciting. I guess that's his job.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's only one moment we need to focus on, really.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...The moment when Drew Misham died?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. There has to be something there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know what I have a problem with? A particular property of the poison used, atroquinine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Prosecutor Gavin was quite clear about the poison. A lethal dosage of 0.002mg paralyzes the central nervous system. If you drank that, even you, Mr. Justice, would be reduced to a quivering pile...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why are you using me as an example!?</thought> Unfortunately, we weren't told everything. There was a vital omission in Prosecutor Gavin's information!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An omission?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Atroquinine is as virulent as he says. But death doesn't come upon ingestion, not immediately. That's because atroquinine is slow-acting!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Slow-acting!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Whatwhatwhatwhat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to one forensic scientist...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's one of the most virulent poisons, but is absorbed into the body astonishingly slowly. It takes at least 15 minutes from the time of ingestion for adverse effects to show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If we suppose that the moment Mr. Misham sipped the coffee was when he sealed his fate... ...then he would still have had time left to enjoy his last cup of joe!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!! What's the meaning of this!? If what the defense says is correct... ...why, that contradicts the entire testimony we've just heard!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Mr. Brushel? Anything to say... on the record!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Slow-acting. S-L-O-W A-C-T... It was virulent, alright. Even then, it had already begun digging its claws into the journalist.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...He's working on his scoop.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It's "Brushel", ja? Herr Brushel... let's take a trip back down memory lane.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did the victim really die the instant he took a sip? Think it over. This is vital.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You know what I think? I think that was... "A Not-So-Subliminal Suggestion"... end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I admit, it does cause a problem if he died when you say he died. ...I would be forced to say auf Wiedersehen to my simple case. And you would be forced to say farewell to your article.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You can't write a story based on conjecture, can you? And as the case drags on, other reporters will pick up the scent. ...And you'll be forced to kiss your exclusive scoop goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Scoop... Scoop... .....................! Look, wait. Just wait a second. Just one second.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We're waiting, we're waiting! Out with it!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I think I just recalled a so-called "important detail"! "A Revival of Recollection", end quote! "A Story's Survival", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Attorney Utterly Confused", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Actually, I did notice something when I visited the studio. I'd heard of poison that "takes its sweet time", see!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...But not what I've been saying for the last few minutes, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Brushel! Are you saying you noticed something that explains what happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You bet I am! The "Antidote For A Poisonous Contradiction", end quote, you might say!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or "I Still Have No Idea What You're Talking About", end quote, I might say.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I figured it out, but only after an in-depth interview! See, thanks to my journalism skills, I know who poisoned that coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">As far as I can tell, the witness is standing by his testimony. ...That Mr. Misham died the instant after he drank.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course I'm standing by my testimony! ...And my dream of exclusive rights to this story!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ach. I suppose it was too much to hope for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course he wouldn't choose a simple case, not him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Him"...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Phoenix Wright, who else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung, Herr Brushel! Report for us, if you would. What is it that you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is a critical trial of the Jurist System. I'm afraid no room for doubt is permissible. You will testify to the court about what you noticed!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">When I arrived at the studio, Mr. Misham was at his desk.He seemed to be writing a letter... but he quickly sealed the envelope.I thought nothing of it at the time, of course.Now that I think about it, what if he was writing a suicide note!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A suicide note?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yes... he had this look on his face. "Man's Face Inscrutable As A Quadratic Equation", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Suicide? Poor Mr. Misham... But that means Vera's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would someone commit suicide in the middle of an interview?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, you may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">When I arrived at the studio, Mr. Misham was at his desk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was there anyone at the studio other than Mr. Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, his daughter Vera, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was anyone besides Mr. Misham and Vera present?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Not a single one. Not a cat, not a rat, not even a mouse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The only person who didn't belong to that studio there... ...was you, wasn't it, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah. Ah! I know what you're doing! I know your game! "Attorney Uses Classic Ramsden Phenomenon Ploy", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If you intend to suggest that this reporter is a suspect... ...I'm sure you also intend to present evidence supporting that assertion, correct? In the meantime, let's move along, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">He seemed to be writing a letter... but he quickly sealed the envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he put the letter away when he saw you?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Early Reporter Gets Worm", end quote. ...That's my secret!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It's the night of the interview. I arrive 15 minutes ahead of schedule! The handle turns, the door opens, and I barge in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure that's OK to do? I mean, isn't that unlawful entry, really?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Mr. Misham sure seemed to think so! You shoulda seen him! He crammed his letter into that yellow envelope as fast as he could. I know a secret when I spot one, and that was one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does seem significant. Well, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder... It does have the ring of something important...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense finds this testimony vital, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please add it to the testimony then.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey, why not? My "account" comes free of charge!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't see what, though. Nothing seemed unusual.</thought> ...It won't be necessary to add this to the testimony, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he put the letter away when he saw you?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Early Reporter Gets Worm", end quote. ...That's my secret!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It's the night of the interview. I arrive 15 minutes ahead of schedule! The handle turns, the door opens, and I barge in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure that's OK to do? I mean, isn't that unlawful entry, really?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Mr. Misham sure seemed to think so! You shoulda seen him! He crammed his letter into that yellow envelope as fast as he could. I know a secret when I spot one, and that was one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you could tell us a bit more about this envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I thought nothing of it at the time, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't think anything might be wrong at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey, when I go in for an interview, that's what I'm there to do. "Interviewer Finds Looking More Effective Than Caring", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what about now? Thinking back on it, did you sense anything strange in Mr. Misham's behavior?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, yeah, that's why I'm telling you all this to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Now that I think about it, what if he was writing a suicide note!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A "suicide note"...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, yeah, don't quote me or anything. I'm just saying it's a possibility, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you didn't actually check the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Of course not! It was sealed! "Contents Of Can Unknown Until Can Is Opened", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You can always check the label.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It was a yellow envelope. ...I heard it was left at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you saw him seal this yellow envelope with the letter?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey, don't look at me like that! I saw what I saw.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! You think this might be...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Our big break. Yeah. <thought>What I need is to show some decisive evidence now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think Mr. Misham was writing a suicide note?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If he was, that would solve the case in a jiffy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It kind of makes me wonder about that letter...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As it just so happens, there was a single letter in a desk drawer at the scene. In a red envelope!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was a yellow envelope found at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Unfortunately no. But, Herr Forehead... ...it's easy to mistake the color of an envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess. But not this envelope. You see, it was postmarked already. Seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...I can explain that. Drew, right, he wanted to get that letter in an envelope, pronto! Get it out of sight of my beady eyes, right? So he grabbed the nearest envelope and crammed away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And what about the whole red and yellow envelope contradiction, chump!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Have you anything to say to the witness's claim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"That night, the victim put a letter he had been writing in a red envelope"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's entirely possible!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But Apollo! We checked the contents of that envelope yesterday, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... You're right! <thought>Gah! The answer was clear if I'd only given it a little thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, I like your expression. So full of confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's simple, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...As it just so happens, the defense team investigated the contents of this envelope! With, erm, the assistance of a forensic scientist.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Note that this letter is addressed to "Drew Misham".</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would he address a letter to himself? Let alone send a suicide note to himself!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...... I... I've been scooped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Mr. Brushel! Can you explain this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh, my, my, my. How could I have forgotten? I suppose this happens to the best of us! "Reporter Gets Old, Forgets Lots", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm still waiting for an explanation, Mr. Brushel!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, that's the thing, see. After he put his letter in that envelope... ...Mr. Misham sat there searching his desk drawer for something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His desk drawer...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yes! A stamp! A so-called "Postage Stamp", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A stamp? Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, to mail his letter, what else? And then, why yes, I think I saw him put it in his letter box. Yes, it was a yellow envelope, and he put it in that box!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, apparently, this yellow letter has nothing to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh, how I wish it did! Just think if that were a suicide note... What a story! "Star Writes Suicide Note In Front Of Reporter, Falls", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. As I was saying, that has nothing to do with this case! That said.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It makes me wonder about the contents of that red envelope. $100,000 is quite a good deal of money!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So this was from seven years ago, ja...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...! So, am I finished? Here, I mean. Am I finished here? I was thinking of, you know, going home, to start writing...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, I hate to state what should be pretty obvious to anyone... ...but when you catch the scent of a story... ...you make that... er, rather unique face.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ack! C-C'mon! "Attorney Has Active Imagination, Little Else", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even I noticed something, and my eyes aren't what they used to be. You know, I'm starting to understand what all this "perceiving" stuff is about!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Judge Has Active Imagination"... end quote.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, continue with your testimony. Tell us about the scent of a story!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey... I'm the one asking the questions here. Usually.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Actually, it took a bit of work to get a thumbs-up on the interview."Reporter Leverages Story, Gets His Interview", end quote.The story concerned a certain case from seven years ago.That red envelope probably had something to do with it.Say what you will, but Drew's talent was without compare.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you threatened to go to press with this "story"? That's how you got your interview? Blackmail?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, yes. ... I mean no! No, no, no, no! It wasn't exactly black... I mean, I'm not... urk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Something wrong, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">L-Look! This is my story! My tidbit! "Journalist's Into Is Livelihood", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">While you have me chatting away in here, what's going on out there? What if some Wally Wordsworth or Sally Scooper gets wind of my story? They could be going to press while I'm going to waste!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court feels your pain, Mr. Brushel. Mr. Justice, let's pick up the pace.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A certain case, seven years ago... Wait... "seven years ago"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Actually, it took a bit of work to get a thumbs-up on the interview.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim, Drew Misham, had an aversion to reporters?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Boy, I guess. Not even my considerable charms did much for him. Until I finally got my thumbs-up, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Maybe you can elaborate on that a bit for us?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Reporter Leverages Story, Gets His Interview", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly what sort of story was this?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh a little one. Like I said. "Nothing More, Nothing Less, Nothing In-Between", end quote. I might have suggested I had a lead on this particular story. But I didn't threaten, or cajole, or nothing! Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So a suggestion was enough to get an interview? Mr. Misham must have really wanted to keep it under wraps...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The story concerned a certain case from seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A certain case, seven years ago? Tell us! What case!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Let me state one thing, Mr. Attorney, and you can quote me on this! I... can't talk about that case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Why not!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It's about journalistic pride, and staunchness, and credibility, and connections! "Journalist Reveals Sources Only Over His Dead Body", end quote. So what'll it be? Gonna strangle me? Dead men don't tell tales, Mr. Attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He sounds pretty determined not to talk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. Our chances of breaking his will aren't looking good.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">That red envelope probably had something to do with it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the one hand we have your "story", and on the other, this letter. What makes you think the two are related?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Oh! Ah, er, I was just saying it's possible. Call it "Reporter's Intuition", end quote. Hey, I say a lot of things. You going to pick all of them apart? Be my guest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>All of them? No. Just the incredibly suspicious ones.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. Anything else to add about Mr. Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Say what you will, but Drew's talent was without compare.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just how amazing was "Mr. Misham's talent"?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Huh? Hoo wee, boy. I mean, hey! He's a star, man, a star! The flow of his brush is like a great, undulating river across the canvas! "Artist's Paints Light Up Studio Like Sun", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This guy is full of wacky gestures... But that one just now was wackier than usual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He looks kind of nervous to me, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Definitely. I'm sensing something different than before here... <thought>Maybe it's time to bring out you-know-what...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...That testimony left a bad taste in my mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It all makes sense. Nothing jumps out as ridiculous.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what this "story" he's talking about is? It must have been good, to get an interview with a famous recluse like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something powerful enough to drag Drew Misham out of hiding. I wonder... Maybe it had something to do with Mr. Misham's art?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sweat much, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Urk! Eh, yeah, well... ...a man can't help his glands, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's more than that. When "Mr. Misham's talent" was mentioned... ...you suddenly began to sweat buckets.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're hiding something... about his talent!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat! Th-Th-Th-Th-Th-That's r-r-r-ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Evidence time. Let's show where Mr. Misham's true "talent" lay!</thought> It just so happens I have evidence showing the "talent" mentioned in that letter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Er, I can't help but wonder what the court is supposed to conclude from this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Other than that you've made a horrible mistake? "Man Burns Bridge, Forgets To Cross First", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Let's try that again. All I have to do is reveal what Mr. Misham really was. That shouldn't be so hard, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This painting was found in Mr. Misham's studio.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are two problems with this painting. The first is it wasn't painted by Mr. Misham. The second is that there was another painting in the studio... ...which looked exactly like this one. Except it was only half done!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we have a letter discussing a payment of $100,000. Which suggests a certain business operation. The business of making forgeries!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Aoooooooooooooogg!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That is all, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Everyone! Please, everyone! Can we keep this private? Please!? This is my story! My scoop!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Forgery... that's a serious crime!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Drew Misham is known as an artist these days. But there were rumors he dabbled in another kind of art until a few years back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Another art" meaning... forgery?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Drew Misham was talented, alright. Talented at making precise, detailed fakes. A fact that certain criminal elements were quick to discover.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Criminal elements...? What...!? You can't seriously be talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Exactly. I'm talking about forging evidence! The rumors started circulating seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Seven years ago...? So, are we to understand that this letter... ...this payment of $100,000 was for...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Exactly. "Forged Evidence Nets Tidy Profit", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Why, it's like our victim was living a double life!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ah ha! This is my chance!</thought> So the victim had ties to the criminal world, right? He could have had plenty of enemies we know nothing about!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is my first time hearing of this "criminal world". We certainly found no criminal connections when we conducted our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But how do you explain all this money? You have to admit there's a possibility of some illegal activity here!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...But there is no proof tying this letter to our case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Our case was, and remains, simple from the beginning. Only the defendant could have poisoned that mug that night. And, you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Hey, hey, hey, the only thing I poison is my pen... when I'm writing reviews!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Brushel, your testimony to this point has been quite unreliable. ...It doesn't speak well of your reporting acumen.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">What're you talking about!? My journalism is rock solid! "Journalism So Solid, You Could Stand An Elephant On It", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case... Let's hear a summarized recap of your testimony. If we can ascertain the situation in that studio from the recap, the trial is over.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! What's he talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The cross-examination showed Mr. Brushel didn't have reason or means to poison him. As long as there're no other suspects... ...then the killer had to be Vera. That's what. ...This next testimony is our last chance!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Brushel, your testimony please!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The only other person in the studio that night was the defendant.It was Vera who poured the coffee. She's admitted as much herself.The only thing that touched Drew's lips during the interview was that mug.And nothing left that studio after he died. Nothing....Clearly, the only one who could have poisoned him was his daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A nice testimony. Clear, succinct... and without room for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Aw... Shucks. You really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this clarifies the situation that night. Very well, Mr. Justice. You may begin your final cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right... <thought>...I still have one trump card left to play. And I won't let this trial end until I use it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The only other person in the studio that night was the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that doesn't prove Vera poisoned it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How many times have we heard that one, Herr Forehead? The poison reached its victim via that coffee mug. And from where did that coffee come, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not to beat a dead horse again, and again, but perhaps you could fill us in?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I'm on it! You need a horse beat? I'm your man!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">It was Vera who poured the coffee. She's admitted as much herself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you witnessed her pouring the coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Course I didn't witness it! When she came in with that tray... ...the coffee was already poured and a-steamin'.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Let us not forget the defendant has admitted to pouring the coffee herself. I heard her statement: "I poured, I served, and I killed."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wha--!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha ha. That last part was just a little joke.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think I'm going to get anywhere with this coffee mug. I need to find another weak spot in this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The only thing that touched Drew's lips during the interview was that mug.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, to be really, really, precise... ...I was busy gobbling mint candies the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One of those candies might have been poisoned!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet, at the time of the autopsy, no fresh fragrance of mint filled the room. ...And no "mint residue" was found.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>It was a long shot anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't tell me you're still trying to prove this? You think the victim ate, drank, or otherwise ingested something other than coffee?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Well, Mr. Justice? If you have some proof...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The possibility is there, I can feel it. Just maybe not prove it, not yet. And possibility isn't going to cut it, not now!</thought> Mr. Misham ingested that poison via a route other than that coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Proof... is possible. <thought>I gotta risk it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? Excellent. Let's see your proof then. Please show us your evidence! What evidence shows that the victim wasn't poisoned via his coffee mug?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Must I explain this over and over and over? We don't need possibilities, here, Herr Forehead. We need proof.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You should also know that every proof has its moment. Perhaps you're a bit early?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I can tell you what we know at this point: The victim put nothing to his mouth but that coffee mug.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Another hole in this case that needs plugging before I can prove anything. But first things first. I'd better uncover a weak spot before I try to strike again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">On with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It... can't be proven.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I do believe our little Forehead is growing up. Pity. We liked the rash, youthful Forehead best.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Another hole in this case that needs plugging before I can prove anything. But first things first. I'd better uncover a weak spot before I try to strike again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">On with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It... can't be proven.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I do believe our little Forehead is growing up. Pity. We liked the rash, youthful Forehead best.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait a second... We already know a letter might have left the studio that night. Couldn't that have opened another path for poisoning? The situation's already changed... I just need to take advantage of it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">And nothing left that studio after he died. Nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not one thing...? You're sure?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yep, sure as sure can be. ...Well, with one exception.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One exception!? What!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">"Journalist Spark Brushel Does Interview, Leaves Studio", end quote. Ah. Ah ha ha! C'mon! It's a joke! Get it? Not funny, I know, but still!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Did something leave the studio that night? Why does that sound familiar? Where have I heard something like that before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that we've proven our witness is a comedian of sorts... ...I'd like to turn to our defense attorney before returning to the testimony. Do you have any idea what, if anything, might have left the studio that night?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I can't think of a single thing!</thought> ...If anything did leave, wouldn't Mr. Brushel have noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">That I would, that I would! Nothing left! Save myself, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Say that again and you'll be held in contempt of court. Let's get back to the cross-examination, then!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think one thing might very well have left the studio that night, actually. A certain something that has vanished from the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By which you mean... ...something other than our witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't tell me. "Vera Misham"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Believe me, any comic relief I may provide is entirely unintentional.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, let's see what you've got for us, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, this thing wasn't at the scene of the crime, so I can't show it to you. But I do have evidence that shows how it could have been taken from the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...I find Prosecutor Gavin more amusing than this guy, really.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If that was comic relief, why do I not feel amused?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We want evidence, not entertainment, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There goes my career in stand-up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the only link between that studio and the outside world.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A letter box?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did Mr. Brushel just tell us? When he entered the studio on the night of the murder... ...the victim had just finished writing a letter!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yeah, I said that. And yeah, it was true.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Furthermore, you went on to tell us... ...that he put the letter in a yellow envelope and put it in the letter box.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that very same letter box was empty! In other words... ...that night, the "yellow envelope" disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ah, yes, intriguing. So an envelope has disappeared from the scene of the crime. Of course... this changes nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He has a point, Mr. Justice. What we're trying to figure out here is how the poison got into Mr. Misham. Is it really important that this envelope the witness says he saw disappeared?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if it did disappear, then something did leave the studio that night. That seems very important to me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then. The witness will add this to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You got it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I still think this fails to change anything, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wouldn't be so sure. A letter disappeared from the crime scene that night... This is exactly the opening I've been looking for!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">A letter was put in the post from the studio, but I hardly think that matters.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing could be more serious than an envelope disappearing from that studio! And you were hiding that fact from us!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Er, yes, well, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I don't argue the possibility that a letter disappeared from that studio. ...But Herr Forehead, isn't there a much more serious question before us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Right, how Mr. Misham was poisoned. I know. But Mr. Brushel's testimony has changed, which means the facts of the case have, too. And what he's told us means something entirely different now, I'm starting to think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's keep thinking, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">...Clearly, the only one who could have poisoned him was his daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say "clearly" as though it were obvious. But this claim that the defendant poisoned the victim is merely conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Ah, yes, well, you see... In my business, it's all about making the most ridiculous things sound right. A bad habit, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yes, well, er, actually... ...I guess this is more a case of "Ridiculous Journalist Sounds Wrong", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is forced to agree with you. Please refrain from wild conjecture.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Understoodloudandclear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If only I could believe that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you think, Apollo? Everything he's saying seems so... not flawed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well, that's kind of what you want from a testimony, really. <thought>...I need to keep my eye on what matters. How, and why, was Drew Misham, killed? Vera poured the coffee, that's not going to change. But if that coffee didn't kill him, I need to find what did... and prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Proof is... possible. <thought>Here goes nothing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You do understand what we need, ja? Proof, Herr Forehead. Not "possibilities".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. And, Prosecutor Gavin, I hope you understand... ...I'm ready to give you that proof.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Wh-What did you say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have proof of the disappearing envelope!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">I saw him writing a letter, I did!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Which was picked up by the mailman, I assume?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course, which means... ...that envelope had a stamp on it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A stamp... Ah..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As we all know, stamps come with dried glue on the back. In order to use the glue you have to wet it... ...by licking the stamp!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Feh. No one worth talking to actually licks stamps in this day and age.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even if you wanted to talk to him, you couldn't. ...He's dead, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">OK, so he licked the stamp. But wait! How does that explain the atroquinine on the rim of the coffee mug?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If he licked the back of a poisoned stamp, the poison would get on his tongue, yes? What would then happen if he put the coffee mug to his mouth, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those traces on the mug weren't the killer's doing! It was the other way around!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The coffee mug didn't poison Mr. Misham... ...Mr. Misham poisoned the coffee mug himself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! B-But that doesn't... Does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall, if you would... ...atroquinine is a slow-acting poison, yes? The poison entered his body when he put the stamp on that envelope. But his time wasn't up until the very moment he touched his lips to that cup of joe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have something to add, Mr. Brushel?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh. His nose is picking up another scent...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Brushel">As I believe I mentioned earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, that's the thing, see. After he put his letter in that envelope... ...Mr. Misham sat there searching his desk drawer for something! Yes! A stamp! A so-called "Postage Stamp", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">But you know, I don't seem to remember him ever finding one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe he'd just run out?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Incidentally, we searched the desk drawer at the scene of the crime. There were no stamps. Not a single one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, that does pose a problem. How will you prove that the stamp was coated with poison?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, I'm glad no other stamps were found. It makes proving the stamp he used was poisoned possible!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha ha ha. ...Good show, good show. You can't even prove there was a stamp at the scene in the first place!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, let's hear what the defense has to say anyway. Where's your evidence that proves the existence of this poisoned stamp?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I think our beloved attorney has been licking too many stamps in his free time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... Do you smile like that when you torture all your victims, or just me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Take care that we don't lick you and stick you in the letter box, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I think I'm making this out to be way more complicated than it really is. That stamp would have left a small atroquinine residue on something... But what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that certainly is a cute little frame. And by little, I mean really little.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was on the victim's desk, Your Honor. ...Quite empty, as you can see for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I noticed that too during my inspection. So what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, apparently you weren't as observant as you should have been. You see, when you saw this frame, it was missing something quite important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Missing" something...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. A pale bluish stain on the inside of the frame... Atroquinine residue!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What!? Why wasn't I told about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The frame is only two inches square. The face of the frame is even smaller. Maybe an inch wide at most.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You aren't saying...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, but I am. Tell me: what fits in such a small frame? A commemorative stamp, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! The poisoned stamp was in this frame...!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Gavin...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why would he put something like that on his desk? Don't tell me he had it there so he could commit suicide if the mood struck!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You know, can I say something? I had a thought, see!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What, Mr. Brushel, and please stop jittering around like that!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">The victim was a forger, right? There's a lot of money in that line of work. "Forger Forges Friends, Makes Enemies, Too", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the poisoned stamp might have been a murder weapon, aimed at him!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Oh, rich. That's rich. Leave the ridiculous flights of fancy to the Gavinners's song lyrics, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Finally, something we agree on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The stamp was a "murder weapon"? Nonsense! Murder is a simple business. Who would go to such lengths? No one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">C-Come again...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Recall, if you would, the victim's reclusive lifestyle. Drew Misham hid from the world. He avoided meetings. His only contact with the outside world... was the mail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The... mail!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now, if you wanted to kill someone you couldn't meet, but you knew read letters... ...a stamp would be the perfect weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ridiculous! Where's your proof? I want proof! Show us evidence that this poisoned stamp was sent to him... as a murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I might not have "evidence" per se... But things are finally starting to come together!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What is it, Apollo? Your fists are trembling!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I know what happened! I don't believe it... but I can see it! I think I know how Mr. Misham was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, fill us in, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...A certain piece of evidence points to the truth, Your Honor. I can show you how someone with the intent to kill sent Mr. Misham the stamp of death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm not sure it's entirely clear to me what this proves, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? <thought>Was I wrong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe we have shown probable "intent to kill". Except the killer would be Herr Judge, and the victim, you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeeeeargh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Consider that a warning, Mr. Justice. Think before presenting next time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Let's think this one over again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Isn't this the envelope... the one from seven years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about the text of the letter again. There were two pages in the envelope. This is page one. ...And this is page two. I want to draw your attention to one phrase in particular. "...Send in the enclosed envelope with the enclosed stamp within 3 days." The enclosed stamp, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">In other words, if I have this straight... "The Stamp! Poison! On The Stamp! Lick, Lick, Gasp..." end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now, what if he had done exactly as the letter asked?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He would sign the document, put it in the envelope... and put the stamp on it, right? Then he would put it in his letter box...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fifteen minutes wouldn't have elapsed between affixing the stamp, and mailing the letter. But the clock started ticking, and when the time came... he drew his last breath. And the murder weapon would be taken away from the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Quite conveniently, thanks to the postal system!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Such a splendid imagination you have, Herr Forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let me confirm one thing with you, if I might. So, this "poisoned stamp" was inside this envelope from seven years ago... ja? Is that what you'd have us believe? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It is a little bit of a stretch, but there's a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. A very small possibility. How small, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A poisoned stamp in this envelope? A stamp that then became the murder weapon? How do you intend to prove this seeming coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! It was seven years ago, and we don't even know who sent that letter!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And your answer... is silence, I see. Very well! I move to...</line>
<line speaker="???">...It's not nice to pick on the Frulein, Klavier.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah... Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well? Like my Kristoph Gavin impression? Did I sound like him?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Don't quit your day job.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't you have a crime scene to be looking after, Frulein Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Someone had to come dig you all out of the mess you're making of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mess...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know, none of this would happen if you just trusted in science a little more. You can find out if that stamp was in that envelope, easy.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Care to explain yourself, Frulein Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Glare at me all you want, but science is on my side. It's all in the residue, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right! The poison detection spray...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Produce the red envelope at once! You can open it on the authority of the court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! Would you look at that!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No mistaking it. That's atroquinine residue!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I don't believe it... A murder weapon from the past... Now, seven years later, it bares its fangs at last!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Absolutely outrageous! ...Tell me why! Why didn't this murder take place seven years ago!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's one possibility. Maybe Mr. Misham figured it out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Figured what out?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He realized that the person who sent that letter wanted him dead. So he sent his reply with a different stamp.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And put his decisive evidence in a frame.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ack! You're still here!?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">C-Can I make a statement here, on the record? I, Spark "Razortooth" Brushel, claim this scoop as mine! "Drew Misham Killed In Cold Blood... ...By Sender Of Seven-Year-Old Letter!" end quote. Hmm, no, maybe something more succinct. "Star Falls After 7 Year Delay", end quote.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! I see no room for further argument here. Though I admit, this is all coming as quite a shock. To think that the murder weapon reached his mouth after seven years...! "Stamp Is Ticket Straight To Afterlife", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uh oh. I think the witness is a bad influence on our judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see no need for further debate on this matter. The sender of that letter seven years ago could hardly have been our defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think we just won!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well! This court finds the defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Is this the bright future of our legal system?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor... Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A ticket to the afterlife from seven years ago...? Tickets for Gavinners's shows are invalid after two weeks.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But it doesn't make sense any other way!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It boggles my mind that so many people haven't noticed this. There's a fatal contradiction in Herr Forehead's claim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A c-contradiction?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A poisoned stamp was placed in this envelope seven years ago. Whereupon it was framed, until now. If that's the case, then why would Drew Misham have done what he did?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Ema explained that! He must have realized it was poisoned!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Therein lies the rub.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Seven years ago, the forger Drew Misham sensed a trap, and put the stamp in a frame. I do not debate this. ...But this begs the question. Why, seven years later, did he use that stamp on the night of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Surely, you don't mean to suggest that Mr. Misham simply "forgot"? He put the murder weapon in a frame on his desk for seven years... and forgot? You expect us to believe he sprang the trap on himself?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Uh... Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While I admit, this is all quite shocking, myself... ...it does seem highly unlikely that he would fall afoul of a trap... ...that had been sitting on his desk for seven years!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think we're winning anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, I'm glad to see we're all back in the real world now. Welcome back to reality! We've been waiting for you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK... Then how do you explain the poisoned stamp that was in this envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The "poisoned stamp"...? Where exactly is this poisoned stamp, again? Have you brought it to court for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see no proof that such a thing ever existed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about the atroquinine residue, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, I agree, that does seem to be atroquinine residue. But, Herr Forehead, it's certainly no stamp.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Y-Yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Even if your precious poisoned stamp did exist... ...Drew Misham never would have used it. ...That is all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Urk.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we've come to a conclusion. Again.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo! Were we wrong the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I can't believe it! The poison traces match up! It can't be coincidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd like to bring some closure to this issue, sometime this year. ...Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's review the facts, and see where we stand. Seven years ago, Drew Misham received a red envelope. There were traces of the poison atroquinine on the document inside that envelope. A similar trace was also found at the crime scene... ...on this tiny picture frame. The defense has indicated the possibility of a yellow envelope. An envelope that left the scene of the crime with the poisoned stamp on it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, but even if this envelope contained a poisoned stamp... ...and Drew Misham, knowing this, put it in a frame... ...he never would have used that stamp!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm afraid you're right. Which means there is a fatal flaw in the defense's case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I haven't been on the wrong track this whole time, I'm sure of it! The traces of atroquinine, the envelope, the frame... ...and Drew Misham's mysterious death... They're all connected somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice, do you have a conclusion for us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The defense stands by its case, Your Honor. We've seen that the logical outcome of the evidence makes no sense. Which means that one of our clues... must be a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, a fake clue? Fascinating! And if we find this fake, your wild fantasies will prove quite reasonable, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The fake clue that's thrown us off the poison's trail is none other than...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This red envelope... is a fake?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Without a doubt, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Wasn't it you who presented this evidence to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hold on a second, Apollo! The poison on that envelope, the frame, and the coffee mug... They're all connected somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... right! <thought>*sigh* I can hear it already. "It looks like the fake... was you, Herr Forehead!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now's no time for wallowing in self-pity! Let's get thinking, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This frame... is the "fake" clue?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Without a doubt, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Wasn't it you who presented this evidence to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hold on a second, Apollo! The poison on that envelope, the frame, and the coffee mug... They're all connected somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... right! <thought>*sigh* I can hear it already. "It looks like the fake... was you, Herr Forehead!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We can flog ourselves later, Apollo! Now's the time for thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-the victim was a "fake clue"? I'm afraid I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'll explain. We have an envelope, a frame, and a mug, linked by poison. That all makes sense. What doesn't make sense is the victim himself!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Congratulations. You've completely lost me. So the fake evidence is none other than the master of fake himself, the forger? ...It makes a good story, I'll give you that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The fake clue... Fakes... forgeries...</thought> Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know that face! That's the "I just had an idea" face!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know if I'm right... but I'm going with it anyway! What if our "forger" is the "fake"!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seven years ago, our forger sniffed a trap, and stepped aside. ...Seven years passed. Now the forger stumbles into that very same trap, and dies. ...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's what I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because the forger who was killed... was a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Here we are again. The victim... was a "fake"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One forger smelled the trap. One forger fell into the trap. That's two forgers! And one of them was a fake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So you are telling us that Drew Misham, the victim, was a fake? Well, if he was the fake, who was the real forger? You'd better not be claiming there was some kind of switcheroo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I'm afraid you're going to have to back up your story. Mr. Justice. Show us just who the real Drew Misham was!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If Drew Misham wasn't the real forger... ...there's only one other person it could have been!</thought> ...Understood, Your Honor. Forger Drew Misham was himself a forgery! The real forger was...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! "Attorney Makes Wild Claim, Becomes Subject Of Mass Ridicule"... end quote! Better come up with something quick before that story goes to print...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There can be only one explanation, really. The real identity of the forger known as Drew Misham is none other than... ...his only daughter, Vera Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ...Mr. Justice! This is going out on a limb, even for you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I kinda agree. I mean, Vera, a forger?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's consider it before you write it off entirely. If you look at the paintings in the studio, one fact becomes quite clear. Forgery had been taking place in that studio for quite some time! The forger wasn't caught in that trap seven years ago. This can only mean that the one who was caught in the trap wasn't the forger!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... Actually, that does make a certain kind of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One more thing! Only two sets of fingerprints were found in the forger's studio. Drew Misham's... and Vera Misham's.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If we know that Drew Misham wasn't the forger... ...that leaves only one possibility, by process of elimination. The forger was Vera Misham. ...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... ...Fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Vera Misham...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You've been paying attention to the trial so far?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let's just ask her and be done with it, shall we? Who are you? Who is the forger, Drew Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...! ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Was that... an expression of emotion I saw on her face? She's staring holes into Prosecutor Gavin's face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I'm used to being stared at by Fruleins, believe me. Though they usually talk to me, too. Tell us. Were you the one who forged those works of art?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... so the forger, Drew Misham was... you!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Yes, it was me...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The court was in an uproar, and it wasn't coming down. We had to break for a ten minute recess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK... So where exactly does this leave us, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the Drew Misham who was killed... ...wasn't "Drew Misham the forger", basically.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Well then, who was he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well "he" was actually...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Doing her nails.</thought> So, you really made those forgeries?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Yes... For Father... ...I know it was wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Could you tell us how it happened?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...My father was a painter... ...I love painting ever since I was a child... ...One day, Father saw it in me... ...He saw that I had the "talent"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The talent... for making forgeries?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...How should I say it? It was not only paintings I made... ...Given the materials, I could make... anything...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anything...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father was so proud, and I, so happy... ...But, in the end, I was making... those...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Forgeries.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I've never had a good constitution, nor... personality... ...I know very little of the world outside my door... ...... ...Now, because of me... Father... is...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Do you know about this red envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I remember that envelope. It was some time ago...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you were already a, um... You were already creating your "works" back then?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I started when I was only twelve years old...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the one who figured out the stamp was poisoned, that was...</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">...Mr. Justice! It's time! To the courtroom, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right! <thought>Out of time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, Vera! Just one more thing, please! Those three paintings in the studio...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I painted those, as part of my work...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right. See, we checked them out and we saw what was underneath. We saw the rough sketches underneath the three finished paintings...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I see... ...... ...Mr. Justice...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father... He knew of you... ...Of both of you...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your late father...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...He was watching, gathering information... ...All about the "Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But lately, we're not doing just law...!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Yes... You do tricks, gags to amuse... and play piano...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, they're not really "gags"...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Yet when Father heard you had resumed the legal business... ...How pleased he was...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Who was Mr. Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...How'm I supposed to know?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What if he was Daddy's Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judging from the relative ages involved, I'd say it's highly unlikely. <thought>Things are already confusing enough with all these daddies running around. We know that the victim's daughter, Vera, was the forger. What does this mean for the case...? Guess we're about to find out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Vera seems pretty tense. She's practically chewing her fingernails clean off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you could begin by telling us how it all worked. How did you set up this "Drew Misham forger" persona?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's that stare again... She's drilling more holes into his head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know it's hard for you, but hey, he's a handsome guy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's "hard"!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, miss, if you would... ...did you really make those detestable forgeries...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you'd rather answer my question? Were you the one who painted that painting. The remarkably similar one?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Ah... Yes... ...I painted it, yes... ...Father praised me quite highly for it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... she was the one who made the forgeries.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet, she did not wish to reveal the truth of their operation. So the victim was a stand-in, a decoy. To the world at large, he was the forger, not her.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...I've done... a bad thing. I have, haven't I...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Regardless, we need a little more information. About, for instance... ...this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You have seen this before, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Y-Yes... It was in the desk drawer...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, you may proceed with your testimony. Tell us everything you know about this envelope.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I created things and Father sold them......This envelope came after my first work... that was other than a painting......Father handled the deal, all of it......I received the stamp that was in that envelope......It was after that job that we moved to the current studio...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There certainly was much of great interest in your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Not that the witness realizes it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please begin the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! OK! <thought>I need more information about this "forger"... ...This "Drew Misham"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I created things and Father sold them...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, these "things" you were making, er... ...you mean paintings identical to other paintings, right?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...The closer they were, the happier Father was... ...I was happy, too...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Still, you're quite young now. When did you begin this work?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...My first painting sold when I was twelve...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Your Honor! She had no idea what she was doing was illegal!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Easy there, little attorney. You're not here to defend her for the crime of forgery.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... true. Please, tell us more about this envelope. ...This envelope that may very well have killed your father.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Alright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... you really didn't know anything, did you? You had no idea how much danger you were in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... About this "commemorative stamp". Could you tell us more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was very pretty. And, more than that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was a picture of people I liked at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>This is something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Apparently, we've got some cross-examination yet ahead of us. If you would be so kind as to continue your testimony, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...This envelope came after my first work... that was other than a painting...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "other than a painting", you mean... ...you'd only done paintings up to that point?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Yes... ...But Father had a realization... ...He noticed my talent extended to making things other than paintings...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For instance...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...For instance... a letter someone had written... ...Or a fingerprint left upon a cup... ...Or a signature on a document... a seal upon a letter...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...None of this makes her sound very innocent at all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And the $100,000 promised in this letter was the start. ...The beginning of a new industry for Drew Misham.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A new... "industry"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The creation of items to be used in criminal proceedings. ...Forging evidence, in other words.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... you really didn't know anything, did you? You had no idea how much danger you were in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... About this "commemorative stamp". Could you tell us more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was very pretty. And, more than that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was a picture of people I liked at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>This is something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Apparently, we've got some cross-examination yet ahead of us. If you would be so kind as to continue your testimony, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father handled the deal, all of it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you didn't know how the things you were making were being used?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I enjoy painting very much...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I think I understand. The Frulein has lived in an... unusual little world.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell us what happened to the "papers" that were in this envelope?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father signed them and sent them back I believe...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... did he follow the instructions? "Send in the enclosed envelope with the enclosed stamp"...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is a rather important matter! Give your answer some thought.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I received the stamp that was in that envelope...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean, you "received" it!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Did I do something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You didn't use that stamp because it was dangerous, correct!? Deadly poison! On the back! Atroquinine...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A moment, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You can't force an answer upon the witness. Now then. Perhaps... you would tell me, Frulein Vera? Why did you "receive" this stamp?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was... beautiful...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ah. You mean it was one of those commemorative stamps?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Yes, I think it was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you didn't know about the poison?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I guess not!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So the trap failed by chance... by mistake. Thanks to this commemorative stamp.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Quite the close call!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... you really didn't know anything, did you? You had no idea how much danger you were in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... About this "commemorative stamp". Could you tell us more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was very pretty. And, more than that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was a picture of people I liked at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>This is something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Apparently, we've got some cross-examination yet ahead of us. If you would be so kind as to continue your testimony, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was after that job that we moved to the current studio...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean you moved to where the current "Drew Studio" is?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Yes... we saw very few people there... ...I began drawing picture books...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This single job had tied them to the criminal underworld. I'd think Mr. Misham wished to reduce their visibility in the world at large.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...When we had to meet someone for some reason... ...Father posed as the creator of the work...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that was the real essence of the artist, "Drew Misham". You did the work, and he supplied the face.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... you really didn't know anything, did you? You had no idea how much danger you were in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... About this "commemorative stamp". Could you tell us more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was very pretty. And, more than that...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was a picture of people I liked at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>This is something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Apparently, we've got some cross-examination yet ahead of us. If you would be so kind as to continue your testimony, Frulein.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...The stamp was a picture of my favorite magicians... so I kept it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Magicians...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I love mysterious things, I always have...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Even though she fainted when she saw Mr. Hat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're confusing "mysterious" with "freaky".</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father took me when I was very young... ...It was a great magic show. I loved it so much...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">See!? See!? Isn't magic great?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine, great, yeah, sure. No need to get all excited.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...But the magic troupe we saw disbanded soon after... ...I was quite sad...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Did she just say what I think she said? Magic "troupe"? Now where have I heard that before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The red envelope came after she'd completed her first "job"... That makes it a letter from her client... whoever wanted a forgery made.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're close. We just have to piece together the parts: A deadly weapon in a red envelope... ...and the path it took to take Drew Misham's life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those magicians you liked, was it this bunch!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! They're not a "bunch"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see! Still, I have to wonder. Why include a commemorative stamp like that in a business letter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good question!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, pretty stamps are always better, and you can't beat Troupe Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, the whole murder plan was a failure because of it. Ironic, don't you think. ...Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Gram... Gram... Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's with Gavin...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Might I ask just one question of this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In your testimony just now, you stated... ...this was your "first work that was other than a painting".</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Please, tell me... ...what exactly did you make?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...Can I ask why--</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No! Answer the question! ...Now!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">Eeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">P-Prosecutor Gavin...? You're usually not the one whose volume concerns me.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Yes, it is unbecoming of me. I apologize. But... I must know. Please, Ms. Misham, tell me.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was... a book... ...A single page... In a "book"...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A "book"...? Please be more specific.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...It was a handwritten book. Like... Like a diary...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Nnnno! I don't... No!!!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wh-What's wrong with Prosecutor Gavin? He looks like he just saw a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ms. Misham. This "book"... ...was there a picture of a silk hat on the back cover? Yes or no!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...! ...How... How did you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin! The defendant is answering all of your questions! Stop badgering her!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... He's told you nothing, has he? ...Your soiled, sullied mentor. Nothing!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sullied... who?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Phoenix Wright. Who else!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He never told you about the trial, seven years ago? About how he came to lose his attorney's badge...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was a certain piece of evidence that decided his fate, you know. ...A certain diary. On the back, it bore the mark of a silk hat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Whaaaaaat!? <thought>Phoenix Wright, tossed out of the profession by false evidence... And the forger who made that evidence... ...is this girl standing right in front of me!?</thought> Vera! You must tell us! The evidence you made was used in a trial seven years ago. Who asked "Drew Misham", you, to forge that evidence!? ...For all of our sakes, who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...We... only met once...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... You met the client!? Well, who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It was... ...It was... ......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's going on with Vera? She's staring at Prosecutor Gavin's face again...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, what? Is there something about me...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... ...I remember clearly... ...I remember who gave me the book... the diary... ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...... Ugh...! *choke*...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ve... Vera!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Brushel! You're hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yooooooooooooooooooowrk! Dontyellallofasuddenlikethat! You'll give a guy a heart attack...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Sorry! It's just... the way you were moving just now. It was particularly suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">What's that supposed to mean!? So usually I'm just sort of "averagely" suspicious?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry. My mistake. You're fine. <thought>I know I'm on to something here. Time to focus!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Vera Misham...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender herself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>