<xml>
<title>Turnabout Ablaze</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So now we know who the Yatagarasu really was. And yet, there remains much to this case that needs to be resolved.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Like how the weapons crossed country lines, for example. The two countries have incredibly strict security systems and entry procedures. Short of a miracle, it's impossible for someone to have smuggled them in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Smuggling them in, huh...? <thought>We will need to open a new line of investigation on just this aspect alone... But before we do, I would like to go through my evidence once more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! There's a VCR here, sir! Now we can see what's on that tape Detective Badd gave us!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This piece of evidence from the KG-8 Incident, hidden from sight for ten long years... I just know that this is related to the current case somehow.</thought> Detective Gumshoe, if you could please play the tape for us.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This man! It's Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A-And he's holding a knife in his hand!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This looks like footage from a security camera at the entrance of an apartment building.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An apartment building? How do you figure that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Unlike you, I actually read the summary file on the KG-8 Incident. And the crime scene was the victim's own apartment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So this footage was shot at the entrance to the victim's own apartment building...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">At the trial, Mr. Faraday claimed that the piece of footage existed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, no one could find it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes. Somehow, someone was able to steal it and hide it through Mr. Ernest Amano.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can see how this would've been a definitive piece, and why someone would want to hide it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But it's a piece of evidence from a ten-year-old case. There's no way it's related to this case we're working on now, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I believe it has everything to do with the case we're working on now. The ringleader even went so far as to use Mr. Portsman to retrieve it. Which means that in this video lies a very inconvenient bit of footage to the ringleader.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Where!? Where!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh. Wait. What was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That bit you played just now... Please show it to me again! This car! This is something we cannot overlook.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why's that, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look here, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you find this section... to be particularly of interest?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't see anything at all... Oho! A-Are you talking about that thing, sir!? I've heard that you can capture ghosts on film. Is that what it is, sir!? So wh-wh-wh-wh-wh-wh-wh-where is it in this picture, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's quite enough. <thought>How could he have mistaken this for an apparition?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, wow! It looks like you can be wrong sometimes, too, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>H-How mortifying to have her point that out in front of everyone...! It shouldn't be that hard. I just need to calm down and think clearly about this. This blade can really only be paired up with that piece of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the national flag of the Principality of Cohdopia. And because it has the national flag on it, we know this to be an official government car. But the question we should be asking ourselves is what was a government car doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, Ms. von Karma and Mr. Edgeworth. So you were here all this time.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ambassador Alba...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Thank you very much for continuing the investigation, even at the time of night. Ah, if only I was even a tiny bit more careful... ...this tragedy would never have happened. I am truly sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This wasn't your fault, sir. This had nothing to do with how careful you were.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You idiot, Quercus! You couldn't chase after a simple thief! Now then, let's get down to the real reason why I came looking for the two of you. I would like you to put the investigation on hold for a while. Can you do that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Excuse me!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I heard you've apprehended the thief that turned this embassy upside-down. And we are in the middle of an event celebrating our countries' reconciliation. We can't exactly have the police and detectives walking around here forever. You're scaring the visitors away. So I hope that you can understand how I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... But we must finish our investigation and resolve the remaining issues.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Why don't we leave the rest to the Allebahstian and Babahlese police?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ambassador! We are so close! Just a little more and...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ms. von Karma. I'm afraid I've made up my mind. And without my permission, you can't proceed with your investigation, anyway, right?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's true, however...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As he said at the very beginning... ...this area can be considered to be Allebahstian soil. In which case, we are nothing but foreigners in their land. Is this really where our investigation ends!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="MIB">Shifu! We found Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Shifu! This way!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang... You're back on the scene rather quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">If I laid back and took a break, I'd lose the scent of my prey, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Agent Lang! Why in the... Why have you returned?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Because I have to solve this case, no matter what.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Well, I'm sorry to inform you... Ah, and don't take this the wrong way; I don't suspect you personally... ...however, a member of Interpol was just found to be a thief, and so...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Grr...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Under these circumstances, I wish to put your investigation on hold. After all, I believe our own police can handle things from here. They are quite capable.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh...! At this rate, our investigation really WILL come to a close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh...... heh heh heh heh heh......... Aha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Ambassador Alba, I get it now. I really do...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh? I'm very glad you understand how I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">No, not that. What I was talking about was... ...I know who the killer is behind tonight's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-You--</line>
<line speaker="Kay">K-Know--</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">T-The--</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">K-Killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">D-Do you really mean that, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, wolves don't lie.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Th-Then who is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, let me first say that I'm not talking about Mr. Coachen's murder. That was all Shih-na.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "The truth lies not at the exit, but rather, shines outside the maze itself." The truth is unexpectedly simple. So let me ask you this: who do you think was DeMasque II's killer? Hmph, I'll tell you who... It was you, Franziska von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I was the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, wait! But that's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah! ...Although, that whip is actually quite... Yeowwww!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hold your tongue, and that ludicrous remark you were about to make!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang... Are you seriously accusing her of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........Yeah, I am.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He doesn't appear to be joking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, sis... I remember that just before Ambassador Alba went to give his speech... ...he called you into his office, right?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Y-Yes, he did... but what does that have to do with anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'm getting to that. Furthermore, in order to solve both cases... ...you moved around rather freely between Allebahst and Babahl, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And where is your evidence that I am the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph... I was just getting to that. Trust me, I'll show them to you in due time. Ambassador Alba. In order for me to bring this case to a close... ...I'll need to inspect your office one more time. Will you grant me permission?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.................. .........With things as they are, I suppose I don't have much of a choice, do I...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Good! Then let's move out! Oh, and don't even think about running away, sis. My pack will be keeping a close eye on you, you can bet your bottom dollar on that!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph! As if I would have any reason to flee! But just so we're clear, your logic had better be sound... ...because I'll accept nothing short of a perfect explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She seems rather upset, not that I blame her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Haaa ha ha ha ha ha hahaha. I expected that you'd accept no less. But we'll see how long you can keep that nose of yours stuck up in the air like that.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang... As someone related to tonight's case, I request that you allow me to take part. And so that I may clean up my superior's mess.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph... I guess I should. The more the merrier, especially when it's the peanut gallery.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! In that case, I want to join in, too! I still haven't seen what it looks like in Allebahst, yet!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">If you let Kay in, then you've gotta let me in, too, pal! I can't sit around and do nothing when Ms. von Karma's in trouble!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Gummy! Let's have a competition to see who can save her first, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! I'll take you up on that! Oh, yeah! I'm fired up and raring to go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...As a detective, I don't believe this is something you're supposed to be excited over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Haaa ha ha ha ha ha hahaha. Sounds like this is going to got real interesting! Ambassador Alba... I'll be bringing these kids along for the ride.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Very well. But I'd like you to keep in mind that this will be your last chance.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph. I'll have this whole mess cleaned up before you know it. Now, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">OK, now, let's first go over the facts one more time. Manny Coachen's body was found over in the secretariat's office in Babahl. The weapon that took his life was one of Allebahst's ornamental knives. And then, the body of DeMasque II, Mr. Ka-Shi Nou... ...was found here in the Allebahstian ambassador's office. Through our investigation, we found that the murder weapon was this Primidux Statue. And that this is actually Babahl's statue. This case... no matter how I look at it... Sis! If it wasn't you, then there's no one else who could have pulled this off!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Lang! Do you understand the full implications of what you are saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Of course I do, sis. And I'm serious. You were on the trail of the smuggling ring, and you wanted any evidence you could find. And so, while people were distracted by the Yatagarasu's appearance, you snuck in here. That's when you two ran into each other. You and that other thief who took advantage of the confusion from the fire!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Even if all that were true, how do you explain the movement of the weapons!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph... Don't worry. I plan to show that you're the culprit behind that, too. You had permission to investigate both embassies at will. With that kind of free reign, you could've easily taken the weapons across country lines. Hey now! Look, sis. I thought I already told you, I'm not messing around here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This case isn't directly tied to the smuggling ring... ...but Shih-na certainly is tied to the smuggling ring!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He is right in saying that she is a member of the smuggling ring... ...however, the connection between this case and the ring... Could it not be deeper than what any of us can imagine?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Grrr...! Let's get this ridiculous circus over with already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, you need to calm down. Because you only know the facts of the Allebahstian side of the case... ...I don't believe you can see the case as a whole, and therefore, solve it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But don't worry. I am taking this seriously as well, and I will prove your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That's the only way to be... Mr. Prosecutor! But can you come up with anything else that can top my hypothesis? Of course, your explanation has to solve the mystery of the moving weapons as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course, and I will. Let us now delve into the truth behind the murder of DeMasque II.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You do understand, don't you, Miles Edgeworth? This isn't just a confrontation against Agent Lang. If you can't figure out how the murder of DeMasque II is related to the smuggling ring... ...then it will mean the end of our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As long as I have no good counterargument to his hypothesis... ...then the best I can do is walk this thin tightrope and see what I can do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Come on, Mr. Prosecutor. Let's get started!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, let's.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">One of Allebahst's knives was used in Babahl to murder Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So as long as I can't explain how the weapons moved about, Franziska will remain a suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You got it, Mr. Prosecutor. So why don't you stop giving me a hard time. Under these circumstances, who the heck can carry a weapon across country lines!? I've worked through every possibility, but there's only one that's plausible. Your boss!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, what I've learned from you just now is that you've lost sight of yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By focusing too intently on that which is in front of us, we become blind to the truth. Don't tell me Lang Zi never said anything to that effect?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You prosecutor...! Who do you think you are, speaking about Lang Zi's proverbs like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I don't need his proverbs. Because MY words are all you will need to see the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">One of Allebahst's knives was used in Babahl to murder Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I concur that this knife crossed over country lines.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Good, but that's not the only thing that did. We mustn't forget about the other weapon! The knife was only one.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And the murder weapon in the killing of DeMasque II is Babahl's Primidux Statue.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that the Primidux Statue was also brought over by Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Like I told you before, that's the only way it makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how exactly did she bring it over?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I... haven't figured that out yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... That's rather weak statement, considering how sure you are.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Maybe, but there is one thing I do know for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Somehow, these two objects were able to penetrate the two countries' impenetrable security.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Impenetrable"...? I should hardly think so.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You've seen the top of the wall between the two countries, right? Who in the world could cross over that?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, not even I could climb over that thing with all that barbed wire...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The only way into either embassy is through the doors in the Theatrum Neutralis. So the only way for the knife and the Primidux Statue to traverse the two countries... ...is through those security camera-equipped, well-guarded doors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">The only one who traversed the two countries just before and after the crimes was you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was Franziska really the only person to have traveled between the two countries?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">According to the guards at both doors, she is the only one to go back and forth. The sis there was in Allebahst when the Yatagarasu showed. And then, just before you guys found Mr. Coachen's body, she entered Babahl. I think we can assume that's when she brought the knife into Babahl.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then how do you explain the Primidux Statue?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...I haven't quite figured that out yet. However, the fact that the two weapons crossed the border... ...proves that the killer must have also traveled across the country lines!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The only things to cross the border are the Primidux Statue and the knife? I should hardly think that those are the only two items, Agent Lang...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, those two items are not the only two to cross the border tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">DeMasque II was killed by Babahl's Primidux Statue, yes. But if that's the case, then tell me, where did Allebahst's Primidux Statue go?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">To Babahl...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. And if the two statues really were switched... ...then this means that both statues were smuggled across the border at some point. Which means that a total of three items were smuggled across the embassies!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmm... I guess so. But you know what? It doesn't matter the number of items, only that the sis is the only one who could've done it! Because the only person who went back and forth between Allebahst and Babahl is her!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is that really true? Was there no one else who traveled between the two countries? Actually, there was definitely another person; one who paid a visit to both sides of the wall!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is that really so, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha ha! What a lousy time to try and bluff your way out of this! I checked out what the guards said, along with the security cameras' footage. You're not going to overturn my hypothesis that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But suppose there was some other way other than through the theater doors?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What other way...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The other entity that managed to cross the border unharmed... If I point it out, it would open up a whole new possibility! And though I hesitate to bring this out... ...as long as this entity exists, the impossible road becomes a possibility.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">It looks like you've got some clever idea in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do, and I can show it to you through a single piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch! Fine, then. Let's see this piece of evidence that will show me this "other route"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence will show us another way to move between the two countries!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe this is the piece of evidence that will show you how!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">......... What about it? You're going to have to explain because I don't see another road or anything else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But how can you not see!? Wolves are known for their keen eyesight!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry, but the only thing I see is the crud that you're hoping will stick to the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I need to think calmly about this and find that other road the smuggled goods look...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, I'm sure you familiar with this unforgettable photo.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch...! That supernatural photo!? Like I said before... Humans can't fly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, of course not. I understand that perfectly well.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And don't start claiming that Shih-na somehow grew wings, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wouldn't dream of claiming that.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And I won't allow you to take back what you've said either! I'll say it again; it's not humanly possible to fly through the air without wings! So you'd better have a good explanation for this, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Arngh! <thought>But how can I prove who it was that flew through the air in this photo!? Wait. "Not humanly possible"...? Eureka...!</thought> Very well. You will have your explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It sounds like you have a good idea simmering inside that head of yours... Let's hear it! The face hidden within this photo's blurry, trailed shadow is...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the face behind the shadow!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I thought I said that you'd better have a GOOD explanation. I can't make heads or tails of what you're trying to say with that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrgh! <thought>W-Was I wrong...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Come on... Hurry up and show me what that shadow that's flying through the air is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I need to think calmly about this and find that other road the smuggled goods look...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Naturally, the shadow is the third smuggled object, the Primidux Statue replica.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You can't be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Yatagarasu... or rather Calisto Yew dressed as Agent Shih-na, was inside Babahl. She dressed the replica statue up in clothes, and launched it through the air.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah... Mr. Prosecutooooooor! You left out a very crucial bit in your explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know I did.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">She "launched it through the air"!? Hah... And how exactly did she do thaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He is literally baring his fangs at me...! But he has a point. How exactly did it move through the air like that? As long as this remains unsolved, we won't be able to move any closer to the truth! Which reminds me, didn't he say this earlier...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, sis... I remember that just before Ambassador Alba went to give his speech... ...he called you into his office, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So, just before the murder, Franziska was called here, right into this very room. If that's the case... then that may be another avenue I can pursue.</thought> Agent Lang. In order for me to answer that question... ...I will need to hear testimony from Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh...? What are you up to now, pretty boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Earlier, you mentioned something of interest to me. You said that just before the murder occurred... ...Ms. von Karma had been in this room because Ambassador Alba had called for her. And for that reason alone, you believe her to be the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, I guess I did say something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, I believe it is my duty to ask her what her side of the story is.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Do you really think a criminal would tell us the honest truth?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How dare you!? As I've said numerous times, there is absolutely no proof that I am the killer! Miles Edgeworth! Don't tell me you suspect me, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't. However, I can't ignore the fact that you were in this room at one point in time. Which is why I would like to hear about your movements in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Krngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... I feel that I still don't have enough information... ...which is why your testimony is incredibly important to the outcome of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............ Alright. So? What would you like me to talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I'd like you to please testify to your movements in this room until the murder occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph... Alright, let's try this your way for a change. But if what she has to say turns out to be a waste of time... ...I'll place her under arrest faster than you can howl "Nooooooooooooo!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">As I said earlier, I was assigned to guard duty in the Allebahstian Embassy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I want us to make this clear from the very beginning... ...so what I wish to confirm is that the only time span in which you were in this office... ...was before the murder occurred. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. <thought>For now, the only way that I can see for us to break out of this situation... ...is to ask Franziska about her testimony in more detail.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">As I said earlier, I was assigned to guard duty in the Allebahstian Embassy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought your duty was to fact-find anything you could about the smuggling ring?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, that was my job. But upon hearing that the Yatagarasu had sent a calling card to the Embassy... ...Ambassador Alba called upon us to protect the Embassy instead. That incident seven years ago... Or have you forgotten what happened here back then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>Anything related to that case we were involved in appears to be rather painful for her. It's not exactly one I can readily forget myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... It looks like you remember the case after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I do.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I inspected every location, every possible escape route... ...and every aspect of the police security detail. I did all that, then after that...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After I saw the Steel Samurai off on his way towards the ambassador's office...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were at the theater as well?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, and I suppose you were also there as well, watching that stage show?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, yes. <thought>So Franziska was there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... Well, after the show was over and I saw the Steel Samurai off...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I returned to the rose garden for a bit, and checked up on the security situation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you need to confirm the degree of preparation for even the speech?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">For security's sake, of course. What other reason could I have had? No one knew just how the Yatagarasu had planned on getting in, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And in the end, the Yatagarasu did choose to appear in the rose garden... Even if it did turn out to be nothing more than a shadow... Arngh... Who would've thought that she would use a shadow!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! C-Calm down, Franziska! <thought>She must still be nursing a grudge over the fact that she couldn't figure it out herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... Anyway, there was no one in the rose garden. And we were aware that the speech was set to start soon thereafter.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After all the preparations were in place, I was called back by Ambassador Alba to his office.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At that time, DeMasque II's body had yet to be found in this room, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's right. But Ambassador Alba was here. One could hardly miss his rather large presence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph! A criminal will say anything to get out of getting arrested! How do we know you're not lying!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, if you need proof, I'd be happy to oblige you.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Seriously!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Like I keep telling you... ...when I arrived at this office, Ambassador Alba was already here. He was standing by the flower box on the windowsill, watering his plants.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, I can attest to that. I remember speaking with the lovely lady around that time here in my office.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Grr! Alright, then... Add that statement to your testimony, and let's hear some details.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So Ambassador Alba was in this room at the time, was he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"When I arrived, Ambassador Alba was watering the flowers on the windowsill."</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">When I arrived, Ambassador Alba was watering the flowers on the windowsill.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the sake of being thorough, I'd like to ask you something. How did you know that Ambassador Alba was watering his plants at the windowsil?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The entrance to this room is on this side, however, the window is on the opposite side. If what you say is true, then when you entered the room, his body would've been like a wall. He would've been blocking your view of what he was doing. Isn't that not correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose it was a bit hard to see around him. But fortunately for me Ambassador Alba is not an immovable wall.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I knocked before I entered, and as I did, he turned around to greet me... ...with a watering can in his hand. So it's only natural to believe that he was watering his plants, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After his greeting, we spent a little time talking about his flowers. He had obtained them himself, and is growing them with the utmost care, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes... The plants in this room... They are all like my children.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The passionflowers in the flower box on the windowsill are growing beautifully, too. All four of them are in full bloom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Ms. von Karma, what did you say just now?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I said that the flowers are growing beautifully. What about that statement do you not understand?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What do I not understand? I do not understand why a certain thing is the way it is...</thought> I'd like for you to append that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"There were four large passionflowers in full bloom in the flower box."</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There were four large passionflowers in full bloom in the flower box.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to confirm this with you one more time. There were four passionflowers in bloom in that box, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes. I should hardly think I could have miscounted such eye-catching flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There must be a deeper meaning to this statement. And it appears that I must take a gamble on its meaning for me to make any progress!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The Primidux Statues were already switched by the time the murder happened. In light of that fact, what Franziska saw in this room before the crime... ...is of incredible importance!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... For some odd reason... your testimony contradicts with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It does appear that way.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! I know it! I knew we couldn't trust your words, sis!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! What are you doing discrediting Ms. von Karma like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, sir! If you keep this up, she's gonna get taken away, sir! Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">All I've done is state what I saw! I have made not a single mistake in my testimony! And for this... I am still under suspicion for murder. Is the number of flowers really all that important at this juncture, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At the very least, it is a contradiction in this enigmatic case. One that I find hard to dismiss as irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Then let's hear it, Mr. Prosecutor! What does the number of flowers have to do with anything? What does it prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the answer to that will become clear if we were to examine that flower box. <thought>How did this contradiction come about...? There must be something behind this discrepancy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Th-They're my beloved flowers. I've grown them with the utmost care. So I ask that you please be gentle with them as you examine them, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This watering can has a rather robust design.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Why are you telling us stuff we can clearly see for ourselves!? Plus, if you keep wasting time talking about that, Ms. von Karma's gonna get arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>I'd better examine something else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This flower box... It appears to be made of marble.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks that way. But, so what? Is it something that's so important that you absolutely had to mention it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, not exactly, but...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Miles Edgeworth. You DO understand our current situation, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, of course. I am fully aware of the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? Then in that case, allow me to ask you once again. Is what the flower box is made out of really all that important?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>It would appear that the construction of the flower box is not that important.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The name of these flowers... I believe they're called "passionflowers". Despite being called "flowers", they are actually a species of vine. They appear to be growing well, and are well-supported by these plant supports.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, but no matter how I look at it, it looks like there are only two here to me! You realize, don't you, sis... Your little lie has failed you!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh! Miles Edgeworth! Hurry up and shut this man up for me already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>I suppose I will need to use some evidence to "shut him up", won't I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Not yet... I still have a thing or two left to examine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I believe I have just the piece of evidence you require.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh? You do, do you!? You have such confidence in the face of your current plight... ...but I highly doubt it'll last until the end!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You howl like a wolf, Agent Lang... ...but we'll see if you have any bite to back up that bark after you see the evidence! The truth the passionflowers reveal can be seen in this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well? What do you think now, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! You may talk big... but as usual, it's nothing more than a big bluff!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk! <thought>Was I wrong!? Perhaps I should gather a bit more information before I attempt this again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hm...? This patch of soil looks as though it has had something removed from it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! What are you doing, Mr. Prosecutor? Why'd you clam up all of a sudden? I'm still here, waiting for an explanation, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you know, Agent Lang? Flowers are best appreciated in silence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...Tch.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like two things were pulled out of this flower box...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shih-na, who was supposedly in Babahl the entire time, had these "hair sticks" on her... ...that look exactly like the plant supports in this flower box. In other words, I believe it can be said that these "hair sticks" are in actuality... ...support sticks for the passionflowers!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! And so what!? Is this really all that important to the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aha... So this ring-like section... ...is there to support vines like passionflowers up, huh? But if that's all they were meant to do, then what is this notch on the top end?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Maybe it's for string or something to run through? To help the stick stay upright?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A notch for string to run through, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose this dirt was from when this plant support was stuck in the flower box.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess that's why only the tip is dirty, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course it is. It means that we've found yet another item that was smuggled between the countries tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aiya!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think about it logically, Agent Lang. These sticks were originally in Allebahst... ...but somehow, they wound up in Shih-na's hands, who was in Babahl the whole night. So make no mistake! These sticks were smuggled somehow, just like the knife and statue!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Arngh! Hmph! Very well, then! I want to hear from you exactly how they wound up in Babahl!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How did these support sticks find their way to Babahl and why? There must be some reason as to why they ended up there... Aha! So that's why!</thought> Agent Lang, if you would please take a look at this and tell me its shape.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph! It's just another stick, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... And so it is. But the shape of the support sticks is what is important. For when they are used with something in this room, that's when it all comes into focus. And the object that completes the picture when used with the support sticks is...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what used with the support sticks!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Isn't it obvious? Someone used those with this...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"Those with this"...? Could you be any more vague!? Why don't you try again!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, I suppose I should. <thought>It would appear that this was insufficient in conveying what I had wanted to say. The answer should become obvious to me if I just think calmly about it once more. But the only tjing that can really connect the two offices together has to be this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Th-That's a crossbow... Wait! You're not really suggesting...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I am. These hair sticks... or rather, plant support sticks... They make for perfect arrows!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aiyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought these loops were just an eccentric design quirk... ...but who knew that they were actually arrow fletchings?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've done it! I've found the common thread that connects the two offices! But this thread has yet to be completely untangled. Even using the arrows, how does this explain how the statues were transported? Furthermore, who could it have been who fired these sticks as arrows? There MUST be a common thread that ties all of these things together!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Mr. Prosecutor! Hold up a second! You do realize what happens when you tie a statue to an arrow, right? They don't fly at all!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So Babahl's statue was draped in the Yatagarasu's clothes, and then shot over here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Primidux Statues didn't sprout wings...? Hmph. Of course they didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Glad you understand. I feel you much better already. I was afraid for a second that you were unaware of that crucial fact!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's only crucial because you're under the belief that wings are necessary to this equation.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You need to free your mind a bit more, and let it fly like a bird on the wind. The Primidux Statues flew, but not on a wing. Allow me a bit of your time, and I'll explain this mysterious phenomenon to you!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So Babahl's statue was draped in the Yatagarasu's clothes, and then shot over here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But that incredible scene just happened to have been caught on film, resulting in this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! And what an incredible scene it was! This photo was taken by a freelance photojournalist, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, so I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And not every photojournalist is known to be honest, right? Especially not the ones that sell photos of spirits and giant creatures to tabloids.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I know what you mean. I've seen those sorts of photos many a time in court. But there have been times when those photos have turned out to be telling the truth. If you had ever stood in a court of law, you would know that it's entirely plausible.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! You really believe the stuff you're spewing right now? A courtroom certainly is a strange place, if what you say is true. But there really is something odd about that photo no matter how you look at it.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Even if you fired the arrows from this side, they wouldn't go far with a statue tied to them!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But we are in agreement that an arrow by itself would reach the other side, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But just the arrow by itself is pretty meaningless, don't you think, Mr. Prosecutor? Because the things they wanted to smuggle were a lot bigger than nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, that's not necessarily true.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What I need right now... ...is not further discussion of my conclusions; it's the launching of my conclusions! What the shooter wanted to launch with the crossbow was not the statues themselves! But rather, something a crossbow can launch that can be used to move the statues!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"If it wasn't a statue that was tied to the arrows, then what did the crossbow launch...?"</line>
<line speaker="Lang">If it wasn't a statue that was tied to the arrows, then what did the crossbow launch...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The thing the crossbow launched...? Allow me to show you the answer!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well, come on, then! Show me what you've got! But I warn you! I'll know when you're just bluffing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what was launched from this Allebahstian office with the crossbow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence is what was launched from here in Allebahst!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And what purpose, exactly, did launching that serve? Because if you're joking, it's not gonna be a fit of laughter I'm about to launch into!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! <thought>That was not the kind of launch I was looking for.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! I knew you couldn't explain this whole thing in a down-to-earth manner!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I don't think I need to tell you that the Primidux Statue didn't sprout wings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. The statues didn't need wings to fly.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Then how would YOU explain things? I'm almost looking forward to whatever fantastical explanation you come up with!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're a realist, after all, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course, and I assure you that my hypothesis is firmly grounded in reality.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Well, all I'm hearing is the fantasy of a desperate man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At times, even reality itself can be a mysterious thing. Even you must admit that.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, do I? If it's so true, then why don't you go ahead and show me!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! I think I understand what went sailing through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I suppose that's because you're an expert at things that fly through the air.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What did you expect from the second Yatagarasu!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Now, to show Agent Lang what really went soaring through the air tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Finally... Finally, we have reached this point in our discussion. For I present to you, that which was carried by the arrow from the crossbow!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh. I get it now, Mr. Prosecutor... I can see exactly what you are trying to say! You're saying that the wire was tied to an arrow and then shot into Mr. Coachen's office! All the way from the fifth floor of the Allebahstian Embassy... ...down to the third floor of the Babahlese Embassy!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">If what you're claiming is really what happened... ...I can see how Allebahst's Primidux Statue could be moved. Gravity could be used to move the statue down the wire from the fifth to the third floor. But then, what about Babahl's Primidux Statue? The dark shadow in this photo is clearly flying away from Babahl! Going in the opposite way of gravity, from the third floor of the Babahlese Embassy... ...up to the fifth floor of the Allebahstian Embassy...! How do you explain that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Aha! I think I finally see how the gears behind this whole trick works!</thought> Agent Lang, the "motion" used behind this trick... I wonder if perhaps you have yet to envision how it works in your head?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"Motion"? What motion?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the motion that was employed to smuggle Babahl's Primidux Statue!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A swinging motion was employed.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! You sure thought that one through, Mr. Prosecutor! Because if they used that... ...the statue would swing right into the building's wall!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>H-He does have me there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">For shame! You should sign yourself up for grade school physics for not realizing that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrrrrgh... <thought>I'm at a loss for words to that... I need to calm down and think through this once more. There is only one feasible motion that could've been used to send the statue up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bit of bungee action was employed!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...Bungee action? Are you saying that the wire acted as a bungee cord, and then the statue was hauled up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's a simple way of putting it, but yes.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Did you think about the weight of the statue at all? That thing is solid gold! Before that thing ever reached the office window, the wire would've snapped!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But OK, let's consider your idea and say that the wire has the elasticity required. If you fired that kind of wire from a crossbow... ...the arrow could come sailing back at the person who shot it! Talk about dangerous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrrrrgh! <thought>H-He's absolutely right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">I thought this sort of thing was common knowledge. I'm having a bit of hard time right now dealing with a jurisdiction thief... ...who lacks understanding of the most basic things like physics, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Unfortunately for me, it appears that Agent Lang is correct. I need to calm down and think through this once more. There is only one feasible motion that could've been used to send the statue up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it was done via rotary motion. If the two statues were transported simultaneously...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"Simultaneously"!? Get real! The statues would collide somewhere along the way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did I ever say that there was only one line of wire between the two offices? If you shot an arrow with the two ends of a wire tied to it, a circular belt can be formed.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Don't object and call a success what is beyond reasonability." Talking into account the tension difference between the two wires... ...the top one would sag too much to the point where the statues would collide anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang... As you know, the Primidux Statue is a one-of-a-kind national treasure. And the fact that Babahl's statue is a hollow replica of the real statue... ...it would naturally be lighter than the real one, meaning that my idea is very possible!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: HOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOWL!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here is what I believe happened. Ms. Yew and her mystery co-conspirator set themselves up in the two different rooms. The co-conspirator bridged the rooms by shooting the 2 ends of the wire down on 1 arrow. Then the two of them covered the statues and proceeded to transport the statues. After the switch was completed, another arrow was fired... ...carrying the other end of the wire down to Babahl, where it was to be disposed of. And to do that, Ms. Yew hid it inside the grandfather clock. Q.E.D.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...Hah! Ha ha ha ha... Grr!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This proves it, right, Agent Lang!? That I'm not the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not yet, sis. I still haven't had my dessert yet. Right, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The proof is in the pudding, as it were?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Pudding IS a nice dessert. So? Do you think you can do it? Can you prove that what you said is what happened? Because remember, if you can't... ...I'll be taking a certain someone back home with me as a souvenir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree that as long as there is no proof, my hypothesis remains just that. However... ...what I have laid out is no mere hypothesis, for there is one more piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">One more? This should be interesting. You think you have a piece of evidence that will turn your hypothesis into fact...? Well then, let's see it, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The thing that made it possible to create a circular belt out of a length of wire... I believe that it is right here in this very room! Now then, I believe this is what made the circular belt transportation method possible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The circular belt method was made possible thanks to this part of the room!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Don't you mean "impossible", Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I have to say, I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Haaa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Even the one in the most precarious situation here agrees with me!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I am a Von Karma... ...and as I have a name to uphold... ...I refuse to accept anything that is less than perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>I guess I was mistaken... I need to take another good look at this room. There is something here that made it possible to create a circular belt out of wire!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! Looks like you dropped another bomb on us again!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The last piece to the trick... are two pulleys!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely! The ceiling fans double as pulleys in this case! And thanks to the fact that there is one installed in each of the offices... ...the ceiling fans made for the perfect pulley set for the wire to run on!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">A...Aaa.........Arruuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This must be it! This is how the smugglers bypassed the impenetrable security!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha... Ha ha ha ha ha! Grr... You really are something else, Mr. Prosecutor! I bet you've figured it all out already, haven't you!? You know who the bug hotshot that set up this real-life stage show is, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The person who set up this rather large and complex stage show... ...needs to be someone who had foreknowledge of... ...the existence of a ceiling fan in both the Allebahstian and Babahlese offices. And that the passionflowers' support stakes could be used as arrows...</thought> The real mastermind behind this case.........</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Well!? Don't you dare make this wolf wait for his food!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Why are you so hesitant, Miles Edgeworth? If you can't say who it is, why don't you present something like you always do!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A single point of the finger here, and this case will explode into an international incident. However! It's already too late for me to stop the forward momentum! It appears that I have no choice now... but to rush in!</thought> There is a piece of evidence that will point us to who the mysterious mastermind is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well? What do you think now, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hah! You may talk big... but as usual, it's nothing more than a big bluff!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk! <thought>Was I wrong!? Perhaps I should gather a bit more information before I attempt this again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This smuggling could not have been possible without the use of the crossbow. Furthermore, the arrows that were shot by the crossbow... ...were plucked, as it were, from the flower box in this very room. They were planted so long ago that the passionflowers had the time to grow so big... ...that Ms. von Karma didn't even notice the arrows when she visited this room today!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On top of all this, the fact that the culprit knew that both offices had ceiling fans... ...tells us that the person has very detailed information on the embassy's layout. So as you may have already guessed, the person I am accusing of hatching this plan... ...is the person who grew the flowers in the flower box with the utmost care. Thus, it can only be you! Quercus Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you out of your mind, Miles Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm certain of what I am saying, and I am sure that he is the culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh... Heh heh heh heh......... Haaa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Tell me, Mr. Prosecutor. What was the ambassador trying to accomplish by doing all that stuff you just outlined? Why in the world would he need to use a trick like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand your need to doubt me. However, there is one thing that stands out to me as very odd.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Just one thing, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The one, single end result Ambassador Alba sought to obtain... If we were to examine the focus of this complex trick... ...I believe we will finally find the answer to everything!</thought> Everything will become clear once we examine this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lang">You want us to examine this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, for I believe that by examining it, we will finally have all of our answers.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Items that become evidence should never have any part overlooked." All evidence related to this case are fine and don't need to be examined again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! <thought>I-It would appear that I was mistaken... Agent Lang is correct... Most of the evidence has already undergone intense scrutiny. However, there is one piece that has only been partially checked... And that piece, which lies at the heart of the smuggling, is what I should present!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would fully understand the reasoning had the situation been the reserve. However, to go through the trouble of swapping the real Primidux Statue for the fake... I sense a very shady reason for such a bizarre action! And who better to ask for that reason than King Primidux himself!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I see... Ambassador, we'll be examining that statue now, with or without your permission!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............................................................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With his sword drawn like that, there is an aura of valor and bravery around King Primidux.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He looks so cool standing like that with the sword stuck in the ground in front of him. Maybe I should try and come up with some cool pose with a shuriken or something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I am seriously beginning to think that her real goal in life is to become a ninja.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. There isn't anything particularly odd about the sword, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not really. I suppose we should examine a different area of the statue now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A shield, huh... There doesn't seem to be anything unusual about it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I bet it's supposed to mean that the guy is protecting something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think it's supposed to have that deep of a meaning behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">In that case, what are we wasting time with this for? Let's look at some other area!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These are Mr. Coachen's fingerprints. The fact that they're on here suggests that this statue once belong to Babahl.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So it was smuggled from Babahl to Allebahst, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why was there a need for them to smuggle it in?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmm... This guy kind of looks like the Steel Samurai, don't you think? Maybe it's because they look alike that he was picked to be the goodwill ambassador?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose that's possible. ............Hm? Take a look at this area around the base of his neck. It looks like a gap.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! You're right! Maybe it's meant to be some kind of secret?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps it's possible to open the statue from this gap in its construction!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hurry up and open it, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Alright, here goes.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! It really did open up! Hey, what's this thing that fell out?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? I believe a more thorough examination of it is required.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What in the...!? Is this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey! Is this what I think it is...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's a plate... for making counterfeit bills!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Somehow... it appears that we've at long last arrived... ...at the exit to this complex labyrinth! We finally hold within our hands, one of the counterfeit money plates... ...and the reason why the replica was smuggled into Allebahst to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Primidux Statue can only be handled by the ambassador or the secretariat. And the replica is nothing more than a hollow shell covered in gold. These two circumstances make the statue the ideal object in which to hide contraband. After receiving the statue containing the counterfeit plate from Shih-na... ...the ambassador had the misfortune of accidentally running into DeMasque II. Surprised by the thief, the ambassador raised the replica statue at DeMasque II, and... Then, in order to frame the Steel Samurai of murder... ...he covered the Samurai Sword in blood. Well, Ambassador Alba?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a counterfeit plate used to make counterfeit Zheng Fa bills. It's incredibly detailed, and even includes a phoenix taking off into the sky. With plates as finely crafted as these, it's no wonder the fakes are so hard to spot.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You're... the leader of the smuggling ring? My country is a mess... ...and it's all because of you!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">YOU'RE... the one who killed DeMasque II?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Answer us!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................I never thought... I never thought... that you would figure things out to this level.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">However, there is one point I disagree with you on. The head of the smuggling ring was......... Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Quite screwin' around! I have no sympathy for someone who would try to pass the guilt onto a dead man! If there is one thing I'm sure of, it's that you're the real ringleader, Quercus Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's not good to speak with such subjectivity, you know, Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">"Subjectivity"? My conclusion is anything but, and is the result of logic and investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">"Logic and investigation"? Only seconds ago, you were ready to arrest Ms. von Karma. I don't think we can give such flip-floppy logic any real weight, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh......... .........Heh heh heh... Haa ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It looks like you still don't get why I came back.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You see, the reason I came back... ...is so that I could sink my fangs into your wrinkly, old neck! From the very beginning, my real target has been you!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agent Lang! I demand an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry, sis. I didn't mean to put you through all that. I knew you were innocent from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You did...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I knew that this whole incident had been meticulously planned and prepared for. So naturally, the occupant of this room, Ambassador Alba, seemed the most suspicious. But without the ambassador's permission, we couldn't get in to take another look around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, so that's why you put on this big show to accuse Franziska of the murder! Using Franziska as the bait, you were able to gain us entry and investigative rights!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, if I hadn't done that, I doubt the ambassador would've given the OK to poke around.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So that's what all this was about... Very well, I will forgive you. But in exchange for using me as bait... ...you will take some responsibility and help us find the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, for giving me such a great opening... I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">............You know, I just knew, Mr. Prosecutor... ...that somehow, if we were able to find some proof by investigating this room... ...that you would be able to figure out the real culprit with your special brand of logic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh, the evidence detectives collect combined with the logic of a prosecutor... That's just as it should be in a "prosecutor - detective team", right?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Tch. I don't know about all that! But one thing I do know is that I'm itching to see that old man get what's coming to him!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ho ho. You're quite scary when you want to be, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, you were the one who was planning to use me to push all the guilt onto the sis. But unfortunately for you, you misjudged me!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................Agent Lang, I wish for you to stop trying to intimidate me. What we need right now is evidence and proof. I wonder if you have what is necessary to prove that I am the head of the smuggling ring?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't be such a sore loser! If you really are the head of the smuggling ring... ...then you should acknowledge your crimes with dignity!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Dignity...? That is nothing more than a fool's insincere display of strength. If you really wish for me to acknowledge my crimes... ...then I would like to first see some of this thing you call "evidence".</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Grr...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I tell you... I knew nothing. Really. I didn't even know that a counterfeit plate was hidden inside that statue.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You swapped a real statue that vested in your country the authority to rule for a sake. It doesn't make any sense that you didn't know anything!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It doesn't make sense? Where doesn't it make sense? Can you prove that it doesn't make sense?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...He's really got us. He's... turned the entire situation around against us.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The proof that Interpol has been after which points to this man as the ringleader... If we can somehow find that proof now, then we can see to it that justice is finally served! Is there nothing I can use to break this case wide open!?</thought> ...! The trump card and the video tape... <thought>With those two items... ...we might be able to finally bring this man down. But...! The card is evidence from a case that Mr. Faraday hid away in secret... ...and the tape was stolen by Detective Badd from the police. They're both illegal evidence! No matter what, a protector of the law can't be allowed to use such pieces of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Needless to say... ...we Von Karmas are commanded to achieve nothing but victory! And by any means necessary!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The only way to bring someone like that to justice was to do so outside of the courts... That's what we thought... at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I no longer follow the path of Manfred von Karma... ...and I won't follow the path of the Yatagarasu! This leaves me with what? What creed will I believe in? If I want to pursue the truth, then I will sully my hands in illegality... ...and if I want to pursue justice, then I will lose the truth! What is the "law", and what is "justice"? And which path is a "prosecutor" supposed to follow!? That choice... is one I must make by my own hand here and now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I am a prosecutor, and I can't allow myself to use evidence such as these!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! If you don't do something, Ambassador Alba is going to get away with it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I know, but...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you holding back for? The only thing a Von Karma should pursue is the perfect proof. If you really do have what it takes to complete our argument... ...then there is absolutely no reason not to use it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "The reason people judge people is because people are people." People weren't born to be chained to the law; laws were born to protect the people. You're the only one here right now who can put this guy out to pasture... ...and that is the only way a second or a third generation of Zheng Fa's people will be born. Can you really still hesitate knowing the fate of a nation rests in your hands?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is no limit to the law. Any limit that exists was set there by man. When a person goes beyond that limit, then the law, too, crosses into new territory! For what reason were laws invented? The answer to that is what I must now show!</thought> Ambassador Alba. I wonder if you might recognize this.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...! Oh, I wonder what that card is? I've never seen that before in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a directives card used by the leader of the ring to relay instructions to his subordinates.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh? Is that what it is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This card was sent to the real culprit behind the KG-8 Incident, ten years ago... A man by the name of Mr. Manny Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........Oh. So why do you have such a card in your possession?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because it was hand-delivered to me... ...by a certain Great Thief... The Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The Yatagarasu gave that to you...? Don't talk nonsense, and let's be serious, Mr. Edgeworth. Do you have any proof that the card contains directions from the ringleader?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll have you know that the card is not the only thing I was given!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This contains security footage that was shot just before the start of the KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...The KG-8 Incident...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The card and the video... These two pieces of evidence are what will seal your fate!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............Hoho, very interesting. I must admit I am very curious now. Very curious indeed in these "case-deciding" pieces of evidence you've presented.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The prey the Yatagarasu has been chasing all this time... now stands before me. I can't allow this man, who has had free reign for ten long years, to simply walk away. Now is the time for me to bring to fruition the valiant spirit that was given to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">So, what is this interesting thing that you wanted to show me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The trump card and the video tape... These two pieces of evidence together make for the ultimate hand! And this is where the real meaning behind Detective Badd's words will realized!</thought> Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you see here is security footage shot just before the KG-8 murder occurred. From this footage, we know that the card is a directives card from the smuggling ring. This is the section that proves that the card was used to relay an order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take a look at this area.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What about that area...? My eyes aren't what they used to be, so I can't see what you're pointing at too well. But from what I can see, it doesn't look like it's related to our conversation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! <thought>It's unrelated...!? I need to remain calm and take another look at this footage. What is the vital clue that shows us that card was used to relay an order!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you can see, Mr. Coachen is holding the card in his right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I see. The killer is indeed holding a card with the exact same design on it. But the card and the one you have... Just because they look the same, doesn't mean that they are, does it now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but there is a very easy way for me to prove that they are, in fact, one and the same. All we have to do is simply take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to Detective Badd... ...Ambassador Alba's directive cards bears the mark of a three-legged raven... ...or in other words, a yatagarasu. I suppose this mark was the inspiration for their group's name, the Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A section of the text has been obscured by blood, but it's clear the writing is Cohdopian. According to Detective Badd... ..."Silence Cece Yew"... ...is what is written here... ...along with the method to be used and where she lived. The evil intent displayed in this writing will not go unpunished!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This dark red blood... Yes, this is your proof. Proof that the orders on this card were played out in that terrible tragedy! The blood belonged to the victim of the KG-8 Incident. With a bit of DNA testing, we can very easily verify that as fact.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you have no objections... ...then I'd like for you to take a look at this next piece of footage! This car that passed by in front of the victim's apartment building... It's an official Cohdopian government car.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! If you could please magnify the footage! This area of the footage directly links the smuggling ring with Cohdopia!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This section will make it all clear to us!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........You must be very tired, Mr. Edgeworth. If you continue presenting completely irrelevant evidence like this... ...I'm afraid your investigation may fall apart. Perhaps it is time for you to retire.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait! <thought>Arngh! But I was so sure it was this area...! Alright, focus, Miles. The area I should be pointing out is definitely here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The shape of this pocket... and the directives card in it... It tells us that without a doubt, this person in this car is Mr. Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The license plate on the car was also captured by the security camera. And with it, we can easily find out who was sitting in this car on that day, ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnnrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which is why I can say with confidence that you were riding in this car on that day!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Arnnnnnnnnnnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................Hah. Hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah! You've done well, boy, to make it this far. However...! About your claim that I was riding in the car at the time... That's going to be mighty difficult to prove.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The Principality of Cohdopia no longer exists. So naturally, all records from that time period also no longer exist.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! That arrogance... What he really means is he's already erased all traces of them!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Are we finished here, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The only weapon I have left to me now... is this piece of footage! There must be something here that I can use against him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, what do you think about this area?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you have to confer with someone, then it's obviously a useless piece of logic!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnoooh! <thought>Arngh! She's right. The only logic that can trap Ambassador Alba is a perfectly iron-clad one. There must be something here in this footage! There must be something that shows that Ambassador Alba was riding in the car that day! No matter how insignificant it may seem, a clue must be hiding here, and I must find it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What the...! Ambassador Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were once an army man in the service of Cohdopia. And it was you who made the many missions you participated in successes, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. Why the sudden back-handed praises, boy? Although, to be sure... ...the brilliant medals on my breast were awarded to me during the era of Cohdopia. But now, I am the only one who owns this particular medal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case... the only person it could be who is sitting in this car is you!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">How do you figure that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By the medal captured here in this footage! It is clearly the same exact medal as the one on your chest!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is how it will be... But I won't look back. For this is the path that I have chosen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnnrrr... Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha. You've moved me with your devotion to this case, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why is he taking such an arrogant stance with me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's almost looking possible, isn't it? For the lot of you to have come this far... It looks like I just might lose our little game this time.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You might lose the game "this time"...? You don't get another round, Mr. Ambassador!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Is that a fact? ...Very well. I've decided to confess and admit my guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're... going to confess?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And I will accept whatever punishment that may come as a result.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What the...?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Regarding the DeMasque II murder, I admit it... I did it out of self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're claiming it was justified self-defense!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">DeMasque II attacked me, and I felt that my life was in danger. If I hadn't done what I did, I might be the one you found dead instead of him.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Haa ha ha ha ha ha ha! What a pathetic performance!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha ha ha ha! I'm not giving you one!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, you two really know how to laugh at inappropriate times!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you wish to claim it was justified self-defense, then we will need some evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's always the evidence with you, isn't it? But if that's what you require, I'll provide it. That man left a mark on me when he attacked!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I don't particularly want to show it off, but this is proof that it was in self-defense. I'm an old man, and sometimes I don't pay enough attention when I should...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But DeMasque II didn't have a single weapon on his body!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hold on. It's nothing to get worked up over, because... I hid the weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You hid it?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I'm sorry, but as you know, a murder is a murder, even if it's in self-defense. And I couldn't let it become public, seeing as how I AM an ambassador... This is the weapon you seek, my special bonsai trimming shears.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oongh... It's covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">He was trembling quite badly during our struggle... ...but that's when he grabbed the shears that were sitting in my office and attacked. So you see, it was an act of self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Is he right, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Since he has both a wound and the weapon that caused it, it's enough to declare it so.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">N-No way...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh, which reminds me. I guess there is still one more accusation I need to resolve. Smuggling and counterfeiting. Unfortunately, all of that is my secretary's doing. I had no knowledge it was going on.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Stop spewing nonsense! You're trying to throw my investigation under the bus in your desperation. If you want to get real honest... ...everything in this case can be connected to you!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The murder of DeMasque II was done in self-defense...!? In my trials, no man escapes his crime alive!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Perhaps so, if you were my opponent in court. However, there is one very important fact that I think you may have forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that...? .................. A.........Aaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Arngh! That's what you mean! Extraterritoriality...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That's right. This embassy sits on what is effectively Allebahstian soil. So any trial that is to be held will be held in Allebahst. Therefore, the crime I just admitted to will never be tried in your courts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang! What is Interpol's stance on this!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Agents investigate. That's our job. The judgment of people who have confessed to their crime... that's the court's job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And I've already confessed to all of my crimes, Agent Lang. Furthermore, by the very nature of my position, I have full extraterritorial rights. These rights are effective, even on your country's soil. Therefore... ...no matter where a crime may take place, I will never stand trial in one of your courts!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That arrogance... and your expression... That's nothing like the face of someone who is ready to accept the consequences. Don't tell me you have your own country's judicial system eating right out of your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">These "crimes" you all speak so seriously of... To me, this has all been nothing more than a game. You may chase me out of this embassy with your accusations... ...but it's no big deal. Allebahst has numerous other embassies in other countries around the world. All you would accomplish is you would change the backdrop of our little game!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>These two layers of protection that extraterritoriality provides him... This is why he is one of those who cannot be brought to court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You see now, don't you? I live in a whole different world than you. Now, if you'll excuse me, I need to go and fetch your eviction papers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! Is there nothing we can do!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe it, sir! Extraterritoriality...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... and there is nothing we can really do about that. In the end, we didn't have enough authority to bring him to justice.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't believe that even though we know he's the boss, we can't lay a finger on him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.................. Hey, Mr. Prosecutor, sorry to skip out on you, but I've got some business to take care of.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If we can't even give an evil guy like him a slap on the wrist... ...then what the heck were laws created for!? What good are they!? If the law can't help us... ...then I'll go as the Yatagarasu, and take care of this myself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you dare!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Sorry, that was a bit too harsh.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I know how you feel, sir. We're trying to take on an ambassador, after all. And he did tell us earlier to get out of the theater. This is kinda their country, I guess... ...but I feel like I've been slapped across the face for just doing my job.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What... am I going to do? Should I retreat for now, and formulate a better plan of attack...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on, everyone! We can't give up yet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I want you to think about something for a sec! We've never let up for even a second, and as long as we don't stop investigating... ...we might find the "rotten" treasure hidden here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sh-She's right!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You're right, Kay. Very well. Let us re-open the investigation and see what we find. Come on, Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Right behind you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK! Then I'll go check out Babahl a bit more, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And I have something that I need to investigate further in Allebahst.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now then... ...before I gather any more information, I should do a bit of housekeeping.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ambassador Alba seemed agitated <thought>Agitated Alba - I sense that there is something he doesn't want us to investigate.</thought> over something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder why?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are two special circumstances that surround the ambassador. First, the embassy itself has extraterritorial rights. If something happens on Allebahstian soil... ...we are unable to legally prosecute him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Cool! It sounds like embassies are the perfect place to steal whatever you want!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And murder DeMasque II, run a smuggling operation, and make counterfeit bills apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But I thought all the counterfeiting was done by Mr. Coachen in Babahl?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he apparently used the embassy's coupon printing press <thought>Coachen's counterfeiting op. - Used Babahlese Embassy's printing press and Babahlese ink to make counterfeit bills.</thought> to do it. But it's the same story over there anyway. Babahl also has extraterritorial rights. Which brings me to my next point: the ambassador's extraterritorial rights. Those rights are effective even in our own country.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No matter what happens, he can never be tried in our courts. He retains some very special rights, indeed. Basically, no matter what wrongs he may commit, we can't bring him to trial here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So I guess we really don't stand a chance, do we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... We might stand a chance if we can somehow nullify either one of his special rights.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We know that the counterfeit bills were printed using the embassy's press... ...but the necessary materials, such as the Babahlese ink and paper... ...must have been hidden in a secure location. But what do you think would've happened if the renovation had begun?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, he probably had to find a better hiding place, or get rid of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right, so we can assume that the renovation was the cause of the plate and bills disposal. And the reason Mr. Coachen was killed as the "ringleader" of the smuggling operation. ...Based on what we know, who do you think was the one with the most to gain?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The answer is Ambassador Palaeno.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Y-You really think so!? But he was the one who had his embassy's offices burned down... ...and he lost his secretary. Do you really think he profited from any of that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Now that you mention it, perhaps not... <thought>She's right... Ambassador Palaeno has gained absolutely nothing from the events of tonight. With that being the case, there really is only one man who gained from everything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The answer is Mr. Coachen himself.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... He was the smuggling ring's boss, right? So maybe he had a lot to gain because of all the money...? But in the end, he was killed... It's kind of sad, really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose there is some truth in that. <thought>No matter how much he may have profited in life, he really didn't gain much in his death. With that being the case, there really is only one man who gained from everything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the one person who has been erasing all evidence of the smuggling operation... ...from both embassies, the co-conspirator who is mopping up, Ambassador Alba. Ambassador Alba had a very strong motive to kill Manny Coachen <thought>Motive to kill Coachen - Alba could conveniently place all of the guilt for the smuggling onto Coachen.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The cause of Ambassador Alba's agitation, the "rotten" treasure we may find... ...and the motive for killing Mr. Coachen... Ms. Yew said it herself that she didn't kill anyone tonight. If we were to take her words at face value... ...then the reason for the ambassador's nervousness can only be one thing. He didn't want us to discover the real circumstances under which Mr. Coachen was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then you mean, Ambassador Alba is the real killer? But I thought the two of them were friends?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe they were, but what if Mr. Coachen was the one who first betrayed their friendship?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, I get it! Wasn't Mr. Coachen pushing really hard for Mr. Palaeno... ...to be ambassador after the reunification?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and that was the real reason why he wanted to steal Allebahst's Primidux Statue.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So Mr. Coachen hired DeMasque II to go steal it for him... ...but when Ambassador Alba found out what he was up to, he killed Mr. Coachen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is definitely a possibility at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Those two really were thinking of no one but themselves. But the question now is "how did he do it?" Ambassador Alba was in Allebahst... ...but Mr. Coachen's body was discovered in Babahl, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right. And that is what we must solve next.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We've come too far to give up! We must expose Ambassador Alba's misdeeds, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And we've gotta find a way to steal the truth and get it out there... for my father's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, and we will. <thought>The reason for Ambassador Alba's nervousness must still be here somewhere. Furthermore, I need to pin down exactly what happened in here... I'll start thoroughly examining this room for any information I can find.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! If you don't pay attention, Ambassador Alba is gonna get away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Now hurry up and do that *schwing!* thing you always do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no idea what you are talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? You don't!? Oh, come on, you know what I'm talking about! That thing you do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are you talking about "Logic"...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes! That's it! So hurry up and let's *schwing!* already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-Alright, alright... <thought>To be honest, it's been a bit hard to connect everything up until now by just looking. However, I should be able to piece things together if I take another look at my leads. Perhaps now is the time to use logic and reason my way to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uncle Badd entrusted you with this piece of evidence, Mr. Edgeworth. I think he believes that you're the one who will finally bring the truth to light.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And I believe in you, too, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Guard">On the orders of Ambassador Alba, no one is allowed into Allebahst.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! But I thought a lady with a whip passed through here not too long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">She is from Interpol, and had the proper paperwork... ...so, while I was reluctant, I had to let her in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Heh... Sounds like Franziska alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">Besides... if I didn't... that whip of hers...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>.........Yup, definitely Franziska...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a backdrop they used in the Steel Samurai stage show today.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I loved the climax of that show! "Steel Samurai Sushi Slice!" That was the first time I'd seen that special move! But, well, the Jammin' Ninja stage show's climax was much better, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Oh, is that a fact?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That scene where he sang for Princess Misola and gave her those hair sticks? I could totally feel the love there in my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Perhaps the Jammin' Ninja is just more popular with female audiences...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Flowers were sent by a variety of people and businesses to celebrate the goodwill event. Even the Steel Samurai received some flowers from the ambassadors.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">There are so many bouquets here, it's like a wedding ceremony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe the flowers for those are for a slightly different reason...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you mean!? This event was supposed to be like a wedding between Allebahst and Babahl, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Actually, I believe they're more in a state of divorce.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK, then! This event was supposed to be their remarriage ceremony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose you could call it that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This was taken just before the two ambassadors gave their bouquets to the Steel Samurai. <thought>Wait, is it just my imagination... ...or is there something in this picture that I've seen before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't believe he was pretending to be a harmless old grandpa. Talk about deceptive!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't suppose anyone expected him to change that drastically...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I bet he's thinking of something evil behind that cheery smile!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, please try to remain calm and focused on the here and now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, you're right. Sorry I got all worked up there. Well, the only way we're going to be able to steal the truth is if we keep on investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears to be a bouquet of Persian cyclamens and roses.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! You even know the exact species!? I never would've figured you for an expert on flowers!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnnngh... <thought>It's all because of those flowers that old lady sends me every month... Just look at me; I sound like some sort of botanist!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, umm, what exactly is this yellow flower here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... That one... I'm not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? You don't know!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As far as I can recall, I've never seen a flower like this before. But I feel as though I've seen this shape somewhere before...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's that troublemaker, standing there smack in the center making two peace signs.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, the Steel Samurai stands out even more than the two ambassadors in this picture! Oh, hey! The person playing the Steel Samurai is one of your friends, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................No, I have no idea who he is.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wait! But you just said "he"! You knew which gender he was, so you MUST know him, right!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I beg that you please refrain from talking about that person with me ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Palaeno has a really great smile, don't you think!? I bet he was really happy that they were going to become Cohdopia again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perhaps... But instead, he became the greatest victim in today's case. An ambassador like him who is always thinking of his country is really to be admired.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah. Although this happened, I hope they'll be able to reunite the country someday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I hope so as well, but for that to happen, we need to solve this case first. We need to see to it that those who would harm the new Cohdopia are locked away.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And we will!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems that lilies are at the center of this bouquet, with an accent of chamomile.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow... I can totally smell the wonderful fragrance!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay... this is just a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Argh! Look, I know that! But it's nice to imagine things once in a while, ya know? Where's your sense of empathy!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you can smell the fragrance of flowers from a photo, that's more like a "hallucination".</line>
<line speaker="Kay">! Y-You don't have to be mean about it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Let's just drop this before it's in full bloom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could this piece of evidence be related to this photo somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Well... Nope! I don't think it's related at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even though I know she's right, she could have at least tried to humor me a little.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Babahl's national symbol is the butterfly, and Allebahst's is the flower... It would appear that someone is employing the old "hide a tree in a forest" trick.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you mumbling to yourself about...? Wait, what? The handle on this knife... Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it's the handle that was supposed to be on the blade that killed Mr. Coachen. The weapon that killed him was carried through the Theatrum Neutralis... ...in the very bouquet Ambassador Alba was carrying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? The flower motif... It looks like one of the flower petals is missing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh! And take a look at the weapon itself! It's missing the exact same petal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then the knife in this photo is most definitely the same as this murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can see the Babahlese Embassy, which is undergoing major renovations. From room expansions to garden upkeep, it looks like a lot of construction is going on.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Palaeno said that all this work is really hard on him. He said that since Mr. Coachen passed away, that maybe I could work part-time for him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She got really chummy with that ambassador...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">What can I say? I just have a good nose for money!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Hello! And welcome to the Embassy of Babahl!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but I don't really need to enter your country at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Right now, for a limited time here at the Babahlese Embassy... ...we're offering the very special "Experience the Terrifying Fire's Ashes Tour!" So, how about it? Shall I sign you up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...We're fine, thanks. <thought>We have an investigation to run.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe we now understand... ...why Ambassador Alba was so nervous and agitated. It must have something to do with where Mr. Coachen was killed. A place where the Allebahstian ambassador was likely to meet the Babahlese Mr. Coachen. The place where Ambassador Alba happened to have committed the murder is...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This area is rather suspicious, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You really think so? Because I don't see anything odd about it at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>I guess it's not related after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! If you keep doing that, Ambassador Alba is going to get away! Come on! Let's see if we can't get a hold of that treasure known as the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agreed. Let's see what we can find.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only place that makes sense is here, at the Threatrum Neutralis.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What? Here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The goodwill event was being held here today, correct? So the only place that the both of them would have been in is here.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But if that's the case, then everything changes. The theater isn't actually Allebahstian land... ...so that wipes out one of those extraterritorial rights he has!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It makes logical sense, in which case, it is a reason for us to investigate further.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So what should we check out?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's see... I believe we should check the immigration records for both Allebahst and Babahl posthaste! Babahl's records should be easy to obtain, however, the problem will be Allebahst. I wonder if they would allow us to see their records, despite the order to vacate...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm already one step ahead of you, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have here, the security footage from both Allebahst and Babahl. You would do well to take a look at its contents.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You move fast.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A Von Karma strives to be perfect in every way! It's not in my nature to keep on retreating like this. I took the liberty of looking over the Babahl investigation reports as well. From now on, you will make no excuse to back down or say that we can't solve this case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I'm sorry about earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We won't be beaten. Because my cute little subordinate is going to try his very best, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hasn't she patronized me enough already for a lifetime?</thought> So this video contains footage from Allebahst's immigration screening area?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I really hope there's something in here that we can use!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which minute's footage should I examine?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">5:21 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's just after the end of the Steel Samurai stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">We were still inside the theater itself at around this time. All because Mr. Edgeworth wouldn't get out of his seat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I wanted to show the actors my appreciation for a bit and soak in the atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, with your eyes closed and a complete lack of motion except for some breathing.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This man is the immigration officer who was on duty.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's making a really scary face... even though there's no one around to see it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder if he's just the grumpy sort? Although, that's wouldn't do much for tourism.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! He smiled a little just now!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder if he recalled something funny?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, even if he did, he still has that hard glare in his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that he was born with stern-looking eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Rather fitting for someone in the security business, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh, I don't remember all these posters! I wonder what they're of?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, I do remember a bunch of these hanging in that hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I believe they were all related to tourism and sightseeing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In Allebahst? Impossible! If it were Babahl, I could believe that, however...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No, no. They were posters promoting tourist traps in this country! And I believe they were mostly of Gatewater Land.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. So they were targeted at the embassy's staff...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the door leading into the Theatrum Neutralis.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I tired so hard to get through this door, you know, but I just couldn't get in. But it felt soooo great when I finally was allowed to go through there! You know what I really wanted to do, though? I wanted to try sneaking my way in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* At least nothing seems out of the ordinary with the door.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">5:22 PM. At around this time, the Steel Samurai stage show had come to an end... ...and Ambassador Alba was making his way back to his office.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And then later, he shook hands with the Steel Samurai in his office... ...and then, he was going to give a speech in the rose garden. Being an ambassador sounds like a busy, busy job! It's like someone is always stealing your time away!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'd imagine it's something like that. <thought>But despite how busy he was, he still managed to find the time to kill Mr. Coachen... ...and move his body somehow from the Theatrum Neutralis.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This man is the immigration officer who was on duty.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's making the exact same scary face that he was making a minute ago! Wait. Is it just me, or is he blushing?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It appears that he gets flustered around the ambassador.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess the ambassador's well-respected inside Allebahst, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You could say that. The guard doesn't appear to be capable of looking at the ambassador.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Those are posters of this country's tourist spots, though most are of Gatewater Land.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder if Allebahstians in general like theme parks at all?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The guard who stopped you has been to Gatewater Land a number of times, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess they don't have theme parks in Allebahst, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't believe how completely fooled I was by the way he carried himself.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He had me fooled, too... According to the files I had sent for earlier, Ambassador Alba... ...was a Cohdopian hero. He saved the royal family from danger countless times. So what bothers me is why would a man like that create a smuggling ring...? Even with all the authority I have, I still haven't been able to figure out why.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like the ambassador was a hero who was corrupted by evil. But no matter what happened in the past, we can't let the man he is now escape justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the door leading into the Theatrum Neutralis.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The more the guy tried to keep me out, the more I wanted to get in! It's human nature! But I guess I can't complain too much. I did get let inside in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* At least nothing seems out of the ordinary with the door.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">5:23 PM... This is just after the end of the Steel Samurai stage show... ...and after I had been given that autograph.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You totally had stars in your eyes at that time, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I most certainly did not!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You had stars in your eyes because of an autograph you received from that man...? Miles Edgeworth... You've just lost any respect I had left for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I believe it's time to change the subject.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that he is inspecting the person coming into the country.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you kidding!? It's more like he's NOT checking the Steel Samurai! Hmph! And then they gave me such a hard time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... There ARE certain risks involved when you give some people preferential treatment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There certainly is a variety of posters on this wall.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's kinda hard to see what's written on them, so they just look festive, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Those are all tourism posters for this country, although most are of Gatewater Land.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder if any Allebahstians actually go to Gatewater Land for fun? It's just really hard to imagine them hanging out there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">True, they do seem to be a nation of extremely serious people...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the outside, he may look like the Steel Samurai, but on the inside, it's just Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Other than the fact that it's that good-for-nothing, nothing else seems out of order.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait. You know as well as I that anything can happen if he's involved.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're not suggesting that someone else could be under that mask, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I don't think that. Just before he entered here, he gave me an autograph, so I'm certain it's Larry under there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the door connecting that hallway and this theater. Nothing appears to be out of the ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doesn't something about this lump's shape strike you as odd?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Isn't it supposed to be this shape?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, there is clearly something odd about the bulge. If only we had the pushcart itself, we could compare and confirm my hunch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Next, let us check the footage from Babahl's security camera.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I hope it shows us something good. ...Phooey. There wasn't a single sign of a suspicious person or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That, right there, is the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Did I miss something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You didn't miss anything... because there was nothing to miss. However, what IS missing is the image of Mr. Coachen entering his own country.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But wasn't his body found in Babahl?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that the true face of our final puzzle has finally revealed itself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Ambassador Alba...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I thought I had asked for you and your group to vacate the premises, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I thought I should let you know that this theater sits on my country's soil.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You've had your fun, and I've enjoyed our little game. I dare say that you've even achieved a new high score. However, once you've recorded a score, that same game can never be played again. Do you understand what I'm saying to you? Your game is done, and it's game over.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Where do you think you're going at this time of night?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">After admitting to my crime, I was overcome with regret. So I am heading to the airport now to return home.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid I can't let you do that. There are still too many issues we need to discuss with you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You can't stop me, Mr. Edgeworth, and you know it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">Please, may I have a little bit of your time, Ambassador Alba?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ambassador Palaeno...!</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">Even just a teeny-tiny bit is fine with me. The already strained relationship between our countries is in a precarious situation, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........Very well. If you insist. I will play just one more round with them, and see what they want. .........Not that they'll get any farther.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ambassador Palaeno...</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">Mr. Edgeworth... All I wish for is the normalization of relationships between our two countries. But there is one person standing in the way of that dream. I... I believe in you. You'll do what's right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Thank you for your vote of confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, what was it you wanted to ask me about? I do have a flight to catch, after all. So I'm afraid I'm going to have to limit you to just one question.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's more than enough, because I only have one question anyway. I want to hear your alibi, about how you couldn't have killed Mr. Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ho! I see... You seem to have a good hand this time around. This should be fun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This really is the very last chance we have to bring him down. I won't allow even an atom-sized contradiction to slip by!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Frankly, I still don't understand why I am being placed under suspicion here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...So that is your alibi?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That is correct. It's simply not possible for me to have committed a crime in Babahl. Now that we cleared that up, I'd appreciate it if you would move out of my way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I said, "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What is it this time? I thought I told you I'd only allow one question.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You did, but you still have yet to really answer my one question.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Until you tell us the truth... I will refuse to budge an inch from where I'm standing!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... Very well. I'll play with you just a little longer.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! As my subordinate, and representative of this country's prosecutors... ...you are forbidden to lose!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. That is something I've understood from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...That guy's the one who... ordered my father killed, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, I believe so.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The goal of the first Yatagarasu was the capture of the smuggling ring's leader. My father and Uncle Badd... Their legacy will live on... through me! So that's why we've just got to catch him, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We will. I promise. Now, Ambassador Alba, let's have at the truth now, shall we!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh... No matter how many times you ask, my answer remains the same.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Frankly, I still don't understand why I am being placed under suspicion here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Being the leader of a smuggling ring while taking on the duties of ambassadorship... Don't you think that the combination is more than enough reason for suspicion? Then there is the matter of the crossbow arrows and the Primidux Statues...</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">All of that is nothing more than your flights of fancy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by that!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Under your hypothetical scenario, Mr. Coachen and I were fellow smugglers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not hypothesis! Earlier, we proved it to be what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha... Well, let's leave that to one side for now. Because it doesn't change the fact that I have no motive.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? So you really had no reason to kill Mr. Coachen?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">If you want to suppose I had one, then why not. I'll indulge you. After all, this is nothing more than a silly game to me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if that's how you see things, I'd appreciate it if you would take me seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gwah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha haaa! Ahem, I'm sorry. I suppose you are in a bit of a pickle. Very well. A game is no fun if the playing field isn't level. Therefore, I formally claim that I had no motive to kill. Now, let's see you disprove it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How can he stand there looking proud when he knows he killed another human being? Well, I'm not going to stand by and just watch him get away with his crimes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"In that case, what motive would I have had to kill my co-conspirator?"</line>
<line speaker="Alba">In that case, what motive would I have had to kill my co-conspirator?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you serious that just because you were partners, that you had no motive to kill?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I'm only following your hypothetical scenario to its logical conclusion. Haaa ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Looks like he's not going to admit it himself that he was in leagues with Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose not. But I do know his relation to the smuggling ring, and to Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You mean, he's the ringleader, and that Mr. Coachen was his subordinate, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct, but I know more than just that. Ms. von Karma, I'm sure you remember the safe in Mr. Coachen's office, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes... The safe had two compartments to it, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and why do you think those stolen goods were being stored in Mr. Coachen's office? Could it be because he was trying to cheat Ambassador Alba behind his back?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So Mr. Coachen didn't turn the goods over, but decided instead to keep them for himself? I suppose that's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, it seems to me that both men were only concerned with their own wealth and wellbeing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then that means that maybe they didn't have a trusting relationship after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What Ambassador Alba had to gain... I believe that is his motive for killing Mr. Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...What are you people whispering about amongst yourselves over there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, I'm sorry to have kept you waiting. Now then, let's continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">But to get to the point, I was in Allebahst the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what exactly did you do while you were in Allebahst?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I had a meeting with the Steel Samurai, and then I arranged a few files. Around that time, that thief who was sneaking in took me by surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you saying that it was DeMasque II that made the first move!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, and it was after I was attacked that I hit him on the head with the Primidux Statue. Unfortunately, he died from the blow, but it was an act of justified self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Calling it that doesn't cover up what you really did!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha ha ha. Cover up? No, my boy, I'm not covering up anything; I'm telling the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You weren't planning to admit to it, which is why you tried to frame the Steel Samurai. If you weren't an ambassador, I'd be letting my whip fly loose on you right now...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I am terribly sorry that I didn't clean up the body better, but I am a busy man. I had a speech to give in the rose garden after that, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yet despite that, you still had time to kill Mr. Coachen, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh... Man is evil, and I'm sure you are familiar with the facts, but... ...Mr. Coachen was killed in Babahl while I was all the way in Allebahst.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">So, it's simply not possible for me to have killed him in Babahl. That is my alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You insist that it's not possible for you to have killed Mr. Coachen in Babahl... ...and you are correct.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh? I thought you would put up a bit more of a flight, but if you must concede to me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The only thing I am conceding is that it's not possible for you to kill him in Babahl. I am NOT conceding that your alibi is the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh... I see. However, no matter how you try, know that you can't crush my alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph. You would be wise not to underestimate a prosecutor of this country.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Heh, we'll see about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So Mr. Coachen was a "friend" of Ambassador Alba...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If that's true, then why did the ambassador kill him? It's not like in the case of my father where he ordered someone to do it...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The problem we have here is we don't know what their exact relationship was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. If they had complete trust in each other, then there is no motive for murder. <thought>However, both men were very selfish, and I believe that is from where his motive arose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you want to know, I believe you did have a motive to kill. It was because Mr. Coachen had betrayed you. But you had your own reason, too. Namely, you wanted to pin the smuggling all on him. Evil begets evil, and because you were trying to test each other, it turned into this mess!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I don't believe this. You have a bad penchant for telling tall tales, Mr. Prosecutor. And if you're not, then I suppose you have some proof to support your argument?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never use guesswork in moving my cases forward. It has been proven that this note was written by Mr. Coachen's hand. Shall we take a look at it? The content of the note is a request calling for the theft of Allebahst's Primidux Statue.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By killing him and pushing all of the guilt for the smuggling onto him, you walk away spotless. I believe you understand what I'm driving at. You had more than a few reasons to kill him.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Are you finished with your hypothesizing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Let's suppose I did have a motive. Even so, a motive or a thought alone can't kill. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I didn't expect him to resort to playing the semantics game with me... It appears that this is where the real battle will begin...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, if you will excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait--!? What!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I told you at the very beginning, didn't I? You only get one question.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh.........!</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">...Ambassador Alba, if you could please give us just a little bit more of your time. It doesn't matter what kind of man Manny was, he was my subordinate. Which is why I would like for us to figure out the real cause of his death.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That is something for Babahl to figure out, and something to which I have no relation to.</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now he's even turning down a request from Ambassador Palaeno...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">I'm very sorry, but it seems that now even my voice falls on deaf ears.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There is no need for you to apologize, Ambassador Palaeno.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrgh! <thought>We must find some way to stop him from leaving!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It seems there are no further objections. In that case, please allow me to return home.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hold it right there, Ambassador Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">K-Kay...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Like I said, Mr. Edgeworth... The Yatagarasu's legacy will live on through me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, but how do you suggest we stop him from leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You just leave that to me! Ambassador Alba, do you recognize this?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">No, and why should I recognize that tattered old organizer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait... Where have I seen that before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">That is a clue my father, Byrne Faraday, left for us.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Did you say, "Byrne Faraday"?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Faraday's organizer... Don't tell me this is the one from the second KG-8 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The one in which he wrote about the Yatagarasu's Key!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes. This organizer belonged to the prosecutor you had Ms. Yew kill seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. I have no idea what you are talking about. You say that like it was related to me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Inside this organizer, he wrote up every detail of every evil thing you did.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What an amusing little girl you are, But that sort of trickery won't work on me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If you won't believe me, then take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And what is that toy there? .........! That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">This thievery device was used by the Yatagarasu, or rather, by my father.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Seven years ago, he used this when he snuck into this embassy.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...What...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">These two pieces of evidence that hold information the Yatagarasu dug up on you... If you go home now, I won't hesitate to send it all to Allebahst, right behind you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Little girl, get to the point.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I want you to go up against Mr. Edgeworth one more time. If you win, then I'll hand over these two pieces of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yatagarasu...! Ever the thorn in my side.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, does that organizer really contain any information on his dirty dealings?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's nothing case-breaking, really.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, then it was just a bluff.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Even if it was, we still can't let all the info my father and Uncle Badd found go to waste! Plus, just the existence of Little Thief is troublesome enough for him.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Those two pieces... Aren't they keepsakes of your father?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's OK! I believe in Mr. Edgeworth! He'll come out on top in the end!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">When the going gets tough... someone's gotta be there to put the wind back in your sails!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">After all this time, you're still quite the feisty one. I appluad your powerful nature. I refuse to lose this, too. Ambassador Alba! You won't be returning home until you give us further testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">How dare you all... Barring a person like me...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ambassador Alba, your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnrk............! Alright, but this is the absolute last. Then, even if you use all the power of Ambassador Palaeno's office, you won't stop me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't let this opportunity Kay has created for me go to waste!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">The last time I met with Mr. Coachen was here at the Theatrum Neutralis.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now, since you people were practically begging, I'll allow you to question me.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...What an arrogant old man!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, but no matter. We can't allow this chance to escape us!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I will warn you though, you've reached the end of my patience. Waste my time with any insane questions, and you will be punished.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........! So any needless pressing or presenting will cost more to our case?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In that case, the only thing you can do is to present the correct evidence. Understood?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Of course. I don't intend to let him intimidate me! <thought>I know Mr. Coachen was killed before he returned to Babahl. In which case, there is only one statement to which I need to present the evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">The last time I met with Mr. Coachen was here at the Theatrum Neutralis.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You met with the victim here?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I was watching the Steel Samurai, as was Mr. Coachen, who was sitting nearby.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I've been meaning to ask, why invite the Steel Samurai as a guest for an embassy event?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I like Steel Samurai Daddy, so I asked for him to be at the event.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I see. <thought>So it was by Ambassador Alba's request...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, will that be all?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait...! I'm not finished yet...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You're not very good at listening, are you? I told you I don't have the time to listen to a bunch of useless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack...! <thought>The time remaining for me to find the truth has just been blown away...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">After that, I was in Allebahst the rest of the time, as I stated earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have anyone who can testify that you never left Allebahst after that?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Of course I do. I was in front of a large crowd to give my speech, wasn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I guess he's not lying about being in Allebahst the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, as long as he is willing to admit to DeMasque II's murder, then I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But he keeps saying that it was justified self-defense... Oh! I get it! OK, so what if I were to pretend being all hollow and sunken... ...and then I run into a klutzy person? Could I call that self-defense?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not self-defense; that's just being careless.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, you never know until you try!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suggest that you don't. Especially since you've given me a statement of intent.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, will that be all?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait...! I'm not finished yet...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You're not very good at listening, are you? I told you I don't have the time to listen to a bunch of useless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack...! <thought>The time remaining for me to find the truth has just been blown away...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">In any case, I did not see Mr. Coachen again after that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you never saw Mr. Coachen again after you left this theater?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That's correct. I'm an incredibly busy man, you know. So it's more likely that Mr. Coachen ran into Ambassador Palaeno.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even now, you would push his murder on to someone else...!?</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">How dare you!? Saying that I would kill Manny!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ambassador Alba! I demand that you refrain from making baseless conjectures!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I was merely offering a possibility. No, this won't do... I can already see this is turning into an international incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Who exactly is pressing who here...? In any case, what I need to do I stay positive and forge on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, will that be all?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait...! I'm not finished yet...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You're not very good at listening, are you? I told you I don't have the time to listen to a bunch of useless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack...! <thought>The time remaining for me to find the truth has just been blown away...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">So you see, there is no time span in which I could've killed him. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your alibi is that there was no time span in which you could've killed Mr. Coachen?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, because I was in the theater watching the stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, Mr. Edgeworth? Do you remember seeing him sitting in the audience?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, but I don't remember anything outside of what was going on on-stage.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You shouldn't have been so focused on the show, and paid attention to your surroundings!</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">Mr. Edgeworth... It is a fact that Ambassador Alba came to the theater. But I guess you didn't know that because you didn't see him at the Steel Samurai show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I do recall that he and you had a photo shoot with the Steel Samurai...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">*sigh* It looks like you are finally beginning to understand. Now then, will that be all?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait...! I'm not finished yet...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You're not very good at listening, are you? I told you I don't have the time to listen to a bunch of useless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack...! <thought>The time remaining for me to find the truth has just been blown away...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Amazing. Diplomats really do know how to craft answers that don't answer anything.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So if the only place he met the victim was at this theater... ...then when was he killed?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We know that Mr. Coachen didn't return to Babahl alive. Which means that the only time he could've been killed is when they were both there.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And that means that he was planning to kill Mr. Coachen from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to take a look at this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's a rather nice picture, isn't it? It was to commemorate the restoration of relations between our nations.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, it's commemorative, alright. One that captures the proof I need to show that it was you who committed the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the knife that killed Mr. Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see you recognize it, as well you should, for it was you who brought it to this theater. You hid it in among the flowers you were to give to the Steel Samurai! Meaning that you killed Manny Coachen here, at the theater!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Grr...rrr...rrrrrnnngh... Gwah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! .........It's time for me to catch my flight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're not through yet!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's game over for you, Mr. Edgeworth. But I thank you for the entertainment.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">No matter how passionately you orate, the end result will still be the same. I won't be returning to this country ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's right... This man is an ambassador... and he has extraterritorial rights! No matter how hard we chase after him, we won't be able to have him tried in court!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, that's exactly the face you should be making. The face of a worthless cur.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnn... Nnngghhoooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, ladies and gentleman, I must bid you farewell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrgh.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I... The courts... Is there no one who can lay a finger on this man!? Is this really the end...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Get out of my way. My plane is scheduled to take off soon.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Sorry, but you're not going anywhere... Mr. Alba.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I'm through playing games with you people. You can't touch me. If you do, it would spark an international incident, Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........Sorry, but no, it wouldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. Good job holding the fort down here until I got back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So, Mr. Alba. Your diplomatic immunity... has just been revoked.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What do you mean "revoked"? Spare me this nonsense and let me through.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Before aiming for the throat, chew the neck shield off first." Interpol headquarters and the imperial household of the Kingdom of Allebahst... ...took a while to get things rolling, but they finally move on it.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The imperial household...? You...! What have you done!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You have been relieved of your duties as ambassador, Mr. Alba.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Whhhhhaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Effective today, effective right now! And you have Mr. Prosecutor's video tape to thank for this!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The video the Yatagarasu protected...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You can't be arrested simply because you're an ambassador? In that case, I thought I'd strip you of that title. You underestimated me, a descendant of the founder of detainment philosophy, Lang Zi. Four thousand years of deeply entrenched connections and networks around the world... ...have really paid off.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It can't be... I don't believe this... My ambassadorship... has been revoked.........!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Haa ha ha ha! Looks like you're finally coming to grips with your new standing.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Whoo-hoo! Looks like he's turned docile again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's probably in shock from the loss of his "shield".</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... What a shame. I had so wanted to use my whip on him!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Why is this happening to me? I'm just a hard-working, honest ambassador...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Do you really think you can still pull that on us now? We've already ripped away the mask and seen you for who you really are, Mr. Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Gnnn... Gwooo.........ooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">No... I won't be stopped now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! <thought>He still intends to fight us!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">So what if I am no longer an ambassador? You still don't have any evidence on me! The fact remains that you cannot arrest me!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh, I'd expected no less from you, the boss of the smuggling ring. Well, the rest is up to you, Mr. Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh... You say that I killed Mr. Coachen in the theater. But even if it's true that there was a knife in my bouquet... ...I left that bouquet in the theater. So anyone could've taken it out from there and used it, right? Besides, the claim that he was killed here itself is odd. After all, wasn't his body discovered in Babahl? Are you claiming that I carried his body all the way over there? Hmph, preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be the one to prove whether it's preposterous or not.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnrk...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ex-Ambassador Alba, are you ready? Because this is no game. This is war!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I killed Mr. Coachen in this theater using a knife that was stuck in my bouquet?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Look, don't you think you've had enough fun with me? You've already stolen my ambassadorship from me. Would you have me surrender, too?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You have no plans to ever return to this country, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Did you know that a bunch of your subordinates are seeking asylum because of you!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Ha ha ha. As if I care,</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor! Boot this guy out of the embassy, and we can finally end everything.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know, and I will give it my all to see that he leaves in handcuffs. Without the title of "ambassador", he is just another witness!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes... Just another witness.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright! What are we waiting for! Let's get this guy!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">And get him good!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if they understand that all I can do is present evidence to the testimony...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I killed Mr. Coachen in this theater using a knife that was stuck in my bouquet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. As I explained earlier... ...the commemorative photo shows that you had the knife on your personage.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You have no proof that the bouquet was prepared by me, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The fact that there was a knife in the bouquet... was something I wasn't aware of.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What a pathetic excuse! The weapon that was used is one of your national treasures! It isn't exactly something anyone other than you could touch, let alone take!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I allowed some of my trusted subordinates to handle them. It could've been my secretary.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You... You're an even bigger slime ball than I'd thought...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would push the guilt of Mr. Coachen's murder onto one of your subordinates!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. In any case, the fact that the knife was in the bouquet means nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I left that bouquet in the theater! Anyone could've taken the knife from there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You still wish to deny your actions!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And you still wish to deny reality and accuse me of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? I am not in denial!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Arngh! Even though he's not an ambassador anymore, he's still got a real bad attitude!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I believe it's BECAUSE he's no longer ambassador that he can let himself speak freely.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, if he's not holding anything back, then neither should I!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! For the sake of the case, please refrain from what I think you're about to do!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, quite the pair of frightening women you are, but I digress.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Besides, Mr. Coachen's body was discovered in Babahl, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if he was found in Babahl, he was killed somewhere else!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Stop bluffing, because you can't prove what you're claiming. If this were a court-martial in my country, you'd have already been removed from the room.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Are you taunting us on purpose, because I'd be happy to show you my claws!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on, Agent Lang! Allow me to fight him my way... with evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! I was just joking. I'm not so easily ruffled by the likes of him!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Too bad. Though I'm no longer an ambassador, it still could've been an international incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you have the will to threaten us with that mouth of yours... ...then perhaps you can use it to return to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Very well... But to be fair, you should watch what you say as well.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">There is no way for me to have transported his body from the theater to Babahl!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that really so? You could've easily blackmailed your subordinates to be quiet and then moved the body.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">That's quite an insult to me and my subordinates, and I'm afraid we can't have yet! It's very difficult to enter my embassy, as the guards always conduct a thorough check. If someone so much as makes an unnatural movement, it would arouse their suspicions.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Come to think of it, there wasn't anything unnatural about him in the footage.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh......... <thought>Wait... Let me think about that for a second. Mr. Alba said that the guard would become suspicious if someone acted unnaturally. But then, by the same token... ...the guard would not become suspicious if someone were to act naturally!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we re-trace Mr. Alba's movements, we should find some hint to solving this case.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, right after the Steel Samurai stage show, he went back to Allebahst, right?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">From there, he started preparing for his speech in the Allebahstian Embassy.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It DOES sound like it wasn't possible for him to have gone to the Babahlese Embassy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He couldn't have gone to Babahl, but the body didn't remain at the theater either. Is it possible that the body was temporarily taken to a different location first?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I do believe there was a way to transport the body out of the theater. Perhaps you should give this a look!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What is that supposed to be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's footage from a security camera that captured the state of the immigration area.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Should I congratulate you on getting your hands on it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just letting you know that we're not the only ones watching your every movement.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. Thank you for the warning.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, if you could take a good look at this section here. This lump here inside the pushcart... Do you know what's causing it?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Should I? Because I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, in that case, allow me to enlighten you. This is the cause of the unnatural lump under the cloth in the pushcart!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence reveals to us what it was that was inside that pushcart!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph! And how exactly does it do that? Because I don't think it's meaningful to your argument at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! <thought>Arngh... I guess I was wrong...! Hmph... I'm getting ahead of myself. I can't allow him to rattle me. I must think calmly about this. It should be almost painfully obvious as to what was inside that pushcart...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh-What is the meaning of showing me that...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's to say that the unnatural bulge in the pushcart is Mr. Coachen's body. You had the Steel Samurai wheel his body away from the real crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gahahahahahaha! What a guess! But I wonder if you have any evidence to support it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I admit that for now, it is but a hypothesis, however...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha... If you can't prove it, then I'm afraid I must be on my way. I don't have any more time to play with you people.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry I took so long, Mr. Edgeworth, siiiiiiiir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. Is that the Steel Samurai's pushcart?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! I found it in the open-air stage area!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So that's where you went...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The detective's spirit that pops left me with...! I thought I'd follow my gut and go with it, sir! So, Mr. Edgeworth!? Is this worth anything to the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... It just might play a major role in solving this case, Detective! <thought>But something isn't right. I thought that the entire Samurai Family... ...was in Allebahst.</thought> Where exactly in the open-air stage area did you find this pushcart?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I found it just there at the edge of the stage, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Well, let's leave that for now and examine the inside, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Steel Samurai Daddy used this pushcart to wheel the Iron Infant around.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The Iron Infant is the Steel Samurai's and the Pink Princess's kid, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. He made an appearance at the end of the stage show. Heh... It was a rather fitting ending to the whole thing. <thought>That the Steel Samurai was unwittingly forced to move the body is just unforgivable!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's... blood!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This must be Mr. Coachen's blood. Which only goes to prove that Mr. Coachen's body was indeed transported by this pushcart.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you understand what this means, correct? You killed Mr. Coachen at this theater, and then placed his body inside the pushcart. And then... ...you forced to Steel Samurai to unwittingly move the body for you!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I forced him to move the body into Allebahst...!? What nonsense! Why would I bother to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were scheduled to make a speech in Allebahst... ...meaning it was difficult for you to make a stop in Babahl. However, what if you moved the body to Allebahst? Because it was your embassy, you could keep an eye on it, and tamper with the evidence. And then you smuggled it out of Allebahst!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">N-Noooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I can show how you moved the body from Allebahst and Babahl... ...then I win.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">But you can't! The security between the two countries is incredibly tight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be the one to judge whether I can or cannot prove it. And so I ask you to provide us with... ...testimony regarding your movements after your return to Allebahst!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Grrrngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... Have you figured it out? Do you know how the body was moved...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To be honest, I have nothing to support my hypothesis at this time. However, I don't believe I've made a mistake in my logic up to this point. Which means.........!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There is no question that can't be answered, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The Primidux Statue was smuggled successfully through a brief flight through the air. So why shouldn't there be an answer as to how the body was moved? Which means that there must be a logic flaw somewhere I can exploit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">After I returned to Allebahst, I had my picture taken with the Steel Samurai, shaking hands.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that all...?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........Yes, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like you left out a few things... such as the murder of DeMasque II! Furthermore, you left out the part about meeting with me in your office!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, those trifling matters... I don't believe I need to speak of those things again. I do so hate to waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You...! Is not every life precious!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh... Do you really need me to answer that for you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">People like you cannot be allowed to wander freely through society.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... Then you'd better try hard, because I doubt you'll find a single contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's really full of himself, isn't he!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he is......... <thought>How can he be so confident at a time like this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha ha ha ha. Come, don't be shy. Go ahead and ask whatever you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">After I returned to Allebahst, I had my picture taken with the Steel Samurai, shaking hands.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So why was it only with the Steel Samurai? I thought the Pink Princess was also around?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The Pink Princess was suffering from a bad hip at the time... ...and the doctors recommended that she rest.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! So you DO have a soft side after all!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The pain of a bad hip... I suppose none of you can really understand how it feels.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, so you tend to strain your back as well, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But isn't that just because you're normally all hunched over?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...He did need to keep up the act no matter what, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... The point of this is not to discuss my back problems! ...For about 15 minutes after our handshake, I was in my office preparing for the speech.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Then, just as I was about to start my speech, the Yatagarasu appeared.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Yatagarasu was just a trick that you had set up!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ha ha ha. A most amusing joke. And how do you propose that I "set it up"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you really want to know, I can explain it in detail for you. You arranged the spotlights in the rose garden so that when you were to take the stage... ...the audience would see the Yatagarasu's "shadow".</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh? That is an interesting tale... Sadly, it has nothing to do with me.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You...! What's it going to take for you to fess up to anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! Very well, then. Let's move on to a different question. After the Yatagarasu appeared, what was the state of the rose garden?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Everyone took refuge inside the embassy. I even helped with the effort. And then, once everyone was inside, well...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I feared for the national treasures, so I raced back to my office.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what happened after you returned to your office?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I don't want to keep on repeating this, however... ...upon my return, I had that stroke of bad luck and bumped into "Mask Man".</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...And I don't want to keep on repeating this, either... ...but his name was "DeMasque II"!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. Who cares what he was called!? By the time he got to the Primidux Statue that he was supposed to steal... ...it had already been swapped for the fake. Talk about an unlucky man... being bludgeoned to death with a fake statue! Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ms. von Karma is really letting her whip fly now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeeeek! I think the scary part is her silence while she's doing it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She must be at the limit of her patience as well... <thought>But physical attacks are meaningless here... Only evidence will suffice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! I can't find a single contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth... He's totally dead on the inside! Just like a hollow tree!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're the only one that can cut him down to size, Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At this point in time, we lack the information require to fight back properly...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor! You just say the word, and I'll get him talking for you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't forget that we have plenty of ways to get him to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We've got some real scary people on our side, huh, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I'm all ready to help out, Gummy! How about you!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't believe even you're getting into this... In that case, I'm ready, too, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! Everyone please calm down! I-I'll think of something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............Gnrk! <thought>I... I can't find a single flaw in his argument! At this rate, I won't be able to prove that he is actually guilty of anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Are we finished here?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Can you not come up with how the body was moved to Babahl!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Grr... Even after proving so much... is he going to get away with it...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N...Nngh...! <thought>Is this the end...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">It appears that we made it just in time...!</line>
<line speaker="S.Samurai">It would be a great honor if you allow us tyo be your allies in battle!</line>
<line speaker="P.Princess">Evil Magistrate! It is time for you to pay!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's... the Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">No, you are mistaken! For I am... ...Steel Samurai Daddy! Married Man of Neo Olde Tokyo! And this is... ...Pink Princess Mommy!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Edgey-poooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nrghhhooooooooooh! <thought>The two people I wanted to see the least.........!</thought> Laaaaaaaarryyyy...! What are you two doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Way to show your gratitude, Edgey! We just wanted to help, yeesh! I'm gonna get the bad guy with a single thrust of my Samurai Spear...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Go away!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">How can you be so mean to us, Edgey-poo!? All three of us came to lend a hand, and this is how you treat us!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, isn't this grand? And I see they managed to find the Iron Infant.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Does that really matter right now!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey...! Is it just me, or is the Iron Infant completely soaked?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hm? Oh, yeah. I found him in Babahl, but he was in the middle of the pool.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Wait a second! Larry, go back to what you just said.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Oh, umm... It appears that we made it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not that far back! Something about finding the Iron Infant in Babahl...? <thought>And he found it in a pool? I don't recall there being one in Babahl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh! THAT! Well, I was in Allebahst the whole time... ...so I have no idea how the Iron Infant wound up in Babahl! I thought I had lost him in the rose garden... ...but I guess maybe this cute kid can swim, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, what? Larry! You lost the Iron Infant in the rose garden? Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, I'm sure! But I found him in...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's enough, Larry! <thought>The Iron Infant that Larry lost managed to move between the two countries. Furthermore, the Iron Infant was found soaked in the middle of a pool? This is what I've been looking for; it's another smuggling route between the countries!</thought> The key to the route the Iron Infant took to travel from Allebahst to Babahl is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is it not the Yatagarasu? No, wait... As Ms. Yew was the Yatagarasu... ...it's very unlikely that the Yatagarasu is the key. In that case, how exactly was the Iron Infant smuggled across country lines...? This one thing is the only thing I can think of that can resolve the puzzle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In order to move the counterfeit bills that were printed in Babahl... ...someone must have made a secret route along which to transport it all. But wait... If there was such a route... ...Agent Lang and his men would've found it already during their investigation. In that case, there must be another secret smuggling route... ...and I must show the key to that other smuggling route!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, that's right. This embassy was built with bilateral symmetry in mind!</thought> Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y...Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a location I wish for you to examine posthaste! It is where I believe the route used to smuggle Mr. Coachen's body lies!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">D-Does something like that really exist, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An embassy built on bilateral symmetry... meaning that this is where we need to examine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe... I would like for you to examine this location.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...I'm back, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good, now report.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, but... there wasn't anything there, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!? <thought>I was wrong...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph hmph hmph hmph hmph... What's wrong? You couldn't find anything there, could you? Not one of your precious "holes", huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh...! I need to think about this calmly and rationally. The Iron Infant that Larry lost managed to move between the two countries. Furthermore, the Iron Infant was found soaked in the middle of a pool. So the location that Detective Gumshoe should be investigating... ...is here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! I'll be back before you know it!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It's too late. It doesn't matter what you do, it's all a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You will stay here with us and wait.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! It's here, sir! This is a reservoir here, just like the rose garden!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just as I suspected...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The two sides of this embassy are mirror images of each other. Which means that there is also a pool at the corresponding location on the Babahlese side. Mr. Coachen's body was moved into Babahl through the pool in Allebahst!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Avoiding the topic with a vague answer like that is unbecoming of a prosecutor. If you don't mind, I'd like to see more physical proof, if you have any.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Iron Infant is positively soaked in water. Why do you think that is? It's because he was fished of a pool, and not just any pool; it was the Babahlese one. I think it's pretty obvious at this point what must be true. The water reservoirs in the two courtyards are connected!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">And where is your proof that the two sides are connected!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The proof is right there before your eyes; the half-drowned Iron Infant!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh...!? Th......This blasted dooooooooooll!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! I'm back! H-Hey... Don't tell me... you guys figured everything out without me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We did, thanks to this hero of justice's son. Even if he is just a doll, he managed to help foil the villain.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor. Look, I don't want to say this, but... ...it's kinda unlikely that the body just happened to have passed on through to Babahl. This guy's a doll, and he's small, so I can believe it made it, but...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........! <thought>He has a point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh... Heh heh heh. Yes, that's right. I'm glad someone here understands. Mr. Edgeworth, are you going to next propose that a dead body can swim through a pipe?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You see, Mr. Prosecutor? Our chase after this man... ...is far from over!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why is he helping Mr. Alba out now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's not. He realized a flaw in my argument, and is helping to move the logic along. <thought>In which case......... I should return the favor and find an answer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">And another thing! Mr. Coachen's body was found in his office in Babahl. So what happened to his body after it was transported to the open-air stage?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Mr. Alba had an accomplice in Babahl, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You mean... Shih-na, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With her there, you can see how it was possible to move the body up to the office.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Are you seriously claiming that she swam through the connecting pipe with the body?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He's right. Ms. Shih-na would drown if she did that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's hard to imagine that she swam through the connecting pipe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It looks like your hypothesis about how the body was moved is still only half-baked. In the end, it's all just the befuddled musings of an accusatory man. Now then, I believe you should give up and allow me passage. Because, from the start, there was no feasible method of transporting the body!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........Mr. Prosecutor. Recall Shih-na's movements.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh.........! <thought>What was happening in the embassy around the time Ms. Shih-na was in Babahl...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh... if only there was a way to get rid of the water in the pool...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Get rid of the water...? Aha! That's it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now, I believe this time we really are done, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Unfortunately for you, it's far from over, Mr. Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You are a most persistent man. Are you saying that you've thought of a way to move the body through the water?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Move the body through the water? That is completely unrelated to how it was done.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The reason I say that is because... there wasn't any water there at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What do you mean, "there wasn't any water"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just what it sounds like. Tonight's events made it possible to drain the water, allowing the body to be moved!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Alba">............ What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What is that supposed to prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes! What is this supposed to be, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Me!? I, uh, have no idea, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Mr. Edgeworth, that question was directed at you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! It would appear that I presented the wrong piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It would seem that you didn't hear me just now, so let's try it again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, and I'll prove it to you with the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tonight, the Yatagarasu set fire to a variety of locations in the Babahlese Embassy. In order to put the fires out, much of the reservoir's water was used. Of course, when the water was used, the reservoir's water level went down... If enough water was drained, the connecting pipe could be used to traverse the border!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... So what!? The water level went down? The reservoirs were connected? Does any of this matter? You can't prove any of this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Pretending to be ignorant won't work with me. We both know what kind of situation we're in right now. Even in a game, there comes a critical, game-changing moment. A moment in which you hit a wall that you must overcome in order to beat the game.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I haven't lost yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've found the route you used to smuggle the body, and that route will lead to your defeat!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Even if all the water was used by the fire fighting effort... ...you still can't really call that a smuggling route.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Hmph. I know that.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! I should've figured that you would notice. Hey, Mr. Alba, how deep are those pools, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh. I'll have you know those pools are extremely deep. And there are no ladders or footholds along the walls, either.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It would be difficult for Shih-na to hold the body and climb up out of the pool...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Ladders or footholds along the walls? There was no need for such things.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If one were to use a certain something, they could go up or down in the pool at will.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oh? It looks like you've got an answer already. Well? What are you waiting for, Mr. Prosecutor? Enlighten us already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The way in which Ms. Shih-na and the body were able to rise up to ground level... If there was a way to control the water level, that could be the way the body was moved!</thought> This was used so that the body and Ms. Shih-na could move up and down in the pool!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This, Mr. Alba, is what you used!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...I don't recall ever using that.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...I don't think that's really applicable, do you, Mr. Prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I don't understand how you think at all, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>It would appear that I was wrong...</thought> I beg your pardon... Please allow me to present you with another piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba used the fountain spouts, in a manner of speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">He used the fountain spouts...? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The water level in the pools can be controlled by opening and closing the spouts. Ms. Shih-na and the body were lifted upward by their buoyancy in water. The fire on the Babahlese side, and the fire fighting effort... These were set in motion all for the sake of smuggling Mr. Coachen's body!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........Gnnnnnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shall I show you where the final destination of my train of logic leads!? First, Mr. Alba closed the fountain spouts in advance, in preparation of things to come. Then, he took the pushcart that was brought to the rose garden... and pushed it, along with the Iron Infant and Mr. Coachen's body, into the pool. At this time, Ms. Shih-na was busy conveniently starting the first fire in Babahl. She then made for the open-air stage's pool to wait for the fire fighting effort to begin. When the firefighters used the water in that pool, the water level went down... ...and by the time the fire was put out, the pipe between the two pools was exposed! This is when she pushed the pushcart from Allebahst into Babahl. Once that was accomplished, Mr. Alba simply opened the fountain spouts once more... ...and the water level rose up to its original level, along with Ms. Shih-na and the body. After that, Ms. Shih-na used the pushcart to carry the body up to the secretariat's office. There is an elevator in the embassy, after all. So you see... ...even with her small frame, she could've easily transported Mr. Coachen's body. And that wraps up my thorough explanation of how the body was moved!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnnn... Gnnnnnnooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Well, Ex-Ambassador Alba? What do you think? Not so untouchable without your precious extraterritorial rights to protect you, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I knew you could do it, Mr. Edgeworth! Way to fight back!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You accuse me of moving the body across country lines...! But when you get down to the nitty-gritty, you don't have what it takes to indict me!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">The "nitty-gritty"...? What does the old man want now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Proof... I believe is what he seeks.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes. Proof. Without any, who is to say whether or not any of what you said really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">He wants proof? What are we going to do, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is no need to worry. I've had all the proof we need all along. <thought>The body wasn't the only thing to do through the pools' connecting pipe tonight. Just as Detective Gumshoe found the pushcart in the open-air stage area... ...so, too, did I find one other item there. And that piece of evidence is what will prove that the pools were the smuggling route!</thought> This was another thing that was smuggled over to Babahl's open-air stage area!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the defining piece of evidence that will prove my hypothesis!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph! I don't think it proves a single thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I think it's about time we put an end to this ridiculous farce of a "trial". If I'm not mistaken, all you're doing is trying to trick me with psychological gimmicks.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrrrngh! <thought>If I continue on like this, Mr. Alba will find a way to worm his way out of this! The body wasn't the only thing to do through the pools' connecting pipe tonight. There was something else that was brought from the rose garden... ...through the open-air stage, and into the secretariat's office along with the body. Just as Detective Gumshoe found the pushcart in the open-air stage area... ...there must be a reason as to why that other item was there as well!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">...And what exactly is this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You have no idea, do you? This little piece that I found on the Babahlese side will be your undoing.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">A guitar pick? Would you care to explain how that is going to "do me in", as it were?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Much to your chagrin, perhaps, but this is not a guitar pick.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wh...What...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is something I found at the open-air stage which was transported with the body. I naturally assumed that you would recognize it... since you took a photo with it, after all. But since you don't, allow me fill you in on what I found at the stage actually belongs to!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is what the fragment belongs to!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don't you dare chicken out on me after we've come all this way!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I demand that you show the correct piece of evidence now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, sir! Do the ol' presenting thing proud and do it right!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, yes, I understand. <thought>It would appear that this evidence isn't enough to convince any of them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph! What's wrong? You seem to have alienated all of your friends.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not quite. They're merely watching out for me. And pointing out to me which piece of evidence I should be presenting! I naturally assumed that you would recognize it... since you took a photo with it, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let us take a good look at the murder weapon that was used to kill Manny Coachen. On the handle of this knife, there is a beautifully blooming flower. However, it would appear that it's missing a single petal.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnn...nnrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, let's see what happens when we try to fit this "pick" in that open slot.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a perfect fit!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assume that the petal must have fallen off of the flower during Mr. Coachen's murder. And then, it was accidentally placed into the pushcart along with Mr. Coachen's body.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Gnrrr... That's an interesting story, nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Oh, I assure you it's more than just a story. Because for some odd reason, this flower petal was wet when I found it.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It was wet... you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and the only place it could've gotten wet from is the open-air stage's pool! Now I ask you, how did a part of the weapon which was smuggled into the theater... ...wind up in the open-air stage area on the Babahlese side of the embassy? I don't think I need to waste any words explaining this, as this petal explains it all for me. It proves that someone went from the rose garden's pool on through into Babahl!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Impossible!!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">The people of Zheng Fa have been waiting to see you, face to face, Mr. Alba. I'll tell everyone back home we'll be there soon. You should be happy.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I... This... Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why? It's a little late to be asking that question. You should've known from the very beginning... ...when you took your first life! No matter how you may plot, or how you may try to cover it all up... ...you can never hide from your crime and what you've done. Because we're here to see to it that justice is served to people like you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You... can't call what you've given a "perfect argument"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You know... ...I don't think this guy is going to ever admit to his wrongdoings, Mr. Edgeworth. Because he values himself above all else. People who can't be negotiated with or people who refuse to admit when they've lost... I don't believe those kinds of people really exist because everyone breaks eventually...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're right. In that case, I have no choice but to use all of the evidence I have. I'll use it all until he breaks under the weight of his crimes! Mr. Alba, I request that you testify once more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This really will be... the end of the line...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba, I request that you testify once more.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">As if there is anything else for me to testify about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I still have yet to fully prove that it was Mr. Alba who murdered Mr. Coachen...</thought> Well... I would like to hear about your movements before the murder occurred. I wonder if you could tell us about what you did here at the Theatrum Neutralis?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Very well. I suppose I could tell you about that. Heh heh heh... Because about all I did was watch the Steel Samurai stage show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, elaborating on even that alone is good enough for me. <thought>The only way for me to place this man under arrest is to pinpoint the exact location... ...of where the murder took place, for that is the key to this investigation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I watched from the last row. The stage was well-lit, but it was dark out in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were in the theater proper, watching the Steel Samurai stage show, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Of course I was. I have a great fondness for the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Heh heh! Yeah! I was pretty cool up there, wasn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're not the one who was "cool"! It's the Steel Samurai who is cool.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, and the Steel Samurai's special finishing move today was really something, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hm? Hey, Edgeeeeey! Who is she!? Who is this super cute girl!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's been standing here this whole time, and only NOW he notices her!?</thought> Her name is Kay Faraday. ...And she's helping me in my investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sorry I didn't get to introduce myself earlier, but better late than ever!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah! So, Kay! I'm Larry Buuuuuuuuutz!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Silence in the peanut gallery! There's no time for such trivialities at a time like this!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Mr. Prosecutor, this is the final battle, you got that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know. This is the end......... for that man there.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha! Now that's the kind of thing I like to hear! I think I'll give trusting you a try, Mr. Prosecutor... or rather, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I leave this critical battle up to you, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have no fear. I will finish the job. <thought>This really is the endgame. The time has come to expose every last one of Mr. Alba's lies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I watched from the last row. The stage was well-lit, but it was dark out in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The last row? I should think that an ambassador would've had special seating reserved.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I wanted my staff to enjoy the Steel Samurai's show as well. So I gave up all of the good seats for them. It was enough for me to simply see him.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! The Steel Samurai wasn't the only hero! Let's not forget about the Pink Princess here!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">My dear madam... ...if you continue to thrust about like that, your hip may begin to hurt again.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, my! Well, aren't you the considerate person when you want to be? But! This young butterfly is on the side of Edgey-poo. So you can spare me the flirtatious come-ons!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow! He's completely frozen!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In frustration, perhaps. I dare say she can be one rather trying opponent. In any case... Mr. Alba, can you actually prove to us that you were watching the show?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I swear I was there in the audience, but it's hard to prove that, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you admitting, then, that you have no way of proving to us that you were watching!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Quiet! You buzz in my ear like a pesky little fly! If you don't wish to listen quietly until the end of what I have to say... ...then perhaps you should pack up and get out of my way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk...!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... I see that you're willing to be a bit more receptive now. While it's true that it may be difficult to prove that I was out in the audience...</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I do remember the contents of the show very well, though. Is that proof enough for you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Well, I remember the contents of the show as well myself.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...That's nice.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"That's nice"!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth, don't allow yourself to be riled up by him at this important juncture.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I wasn't planning to let him...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, if you ask me, I think I'M the biggest Steel Samurai expert around here! And didn't you think the climactic scene of today's show was just totally awesome!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, I remember that well. And that spectacular special move! The way you delivered the final blow against the Evil Magistrate, "Early Summer Rain Jab"... Oh, that scene will live on in my heart forever.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Is that how it went? Heh, I totally forgot about that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How can you forget your own special moves!? That's the special attack that the Steel Samurai uses when he's using the Samurai Spear.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Yes, and today was the first time they showed it off, was it not? If I hadn't watched the show, then how could I answer you with the name of the move?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose you are correct, but if you could, please elaborate on this point for me.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"One of the scenes was the never-before-seen "Early Summer Rain Jab" move."</line>
<line speaker="Alba">One of the scenes was the never-before-seen "Early Summer Rain Jab" move.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Early Summer Rain Jab" was a move that was to be unveiled today.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And because I saw that brand new special move, I believe it confirms my alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">How sad. The only way he's got to protect himself is that he watched the Steel Samurai. I guess... this guy really has nothing else left...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and to avoid arrest, you can bet he'll say or do anything. But, with all of us here, there will be no escape for him!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! We'll find a way to bring him to justice!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, let us continue with your testimony, Mr. Alba.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. Very well. The Steel Samurai's special move and the various other scenes...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Those moving scenes were seared into this old man's heart. I'll never forget them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree, today will be a day to remember. Especially when we finally make you pay for all the wrongs you've committed!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! That's what the Steel Samurai says when he defeats the Evil Magistrate!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Heh heh... Actually, that line was just something I ad-libbed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You may act all surprised, but naturally, you remember this line, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........! Of course I do. I just now understand how the Evil Magistrate felt, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then allow me to make you identify with the Evil Magistrate some more!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey, then that makes you the Steel Samurai, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Well, if you had to complete the analogy, I suppose then, yes. <thought>And I do believe it's about time to bring the curtains down on this with a bang!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wonder if Mr. Alba was really there watching the show?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't think so, because the only time he had to commit the murder was during the show. And the only time he could've placed the body into the pushcart... ...was during the scenes when the Iron Infant was not out on-stage.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Then that means that by the end of the stage show... Are you saying that the body was already in the pushcary by then?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">No waaaaaaay! I-I... You mean, I was pushing a dead body around!? That you used me in such a foul manner... is unforgivable, Evil Magistrate!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Well put, Steel Samurai. And now, I will show to all those present... ...just who is the Evil Magistrate that the Steel Samurai must defeat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay and myself were also in the audience of the Steel Samurai stage show...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...He's got nothing on the Jammin' Ninja, but he was still cool enough, I guess!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Heh heh! Wasn't my brand new special finishing move totally rad!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, don't tell me! It was YOU who thought up the special move!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yup! Umm... Now what was it again? "Extremely Silly Reign Jab!" ...Was that it? No, wait, it was "Stubble Breaking Chop!" ...That doesn't sound quite right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How can you forget a move you came up with!? <thought>The final piece to Mr. Alba's alibi is that he was watching the Steel Samurai's show. However, if he was busy killing Mr. Coachen, he should not have had the time to do so!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The special move today was the "Early Summer Rain Jab"? Is that your final answer?</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You little irritating gnat. Do you think you can trip me up by asking the same question over and over?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was not my intention. Your testimony is more than sufficient. However, I believe it would be wise for you to take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The Samurai Spear? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This spear... actually never made it on-stage today.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...E-Excuse me...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Unfortunately for you, tonight's Steel Samurai... ...happened to be a goof of a young man with an abundance of useless hot-bloodness.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Having said that, said useless man bent the spear during his rehearsal this evening. Kay, do you remember what the Steel Samurai's special move was tonight?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It was the "Steel Samurai Sushi Slash"!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...A...Aaaaaa...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. Because he couldn't use the spear, a last-minute change was made. Had you been watching the show, you would've known the move that WAS used.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Gnrk...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quercus Alba! You didn't watch even a single minute of the Steel Samurai stage show tonight, did you!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">G.........Gnnnn... Gnnnnraaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Aha! So if he wasn't watching the show tonight...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Then it opens up the possibility that he was busy killing Mr. Coachen instead!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So where were you during the show? I demand an answer, now!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................Heh. Heh heh heh heh heh......... Ahaaa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just what is so funny!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You're so sloppy. And so are your conclusions. I still insist that I watched the show. Or most of it, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by "most of it"...?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, you see, during the show, I left my seat for a spell to visit the bathroom. I assume that was when that dramatic scene was played out on-stage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-That is the lousiest, lamest excuse I've ever heard in my life, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Arngh! Just because he got the name of the move wrong... ...we can't really use that as proof that he didn't watch the show at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk............!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">As a fan of the Steel Samurai, I had wanted to watch the entire show... Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As a "Steel Samurai fan"...? For someone who wasn't even in his seat for the climax of the show...! You have no right to call yourself a Steel Samurai fan, ever!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-Who was that just now?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">It would be I, young ladyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry! What are you doing interrupting me like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgeeeeeey! Just hold for a second, I beg! You may never accept this old man as a Steel Samurai fan... ...but I totally think he's a Steel Samaniac!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um, what exactly is a "Steel Samaniac", pal?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I believe he meant to say "Steel Samurai maniac".</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah! And trust me, I know a real fan when I see one, because I'm the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I will never acknowledge you as the true Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What are you getting so worked up over, Mr. Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">It appears that the real Steel Samurai recognizes me as a fan. As well he should, for I am a fan! It's not as though I missed the entire show. It was a most amazing show, filled with the spirit of the young and the young at heart.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hmph. The sarcasm dripping from his long, wooden nose couldn't run any ticker.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Getting the name of the move wrong only proves that he didn't watch the last scene. What I really need here is something more definitive! Something that links Mr. Alba directly to the murder of Mr. Manny Coachen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">You know what, gramps? You're really something else!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I'm honored to receive such praise from the Steel Samurai, but what is it for?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, I was just wondering how you found out about the "Early Summer Rain Jab". That move is a bit of a secret that only a small portion of the staff know about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait, it was a secret...?</thought> Larry! Wait, what did you just say!?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Did I say something stupid again?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you say that the "Early Summer Rain Jab" was actually a secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, maybe I shouldn't have said "secret"... It's more like we only decided on the name of the move right before the start of the show.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Right before?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah! The stage director was going nuts because we were supposed to debut the move! About 5 minutes before the show, we threw it up on the dressing room's white board. "Early Summer Rain Jab"! That's kinda how we decided the name of the move. But, by that time, I'd already bent the spear, so I guess the whole thing was kinda pointless.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">All of you Steel Samurai actors are the same. The director has my complete sympathy.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">So basically, because we changed the move to the Sushi Slash... ...we kinda pretended that the Early Summer Rain Jab didn't exist at all! I mean, it'd be had if someone found out we'd changed the move, so we made it a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So basically, a gag order was issued for publicity's sake...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It almost makes the "Early Summer Rain Jab" sound like a lost art!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, which is why I think most of the staff haven't even heard of the move.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hold those lips of yours still...!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">What the heck, old man!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I've done nothing but listen, and from what I can tell, it's all very unrelated to the case. It's also very tedious and a pointless exercise in wasting time, much like a kids' show.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba. I believe the one who should be quiet now is you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">How dare you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspect that you've already noticed... ...exactly what the very severe implications are in this man's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hah! So now you're trying to bully me, huh? There are no implications to be read into a behind-the-scenes story of a kids' show!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Don't even think about trying to slither your way out of this, Quercus Alba.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were the one who said it yourself, that the name of the move was... ..."Early Summer Rain Jab". But that name was only decided upon right before the show was about to start.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">So? Just what are you driving at?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That the name of the move you told us was never used in the show or said aloud!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, would you care to tell us about how you found out the name of that move?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Because I can only think of one way you could've known...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quercus Alba! This is the only way you could've known the name of the special move!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You knew the name because you asked about it! You asked a member of the staff, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, now! Didn't that samurai say just a few seconds ago... ...that the people who knew were ordered to keep quiet about the move!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I somehow doubt that he could've simply asked someone and gotten an answer.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Besides, even if what you said were the case, what do we learn from that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not much, actually. Not if Mr. Alba had asked a staff member, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaah! <thought>I was wrong...!?</thought> Mr. Alba, would you care to tell us about how you found out the name of that move?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You knew the name because you thought it up! Therefore, it's only natural that you knew! You are the one who created the name of that move!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Lang">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........Mr. Edgeworth, somehow, I don't think that's it.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Let's just leave it at that, since it clears everything up for me nice and neatly.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey! What exactly did you find out by saying that, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... Not much, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Will you please take this seriously!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaah! <thought>I guess I made a mistake...!</thought> Mr. Alba, would you care to tell us about how you found out the name of that move?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You knew the name because you saw it! You saw it on the dressing room's white board!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The staff members who knew were keeping it a secret. So you couldn't have simply gone up to a staff member and asked. Which means that the only other option left is that you saw it on the white board.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So, that means that Mr. Alba was in the waiting room at some point, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But what's the big deal, sir? I don't see what that means!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is another piece of evidence that has a great deal to do with the dressing room. So we can't afford to let this slide! This is related to both the dressing room and to Mr. Coachen's murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a very close connection between this and the dressing room!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">And what sort of connection would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's... a bit difficult to recognize at first glance, however...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor! I only trust what I can see! And when it comes to evidence, I think everyone here agrees with me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr... It would appear that this piece of evidence was not what I was looking for.</thought> Yes, well, this time I will present to you the real piece that will prove my point.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The pushcart that was used to move the body was right there in the dressing room! During the show, the pushcart awaited its turn to be pushed on-stage in the dressing room. And it was finally pushed there, along with the Iron Infant, in the last scene of the show. And then, right after the show ended, it went into Allebahst along with the Steel Samurai. Which means that the only time the killer could've placed the body inside the pushcart was... ...when the pushcart was in the dressing room backstage!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So basically, the killer has to be someone who visited the dressing room during the show!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........Gnnraaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! But wait! What if, and this is just a "what if"...! What if the murder didn't take place in the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What do you mean, Kay!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have to admit, she brings up a valid possibility. During the show, the dressing room was supposed to be devoid of people.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Anyone going into the private dressing room would stand out like a sore thumb!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But despite that, the killer still managed to move the body with the pushcart.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct, and it is because of the set-up of the theater's dressing room... ...that it would be the ideal location for the murder of Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quercus Alba! During the show, you went down to the dressing room. And I want to know why!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................Yes. .........Yes, I was there. I went into... the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I knew it! I'm placing you under arrest right now, pal! You got that!? ARREST!</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Not so fast.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What is it now!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh. Don't I deserve a chance to explain myself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Explain? What is there to explain!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I believe I told you earlier that I went to the bathroom. Well, I got lost when I did. I wanted to ask for directions but when I opened the dressing room door, no one was inside. And that's when I saw the name of the move on the white board.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">You punk! Still trying to get out of this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do you really think you can get away at this point...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Isn't there anything you can do to stop him!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh...! I don't have enough evidence on hand to do anything! I don't have the airtight evidence I need to put this man away for good. But if that's what I need, then perhaps...</thought> Agent Lang! I believe an investigation of the dressing room in question is in order. It's possible that we may find new evidence there!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! If Mr. Edgeworth pokes around in there, I'm sure he'll find some new facts, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ooh! And if we use Little Thief, we may even learn something from a re-creation!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...We don't need to do any of that.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What!? Wolfy!? How could you!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'm not saying this to be mean. It's just that... we've already searched there. My men really are something else.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And they found nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">There's only one thing I can say to you, sis, and it's that they found nothing. That's it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I... guess you're right. If they had found something, they would've reported it to us.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh heh. They couldn't find anything because there was nothing there to find.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">And if there is no info to feed into Little Thief, then I can't do much to help either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this the end? The murder took place in this theater, which is not protected under extraterritorial rights... ...and the fact that it was Mr. Alba himself who committed the murder... If I can't prove both statements to be true, Mr. Alba walks away a free man! Is there no other course of action left to us...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">It would appear that your hand of cards has turned out to be a bust. Now if you will excuse me. Because of you people, I missed my flight. Now I must make haste to arrange for a new one...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-Who is it this time?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hold it right there, you whippersnappers!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! First Larry, and now YOU!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What is with that scary, mobster-like scowl on your face, Edgey-poo!? Don't treat me like I'm some sort of nuisance! I've been meaning to say this, but all of you keep talking about things I don't get at all! You're all leaving this lady in the sad, depressing, lonely dust that I'm about to cry in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why did you have to speak up right at this instant...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But you know what, Edgey-poo!? Cheer up! Because I'm about to give you the most wonderful thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">? The most "wonderful thing"...? From you...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It's so super special that I couldn't give it away to just anyone, you know! Ah, my special present of love to my sweet Edgey-poo... Are you ready!? ...Is this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It's...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's... a box of those "Samurai Dogs", right?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes! Oh, Edgey-poo! Here, go on and eat one and you'll feel as right as rain.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kay">.........</line>
<line speaker="Lang">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.........</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Are we through here?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...Why did everyone get so quiet all of a sudden!? Edgey-poooooooo! Tell me YOU understand the depths of this lady's love for you!!! I'm not one to hand out snacks willy-nilly, you know! No sir! The thought occurred to me that maybe it would be good if I fed you and made sure you were nice and full! One day, it's my dream to serve you some of my own home-made food! I mean, isn't it the desire of every woman to make sure that their beloved never goes hungry? And that's what I wanted to experience! I'll tell you one thing, though. A long time ago, they used to say that I could make the most delicious meal out of any ingredient you threw in front of me! Oh, I was a star in the kitchen back then, and I was</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Can't you do anything about her!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is no power on Earth that can force THAT woman into silence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But I'm so sick and tired of it! All you people do is look down on me! Even this box of "Samurai Dogs" played me for a fool! It had a special design on its fan, like the Japanese flag, so I thought it was special! But when I ate one, it tasted just like all the rest! Ooh, it made me so mad!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait, a special box with a Hinomaru-like fan on it? I've never heard of such a piece of merchandise existing before. However, there it is The red rising sun on this fan is filled in... I-Is it possible!? Could it be...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After the show, the Samurai Dogs were piled up on the dressing room floor. However, there is no such thing as a "Rising Sun Dog <thought>Rising Sun Dogs - Taken from the dressing room, the fan's rising sun is filled in for some reason.</thought>". This contradiction of facts between something that should not exist, and yet does... The rays from this rising sun may be just what we needed to point us in the right direction!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A present...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">The studio big-wigs basically told us to play delivery boys. We were supposed to hand the Dogs off to the embassy people and tell them "hi". I had to pile them all into the pushcart just to move them <thought>Samurai Dogs - Boxes of Samurai Dogs were sitting in the pushcart.</thought> all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you understand what this means, correct? You killed Mr. Coachen at this theater, and then placed his body inside the pushcart <thought>Body in the pushcart - The killer placed Coachen's body in the pushcart in the dressing room.</thought>. And then... ...you forced to Steel Samurai to unwittingly move the body for you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's time to piece the final pieces of this logic puzzle together. No matter how fragile or small the connections may be... ...once we've found them all, the way to the truth will be revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The killer used the pushcart to transport the body... ...which means that they had to remove the Samurai Dogs from within first! Therefore, the Samurai Dogs that were piled up on the dressing room floor... ...were most likely taken out of the pushcart (Samurai Dogs were removed - Dogs were put on dressing room floor by the killer to make room for the body.</thought> by the killer!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That which should not exist, this box of Samurai Dogs with a hinomaru on it... If this red rising sun... ...was filled in when the killer was busy removing Dogs from the pushcart... ...then it's proof that the murder took place in the dressing room. As long as this red substance turns out to be what I believe it to be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Wendy Oldbag. I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you have given to me is truly something very "special".</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">E-Edgey-poooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Edgeworth? Are you sure you're feeling OK, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba. As I suspected, you killed Mr. Coachen in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">How many times must I listen to you repeat yourself? Haven't you figured it out yet? You words are meaningless, worthless, and powerless. The only way I'm going to continue to cooperate with some definitive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That arrogance, that self-confidence... You believe that you've erased every piece of evidence that could incriminate you. However! There remains one piece here, and it is what will put you away for good!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hah! You're bluffing!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Oho... Hey, Mr. Prosecutor! Sounds like you finally found them. You finally found the fangs we need to go after this guy's jugular! So tell us, what about that box of Samurai Dogs is going to put the old man away!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The trace evidence that will bring him down? Why, it's here of course!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This part is just the same as all the rest of the boxes. But there is one spot in particular on this box that seems off. What exactly is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The box of Samurai Dogs with a rising sun fan on it... This should never have existed. So I want you all to take a good look at this red spot. It's a single drop of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Blood, you say...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, I'd like this blood analyzed posthaste.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I've got to admit, I'm a bit surprised! I can't believe we found blood in a place like this! Hey, you! Get this down to the lab, pronto!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But why was there blood on that box to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If we think about the flow of the crime, I think the reason will become obvious. Larry, you said that you transported the "Samurai Dogs" with the pushcart, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, umm, yeah! You have a great memory, Edgey! That pushcart was a bit too big for my son, you know what I mean? So to make sure everyone could see him, I had to pile some stuff in. I figured the Samurai Dogs were there, so I used them to fill up the cart.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If what Larry says is true, then what were the boxes doing on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ah, I see. The killer took them out in order to place the body in the pushcart!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly. And that is when I believe the victim's blood found its way onto that box.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">But when my men investigated that room, not a single box of Samurai Dogs was in there... ...because embassy staff members had already confiscated them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. No doubt to hide the evidence of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's a good thing Ms. Oldbag managed to steal that one box before they got to them, huh? Looks like Ms. Oldbag also managed to put this Great Thief to shame!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What a scandalous way to putting that! I didn't "steal"; I received it from myself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quercus Alba, I'd say this was one very fatal oversight on your part.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh. Sorry to rain on your little love-fest, however...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How... How can he be so self-confident in a no-win situation for him like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Even if that blood turns out to belong to Mr. Coachen, then what?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Heh! So, Mr. Edgeworth! It sounds like he's not ready to call it quits yet, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The sole piece of evidence that was left at the scene of the crime... That alone has shed light on a new fact. At the very least, we now have proof that the murder occurred in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........And? You say that like it means something.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Excuse me, sirs!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">REPORT! What were the results of the analysis?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! The analysis came back and confirmed that the red substance is blood.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I knew it! With this, Quercus Alba...</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Mr. Edgeworth, I wonder if you might humor my question?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your question?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The one from before, or have you forgotten? Even if that is Mr. Coachen's blood, what difference would it make?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Like we already told you. It proves that the crime scene was that dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">But it doesn't prove that I am your killer, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Gnnnrk! That's... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh...! He has a very good point. The blood on that box doesn't prove that Mr. Alba is the killer...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-Then... this evidence... It's meaningless...!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That can't be... We were so close, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wanna smack that smug look off his face! Come on, there's gotta be something we can do!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>We finally found a solid piece of evidence! There must be something I can expose with it!</thought> .............................. <thought>A-Ack! I can't think of a single thing...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh heh. Heh heh heh heh heh heh. ...Now if you'll excuse me, I'll be on my way.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Who was that!? It's too late. I won't allow anyone to stop me now!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-It wasn't me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">And it wasn't me this time, either!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">It wasn't me either!</line>
<line speaker="???">I-It was meeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did you--!?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Umm... Because I haven't finished reporting everything to you yet, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's more...?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What!? Hurry up and spit it out!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Y-Y-Yes, siiir! Th-That blood I mentioned... It's not of the same blood type as the victim's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No--!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What do you mean it's "not the same type"!? You mean it's not the victim's blood!? If it isn't his... then who the hell's is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I-I don't know, siiiiiiiiiir! All I know is that it's not the same blood type as the victim's, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What should we do now, Mr. Edgeworth!? I have no idea what's what anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Neither do I.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heheheheheheheh. My, what an amusing turn of events!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That blood drop proved something to be true alright -- namely, my words.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And which one of your words would that be?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The ones where I said that your words are meaningless, worthless, and powerless. That blood has nothing to do with the murder investigation whatsoever! Need I remind you that the blood got onto that box long before it entered my embassy?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wh-What sort of nonsense--!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! It's BLOOD, pal! There's no way it's not related to the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh. So you would like to believe. But what if someone preparing the Samurai Dogs had a small nosebleed? What then?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gnrk! I-I guess that's possible...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Damn it! Have we been wasting our time on a red herring?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">The blood doesn't belong to anyone connected to the case. That should be clue enough.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Quercus Alba! You BASTARD!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Silence! Don't you ever address me with such a filthy word again. I've wasted enough time here with you, and you have your answers. Now, let me through.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Alba! It doesn't matter where you run off to, you'll never escape me! Someday, I'll have the satisfaction of sinking my fangs into you. You'll see! And all of Interpol will be behind me, working to see to it that that day comes!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh. Do you know what your words sound like to me? They sound like the whinings of a pathetic loser of a mutt.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Arroooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this really the extent of all that we can do? Is the blood really from someone completely unrelated to the case? Or is there another possibility? Someone else other than the victim? Just when I thought I had him backed into a corner, it is I who has been backed into one! In a situation like this... what would that man do...? What would he who can turn any desperate situation around do...? .........Turn it around...? That's it! I must turn my way of thinking around! It's not, "Whose blood is this?" It's, "Whose blood could get onto the box like this?" And if I think about it that way...! If the blood got onto the box when the body was being placed into the pushcart... ...then the owner of said blood must have been in the dressing room at the time! And there is only one person that could be!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Well, I must praise you for trying so hard. It's because of you kids that I was removed from center stage. ...and will be forced to live out the rest of my life in the shadows, unfortunately. But it's not a total loss, as the underworld will allow me more freedom than you'll ever know. Freedom like what the raven feels as it flies through the dark night sky. You can't lay a finger on me, not now or ever. The arm of the law is powerless before me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph......... "Powerless", is it? I wouldn't be so sure about that if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to describe you in one word: pitiful.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Pitiful...? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Quercus Alba! Your wings were clipped long ago.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And for someone who is trying to fly away on them without noticing that fact... ..."pitiful" is the perfect word to describe you!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hah! Mere words!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What do you mean by "his wings are clipped", Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just what you think it means, Kay. We had already caught him in our trap a while back. With an incredibly powerful, definitive piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, hey! Earth to Mr. Prosecutor! Care to speak in English!? What are you talking about? What piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The piece I speak of is of course... this drop of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But we know that it's not from the victim! I don't see how it remains relevant to the case at all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. von Karma... I believe that is exactly why it's very important to the case. And the part that is the most important is the fact that it's not the victim's blood!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're looking a little pale. Good, then I believe you are already aware of what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Then, you know who the blood belongs to!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Of course I do. This piece of evidence is the irrefutable proof that will stop the killer in his tracks. The blood that soiled this box of Samurai Dogs belongs to this person!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The blood belongs to Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, didn't you hear the forensics guy, Mr. Prosecutor!? He said that blood isn't Mr. Coachen's, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arnnngh! A-A simple slip of the tongue...!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...Is that all? Then I guess this time you'll get it right, right? Who's the owner of that blood? You know the answer, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The blood belongs to this person!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? But why is that person's blood on there, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's because! .........That's something I'll have to explain to you at a later date.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hey, Mr. Prosecutor, I know the answer; it's because you screwed up, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! I suppose there's no fooling Agent Lang...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Now give me a real answer this time! Do you or do you not know whose blood it is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Of course I know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The blood of the rising sun on this box belongs to you, Quercus Alba!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Grrr!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh--?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Why is HIS blood on the box of Samurai Dogs!? He's not even a victim!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The blood fell onto the box when Mr. Coachen's body was being loaded into the pushcart. At that time, the only two people in the dressing room were the victim and his killer.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">So that's what you mean! If the blood doesn't belong to the victim...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Then there is only one other person it could belong to!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and that person is the murderer himself. That's the only logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But Mr. Coachen was the one who was stabbed, sir! Why would Mr. Alba have been the one who was bleeding?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What if during the murder, Mr. Coachen had fought back?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You mean, if before Mr. Alba could kill him, Mr. Coachen managed to wound Mr. Alba...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, and I believe we have a piece of evidence that proves that he was bleeding then! <thought>What is the piece of evidence that shows that Mr. Alba was probably bleeding at the time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece shows that it's possible that Mr. Alba was bleeding at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I see... I suppose that does show us something. That you are quite possibly the most consummate liar of a prosecutor I've ever met!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What!? Look who's calling who a liar!</thought> Please excuse me. I will now show you the evidence you seek! Evidence that shows that Mr. Alba was counterattacked, and was bleeding because of it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba, you bear on your body a great wound.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">That was from when DeMasque II attacked me with a pair of scissors...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, and that happened way after he was in the dressing room...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but is that what really happened? You can manufacture a weapon by smearing blood on it, so I can't just accept that as fact. Shall we try a test, Mr. Alba, and see if the shape of your wound matches the scissors?</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">You really are something else, Mr. Edgeworth. You don't let a single thing slip you by, no matter how insignificant the possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You're one to talk Mr. Alba. You've managed to give the law the slip for ten years as the smuggling ring's leader. No matter the danger, you can hide every last ounce of fear and anxiety from everyone. You truly are a one-of-a-kind criminal.</line>
<line speaker="Alba"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh heh heh heh. I am the master of my fear. However, to think that a person such as you... ...could miss such a large thing...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You believe I've overlooked something?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">You said that my wound was caused by Mr. Coachen. And that it was caused here in one of the theater's dressing rooms, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I'd like to point out... that it's simply not possible. My wound is a stab wound, and one that could only have come from a blade. I wonder where you will propose that such a weapon came from?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Ah! This theater was packed with security guards...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It would've been impossible for anyone to come into this area with a weapon of any sort!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Just as Mr. Alba was able to bring in the Allebahstian knife in a bouquet... ...there must have been some other way to sneak in a weapon of some sort!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Ah, but as long as you can't prove what that other way is... ...all your talk about Mr. Coachen stabbing me is pure nonsense. So if that other way does exist, you'd better hurry and tell me now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........With pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Wait, what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence shows us how Mr. Coachen brought a weapon into this theater!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Using this, Mr. Coachen was able to bring a weapon into the Theatrum Neutralis!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Oh, really? Would you care to show me exactly how he did it using that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's... <thought>Curses. I can't think of a single way to use this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you had no confidence in your answer...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">...You'd have been better off thinking a bit more before picking something, you idiot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! Their double team efforts are worse than Larry and that old lady!</thought> Please excuse me. This time I will show you the evidence you desire to see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Among law enforcement, this piece is known as the Yatagarasu's Key.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Th-That key...!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">That's the key that my father stole from here seven years ago...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And it is very unique, in that it is both a key and a knife. Meaning that under the guise of a key, it could've been easily brought into the theater!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">...Gnnrooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You couldn't dispose of the knife that stabbed you... ...therefore, you wiped off the blood, and placed it back in Mr. Coachen's pocket! After all, the key itself opens the safe in his office. And inside that safe, there was a document about Cohdopian paper, signed by Mr. Coachen. In order to make it look like Mr. Coachen died as the leader of the smuggling ring... ...you had to make it so that the police were the ones who opened that office safe! Hmph. All that hard work to save yourself only served to destroy you in the end. Shall we try matching this knife's blade with your wound, Mr. Quercus Alba? ...And that is what some may call, the coup de grce.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">............I-Impossible... You... You can't take me down! Swine! All of you! Especially Manny Coachen!!! This is all because of that man's betrayal! He sought to steal control of the smuggling ring from me by removing me as ambassador! Which is why he deserved to die while bearing the guilt for all of my crimes for me! That's why I sent out the Yatagarasu's card, and how this incident was born! Manny was supposed to be the smuggling ring's leader who was killed by the Yatagarasu! But! I had... yet another reason, yet another story that was supposed to play out! Manny's death was supposed to bring everything to a close! And I would've gotten away with it too if it wasn't for you meddling prosecutors!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Alba, I'm afraid there is one more question I forgot to ask.........</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This country's, or Allebahst's: which country's court would you like to face first? Either way, it's game over for you.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">..................E... EdgeoooooooooEAaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaAAaAaaAaaaaAaaaaaaaa! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAaAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whew! This is it, the big day! It's Mr. Alba's trial today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And next week, he's scheduled to stand trial in his own country of Allebahst. Franziska is heading that one. I suspect she'll be serving a full course of whip lashes at it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Having to face Ms. von Karma in court right after facing you, sir... *shudder* I don't even WANT to think of what that would be like. I caught a glimpse of Mr. Alba as he was being escorted into the courthouse... ...and boy, he looked about as glum as I do the day before I get my monthly paycheck! You know, I've been thinking... ...that flight attendant, and even Mr. Portsman were all Mr. Alba's secret agents.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. That smuggling ring was the common thread between all of the incidents. Cammy Meele was to provide support during smuggling ops, using her job as an attendant. And Mr. Portsman was to manipulate trials related to the ring to end in their favor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oorrgh... iFly Airlines, and even the Prosecutor's Office... No one was safe from the smuggling ring, huh, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspect there are even more members of this ring spread throughout the world.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... It sounds like such a big op that I can't even begin to imagine what it's like! ..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? What is it, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Nothing! It's just... Well, come to think of it... ...Mr. Ernest Amano's trial is also scheduled for later today, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm aware of that... Mr. Amano has been working with the smuggling ring now for over ten years. He used the Amano Group's various connections world-wide to assist the ring. But all of that has come to an end as his conglomerate is now undergoing harsh scrutiny. I owe Mr. Amano a debt of gratitude, but he must pay his debt to society.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, with the arrests of both Mr. Alba and Mr. Amano... ...I guess that about wraps up the KG-8 Incident as well, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose so. The real killer in the KG-8 Incident ten years ago was Manny Coachen. And seven years ago, the killer in the second KG-8 Incident was Mack Rell. Those two facts are the unshakable truth, however... ...it seems that a lot of effort was put into hiding these and other truths from us. And I will expose it all at the trials today.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're solving cases left and right today, aren't you, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Cece Yew and Deid Mann... Perhaps now, these two brave souls who tried to make the truth known can rest in peace.</thought> ...By the way, I received some gifts from Ambassador Palaeno. Shrimp, crab, beef... I don't need any of these, so I'm giving them to you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? Seriously, sir!? W-Wait... Actually, I don't think I want them anymore... The way you're holding them... Don't tell me they're just coupons, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, have you not read the paper recently? Ever since the two countries became Cohdopia again, its economy has changed.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And it seems that Ambassador Palaeno has reaped a few benefits of his own from it. He has been announced as the official ambassador of the newly re-unified Cohdopia.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, but what a pity... Even though every item he sent is a "treasure", you don't seem all that interested. Well, if you don't want them... I can give them to my lovely assistant, Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Wait! That's not what I said! So, umm, Mr. Edgeworth! Please let me have them, sir! Actually, come to think of it, where is Kay? How come she's still not here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! You've gotta be more alert than that!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I can't believe you didn't notice I was even mimicking Mr. Edgeworth's voice for a bit!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I totally didn't notice you, or realize that voice was you!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Ferocious love blooms with each new Spring."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang... A pleasant surprise to see you here.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">It's been a long time since I set foot in a courthouse. But I wasn't going to miss... ...watching the guy who screwed up my country finally get what's coming to him. Well, that and something else. I want to see you in action in court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so, Agent Lang?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">We flushed out all of the counterfeit bills, so Zheng Fa is finally at peace again. And it's all thanks to you, so I just want to say... thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Wow, I never thought I'd see the day ol' Wolfy says thanks to Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I should be the one thanking you, Agent Lang. If you hadn't negated Mr. Alba's extraterritorial rights... ...I would not have been able to bring him to trial. I believe the victory belongs to the both of us in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">..................Tch. A shared victory, huh? Look, don't get me wrong; I'll still never forgive you prosecutors... ...and I have zero interest in that "truth" thing you talk about in court. I've always done things my own way, and that's not about to change, you got that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, I see... Well, I believe you should follow your own creed when you do your job.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yeah, and if there's ever someone your precious "truth" can't catch... ...feel free to sit around and cry about it all you want. But as for me, I'm going to get that person no matter what!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Alright. It's about time for the trial to start. I will see you later.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I'll be watching your performance from the gallery. I'm looking forward to this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I prepared a whole ton of ticker tape for today's victory, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'll help throw some around when Mr. Edgeworth wins!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Ha ha ha. Hope you've get enough, because I'm going to go call my men up as well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...A modest amount of ticker tape goes a long way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The scene shifts to the courtroom, and the final act of this long tale begins. "The Legend of the Great Thief Yatagarasu". It's the story of those who chose to dedicate their lives to the pursuit of the truth. "Prosecutors are those who seek a guilty verdict for the defendants they meet... ...and to that end, you have no choice but to win by any means necessary." That creed was forced on me since I was very young... ...however, I no longer think that is all we prosecutors are. And that is because...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even though I've only been away from the courtroom for a short time... ...I feel as though... it's been a lifetime since I've set foot in one. And today, more than any other day, I feel the fight within me rising...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Teneiro">I am really in Mr. Edgeworth's debt for the other day! Thanks to him, I'm still free to serve in the friendly blue skies. Oh, so about my suitcases... ...I've been selling them on the internet, and they've become a real sensation! Thanks to the praise the art world has lavished on my work as being truly post-modern... ...the airline has chosen me to design their new line of iFly jumbo jets! Just think! Someday, you will be able to take a ride in my pink-walled, yellow-seated jet!</line>
<line speaker="Lablanc">Edgeworth? Ah, that rudeness of a rude man! Hmph! Because of him, my time and money is wasted. But more importantlier! I received a most fantastic treasure mostly! The Primidux Statue of the Principality of Cohdopia! It weights a bit light in my hands, but the Ambassador Palaeno was most generous.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We finally caught Agent Hicks's killer, and I was able to witness Mr. Alba's teary eyes. It feels good to finally bring everything to a close. I received another offer from Interpol to work another case in cooperation with them... ...however, the Cohdopian courts await. Cohdopia's air is supposed to be very fresh, so my whip should find new vigor there.</line>
<line speaker="Meekins">This little patrolman has been fired as of today, sir! I thought I was safe since we found the gun I had dropped... ...but I hadn't noticed that I had dropped my police badge, too! I guess what really broke the camel's back was that I couldn't find my badge. My little life has suddenly tripped into a dark, black hole, sir! I think I'll go the courthouse and file a complaint with Ruffles Man!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was actually hoping to talk with Mr. Edgeworth a bit more than I did... But I've got to get going and return to Europe. I've still got a long way to go and a lot of stuff to study there! Next time I help Mr. Edgeworth on a case, I'm going to do it as a real forensic scientist! I'm sure he's going to need all the help I can give him, scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Paups">Because the kidnapping was staged, I was let off easy... ...but I won't be going outside much any time soon, but that's... really OK. The only prison I'm forever trapped in is the cage of love. The guard down at the detention center... well, when he's on guard duty... ...he has such a cold look in his eyes, just like that prosecutor... *ba-dump* Ah! Stop it, Lauren! When will you ever learn to stop being a prisoner of love...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears there are all sorts of drama that takes place outside of the courtroom. Since we judges are here day in and day out, I've only heard a few rumors, but... ...apparently, Mr. Edgeworth teamed up with a thief, and became a detective. Maybe I should team up with a bailiff and try to become a lawyer or something...?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Whew! I barely escaped death yet again!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but boy were we lucky to have Mr. Edgeworth help us out, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">Yeah... but because I lost the key, I got fired from my security guard job.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't let it get you down, Maggey! You've still got me!</line>
<line speaker="Byrde">You're right, sir! I won't be sad! I'm going to pick myself up and get through this! I wonder what my next job should be...? Ooh, this is actually kind of fun!</line>
<line speaker="Palaeno">Why not come to Cohdopia for your Summer vacation!? We have coupons aplenty! Right now, our embassy is proud to present our "Let's Investigate a Murder!" show. Although, recreating that particular case has created a few small fires of its own. Then we had a few problems with the fire marshals... but the next event will be great! It will be an attraction entitled, "Capture the Yatagarasu!" Of course, I hope to enlist Kay's help in creating our latest attraction!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I can't believe that Mindy ditched me and went to Japan... But it's OK! Because that's how I met Miharu! We're planning to go to Paris soon, and start a business! We're going to sell "Blue Ocean Dogs"! They'll sell like hot-cake hot dogs for sure! A blue hot dog in a blue bun, I guarantee it'll turn your tongue, and your face blue! I know I'm not really the type to work a lot, or at all really, but... Oh, so I noticed that I really haven't seen the guy in the blue suit at all recently. I wonder what's up? Well, the next time we meet, I'm gonna make him eat one of my Dogs!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Today I gave testimony in court today... as a member of the Yatagarasu...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Yo, Mr. Badd! You look well, all things considered. By the way, have you noticed that elements within the ring have begun moving?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">They're probably fighting over who should succeed... over who should be the next boss... .........Although, to be honest, I wish I could forget I'd ever heard of that smuggling ring.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Thoroughly bite the poisonous snake from head to tail!" No one runs afoul of the law and escapes this wolf's fangs! I'll get you all yet!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Ah, youth. When did I become so old, I wonder...? I've begun noticing the gray hairs in my beard more. I'm thinking of retiring my mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was the Pink Princess and the Pink Badger, all in the span of two days! Talk about busy! But it's alright, because I got a letter from my beloved Edgey-poo. "Please take care of your hip, and when you wish to speak, first take off your headpiece." ...What does he mean by that last statement!? It's not like I enjoy being under a head piece every time I see him! I've been an alien, and then some creepy, fuzzy, pink animal, and then I was the Pink Princess, a great hero of justice! But ever since I was a young maiden, I could be spotted wearing the most stylish hat on my head, although right around now, maybe it'd be more preferable to wear my own costume or something, but even that just sounds like a terrible idea...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whooooop! I feel so much better now that the trial's over! And as always, your legal prowess was top-notch, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, and nothing beat the look on Mr. Alba's face when you revealed the ring's secrets! I was amazed! You're like a totally different person when you step into a courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth is always ten times fiercer in court!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Based on the information Mr. Alba offered up, they've begun large scale operations... ...to clean up the rest of the ring, which I'm happy to leave to Franziska and Agent Lang.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So, what are your plans now, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hm? Oh, well, we've taken care of the creep who killed my father, so I'm not sure... Hey! I know! Maybe I'll just keep on being Mr. Edgeworth's assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Are you still trying to steal my job, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Just kidding, just kidding! I can't steal something so important to you, Gummy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Phew, what a relief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even after all that's happened, are you still planning to become a Great Thief?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Of course! But I don't want to tarnish the legend of the noble Yatagarasu... ...so I'm going to hold off on doing anything until I make a tight 3-person team of my own!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A three-person team...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">A three-person team of young beauties the same age as me, if possible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...With those criteria, I highly doubt you'll find the two other people you need.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">My father chose to fight for the truth. I think that's what was so noble about him. So you see, Mr. Edgeworth... ...the only things I will ever steal... are the truths that have been hidden away. I'm going to work extra hard to make a world where the Yatagarasu isn't needed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Let's both strive for such a future.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, I guess it's time for me to get going.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay! Keep your chin up and stay strong, OK!? And don't be a stranger!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Don't be worry! I'll be back! I'll be sure to break the lock on the window and sneak in!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could, I'd appreciate it if you came in through the building's front door...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's OK, Mr. Edgeworth! The lock on my window at home has been broken for forever!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! One last thing before I go! Let's take a group picture, just the three of us!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, a commemorative photo! Every big case has to end with one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................No.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey! Why not!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't tell me you're camera shy, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-Of course not, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Come on, Mr. Edgeworth! I'm taking the picture now! Hey! Come back here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth! You can't run away from this, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! Hey! Detective Gumshoe! S-Stop that! I can't be seen doing... that!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! I'm totally taking it now! Say, "cheeeeeeeeeese!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And thus, the long tale of the KG-8 Incident came to a close. It saw the demise of a smuggling ring and the birth of a little Great Thief. But there is little time to rest and relax... ...for I am eager to tackle the investigation into a new case. The reason for my eagerness is... ...my want to pursue the truth, and... ...my want to believe in the strength of those who use the power of the law for good. As someone who has chosen to live my life as a prosecutor... ...that is my new creed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Not so fast!!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Lang Zi says: "Confidence is like a soul, and words without confidence are but empty shells." You shouldn't waste your breath on words you have no confidence in, Mr. Prosecutor. Although, it's just as bad to say something in full confidence and be wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arghn!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you going to let him lecture you about your self-confidence like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't need to be overflowing with self-confidence; I just need to think rationally. After all, I only need to be confident in the facts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang, if you could take a look at this piece of evidence... ...you'd see that there is a very big flaw in your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Flaw? Are you sure it's not your eyes that are flawed? Talk to me again when you can see straight!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnnrk! Maybe this wasn't the piece I was looking for after all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement just now stands in contradiction to this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">That thing has nothing to do with what I was saying. Now, put it away! And your logic is so badly in need of repair that you might as well throw it out, too! This is the real deal here. Your courtroom mannerisms are worthless at a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk...! You dare to insult the courts!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence perfectly exposes the flaw in your logic!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? Well then, why don't you show me how it does just that? Go on!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh! I bet it's this part, right? This conflicts with something, right, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You have no idea what you're talking about, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe! Don't speak up when you don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ouch... I was just trying to follow your head, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That you would allow a subordinate to take over... You're a disgrace!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnnnnnrrrrk! <thought>I guess that wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. It would seem that your logic is not as perfect as you think it is.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence should show you exactly what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Oh, yes. It clearly shows what you're thinking. That you're attempting to buy yourself time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnngh! <thought>I knew I shouldn't have tried to pull a fast one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I believe your testimony just now conflicts with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And I believe that when you use the phrase "I believe", you are anything but certain. Which means that showing me that piece of evidence is just a way to waste time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaaaaaah! <thought>She even managed to whip the evidence at the some time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owwww!! Why did you whip me, too, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's one more victim besides myself and the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That statement just now stands in clear contradiction to this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">No, it doesn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! <thought>But that's impossible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. The prosecutors of this country... Are you all prone to pointing out nonexistent "contradictions"? How frightening it is to think that it might be true.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... I can't let him drag me down with his insults!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence will reveal the whole sad tale to us!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph. I have no interest in listening to such a story. The only story I'm interested in is the glorious one of my shining life. Shall I write you into one of its pages? Consider it an honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's quite alright! <thought>He didn't even bat an eye... I suppose this wasn't related after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">Phwwh... I guess so! Ahahaha! Oh, I just love the way you say that with such confidence! But just as you said, you can only say something is perfect after you've verified it! Now try presenting evidence to me again, but this time, in the correct way, rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Gnrk! <thought>I was a fool to claim that it was perfect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement directly contradicts this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Does it now? Hmph. Not that it really matters to me either way. But are you really sure my statement contradicts that piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>Judging by his overconfident attitude... ...I guess this piece of evidence wasn't related to his statement after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... You can't chase him down with that kind of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, I know... <thought>I must think calmly and rationally about this... ...because it's NOT impossible to take this man down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">You guys... are still here...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agent Lang! You're back already...!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">I told you I'd be back, didn't I? This is my case! And I'm not going to let you guys take it away from me!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I thought you no longer had authority over this case?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Authority? I don't care about petty logistics! I am not about to just walk out on this case, not after how far I've come. So sorry, sis... but I need you to get out of here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How dare you!?</line>
<line speaker="Lang">This is my turf, so get yourself on home to your den! You guys! Escort the nice prosecutors home, will you!?</line>
<line speaker="MIB">Sir! Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What in the world are you thinking, Agent Lang!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Looks like I've got all the answers I need. Come on, sis... It's time for us to go.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A-Agent Lang! Please wait!</line>
<line speaker="Lang">Heh! Sorry, but I'm tired of waiting! Because I'm not one for waiting around for others to solve my case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I demand that you to something about this at once!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack! <thought>But I'm at a loss of what to do myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lang">Hmph... Well, I know I have plenty to ask the sis here about. Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Arngh! Is this really where it all ends...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, if I could ask you to please leave the premises... As you can see for yourself, I am an old man... and I'm a bit tired from all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait, please!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I've made up my mind, so if you could please leave... Agent Lang, a good job to you as well. Although, I don't think we'll ever be meeting again.</line>
<line speaker="Lang">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, please respect the request of the ambassador of the Kingdom of Allebahst... ...and vacate the premises.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnrk! Is this it...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph! Are you still here? Are you still trying to force me to admit!? You people have no reason to still be here. Now, please leave.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm afraid I can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Heh... If you won't leave on your own, I will have no choice but to force you out.</line>
<line speaker="Kay"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I don't believe we'll be meeting again, however, I will pray for your success. Heh heh heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're not through here yet!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Haaahahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnrk! Is this it...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Now then, I believe I must end the game here. You've had enough fun, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! If you don't do something, he's going to get away!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">I've already confessed. What else do you want from me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...No... No... I have yet to obtain the truth behind tonight's events!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Hmph... Do you think I really care about this "truth" you seek? Now, since I have admitted to my crime, I will need to pay the airport a visit. So if you would be so kind as to move out of my way...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>Is there no way to stop this man...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alba">I don't believe we'll be meeting again, however, I will pray for your success. Heh heh heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We're not through here yet!</line>
<line speaker="Alba">Haaahahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Gnrk! Is it really "game over"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>