<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Will">... ... Umm... Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Why do you look so... unhappy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-oh! Oh, nothing! Eh heh heh. Really, it's nothing. Right, Mia? <thought>Uh oh. She looks even unhappier...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Your client is now practically a dead man walking... Perhaps that's why I feel particularly close to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is no time for dead-people jokes, please.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You know we're going into this trial utterly defenseless. Yet, if Mr. Powers is truly innocent... We should be able to find something overlooked in the evidence to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something "overlooked"...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We have to find something, Phoenix, today. It's that, or lose the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't going to be easy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Edgeworth, your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An unexpected fact has come to the attention of the court. Yesterday, we learned that there were other people present at the studios! Today, I would like to show evidence proving they had nothing to do with the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may call your first witness, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder if that producer is going to come out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution calls Mr. Sal Manella to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... or that director.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness state his name and profession?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">... How r00d can j00 get! J00 don't know ME!? I'm the director! I make the Steel Samurai, n00b! ROFL!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Manella">S... Sal Manella. I'm a director. Television.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Were you at Global Studios on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Y-yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Please testify to the court about the events of that day.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Let's start by picking this testimony apart. If Powers is innocent, you know what that means. Someone in the trailer on that day did it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right. <thought>She doesn't waste any time putting on the pressure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">I was at the studios from around 9:00 that morning.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">That's about it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The time of Mr. Hammer's death was 2:30 PM. And according to your testimony, you were in a meeting at that time. Mr. Wright, you may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">I was at the studios from around 9:00 that morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that when you always come in to work?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, oh no. I come in all sort of hours. It's the "industry" way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, I know all about the freaks in your "industry"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">Still, FWIW, I was pretty busy all that day.&#160;:(</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell us more about that.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">During the morning, I was doing... umm... an action scene run-through.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the Employee Area?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">That's right. It was a fight scene between the Steel Samurai and the Evil Magistrate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was anyone else at the run-through?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, yeah. That security lady was sitting there watching the whole thing. LOL. She was cheering on Hammer, if you can believe it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She certainly has the lungs for it...</thought> Anyone else?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Nope, just us four.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">It took a lot more time than I thought it would.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did it go on so long?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Um, I'm pretty sure j00've already heard about this... But WP twisted his ankle during the run-through, see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right, thus the limp.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">Which of course led to me missing my lunch. ROFS!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>ROFS? Rolling on the Floor... Starving?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">I hear that everyone else ate lunch in the Employee Area...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What exactly did they have for lunch?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">T-bone steak! The assistant cooked some up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, there was a plate with some bones on it in the Employee Area.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Everyone else" meaning that the witness did not eat with them.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">But I had a meeting in the Studio Two trailer, so I ended up skipping lunch.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, in the end, you didn't get to eat?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah. No steak, at least! Can j00 believe it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must have been tough.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Doesn't something about that seem odd to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, no, not really. Seems pretty straightforward.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh. Perhaps I was wrong, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, there is something bothering me. Mr. Manella, just now you said "steak, at least." So you ate something other than steak?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, good call! I had some chocolate in my pocket, which I used to stave off starvation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>Is that all? I was sure I was on to something there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it does seem odd, now that you mention it. Mr. Manella!</line>
<line speaker="Manella">H-hmm? W-what do j00 mean? *sweats*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I went to that trailer, I saw something on the table. There were two plates on the table--the same kind of plates as in the Employee Area. Who ate lunch there?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">M-mmpf! No, er, ah, um, eh heh. Good call! *sweats* I, er, I was embarrassed so I didn't mention it... But I did eat, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A t-bone steak, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, well, I mean the assistant went through all that trouble... I brought it to the trailer thinking I could eat it later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Clearly a man who likes to eat. I'd suspected as much...</thought> So, when exactly did you eat it?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">We took one break during that meeting. I, er, wolfed it down then. *drool*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A mental image I will carry with me to my grave... Wait a second...! If they took a break in that meeting, that contradicts his testimony! I'll press on that one a bit more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">We were in the meeting until around 4:00...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were you discussing?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">The Steel Samurai story, and our budget. Get this! The sponsors turn to me and say, "Mr. Manella. Those scripts of yours are not appropriate for children." Can j00 believe it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, I kind of can.</thought> So, nobody left the table during the whole meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">During the meeting, well, I'm pretty sure no one left their chairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't take a single break?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Er... well... Y-yeah! Not a one! *sweats*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... what's he sweating so much about, I wonder? If only I had an idea...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll wait for one to come up and hit him with it later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second... Maybe I do have an idea!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, on second thought, I'm drawing a blank. If I press too hard in the wrong place, I'll just end up scaring him into silence. Maybe I'll just sit back and see what happens.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. If his alibi holds, Powers is finished. Press him as hard as you can and find out where he's lying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! Mr. Manella, you've just contradicted yourself! Didn't you just tell the court that you ate that t-bone steak during a break?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oops! ROFL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Manella, what's this all about?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">W-well, yeah, I guess we did take a little break.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Great job! If they took a break, one of them could have gone to the studio during that time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I call on the witness to testify to the court about this break!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Manella, your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. Edgeworth is laughing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, FWIW, we took a break... ROFL!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't think it would even be enough time for that, but that's just me. Very well. You may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Yeah, FWIW, we took a break... ROFL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What time exactly did you take this break?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Hmm... I'd say it was from around 2:30 or so untl 2:45.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>2:30!!! That's the time of death! So he could have gone to Studio One, killed Hammer, and come back... I guess it's possible, time-wise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Manella">But it was only 15 minutes! 15! That's only 13 in Base 12!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were you doing for those 15 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Eating my t-bone steak! What else!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were two plates on the trailer table...?</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Oh, right. The other one was Diva's... sorry, Dee Vasquez's plate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dee Vasquez... the producer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To eat a t-bone steak in 15 minutes... that's quite a feat.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Not enough time for someone to, say, commit murder in Studio One! LOL!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Manella">That's only just enough time to eat a t-bone steak, if you ask me! *steams*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to say, you look like a guy who gets through his meals pretty fast.</line>
<line speaker="Manella">Well, I was facing a cold, slightly chewy t-bone steak... Even I have to take my time eating that kind of food. LOL</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Phoenix?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That testimony was too short to wring any kind of useful information out of!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">All you have to do is prove that he was able to go to Studio One in that time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, great. Is that all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Haven't we had enough of this pointless line of questioning? Your Honor! The testimony to this point has made one certain fact painfully clear: The people in the trailer had nothing to do with this murder! It was impossible for any of them to go to Studio One!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something wrong, Mr. Wright? Surely you aren't suggesting one of the people in the trailer went to Studio One!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, this is critical! Think about it before you give your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you claim someone from the trailer went to Studio One?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I agree to let everyone in that trailer off the hook then the trial is over... Mr. Powers will be found guilty for sure!</thought> The victim was murdered at 2:30, the exact time of the break in the meeting. With 15 minutes, murder is certainly a possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose you might say that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Alright, I've got the judge thinking now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tsk, tsk, tsk... Never a dull moment with you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's your point, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've been doing your homework, haven't you? Look at the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Court Record...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Surely, you knew that from 2:15 to 4:00 the path between the studios was blocked? Mrs. Monkey's head had fallen across the path!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">True, the break in the trailer meeting came right at the time of death... However! The path from there to the scene of the crime was blocked! The fallen Mrs. Monkey head barred the way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>It's actually "Mr. Monkey," but Edgeworth has a point... And somehow, I feel no desire to correct him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">No counter-argument, Mr. Wright? Then I'm afraid you lose this round.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't want to write off so many possible suspects... But I can't keep claiming the impossible, either...</thought> I agree that it was impossible for anyone in the trailer to go to the studio in that time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ha hah! I thought you might be thoughtlessly treading on thin ice again! But I see you had at least an inkling of the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's quite simple... True, the break in the trailer meeting came right at the time of death... However! The path from there to the scene of the crime was blocked! The fallen Mrs. Monkey head barred the way! At around 2:15, a strong gust of wind knocked off the studio mascot's head. Ergo! When the people in the trailer took a break at 2:30, the way to the studio was blocked. Blocked... by Mrs. Monkey's severed head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>It's actually "Mr. Monkey," but Edgeworth has a point... And somehow, I feel no desire to correct him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe we have seen enough evidence. I would like to relieve Mr. Manella from the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wh-what? It's over?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court's opinion on this case is as follows: We have found that there were several other people in Studio 2 on the day of the murder. However, it is also clear that none of these people could have gone to Studio One. They therefore have no relation to this case. Furthermore, with regards to the photo of the Steel Samurai... Given the size of the costume, no one other than Mr. Powers could have worn it that day. All that is lacking is decisive evidence that he is the one who did it. If we had that, I'm afraid I would have to find Mr. Powers guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. The prosecution is pleased to announce that we indeed have decisive evidence: a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this witness, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My witness saw the very moment when the Steel Samurai skewered the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! I will have order! I see. The court will take a 10 minute recess, after which we will hear your witness. Court is adjourned for recess!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do we do now, Mia? If everyone in that trailer has an alibi...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... I'm sorry, Phoenix. I guess I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia! Don't tell me you're giving up! If you give up, what hope do I have...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Don't get me wrong. I've never given up on a trial before, not while there was a chance. Only one thing became clear in your cross-examination. The people in the trailer could not have gone to Studio One. I thought there was more to it than that... But I was wrong. That's all there is.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Umm... Er... What's going to happen to me? It kinda seems like everyone in that courtroom thinks I did it... They think I'm a murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't worry, Mr. Powers. If you are innocent, we will prove it. I guarantee it. Leave it to us, and... be yourself. Be strong. You are the Steel Samurai, hero to children everywhere, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Will">I... You... Thanks. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Okay, Phoenix. This one's for the kids! Let's do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is back in session for the trial of Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has a concern. As our witness is a grade schooler of tender years, and this is a murder case... We worry that the defense might cause unnecessary trauma with his cruel questioning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice to see Edgeworth taking the moral high ground...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, we have no choice. The prosecution calls Cody Hackins to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Perhaps you could arrange a box for him to stand on?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, r-right. Guard, please bring him a box. One of those donut crates should do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness state his name and grade in school.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">What!? Just 'cause you're all grown-up don't mean you can push me around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mrph...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Cody? Answer his question, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">H-hey, it's you! The nice lady! I'm Cody Hackins. I'm in 2nd grade!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get the feeling this is going to be a long, long day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. Please remember that you're speaking to a child. Try to be gentle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-mrrrrph! Witness! Er, I mean, Cody.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's having trouble with this "gentle" thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were present, er, you were at Global Studios on the day of the, er, incident?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">You got a problem with that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please tell us what you saw that day.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">What, pops? You want me to tell you and gramps with the beard over there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just.. Mr. Edgeworth will be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I prefer "bearded gentleman" myself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A very long day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Incidentally, photographic equipment is strictly forbidden in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-mpht! M-my apologies, Your Honor. He said he wouldn't testify if he couldn't bring it... I'd like special permission, if that's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, so you're saying you had to bargain terms with a kid... and you LOST?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hey! I just got this new camera! Don't really know how to use it all that good yet! But I bring it with me wherever I go!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. I wonder if he had that camera on the day of the murder... You'd better make a note of it in the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Cody. Please testify to the court about what you saw the day of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I wanted to see a Steel Samurai rehearsal, just once.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Anyway, I couldn't get into the studio, so I went home.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. The defense may begin its cross-examination. And, be gentle. Remember you're talking to a child.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This kid is tougher than most adults we see in here, honestly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">I wanted to see a Steel Samurai rehearsal, just once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You really like the Steel Samurai, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Course I do! I've taped every show! And I go to all the live performances!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's impressive. Have you been to the amusement park?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Course! Duh! My Dad always takes me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor, poor Dad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">I found a map on the Internet, and went to the studios that day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that day the first time you'd been to the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Uh, actually I've been a couple of times. I never manage to get there on a rehearsal day! And that security lady's always yelling...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right, right. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Chill, pops! I'm getting to it! How am I supposed to talk with you cuttin' me off all the time? Geez!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I went through the woods, off the path, so that old lady wouldn't catch me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Off the path"...?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, you know how the studios are in a valley there? If you go off the path a little, there's woods. That's where I was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Anyhow...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I was going for the studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did nothing unusual happen on your way to the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">"Unusual"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you see this monkey by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Oh, you mean Mr. Monkey? Yeah I saw him, but his head wasn't busted!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you went straight to the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I got kinda lost on the way, though. For about 30 minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got lost in the woods?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah. I couldn't figure out which way I was walking. Man, was I relieved when I saw the blue studio doors. But guess what happened next!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">When I came out by the studio, there was the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, he was standing by the studio gate. It looked like he was thinking about something before going in. Then he opened up the gate and went inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. What then?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">It totally rocked! Right before my eyes, out came the bad guy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What sort of "bad guy" was it?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">A guy. A person. Kinda tall. Skinny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it was a guy?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... I dunno. He was kinda far away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh, he's being awfully vague...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Of course, the Steel Samurai took him down! Pow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened to the bad guy?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Huh? Well... Well, he kinda didn't move. Not a bit. Like he was dead. I-I guess he's a real pro! What a great actor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, I suppose he was.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">If I had my camera with me, that woulda been the time for a shot, I tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"If" you had your camera? You mean, you weren't carrying your camera then?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">N-no, I wasn't. I-it's not like I have it all the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess seeing the killing freaked him out and he went home...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Remember, he's a child. Use gentle words... but be firm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Easy for you to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody, what you just said seems, well, a little strange. Didn't you say before that you always bring your digital camera wherever you go? You were quite clear about that.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody, you shouldn't lie here. You understand that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! A word with you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... was I putting the pressure on too much?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is this "digital" camera contraption you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's umm... a digital camera, Your Honor. It's kind of a new sort of camera. <thought>How do I explain that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, Cody... I can't believe you wouldn't bring your camera on a trip to the studios! You did bring it, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright! How cruel you are, to terrorize a poor child so!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care if he's a child or a prosecuting attorney! No one should lie in court!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean "or a prosecuting attorney"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Cody?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Wh-what! Yeah, so I had my camera. So what!? You got a problem with that!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, you did have a camera? And did you use this camera?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">W-why would I use it? I... I was too busy watching.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Please testify to the court about what you were so busy watching.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah, I had my camera with me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ah? Is that all? Well, that was brief. Mr. Wright, your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah, I had my camera with me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, why didn't you use it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's getting to that! Relax and listen.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Umm... I didn't use it 'cause I was too busy watching the real thing!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">But I was glued to the action! I couldn't take my eyes off it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were watching the Steel Samurai. Did you watch the whole fight?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't turn away, not even once?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">N... no!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, then tell us exactly what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah! I'm getting to that!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">The Steel Samurai, he goes for the bad guy... wham!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the bad guy attacked him first?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What sort of person was this "bad guy"?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I told you, a person. He was a person.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How was he dressed?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... I kinda don't remember. I was too busy watching the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. And what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Then... then the bad guy stopped moving!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Huh? Whaddya mean, "why"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why wasn't the bad guy moving?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">W-well 'cause the Steel Samurai brought him to justice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And how exactly did he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">H-how did he do it? With a Samurai Kick! And a Samurai Punch! Samurai Chop! ... Samurai Slap! S-something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's still being vague about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">What! Don't give me that look, pops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How should I play this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah... If I press too hard now, the judge might keep me from continuing. I'll sit back and see how the rest of this goes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">He's so strong! The Steel Samurai rules!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you do after the bad guy fell, Cody?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... Um, actually... The fight was so... so intense that I got kinda scared. So I went straight home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something isn't adding up here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something about his account doesn't seem right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. It doesn't seem right because he's being deliberately vague! Press him on the facts, Phoenix! Find out what he saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something's bothering me. Before you said that you "couldn't take your eyes off" the action.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah? So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet you missed the most important part!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is the meaning of this? The witness has stated what he saw quite clearly...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know as well as I do that he's being vague! Tell me, what kind of murderer uses a "Samurai Slap"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-mmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My point is this: Cody, you may have seen some of the Steel Samurai's fight... But you missed the most important part: the killing blow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Mr. Wright! How could this be? Can you explain how he might have missed something so vital?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... er, that's the thing...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! I believe you're on the right track with this! Think: why didn't Cody see the climax of the fight? I know you! You can figure this out!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, your answer! We have ascertained that this young boy is a great fan of the Steel Samurai... Why wouldn't he watch the climax of the fight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he couldn't watch it! How could he calmly watch a murder taking place at his age!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just a moment, please... One thing has become quite clear in this boy's testimony. He did not believe he was witnessing a murder! He was watching the Steel Samurai fight, like on TV. The more real the fight, the more he would have watched!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... huh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to agree with Mr. Edgeworth. Well, Mr. Wright. Do you have another explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He missed the climax of the fight... because he was looking at something else! Probably!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Probably"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Something else"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright, explain yourself! What could possibly distract this boy from seeing his idol, the Steel Samurai, fight!? What do you claim he was looking at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-ooof! <thought>C'mon, think of something... think of something... Nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Please refrain from making baseless claims!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes... Sorry, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have another explanation for this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I have evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Evidence"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. Why did Cody look away from the fight?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proof?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh... Can I... do that again? <thought>This doesn't prove anything...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! Lost your nerve, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well... I'll ask you the question again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that? The camera...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness stated that he recently received this camera.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I'm aware of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He wasn't entirely familiar with its operation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm aware of that, too. Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct! Why would Cody be looking somewhere else at the critical moment? Because he was looking at his camera! He was trying to take a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bullseye!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">W-what's your problem, pops! You got a thing for picking on little kids!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pressing, not picking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Good job, Phoenix! Cody was lying, clearly. Smart of you to realize there was no way he could just stand there, watching his hero... and not take a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! Cody? There was only one reason why you would have looked away from the fight. And that was because you wanted to take a picture. But having just received your camera, you weren't used to using it yet! So, you missed the climax of the fight. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... ... ... Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Phoenix. I'll bet you anything he's hiding more than that. Have him testify again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right. <thought>Mia means business!</thought> Your Honor. The defense would like to request that Cody Hackins testify once more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-very well. Cody? Could you please tell us about your camera... And about why you didn't take a picture of the fight?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Welcome to the real world, kid!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, you're right, pops.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Anything strange in that testimony, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure... But I'd like to proceed with the cross-examination anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, you're right, pops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Pops"...?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, I called you "pops," you spiky-haired geezer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">G-geezer...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm "Mr. Edgeworth."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I guess I'm the "bearded gentleman"...</line>
<line speaker="Cody">That's what I hate about grown-ups. You're all so self-conscious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, off with the kid gloves! Testify, witness, testify!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">The Steel Samurai had just escaped from the clutches of the villain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you did see the beginning of the fight?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you notice anything unusual?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Umm... well... uh... I guess the Steel Samurai was moving a little strange...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Moving... strangely?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">So I held up my camera to take a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why couldn't you take a picture?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">My new camera has too many buttons. I couldn't figure it out. I tried to take a picture, I really tried.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">But the lens wouldn't open in time, so I missed it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When the lens opened, what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Uh... well, a person on the ground. And the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Th-that's all that happened. Yup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah! I told you, I didn't take a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I would have, once I got that lens open... Did he really not take a picture? Not even one?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nah, he definitely would have taken a picture. There's got to be something here I can use!</thought> Cody! Listen up, Cody Hackins. I know exactly what happened that day. You took a picture!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Bullseye...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">H-how did you know!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see through all your lies Cody Hackins. It's one of my powers!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">W-wow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This feels great!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah... Yeah, I took a picture.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you can change your testimony to reflect this, Cody?</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Th-that's all that happened. Yup." to "I took a few shots, but it was too late, so I erased 'em."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He looks ready to burst into tears... I'd better lay off him for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Cody">I took a few shots, but it was too late, so I erased 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "erased" them?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Y-yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would you erase a picture of your beloved Steel Samurai, victorious?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Well... y'know. W-why would I want to keep a picture like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... he's becoming less and less cooperative. I better find a clear contradiction soon... or some solid evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How can I pick holes in such a short testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There has to be something. Dig up the dirt, Phoenix! Find out what this kid's all about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Wh-wh-what!? Man, every time you say "Cody" you follow it with something bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just wanted to thank you for giving me this the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Huh? O-oh... right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was it you told me then?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I go to every live performance! I always take a picture when the Steel Samurai lands the final blow! Whizzam! I got 'em all! I never missed one! A perfect collection!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody. Did you really get a picture of the Steel Samurai standing victorious over his foe? If you did, I find it hard to believe that you would just erase it! Wouldn't you keep it for your album?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... What exactly is this album?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's called "Path to Glory." It's a collection of pictures of the Steel Samurai, all taken by Cody Hackins. He claims it's a perfect collection of every battle the Steel Samurai has won!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you find this very odd, Your Honor? Among all his pictures of the Steel Samurai, none were taken that day!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Mr. Wright. Have you an explanation? If the Steel Samurai had just defeated his adversary... I certainly would expect to see a picture of it in this album...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly my point, Your Honor! ... ... .........! <thought>No... wait... no way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix? I think we've finally discovered the truth. And what a truth it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mia... are we sure about this? Did he actually...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes. I'm pretty sure what you're thinking is right. Tell them, Phoenix. Tell them what the truth is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Please explain to the court what is going on here! Why was there no picture in the album from the day of the murder? Why would the boy have erased the photos he took?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe that Cody Hackins is what we call an "artiste."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An... "artiste"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He didn't like the photos he had taken! They were blurry, or maybe his framing was off... Anyway, for some reason, he erased the data!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that right, Cody?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Wh-what do you mean "framing was off"!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems the only thing "off" is your guesswork, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh... Yes, well, I'm sure the reall reason is...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes? The real reason is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Simple, Your Honor. Cody wasn't used to using his new camera. He erased those photos he took by mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-wait a second, Phoenix. If that's your answer, we're back where we started!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean, that wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! If you have something to say to the court, speak up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well... S-sorry, Your Honor. Can I change my answer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can think of only one reason, your honor. The Steel Samurai didn't win! That's why Cody deleted those photos.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the Steel Samurai... lost?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Cody? I'm right, aren't I? Tell the truth. The bad guy defeated the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">N-n-n-no way! No! I-it's impossible! Th-the Steel Samurai never loses! He never loses to anyone! Ever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... The witness has revealed everything with his words. There was a reason why he lied and told us he didn't take a picture. The same reason he erased his precious photos! For Cody, it was inconceivable that the Steel Samurai could be defeated. However, Cody witnessed the impossible! He saw the Steel Samurai lose! Yet to admit what he saw would destroy everything he believed in! That's why he lied and said the Steel Samurai won. He couldn't handle the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Order! I will have order! W-witness! I mean, Cody! Is this true!? W-what did you see? Tell the court what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I...... Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cody... That day, you saw the Steel Samurai lose a fight. Right?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Waaaaaaaaaaaaah! Okay okay! Y-you're right! Th-the Steel Samurai f-fell down... Th-then he didn't m-move... Waaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of stunt are you trying to pull, Wright!? The Steel Samurai was the murderer, not the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet according to your witness's testimony, the Steel Samurai was the one who fell!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! What's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently, we have all made a serious error.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An... error? What's this all about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Quite simply, the victim was Jack Hammer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Mr. Wright? We all know that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you'd like to reconsider your last statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry. It was I who was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Okay, Wright! First you're right, now you're wrong!? Which is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-look, I'm sure there's something we're overlooking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're so sure, then tell us what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was no victim in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-wh-what!? Has the defense taken leave of its senses!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, Jack Hammer died. But the Steel Samurai fell too! It was a draw!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Sorry. I was too shocked to say anything for a bit there. Listen, Wright! Only one person died in this incident, and that is Jack Hammer! Yet now you claim there "was no victim"? Are you insane?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, he's pulling out all the stops now.</thought> ... I'm sorry. It was I who was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Okay, Wright! First you're right, now you're wrong!? Which is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-look, I'm sure there's something we're overlooking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you're so sure, then tell us what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you understand what really happened, it's actually quite simple. At the end of the fight, the Steel Samurai fell to the ground, and lay still. In other words, the Steel Samurai was not the killer, he was the victim! Don't you see? Jack Hammer was the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! So, the Steel Samurai in this photograph... You're saying the man in this costume was the victim, Mr. Jack Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I'm saying, Your Honor. Jack Hammer was present at the action scene run-through that morning. Thus, he obviously knew about Will Powers's foot injury.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but wait! Hadn't Mr. Hammer gone to Studio One already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what everyone thought! But remember what Ms. Oldbag said in her testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">On the day of the murder, I arrived at the guard station at 1:00 PM. Did I see poor old Hammer? Nope. He'd already gone to the studio before I got back to the guard station.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Jack Hammer left the Employee Area after lunch. However, no one saw him going to Studio One. Nor was there a picture of him. He waited for Mr. Powers to take a nap in his dressing room. Then he snuck into the dressing room and stole the Steel Samurai costume.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why would the victim do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Cody">... I get it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">I thought that the Steel Samurai was moving strange. So it was a different person inside the suit! Pops!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, me? What?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Actually, there was one piece of data I saved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Data?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Yeah, a photo on my digital camera!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Show us, quick!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">No way man, not if you're gonna look at me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now!</line>
<line speaker="Cody">*sniff* Here... This is it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, looking at this it's still a little hard to say. I'm afraid that it could be anyone in that costume. Your opinion, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree, Your Honor. This isn't decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, this doesn't look like it's the proof we need. I'll give it back.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wait, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia? What?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Look at that photo once more! That's it Phoenix! That photo is all the evidence you need to win this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!? Y-Your Honor! May I see that photo once more please?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">C-certainly. I don't see why not.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix! Show him! There's a glaring, decisive inconsistency with the facts as we know them in that photo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Find the inconsistency in the photo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Steel Samurai...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's about the only thing in this picture that could be inconsistent. The Steel Samurai is inconsistent with... something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright! This is no time for daydreaming and pointless pontification! Think about your client, and us, who are forced to listen to your rambling!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please rethink your position.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You seem to be lacking even more confidence than usual.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose that's because I'm not confident about it at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe you want to rethink your case, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... a gate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Might I draw your attention to the number on that gate?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The number? Ah yes. Well, it's hard to see, but it looks like a "2."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Clearly not a "1," Your Honor, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe Mr. Edgeworth sees what I'm getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-but... Th-that's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? Eh? What's this all about? Please explain so that I might be shocked along with the rest of the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll use the studio guidemap. The body was found here, in Studio One. However, what do we see in this photo taken at the time of the murder? It does NOT say "1" on that gate in the photo. Your Honor! Here is the true scene of the crime! <thought>Show the judge where the murder took place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What does that have to do with the number on the gate in the photograph...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... well... Sorry, Your Honor, I guess I hadn't thought it that far through yet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Think it through before you point at the map this time, Mr. Wright! Once again! Where is he scene of this crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here, at Studio Two.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! That would explain the "2" on the gate in the photo.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I find it very significant that the murder took place in Studio Two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you may recall, there is a trailer in Studio Two. Now, on that day, a meeting was held in that very trailer. There was a break in the meeting corresponding to the time of death. During that break, Mr. Sal Manella and Ms. Dee Vasquez were outside, eating steak. They were at the scene of the crime! The path to the trailer was blocked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So we have heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The path was blocked at 2:15... In other words, the victim went to Studio Two before that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... yes, I suppose that would be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember Mr. Sal Manella's testimony? Allow me to remind the court: He said no one in the trailer was guilty because they could not have gone to Studio One. Yet, in actuality, the reverse was true! Only someone in the trailer could have committed this murder! They were the only ones with access to the scene of the crime: Studio Two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The path to the trailer was blocked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So we have heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The path was blocked at 2:15... In other words, the victim went to Studio Two before that time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... yes, I suppose that would be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember Mr. Sal Manella's testimony? Allow me to remind the court: He said no one in the trailer was guilty because they could not have gone to Studio One. Yet, in actuality, the reverse was true! Only someone in the trailer could have committed this murder! They were the only ones with access to the scene of the crime: Studio Two! As you may recall, there is a trailer in Studio Two. Now, on that day, a meeting was held in that very trailer. There was a break in the meeting corresponding to the time of death. During that break, Mr. Sal Manella and Ms. Dee Vasquez were outside, eating steak. They were at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Studio Two is no longer being used for filming!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... And this is significant... why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good question! I really should think these things through more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you like to take another stab at it? So to speak?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-stabbing away, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense makes the following claims: The scene of the crime was Studio Two! The person that the security guard, Ms. Oldbag saw was the victim, Mr. Jack Hammer! Mr. Hammer, for some reason, stole a Steel Samurai costume. Then he went to Studio Two!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is madness! Jack Hammer is the victim! The victim! Why would he steal a Steel Samurai costume!? Are you suggesting he did so to cover up the details of his own murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well, no, of course not...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Or do you have proof!? Give me proof that the victim, Jack Hammer, stole the costume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have proof!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-you do!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that they're so surprised suddenly I'm much less confident... I think I'm right, though!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Proof? Uh oh... I'm pretty sure I don't have anything like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix. Even if you're not 100% sure about this, you have to try. And I think you've got proof that's good enough to win them over! Just go for it! All or nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually... I do have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here's my proof that Jack Hammer stole the costume!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, no, that can't be right... I've got to have some proof that will knock their socks off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! We don't have all the time in the world, here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An empty... medicine bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this on the table in the Employee Area. The same table where Mr. Hammer and Mr. Powers ate. The label reads "sleeping pills."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Sleeping pills"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant, Mr. Powers, spent that entire afternoon sleeping. He was drugged... by Mr. Hammer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait a moment... That bottle does raise some suspicions, yes. But there is no proof that Mr. Hammer used it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I have an idea.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An... idea? Continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Run a test of Powers's blood. You should find traces of the sleeping pills.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This much time after the day of the murder!? Even if there were traces it still proves nothing! No blood test could tell that Hammer was the one who drugged him, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right. Darn. That didn't work. Time to try another idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">An idea, Mr. Wright? And that would be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... we should examine Mr. Hammer's body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Hammer...? I thought that it was Mr. Powers who was made to take the sleeping pills?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-indeed it was, Your Honor. <thought>Wrong again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">An... idea? Very well, let's hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to check this bottle for fingerprints! If my claim is true, Mr. Hammer's fingerprints should show up on this bottle!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose you're right. Very well. The court will take possession of the bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court will suspend proceedings on the current trial for today. Cody Hackin's [sic] testimony has revealed new possibilities in this case. In fact, things may have happened very differently than we previously thought. The Steel Samurai seen by Ms. Oldbag may have been the victim, Jack Hammer. The scene of the crime was not Studio One, but Studio Two. And those in the trailer did have time to commit murder. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your homework is to find the answer to the following question: Why would Mr. Hammer steal the Steel Samurai costume? Also, who killed him, and why? Find the answers for me by tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's a lot of homework!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mm?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will need to reconsider your stance in this case. Above all, you will need to reconsider your suspicion of Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you say, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This trial will be extended until tomorrow. This is the last extension! Very well... Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew! That was a close one!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">We were saved by a hair, but that's all that counts. I thought seriously about going home about three times during the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-me too!</line>
<line speaker="Will">Really? You both seemed so... so confident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah! Maybe I should take up a career in acting? I was ready to pronounce you dead about three times back there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Me too!</line>
<line speaker="Will">D-dead!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hoh hoh. Of course, we're kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wasn't kidding...</thought> Now, Mr. Powers. We have to go make our final investigation. But I promise you, we'll find the true killer by tomorrow's trial!</line>
<line speaker="Will">R-right! Thanks! *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court see no reason to further prolong the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Mr. Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>