<xml>
<title>Turnabout Time Traveler</title>
<line speaker="Ellen">Good morning, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning, Ellen. I see you're still wearing your wedding gown.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">And I will continue to wear it until our marriage is saved! ......... Oh! S-Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">.............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think he came to see how she's holding up?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Sorin, my love! You came all the way to the courthouse just to see me? Oh, Sorin! I don't know what to say!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...... Blueprints.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The engine blueprints... I can't find them. Do you know where they are?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oh! They're in your room, third shelf from the bottom, on the right-hand side.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...... Ah. I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's leaving already...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't tell me he came just to ask about some stupid blueprints? Is he really that cold of a person, or is that just how he comes off, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">*sniffle* Wh-What about me, Sorin...?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...... Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ ...Come home soon. ......I'm... lost without you.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">............ S-S-S-Soriiiiiiiiiiiiin!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Later...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like showing your vulnerabilities is the fastest way to capturing a woman's heart. You should take notes on this, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please leave me out of this. <thought>Anyway, it looks like Sorin isn't big on words... ...but it's clear that he cares about Ellen. Knowing that, I actually feel kind of relieved.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Wright! I just absolutely CAN'T be found guilty, you hear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. I'm going to do everything I can to prove your innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">THANK you, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to start, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>.........Edgeworth. Knowing him, he's not going to yield an inch. So I've just got to fight with everything I've got and save Ellen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Ellen Wyatt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution has been ready for a while, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Seeing so many familiar faces gathered together like this... I feel as though I'm at a grand reunion. It makes me want to go out for dinner and a drink, and reminisce with all of you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! That sounds like a great idea! I was dying for a real burger the whole time I was away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We could make it a welcome back party for Maya. How about it, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I have no intention of cavorting with my enemies. Now then, Your Honor, let us start this trial at once.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho. Still not one for lighthearted banter, are you, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Jokes and good humor are beyond worthless in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Guess we'll just have to have the party without him, then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ However, were it after the conclusion of this trial... ...I might consider joining you for your little welcome back party. I certainly wouldn't mind an invite, at the very least.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...He's still as emotionally constipated as ever, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Edgeworth, if you could please go over the details of this case for us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim was Dumas Gloomsbury, a servant in the Sprocket household. He was in attendance at the wedding reception that occurred from 7 PM to 10 PM. Mr. Gloomsbury apparently felt some animosity toward Ellen Wyatt, and so... ...a bit after the reception ended at 10 PM, he assaulted Ms. Wyatt with the intent to kill her. The defendant fought back, and ended up killing Mr. Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... In other words... it was justified self-defense, correct? If that's the case, then the defendant might not be criminally responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's right... Worst-case scenario, I could go for self-defense to avoid the criminal charge. I wonder how Edgeworth plans to counter that, though...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The prosecution's first witness will make my view on the matter clear, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff, please bring in the first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please state your name and occupation, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ema Skye. Forensic investigator. A-And I'd just like to say, sir...! That being in the same courtroom as you is a great honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's right... You're a fan of Edgeworth's, aren't you, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We're good friends and all, Mr. Wright... ...but, just this once, I intend to faithfully and fully testify for the prosecution! And I do mean that wholeheartedly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh. I expect no less from you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, sir! I'm going to do my very best!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like you lost the popularity contest to Mr. Edgeworth, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Meh, I really could care less. Besides... ...she'll see who's the better lawyer once I win this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Maybe then you'll actually really care less.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, Detective Skye, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The murder weapon was a clock called the "Time Keeper."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was struck twice?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. There's no mistake about it. The first blow was to the back of the victim's head. It was hard enough to knock him unconscious. Yet, despite the fact that he had been immobilized by the first blow... ...the defendant delivered a second, fatal blow to the side of the victim's head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Which means... what, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I figured it would go right over your head. Let's put it this way: By striking the victim a second time... ...the defendant killed her last chance to escape from any criminal wrongdoing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">She did? But how, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant may have been fighting back because she was being attacked. However... ...she then went on to deliver a fatal blow to a man who was already fully unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick, is he saying what I think he is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't feel so well...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And thus, Mr. Wright, has justified self-defense been removed from the table. The prosecution intends to prove that the defendant killed the victim... ...with murderous intent. Allow me to, belatedly, submit the victim's autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......A... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARRRRNNGH! <thought>So THAT'S why he was acting all smug...! Well, more smug than usual...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-It's fine, right? It's not like we were going to plead self-defense anyway, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but... now the judge has a negative impression of Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He may not get to prosecute much anymore, but he definitely hasn't lost his touch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Mr. Wright. You may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The murder weapon was a clock called the "Time Keeper."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, completely. The shape of the injury on the victim's head matches up with that of the Time Keeper. And it's definitely heavy enough to kill someone with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But would the defendant have been able to pick up and swing something so heavy?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I tried it myself, and I was able to lift it up just fine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you're just freakishly strong...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Excuse me, Mr. Wright?! I'll have you know that people on the force know me as the dainty forensic investigator!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry... <thought>...But really, you're hardly a delicate flower.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Mr. Wright. This is a court of law. Save your antics for after the trial, if you know how.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, sir... It won't happen again, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmph! ...Moving on!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim was hit with it from behind, and he fell over, right into the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim must've tried to run once Ms. Wyatt started fighting back. That's probably when he got hit from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... Thus, the blow to the back of his head.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defendant must've looked awfully scary when she was brandishing that clock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know about that... <thought>Regardless of how scary Ellen looked, the victim was definitely hit from behind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...May I go on?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, of course. Please do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defendant was spotted then, standing in front of the body holding the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But Ms. Wyatt really believed she could travel through time with that clock!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You really should've come up with a more credible story, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Me, three... But it's all I have to go on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Anyway, under the circumstances... ...the only conclusion we can draw is that the defendant killed the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim was struck twice, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, about that...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Allow me to explain. Why did she strike him again, indeed? To finish off the victim, of course. This very act clearly shows that she had every intention of killing Mr. Gloomsbury!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But Ms. Wyatt would never do a thing like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then let's see some evidence that disproves my theory!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nnrrgh...! Are you going to just stand there and take that from him, Nick?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't refute his claim head-on, so I'll have to approach it from a different angle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... ...it looks like we won't be going anywhere until we can refute Edgeworth's claim.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is so exciting! We haven't taken on Mr. Edgeworth in ages!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Now, go get him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No need to rush me, Maya... <thought>All right. I'd better start by comparing Ema's testimony with the evidence we have... ...and look for any glaring inconsistencies!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Skye, I'm afraid I have to apologize in advance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">For what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For embarrassing you in front of your idol.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you take a look at this photo of the crime scene... ...you'll see that the victim is lying on his back. But if the victim had been hit from behind as you claim... ...then he should have fallen over into the lantern facedown.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not enough to simply take someone's side, Detective Skye. Even if it's Mr. Edgeworth's.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah...! Oooh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There does appear to be a flaw in Detective Skye's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ema:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ema is unusually fired up today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't forget, she's in front of her hero, Nick. If the Steel Samurai came to watch this trial, I'd want to do my absolute best, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Listen, Mr. Wright. It's entirely possible that the defendant moved the victim's body after he fell over. In that case, there wouldn't be any contradiction, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. That was an excellent counterargument, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You can count on me, sir! So, what do you have to say to that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it possible that the victim's body was moved after he fell into the lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense believes... it's possible that the victim's body was moved by the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What are you doing, Nick?! You're backing up Ema's claim?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Oops! I meant to answer in the negative!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In other words, you wish to claim the exact opposite of what you just said? A reversal that dramatic... ...deserves an equally dramatic punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no need to be such a drama queen about it, Your Honor... <thought>Well, I guess this leaves me with just one answer. I can't mess this up now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Detective, but there's no way the victim's body was moved after his death.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, really? And what makes you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One look at this here, and it should become obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ema:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... uh... This right here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What you're trying to communicate is not obvious at all, Mr. Wright. But this penalty should make my feelings on the matter pretty obvious -- even to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The only thing that's obvious right now is the pain in my attorney's badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Th-Those broken bits of the lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. If the body had been moved after the fact, these fragments would've fallen off of it. But, as you can see, they're lying perfectly undisturbed on top of the body. This means that the victim must've been lying face up from before the lantern even broke.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">.......You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But wait a minute. If that's true... ...then when was the victim killed? I mean, the lantern was still whole during the reception, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Which means we've just overturned a major assumption about this case. If the victim was already dead before the lantern was even broken... ...then the body must've been inside the lantern since before the reception started. In other words... ...the defense asserts that the victim was killed before the wedding reception!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In short... ...when Ms. Wyatt was seen standing in front of the body after the reception... ...it wasn't the moment just after the murder was committed. It was the moment she happened to discover the body -- just as Ms. Wyatt claims!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">AAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urngh... Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even you have to admit, Mr. Edgeworth, that this has opened up a new possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do explain, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if Ms. Wyatt didn't commit the crime in the reception hall... ...then that means someone, somewhere put the victim's body into the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose that makes sense. A dead body couldn't have put itself in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor. In other words... If the murder actually occurred before the reception, it opens up the possibility that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant didn't commit this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that was too ridiculous of a leap backwards for Mr. Edgeworth, Mr. Wright. I suggest you look before you leap, and think before you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I got ahead of myself on that one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was killed some other way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was worth a try...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You should know better than to just say the first shocking thing that comes to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've got this. I just have to stay cool and answer rationally.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the body was hidden inside the lantern... ...then, it's possible that the body was moved along with it from somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can run that mouth of yours all you want... ...but do you have any evidence to support what's coming out of it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I do. <thought>I think the answer lies in that piece of evidence -- and in something... ...that was left at the crime scene that will point us to where the victim was really killed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. In that case... What proves that the lantern and the body were moved from somewhere else?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I can't say that I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That piece of evidence won't help you make your point, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yet another pointless piece of evidence from a senseless attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fine, so this piece wasn't convincing enough. Then there must be something else that would be easier for the judge to understand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The photo of the victim again...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. I'd like the court to focus on this thing, right here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. That far-off look in his eyes suggests that his mind is equally as far-off in La-La Land.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will focus on the trial, if that's not too much to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that brought me back to reality fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Flower petals, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These petals are from a kind of flower that were not present in the reception hall. This means they must've gotten into the lantern when it was somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And just where do you propose this "somewhere else" to be, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I propose that this piece of evidence will tell us where the flower petals came from.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Are you sure about that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I am, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Because I'm afraid I can't see how.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even if you take a really good look?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if you... smelled the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Still nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh. That's odd. Aha ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is no laughing matter, defense! I hope this will teach you to take matters seriously!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suggest you refrain from embarrassing yourself any further with such stale jokes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll make sure to whip up a fresh batch for next time, then... A-All joking aside... <thought>Even though I was actually being serious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at the flowers in this picture of the hold. Notice how their petals are of the same shape as the petals in the crime scene photo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. I see. They do look to be from the same kind of flower.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I couldn't disagree with you more, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I gave a flower of this type to my lovely wife once when we were young. So I can assure you that this is very meaningful and compelling evidence indeed. The soundness of my judgment on this matter is backed by nothing less than pure love!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let it go, Mr. Edgeworth. It's clear you don't know much about flowers. It's not like you have anyone you'd actually give any to, after all. But maybe you should study up on them, just in case the opportunity presents itself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngoooh! This is from the man who only knows the names of three types of flowers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's hardly relevant to the case at hand! The defense asserts that it's highly probable that the victim was killed in the hold! If the body was then placed in the lantern and moved to the reception hall for some reason... ...it would completely destroy the prosecution's case!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then you mean, the body was...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. The victim's body was... ...inside the lantern during the entire beautiful wedding reception! While the defendant and her betrothed were celebrating their love!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Take another look at all of the evidence and you'll soon see what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>I wish he would just tell me already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Skye, I'm sure you've already figured out what I'm talking about, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Heh heh heh. Of course, sir! Mr. Wright is the only one here who hasn't. Why don't you leave this to me, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Let's see what you can do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Skye, please give your testimony to this court.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim could not have been killed before the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's clear Mr. Gloomsbury was killed after the reception. And that completely contradicts your claim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm......... I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Tell me you took at least a cursory glance at the autopsy report, Mr. Wright. It appears you've grown rusty since our last outing. Might I suggest you go back and brush up on the basics?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Sure. Though I must say, you're as cocky as ever, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wh-What are you trying to say, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just saying that I'll go back to basics, if that's what Mr. Edgeworth wants. I'll prove how badly he's underestimating me with a good old-fashioned cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............... </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's see you put your money where your mouth is, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim could not have been killed before the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Of course I do. And you're gonna feel silly when I show you what they are. Ready? Feast your eyes on this!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The autopsy report states that the estimated time of death was after the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Then you don't need me to explain it to you, right? How there's no way the victim could've been killed before the reception, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Skye... ...I think you've overlooked something big.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I have?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you take another look at the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...But I've already looked at all the evidence! And quite carefully, too, I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Skye. Do not be taken in by his verbal antics. He is simply bluffing, as always.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">R-Right, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And that estimated time of death is correct. There's no way it could be wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, not in this case. There was no snow or anything to keep the body from decomposing. And there's no fridge on that airship big enough to fit a body into.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you've already checked into that, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It all comes down to the estimated time of death, doesn't it? Couldn't the killer mess with the victim's time of death by keeping the body on ice?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, if they had the means to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The prosecution is treating the estimated time of death as an absolute. But is it really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I take it you don't think it is, huh, Nick? In that case, we're going to have to find a way to convince them otherwise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, there's gotta be a way somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I admit that the estimated time of death does contradict my theory.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Finally! And that means your theory that the victim was killed before the reception...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Is still entirely plausible!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? Wh-What makes you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The killer could've falsified the time of death by using a certain item in the reception hall. Please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is that contraption, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a fog machine, Your Honor, used to create a special, romantic atmosphere in the hall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this machine could have been used to falsify the time of death?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor, because this machine uses dry ice to perform its magic.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dry ice? Ah yes -- the super cold stuff commonly used to make theatrical fog, right? I see. So your claim is that this dry ice was used to keep the body cold?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......Oh...! In that case, I guess the victim COULD have been killed before the reception...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in this court! Well, Mr. Edgeworth? What do you have to say about this development?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......That the victim was killed in the hold before the wedding reception? .....The prosecution acknowledges the possibility of this claim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now we're getting somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The prosecution would also like to thank you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? For what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I didn't know how a certain piece of evidence fit into this case... But now, thanks to you, I do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To get into the hold, one needs a key card, like this one. And, here, we have a record of those who entered the hold with such key cards. The times aren't specified, but these are the last three entries on the day of the murder. And as you can see, the last person to enter the hold that day... was the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the one who moved the body out of the hold must have been...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. It was none other than the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, take a look at this entry record. There are a couple of other names on here besides Ellen's.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right! According to the entry record, Mr. Edgeworth, Pierce Nichody had also gone into the hold. Isn't it possible that he could've been the culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh... </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, it's probably safe to assume that after killing the victim in the hold... ...the defendant moved his body to the hall in order to dispose of it discreetly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by "discreetly"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The defendant volunteered to take care of the reception's cleanup personally. That means she would've had the chance to dispose of anything in any way she wanted. Including taking the lantern off the airship without raising any suspicion. Don't tell me you didn't know about Ms. Wyatt volunteering for cleanup duty, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">For my last task as a servant of the Sprocket household... ...I offered to take on the preparation and cleanup of the reception banquet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look at you, sweating buckets like a rookie... even after all these years. Nevertheless... Thank you for proving that the only person who could've killed the victim in the hold is... ...Ellen Wyatt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! <thought>Great job, Phoenix. Now we're back to square one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh. Perhaps you should ask Ms. Cykes for some help in reviewing Defense for Dummies.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Way to go, sir! You've got Mr. Wright in a cold sweat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I wonder if maybe the promise of seeing that miserable look on his face... ...is what brought me back to court today. It's certainly made all of my stress and woes as chief prosecutor just melt away.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess he had a lot of stress built up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll give him something to stress over before we're through today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, the prosecution asks that you render your verdict at this time. Before that man over there tries to throw the court into chaos with his meaningless bluffs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Hmm, I see. Mr. Wright... ...are there any last meaningful bluffs you'd like to present to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... <thought>Why does he have to assume it'll be a bluff?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Hurry up and throw a good one out there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I will! I will!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........... Well, all right, then. Let's see... I-I've got it! How do you know it was Ms. Wyatt who used her key card? After all, if it turns out that somebody else used her card... ...it would mean Ms. Wyatt didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Interesting. And are you able to prove this bluff to be true?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I assure you, I'm not bluffing, Your Honor. <thought>Well, now what...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait a minute, Nick. I can think of a certain somebody who might've used Ellen's key card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember? The one who was sneaking around the hold, in spite of not being a family member...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's right! Your Honor! The defense would like to call a certain witness to the stand! I need the testimony of this person, who may have entered the hold with Ms. Wyatt's card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you talking about, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, did I make a mistake...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would know if you had been paying any attention to our arguments up to this point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ahem. So... So that means...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Exactly. It means you get a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was afraid of that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd advise you to take this a little more seriously, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I will! Your Honor! The defense would like to call a certain witness to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's your witness?! A-Are you saying that THAT numbskull was on the airship? He never breathed a word about that to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not surprising, because Mr. Nichody told him to keep quiet about it. But Mr. Butz himself admitted it to me. He claimed to have found a way to sneak into the Flying Chapel's hold to see Ms. Wyatt. This photo he took and gave to me is proof.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-Then was it he who moved the lantern with the body inside to the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know as well as I that with him, anything is possible. And this is one possibility we should definitely look into.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....I-I can't believe this. What in the world is HE doing mixed up in this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Mr. Edgeworth. Remember what we've been saying since elementary school?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">....."When something smells, it's usually the Butz."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gaaaaaagh! That Larry! He'll pay for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you want to extract your payment now... ...he's right up there in the gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Seize the witness before he makes a run for it!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Noooooooooooooooooo! Why does this stuff always happen to MEEEEEEEEEE?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry, Larry... but you brought this on yourself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let us break for a fifteen minute recess. I ask that both sides prepare for the next witness's testimony during this time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. It's been a while since I've had this much fun and excitement! A face-off against Mr. Edgeworth! A harrowing tightrope walk for the defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew! I'm exhausted already.</line>
<line speaker="???">Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm here for moral support!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena! Are you all done practicing for Trucy's magic show?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... to be perfectly honest... I sorta ran away. But that's because she was putting my life in danger, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... I think I'll need to have a one-on-one with her... You're really athletic and fit, Athena, so Trucy probably thinks she can run you ragged.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That may be true... ...which is why not even Trucy can keep up with me when I run at full speed!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hah! Looks like you spoke too soon, Athena! Never underestimate the resourcefulness of a great magician!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Magical Girl Trucy Wright... is on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Nooooooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, Athena! It's time to practice human combustion magic! Go on, douse yourself in this gasoline! But don't worry! It's a magic trick, after all, so it's perfectly safe!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...... R... R... Run awaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay!!!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, you! You're not getting off that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ha ha ha! They get along so well, don't they? It reminds me of the good ol' days. You, me, and Pearly... Oh, and Detective Gumshoe! Can't forget him. We had all kinds of fun at the crime scenes back then, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Leaving me to do all the serious investigating as I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Court will soon be back in session, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So Larry's the next witness, right? I can't wait to see what happens!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sadly, I can already imagine it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">......Nick! Edgey! The two of you are gonna hang me out to dry, aren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not the both of us. Just Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">N-Nick... How could you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't really think he did it, of course, but I've gotta use whatever leads I can...</thought> Mr. Butz, there's a possibility you moved the lantern that had the dead body in it. So if you want to clear yourself of any suspicion, all you have to do is testify.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, your testimony, please, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick, you big, fat, stinkin' jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.....Well, go ahead, Mr. Wright. He's all yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why me?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're the one who called him to the stand, so he's your responsibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, old chum...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">C-Can't any of you show me a little respect?! Even just a shred?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may cross-examine the witness, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I would, if there were any testimony to cross-examine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick, you big, fat, stinkin' jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Don't think I don't know about your tricks! If I say something careless, you're gonna shove some evidence at me with a loud... ..."<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" and a super smug look on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, well... that IS my job...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">And if I get found guilty, how are you gonna take responsibility for what you've done?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why should I take responsibility for just doing my job?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You heartless jerk! Don't you have any compassion for me?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come off it, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't quit fooling around and start testifying, Ms. Wyatt will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">F-For real?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If no new information comes out of this cross-examination... ...then, yes, Mr. Butz, for real.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not that I would have a problem with that, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............ </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, just tell us the truth already. Did you or didn't you go into the hold and move a lantern up to the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I... I never moved any bull lantern, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Bull lantern"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What? Did I say something weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You told me that you didn't attend the wedding reception.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Can you believe they told me only family and relatives could attend?! They wouldn't even let me into the reception hall!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Uh, y-yeah. So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, that's odd... No one in this courtroom ever mentioned the sex of the lantern that was moved. So how could you know that it was a "bull" lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Y-You didn't have to actually go to the reception to know that! Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I can tell right now is that there's a strong scent of bull in the air in here.</thought> Please add that last statement to your testimony, Mr. Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!"</line>
<line speaker="Larry">How can you doubt your best bud?! We've known each other since elementary school!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick! Are you seriously doubting the innocence of your old childhood friend?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, technically, yes. But it isn't personal, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Ooooh... A true friend would believe in me no matter what. Can't you see my tears? Don't they mean anything to you? Nick... Niiiiiiiick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't really think you can cry your way out of this, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Okay, FINE! In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come off it, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't quit fooling around and start testifying, Ms. Wyatt will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">F-For real?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If no new information comes out of this cross-examination... ...then, yes, Mr. Butz, for real.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not that I would have a problem with that, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............ </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, just tell us the truth already. Did you or didn't you go into the hold and move a lantern up to the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I... I never moved any bull lantern, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Bull lantern"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What? Did I say something weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You told me that you didn't attend the wedding reception.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Can you believe they told me only family and relatives could attend?! They wouldn't even let me into the reception hall!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Uh, y-yeah. So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, that's odd... No one in this courtroom ever mentioned the sex of the lantern that was moved. So how could you know that it was a "bull" lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Y-You didn't have to actually go to the reception to know that! Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I can tell right now is that there's a strong scent of bull in the air in here.</thought> Please add that last statement to your testimony, Mr. Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!"</line>
<line speaker="Larry">W-W-Well, get this, pal! Our friendship's over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Sh-Shut up! I'm not talking to you anymore! ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is getting us nowhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come off it, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you don't quit fooling around and start testifying, Ms. Wyatt will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">F-For real?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... If no new information comes out of this cross-examination... ...then, yes, Mr. Butz, for real.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not that I would have a problem with that, myself.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............ </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, just tell us the truth already. Did you or didn't you go into the hold and move a lantern up to the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I... I never moved any bull lantern, I tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Bull lantern"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What? Did I say something weird?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You told me that you didn't attend the wedding reception.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Can you believe they told me only family and relatives could attend?! They wouldn't even let me into the reception hall!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Uh, y-yeah. So what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, that's odd... No one in this courtroom ever mentioned the sex of the lantern that was moved. So how could you know that it was a "bull" lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Y-You didn't have to actually go to the reception to know that! Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I can tell right now is that there's a strong scent of bull in the air in here.</thought> Please add that last statement to your testimony, Mr. Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!"</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Anyone could tell there were two Pegabulls by looking at the Flying Chapel's pamphlet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I-I'm telling ya! I don't know nothin'! Why do you have to doubt me so much?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? Because you're you, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgey...! You think Nick's being awful to me, don't you? So you tell him...! Tell Nick what a big meanie he is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would... if I thought he was being one.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">N-Not you, too! Why doesn't anybody ever take my side?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wish I didn't have to doubt him... But something about what he just said doesn't add up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess about all I can do... ...is try to get some kind of statement out of him somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good luck.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You finally got a decent statement out of him, huh, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, finally. <thought>It sure took a lot of work, though... I hope all of this leads somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want you to take a look at this, Mr. Butz. Because unfortunately for you, the pamphlet clearly shows... ...a Pegacow and a Pegabull in their example diagram of the reception hall.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But on that day, instead of putting a Pegacow and Pegabull out for the bride and groom... ...there were two male Pegabulls on display.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet, somehow, you knew there were two Pegabulls in the reception hall that day. There's only one way you'd know something like that, Larry... It was YOU who moved the Pegabull to the reception hall, wasn't it?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No... Larry, y-you didn't...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Butz, did you move the lantern containing the victim's body to the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Th-That's what it looks like!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...............!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Larry:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe you and Mr. Gloomsbury were fighting over Ms. Wyatt, and you ended up killing him?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">M-Mayaaaaa! Not you, tooooo! Look, I did sneak into the reception, but that's as far as it went. You know me! I wouldn't hurt a fly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You "snuck into the reception"...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, sure. But some of the Sprocket men caught and locked me up in one of the cabins. It was pretty awful, actually! But that's when I made that drawing of the pterodactyl I showed you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ix-nay on the erodactyl-ptay, Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright, not even you would take this farce that far... would you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ <thought>We ARE talking about Larry... What do I do? Do I accuse Larry of being the true culprit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I have no choice but to accuse him...! Wait a minute... But Larry didn't have any reason to kill Gloomsbury!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, you're right, Mr. Edgeworth. Mr. Butz didn't have a reason to kill Mr. Gloomsbury. He might've had an imaginary reason to kill Sorin Sprocket, sure, but not Mr. Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">After all, he did steal Mr. Sprocket's bride and try to elope with her...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Just 'cause I tried to steal somebody's bride doesn't make me a murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I believe you, Larry. And I don't think you killed anybody, either. You would never do anything like that.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">N-Nick, ol' buddy, ol' pal! I knew you'd come through for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Funny, that, considering your sworn testimony just now that we were through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Butz, it's time you told this court the whole truth. Understood?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">It's just like Nick said, I'm the one who moved the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you switched the lanterns before the reception, did you? Then that means the victim really WAS killed before the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear... that Mr. Butz completely fell for the defendant's scheme.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Scheme? What scheme?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This note from the defendant: "Exchange with the one in the hold. --Ellen"... Mr. Butz moved the lantern with the body in it up to the reception hall because of this note. And thus, he has become a suspect in Mr. Gloomsbury's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">*gulp*... That second lantern did feel pretty heavy... ...but I never would've thought there was a dead body in it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Arnngh... What was a note like that doing on a lantern in the first place...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Ellen:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">No way, Edgey! I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Of course. My stance on the matter remains unchanged. If you think I'm wrong, then prove it with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gladly!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Wright, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">It's just like Nick said, I'm the one who moved the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Because I knew you guys were gonna be suspicious of me, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're suspicious of you now because you tried to hide it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My thoughts exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hmph! Well, now I've told you! Happy? So how about letting me go?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, not yet. We need you to stick around to sort a few things out.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Grrrrr! FINE!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I was poking around the reception hall before the main event and saw a lantern was broken.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you replace a female lantern with a male one?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Because I was too busy trying not to get caught. I didn't have time to check for little details like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you didn't want to get caught, you could've just left well enough alone, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whatever! Anyway, when I took a look at the broken lantern, I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">There was a note on it that said, "Exchange with the one in the hold. --Ellen."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, I guess not, but... ...how could I let my dear, sweet Elly do all that hard physical labor on her own?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's precisely that thought process that constantly gets you in trouble, Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Besides, it was my big chance to show her how much I cared about her.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">So I decided to do Elly a favor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nope. I didn't get caught. Not that time, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Not that time"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah. When I'd tried to sneak into the reception hall the first time... ...I didn't have as much luck. Those Sprocket guys spotted me and nabbed me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All of my words are failing me right now...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Pretty exciting, don't ya think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Larry... You need help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">And then they locked me up in one of the cabins. ......Nick, what are you asking about stuff like this for, anyway? Shouldn't you be trying to prove Elly's innocence?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well... Is that statement of his important to the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Butz trying to crash the reception, and subsequently getting locked up in a cabin... I believe these might be important facts in this case, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Butz, please add that statement to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I tried to sneak into the reception hall, but I got caught and locked up in a cabin."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Given the lack of any important info... I guess I can let this line of questioning go for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nope. I didn't get caught. Not that time, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Not that time"?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah. When I'd tried to sneak into the reception hall the first time... ...I didn't have as much luck. Those Sprocket guys spotted me and nabbed me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All of my words are failing me right now...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Pretty exciting, don't ya think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Larry... You need help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">And then they locked me up in one of the cabins. ......Nick, what are you asking about stuff like this for, anyway? Shouldn't you be trying to prove Elly's innocence?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I tried to sneak into the reception hall, but I got caught and locked up in a cabin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I broke out. Then I started looking for Elly and wandered into the reception hall again. That's when I saw the broken lantern and replaced it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Even after they caught you and locked you up, you still went looking for Ms. Wyatt? ...But, hold on a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What is it, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, doesn't something seem weird to you? Larry is saying he replaced the lantern after he broke out of the cabin.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right-- Oh, wait... Huh? You're right. It doesn't make much sense, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, have you found an inconsistency in the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I believe so, Your Honor. Mr. Butz moved the lantern after he broke out of the cabin, but that contradicts with this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Larry">It doesn't contradict at all, does it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urngh...! Oh, don't mind me, Your Honor. It looks like I just made a tiny mistake. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Knowing Larry... ...he definitely did something stupid somewhere along the way.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. Larry sure is one special guy... Not everyone has the privilege of being THIS distrusted by their best friends...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Assuming he can't be trusted from the get-go usually makes things easier, I've learned.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I see! You totally trust him to be totally untrustworthy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess that just about sums it up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it's the broken lantern, Your Honor. Mr. Butz, what you're saying doesn't make any sense at all.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">WHAT?! Why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You swapped the lanterns before the reception began, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah. That's what I said, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you also just said that you swapped the lanterns... ...after you got locked up in a cabin for trying to sneak into the reception. In other words, you're saying you swapped the lanterns both before the reception... ...and after the reception took place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That certainly doesn't make any sense, does it? Mr. Butz, did you swap the lanterns before or after the reception?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which was it: before or after?! There's a world of difference between the two!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Butz?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">.....I guess I can't expect guys like you to understand. In a nutshell, it was both before... and after the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I tried to sneak into the first reception and got locked up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "first" reception? <thought>Uh-oh. I don't like where this is going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Then, through the power of Elly's pendant... ...time got rewound, and we went back to the time before the reception. It was after that when I replaced the lantern. So it was both before the reception and after the reception. Get it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Larry">We went back in time to before the reception. So, of course, the reception would take place one more time after that, right? That's why what I said makes perfect sense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......Mr. Wright, what in the world is the witness talking about? Has he developed some sort of intellectual ailment I'm not aware of since I saw him last?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">None of the Sprockets seem to remember the time skip, but I do. And Elly remembers it, too! I think the power of our love for each other made that miracle happen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I'm sorry, but... ...could you please translate this man's gibberish so the rest of us can understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So now I have to be the one to explain about the whole time travel thing?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Go on, Nick. I know you can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like you don't have much choice, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>To heck with it! I can't lose any more of my dignity today anyway!</thought> ............ The defendant, Ms. Ellen Wyatt, has told the defense the following strange story. She said that after the reception ended, she was attacked by Mr. Gloomsbury. She claims that, as she was being assaulted, she made a wish upon her pendant. "Please, take me back... back to that blissful moment...!" In doing so... ...time apparently rewound itself to just before the reception began!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......It what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know it's hard to believe, but think about it this way. Through the power of the pendant, both Ellen Wyatt and Larry Butz... ...experienced time travel!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh.... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth of the matter is, the future president of Sprocket Aviation, Sorin Sprocket... ...has been researching time machines. So, what if a time machine has already been successfully created? And what if that's one of Sprocket Aviation's top secret inventions?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-A time machine?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah! I even saw something while we were time traveling! I saw a pterodactyl flying through the sky! Maybe the airship was set to travel through time for their honeymoon trip?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAT?! A-A pterodactyl?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. As I thought. In any case, I now have the evidence to prove... ...that you're no more intelligent than Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Larry:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You want evidence? I've got your evidence right here! This is a photo I secretly took of the first reception!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! L-Larry! I can't believe you--! ......Well, anyway, good job! If we compare the photos of the first and second receptions and can find a difference... ...then we'll be able to prove that the reception was held twice!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But do you really think such a difference exists?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. I just need some time to find it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please show the court what's different, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is proof positive that the wedding reception was held twice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right here, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">........... ......Right where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Right... not here, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears you've missed the mark, defense. I hope you take better aim next time before you fire off that mouth of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But my aim is usually impeccable! I'd better take another good look at the two photos before I answer again, though!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please direct your attention to Ms. Wyatt's bouquet of flowers! In the photo one of her in-laws took, the defendant is holding a yellow bouquet. But in the photo Mr. Butz took, she is holding a red bouquet!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......That's... impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that the defendant really did experience two wedding receptions! And she did that... when she traveled back through time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! You did it! You proved Ellen's time travel story to be true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I can hardly believe it myself... <thought>It's just as Ellen said -- the reception was held twice. This turns every assumption we've based this trial on upside-down!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know it's hard, but can't you suspend your disbelief for one nanosecond, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet sci-fi movies push all your buttons the wrong way, don't they, Mr. Edgeworth...? I can totally picture you yelling, "That'd never happen!" every five seconds at the screen. Maybe you should stay away from movie dates altogether...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's neither here nor there! This is real life we're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the proof is clearly shown in the two photographs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Mr. Edgeworth, no matter how inexplica--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......Let's start with this, then, shall we? There is one thing your time travel theory fails to explain. And that is the memories of the other guests there. The defendant and Larry remember the reception occurring twice... ...but no member of the Sprocket family has even mentioned such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because the time machine is classified technolog--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-Birdbrain?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I was saying, if the entire family had been sworn to secrecy... ...then why hadn't they sworn the woman who was marrying into the family to secrecy, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's a good point...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Honestly. All it takes is a little common sense, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Even still... ...how do we know that the trip through time did not really occur? There is proof in the photos that it did. And besides, if time travel doesn't exist, well... ...I'd be a little disappointed, frankly. I was hoping to go back to the days of my youth--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mustn't allow yourself to be taken in by Mr. Wright's whimsical tales, Your Honor. I've read about it in various literature, you see... And they all say that time travel is just not logically feasible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Maybe our argument was just a little too nonsensical, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Well, in that case... ...why don't we put "common sense" to the test?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The wedding reception was held twice. The photos are proof of that. But it wasn't because of time travel. It's simply because the reception had actually been held twice. Isn't that the most reasonable way to interpret the situation?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Would you care to elaborate, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If time travel doesn't exist, then there's only one way to make sense of what happened!</thought> Somebody must've orchestrated this strange phenomenon. And that somebody is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Gloomsbury!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how exactly did a dead man orchestrate such an event? And more importantly, why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, it was... ...to make it look like Mr. Sprocket had been successful in his research...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you asking me for?! Besides, none of the other people interviewed... ...thought that he had succeeded in accomplishing time travel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, could we rewind time... by just a teeny bit?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Sorry, but no.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better rethink this quick, before I lose any more time, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Such a mysterious phenomenon could only have been caused by... ...the gods themselves!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose the gods would be able to rewind time... ...or make the wedding reception happen twice, wouldn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Indeed they would, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, Mr. Wright... ...please bring these gods here to testify before this court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Maya...? Do you think you could...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Not a chance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">On behalf of the gods who can't be here today, please, have some divine punishment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew I was reaching with that one... I guess I'd better come up with something more grounded next time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if all of the guests at the reception conspired together... ...to hold the reception twice and keep quiet about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? ......And for what purpose would they conspire to do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Well, uh... ..................</line>
<line speaker="???">Ha ha ha! A brilliant deduction, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I can tell that you are not a renowned lawyer for nothing. I must say, I underestimated you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How so, Mr. Nichody?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You have managed to name each event, precisely as they happened. You have revealed it all to the light of day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Then, that means...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It was us. We orchestrated the whole thing. Yes, the reception was held twice. But not because of time travel, no -- we simply held it a second time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Why?! Why would you do such a thing?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">To make it as though the murder Miss Ellen committed... never happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin figured that if Miss Ellen, who'd killed Gloomsbury after the first reception... ...experienced the reception one more time, she would think it was all a dream. It was he who ordered us to make it happen. However, only a few, myself included, knew of Miss Ellen's crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you saying most of the guests attended two receptions without knowing why?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Indeed. They needed no reason... Master Sorin told them to do it, and do it they did. That is the Sprocket way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then who hid the body in the lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">We did. But we did not anticipate the petals finding their way in, nor the actions of Mr. Butz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's how you intended to cover the whole situation up?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">There is just one thing everyone here has wrong. The real scene of the murder was not the hold. It was the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Th-Then Ms. Wyatt's recollection of the events must be correct!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I admit we tried to cover this incident up. But the fact that Miss Ellen killed Gloomsbury is undeniable.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is quite a turn of events!</line>
<line speaker="???">......... ......Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And so it appears we have arrived at the truth at last.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please do feel free to travel back in time, Mr. Wright... ...and attempt to do this trial over again. Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not get hasty, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I bet you can't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet I can't, eeeeeiiiither!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, we will have to hold a separate trial for the cover-up conspiracy later. But as far as this case goes... ...I believe we are ready for your ruling.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nrgh... You never know when to quit, do you?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now. Calm down, both of you. In any case, there isn't enough trustworthy information yet for me to render a verdict. I suggest we continue the trial after both sides have investigated the matter further.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.....Nnnnrrrrgh. Very well, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Phew! That was close...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Nichody... As for you and your cohorts' attempt to cover up this crime... ...your case will be brought to a separate trial following the resolution of this current one.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Understood, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, then... This concludes today's trial. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A "feeling," defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor... Or, rather, a "hope" that it indicates a contradiction...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is there or isn't there a contradiction here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there is... but there really isn't one, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you asking me, Mr. Wright? Because what it really seems like to me is you're asking for a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for that definitive answer, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* With a lawyer like you, Mr. Wright, even I feel bad for the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, you don't have to feel bad for her for long! I'll get it right next time, you'll see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Will it start saying something anytime soon, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ ............ ...It's not speaking up at all, is it? Maybe it's being shy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Your evidence has said nothing at all to this court. But your choice of tactics speaks volumes about you, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even I knew that wasn't a very smart move, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrrngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Wright. Would you care to tell this court what percent sure you are of your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why, of course! I'm a hundre--! Well, er... ninety... Wait, maybe eighty-ish...? W-Would you accept... fifty percent?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I won't have such half-hearted bluffing in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Might I recommend that the defense be penalized with one-hundred-percent severity?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I intend to, Mr. Edgeworth! You can be sure of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>Guess I can't say I deserved zero percent of that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you think we should do now, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That one statement sounds awfully fishy to me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So now it's just a matter of deciding which piece of evidence to present, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I'll take another look at the evidence and compare it to that statement, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you can press the witness some more... ...and try and get new information out of them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. <thought>Guess I'd better get down to pressing the witness, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Ellen Wyatt...</line>
</xml>