<xml>
<title>Turnabout Serenade</title>
<line speaker="Klavier">We love you! Rock on, everyone! This party's not over yet! Get out your handkerchiefs for our special guest! That's right, baby! The night's just getting started!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is so cool! Us, at a Gavinners concert! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Did you say something? My ears are still ringing... The Gavinners: putting the "sick" back in "music".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I thought Mr. Gavin was really nice! Sending us those tickets at 20% off! They're hard to get ahold of, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When you invite people to a concert it's usually free.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's head to his dressing room, Apollo! You know, like we're a couple of VIPs. I've always dreamed of being a VIP at a Gavinners show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Trucy... You didn't know who Prosecutor Gavin was before that case. What kind of fan doesn't know the lead vocalist's name?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! This guy, well, he was more like a prince really. He let us in...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Klavier... What a lovely name! He's so dreamy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, but I'm a girl! I'm supposed to swoon over gods of rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">God-awful, maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I bought all their stuff on the way home from the trial! I got twelve Gavinners albums, and fifteen concert videos!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That was quite a bit of impulse shopping.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I got an advance on my next 15-years-worth of allowance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...For Mr. Wright that sounds like a real act of generosity.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Who would have imagined me here... ...at a Gavinners concert, watching Prosecutor Gavin "rock". To be honest... ...he was kind of cool. And I'm kind of envious. Not that I'd ever admit that to Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a number inscribed on the back of the badge. There are many numbers like it, but this one is mine. Proof that I'm an attorney. To tell the truth, I get a happy feeling inside just looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, you made it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin! Thanks so much for the tickets!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And the invoice you sent along with them.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You were incredible up on stage, Mr. Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nothing like music to brighten the mood after a trial, ja? ...And we're almost ready for our next act. I'm looking forward to it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir's singing, right!? The "Siren of the Ballad"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh yeah... That flyer said she flew all the way over for this show.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. I happened to catch her show while overseas. Her voice... is divine. I knew I had to invite her to perform with us.</line>
<line speaker="???">Lamiroir says... "You praise me too highly."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! Who's this guy? He's huge!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, allow me to introduce Mr. Romein LeTouse. ...Lamiroir's manager. And her interpreter, incidentally.</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">It is a great honor for us to be here. And a great honor for Lamiroir to be heard in this country.</line>
<line speaker="???">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That voice... I wish I could understand it... It's beautiful.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooooh! It's Lamiroir! I'm actually meeting Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Lamiroir... Mysterious songstress... Her quiet, deep song glides through the air... Lilting above a sparse, but elegant piano accompaniment. Now this is music. She's a real artist.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">Lamiroir says... "We have long looked forward to this joint performance."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, Lamiroir... Your voice... ...It is art.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">"Yet without his piano to guide me... ...it is but a voice."</line>
<line speaker="???">....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've seen this kid somewhere before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He plays piano at all of Lamiroir's concerts! He's cute! And he's a really good pianist.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good pianists are a dying breed, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">Allow me to introduce Machi Tobaye. ...He is blind. This is why he never strays far from Lamiroir. They are always together.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They're like characters from some fairy tale..</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lamiroir's so, um, what's that word... Exotic! ...And mysterious!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She does seem quite pretty. At least, her eyes do.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hers is a kind of "sight-seeing musique"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She travels the globe, putting the sights she sees into song. Even though her appearance and voice are exotic... ...her songs remind us of something close, and warm.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sights into song... That's so poetic!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She was gracious enough to put music to my lyrics tonight. "The Guitar's Serenade". ...I hope you enjoy it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't wait!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And now it is time. For the next part, we're giving the Gavinners's hard rock a little rest. Lamiroir, the stage is yours.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The band members will not play during Lamiroir's ballad. Only Machi's tender tones, and Lamiroir's dulcet voice...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...And my guitar, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo hoo! Nights like this make it all worthwhile, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I should have learned to play the guitar. There's not much romance in Chords of Steel.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Shall we hit the stage, then?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good luck, Mr. Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Take care your hearts aren't stolen away, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's get back to the concert hall, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, wasn't Lamiroir amazing? I *sniffle* I even cried a little!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was surprised Prosecutor Gavin actually burned his guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! That even surprised me, and I'm a magician! What a production!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What a destruction. <thought>I don't think Prosecutor Gavin was expecting it either, oddly. He looked as surprised as I was.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is that what they call "risking life and limb for art"? I think he's my new hero!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure I'd call that "art".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, what are we doing here? Let's get going to Mr. Gavin's dressing room! There's twenty minutes till the last part of the show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How many breaks does this band need?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What the heck was that!? I was never consulted about it!</line>
<line speaker="Staff">S-Sorry, Mr. Gavin, sir! I've asked the man in charge...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I play new rock, not Great Balls of Fire! Speaking of fire, I have a good mind to fire whoever's responsible!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...He seems upset.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apollo Justice! Were you the one who tried to torch me!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So much for risking your life for art...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"The Guitar's Serenade" is ruined! Ruined!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's try to talk to him at least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm not sure that's the best move right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Those are some pretty heavy-duty gloves. Maybe they have to carry around hot pots or something?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They are a little thick. I couldn't even stuff a pigeon in those.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... That's exactly what I was thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why is that plastic bowl of stew sitting there?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they use it for interrogating bad guys... "'Fess up to what you did, and we'll let you eat that stew!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's just mean.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It gets worse! See, if the bad guy confesses, they say: "OK, eat it... If you can! See, it's made of plastic!" It's like, you don't know which ones are the real bad guys!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you need to take a deep breath, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This place is decorated like a high-school dance. Though I think our decorations were paper, not... chains.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Gavinners are into chains. It's part of their image.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, no kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ever since they used chains on the cover art for "Gunna Lock U Up".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're really into the whole police thing, aren't they.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It'd be cooler if they turned that red light on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...They don't have to turn on the red light.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! A "Cruiser Guitar"! They sold those to commemorate five years of the band.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Rocking it hard... under the speed limit.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's a "Cruiser Bass", and a "Cruiser Drum Set", and a "Cruiser Keyboard"... ...Even a "Cruiser Whistle".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm not so sure about that last one.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's for blowing the whistle on criminals!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I don't think that requires an actual whistle, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone drew the Gavinners's mark in lipstick here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Lipstick... I'd like to wear lipstick someday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? You don't use lipstick yet, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy won't let me. "Not until I learn to play piano," he says.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You'll be waiting a long time then, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A police uniform hangs on the stand here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I want to try it on! "Nothing to see here, move along."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's OK, you don't have to go that far to be "special". I mean, you're not exactly the type who's "just another face in the crowd".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? You think so? Hmm... I guess you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Now I feel like a meanie for making that insinuation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! It's a postcard of Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are these letters at the bottom? I've never seen these before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must be her native tongue, Borginese!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Borginese, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a stack of Lamiroir's postcards. They have an air of mystery to them that matches her voice.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That guitar! That's the legendary AA-400! The "Red Badger".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought rock was supposed to be rebellious, not... civic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Every aspiring guitarist wants one of these! They even paint their own guitars to look like it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, the fickleness of youth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You should dye your hair "Badger Red", too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I like my hair the way it is, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Argh, the stubbornness of age!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That speaker looks familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, like the one for the P.A. system back in school.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, we have one of those in my classroom, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right, she's still in junior high. ...I feel old.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's a police recruitment poster doing here? "Rock on ...with the police."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they're trying to trick kids into thinking the police are some kind of band.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that's just silly. Who'd name a band the "police"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Where do you think you're going!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, I was just...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's talk to Mr. Gavin while we have the chance!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean, the guitar... That wasn't part of the act?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Part of the act!? Who'd burn up a guitar on purpose!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, it worked really well with the lyrics just then... Burning on in my heart. Fire. Burn my love away. All away.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......&#160;! Wait, you think the audience thought it was...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like he got lucky.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They probably thought it was part of the act. At least, I did.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He got lucky, and he didn't realize it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A-Anyway, that guitar was the Ferrari of guitars! All the speed, all the sound ...and all the price. If I burned one of those at every show I'd go broke!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Unusually frugal for a rock band.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Try saying that to Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung! Today's been one disaster after another... My hog won't run, my guitar case's broken...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy told me there'd be days like these.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">W-Wasn't Lamiroir's song incredible!? You worked on it too, right, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, yes, thanks. It was a collaboration. I wrote the lyrics, and she wrote the melody.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know... I was surprised she could sing in English...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm sure she practiced a long time for this day. Ah, here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A lyrics sheet. It's yours. Signed by myself and Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yippee! Thanks so much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>All I ever get to sign are client defense agreements.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">For that song, I wrote the lyrics and she wrote the melody. It was a collaboration.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's so cool... I'd love to do a collaboration myself some day, or a song...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can't do a collaboration alone, you know, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then practice singing those lyrics. If you get good, I'll invite you into the band.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeek! R-Really!? I'll sing 'em every day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about your magic act?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Maybe I can be a singing and dancing magician!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then you'd end up only being average in both, no?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not at all. Why, I'm a rock star and a star prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! <thought>That's right, he is. I'd totally forgotten.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! See, you can excel in more than one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... I'm having trouble enough with just one thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Understand that I am not Prosecutor Gavin now. I am lead vocal of the Gavinners. That badge sings a different song... on a different stage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... <thought>I wish I had an alter-ego to hide behind sometimes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are those postcards there, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Eh? Lamiroir's, you mean? It's part of her PR campaign. I received a stack. You can have one if you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ah, that's good to hear. Trucy already swiped one, is why.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh! B-But that... But I... ... What's the big idea!? Making me look like a criminal... It was... a collaboration! I've always wanted to do a collaboration!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Usually, a collaboration is for creating, not stealing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Let the kid dream.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I wrote those lyrics, you know. Though it was Lamiroir who gave them life.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow... That's beautiful!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr. Maybe I should try to write some lyrics someday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! There's more?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes! Lamiroir's part is done. Now it's time for us to drop our groove again, ja? Hope you're ready to catch it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Woo hoo! Ready, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... I think I'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I liked the bit with Lamiroir. But the rest could use a volume knob. Turned way down.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah, Apollo, you're getting old!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>Does 22 quality as "old" to a 15-year-old...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I'm going!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let the old folks rest backstage, ja? ...Time to rock.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, you're older than I am!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thick leather gloves and sunglasses... Maybe I'll try these on... ...On second thought, no. They might be evidence for one of Prosecutor Gavin's cases.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A delicious bowl of stew! ...Made of plastic. Huh, the bottom of the bowl has a "G" on it. They sell these at concerts? Whatever happened to T-shirts?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Chains dangle from the ceiling. They aren't "glimmerous", but I bet Detective Skye'd have something to say about them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That guitar looks like it was made out of a cop car door. ...... That's right. Trucy's not here to set me straight. Now I feel kinda lonely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's graffiti on the mirror... in lipstick. Wait, but the Gavinners are all guys. ...Maybe Prosecutor Gavin wears lipstick?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A police uniform. Next to it is a policeman's hat, and a pair of handcuffs. One of the band members must like the police. Must be Mr. Gavin's "bad influence". ...... I thought rock 'n' roll was all about being rebellious.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A postcard of Lamiroir... I can't read a single word of the sentence at the bottom. Hmm. Trucy might want one of these. I'll show it to her next time we're here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's an odd guitar. The design is that character I saw in the hallway, but with sunglasses. What a strange mascot. He looks like he's crying. Since when was rock about crying? ...They should name this guy "Emo".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An old-fashioned speaker hangs from the ceiling. That must be to monitor what's happening out on stage. I think we had the same kind for my school's P.A. system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That police officer looks ready to rock. Some kids must see this and actually want to be cops. Somehow I don't think a rocking defense attorney would work too well.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, it's you! That Wright kid.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Detective Skye! <thought>I'll let that "Wright kid" business pass.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Call me Ema. There's no need for titles once you've shared a bottle of fingerprinting powder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a new one. So, um, Ema, what are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Isn't it obvious? I'm snacking. You think I want to be here!? Me, in charge of security in this pit!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Security...? Did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's no knowing with that glimmerous fop. Apparently, he's all upset because something was stolen. He wanted security back here during the concert. Where does he get off acting like he's some big rock star?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...He is a big rock star.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! You listening to me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... Where's this door here lead to?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This one? That's Lamiroir's dressing room. Don't even think of going in there unless you want a piece of Snackoos in your face!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is she ever in a good mood, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that odd looking doll doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH... oh, MUNCH, that's the Blue MUNCH Badger.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you try either talking or munching, but not both?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She hit me with a snack.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Serves me MUNCH right MUNCH for going MUNCH out MUNCH of MUNCH my MUNCH way MUNCH</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Sorry, I don't speak Snackoos.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? Some kind of headset earpiece?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would someone leave this in the hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Lamiroir's bodyguard dropped it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema! Will you stop eating those snacks for one second and listen!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hah! If you think you're going to pull me away from my snacks just to hear you mumbling... ...on and on about whatever, you're going to be sorely disappointed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...At least I got her to stop munching.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a pretty sturdy-looking box there. Maybe it's an instrument case. There's a guitar next to it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't even think about taking that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think I could even carry it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She Snackoo'd me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Prosecutor Gavin's... er, the Gavinners's dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Put so much as a hand on the door and I'll Snackoo you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hold on! But I just came out of there!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't play smart with me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come to think of it, I am a little thirsty.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll have some tea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... I think I'll get a water.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll have tea!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you want tea so bad go buy it yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She Snackoo'd me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll take a tea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A Gavinners "Guilty As Charged" tour poster.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They're plastered all over the place. It's annoying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, this is the concert venue. It makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why? Everyone here is already here! Why advertise to them?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">People like to see the poster at the concert... It's part of the experience.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Do you have to find fault with everything I say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She Snackoo'd me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've never seen someone eat snacks with such vehemence. Better give her a wide berth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She Snackoo'd me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That must be a bottomless bag of snacks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is Lamiroir's dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">If you even think about going in there, I'll--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was that... a gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something's going on!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You, out of my way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Lamiroir! Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's not locked... I'm going in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that awful noise... Oh, it's the concert.</thought> Aaack! That's-- <thought>It's Lamiroir's manager! Mister what's-his-name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">LeTouse! Oh no... Hey, you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Watch this room for me. I have to call for backup!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right, understood. You want me to make sure no one comes in, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And don't touch anything! I'll be right back!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...What's going on? I just talked to him, and now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">......Nnnh......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>He... He's alive!</thought> Mr. LeTouse! Can you hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Sh...Shot. ...I was...shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who? Who shot you!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...I don't know... Ask...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ask? Ask what?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">Ask... wi...witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Witness... There was a witness!? Who!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Cold... so cold... Witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're cold? D-Don't worry, you're going to be fine! Help is on the way!</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">...Can't s...see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hang in there, Mr. LeTouse! Tell me, who was the witness?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>..."Siren"? How can a siren witness anything...?</thought> Mr. LeTouse! Yipes! Ema!? <thought>What was that!?</thought> Wh-Who's there!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema! Did you see anyone just now!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Huh? No...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I could have sworn I heard a door close...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The concert's been cancelled. Backup's on its way. Is Mr. LeTouse... ...He's dead, isn't he? That's terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>I lost him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Romein LeTouse... shot. And I heard his last words... "The witness is the siren"... Whatever that means.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">The venue's locked down. We took names and addresses before letting the crowd go.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good work, Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="???">I'll let you know if I find out anything about the victim. Later.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's investigation time, then, ja, Fräulein Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I don't need some rock 'n' rolling prosecutor to tell me that.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">One request I must make... Tell no one, on staff or otherwise, anything of this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, a gag order!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No word gets out, other than that Mr. LeTouse is dead. No word of the cause of death, or of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell no one... Not even Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not even her. We must keep everything under wraps. Oh, one other thing. I'll need your signature on this, Herr Forehead. Yours too, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On that? Hmm... An "Investigation Request"...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why just us?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You two are civilians. It's standard procedure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That should be OK to sign, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Right, well, get started with the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm on it already!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, and one tip for you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Try not to get in the Fräulein detective's way. ...She's in a foul mood today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Gee, I wonder why...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We were all questioned as witnesses... ...And now none of us can go home. We'll investigate alright. ...Our way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Somehow I don't see us getting back to that crime scene any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I still can't believe I was there when it happened. Not an experience I care to repeat any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is no time for navel-gazing! Let's crack this case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I worry about Trucy. She seems to have a very loose idea of what it means to be an "attorney". Of course, that's not surprising considering who her father is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... Let's get cracking!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm the only one who was there... The only one who heard Mr. LeTouse's last words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>First order of business is to find out what he meant by "siren"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the Blue Badger, the police mascot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does the Blue Badger have something to do with the band?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, yeah! The Blue Badger is the Gavinners's mascot, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh. Go figure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I hear those things fly off the shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll have to take a closer look at one some day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's that? It looks like some kind of future-phone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not a phone, a transceiver. It's called a "headset".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's a headset doing on the floor? Wait! Do you think Mr. LeTouse might have been wearing it? Like one of those bodyguards?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. I don't think he was wearing one when we first met. <thought>The L.E.D. on this thing is lit. It must be on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like an instrument case. A big instrument case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's a great magic trick you can do with one of these!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What kind?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The "Miraculous Beautiful Girl Escapes the Case" illusion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So it's the girl who's miraculous, not the escape?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So picky!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the Gavinners's dressing room. The crime scene was Lamiroir's dressing room... ...Next door.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Never know where clues might be hiding, Apollo! Let's case this joint!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>After you, Trucy, P.I.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir's dressing room...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're not supposed to go in there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But aren't we involved? Aren't we duty-bound to investigate!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sadly, no. <thought>Though, the situation being what it is... Now may be our best chance to do some snooping...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm thirsty, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Want something to drink?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... How about... this one! A Steel Samurai Soda!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Now in Real Steel flavor."</thought> ...Hmm.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Here, my treat.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! This isn't enough change.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The machines outside are cheaper. This one is highway robbery.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A concert poster for the "Guilty as Charged" Tour.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I love that name! "Guilty As Charged"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Seems kind of negative to me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, why don't we do the opposite! Magician Trucy presents the "Innocent as Charged" tour!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It kind of loses its impact, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh. Looks like nobody's here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin's probably busy with the case, too. No rest for the wicked.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No rest for us, either, Apollo! Let's get rocking! Rock, rock!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. The stage looks empty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was hoping to get a chance to talk to Prosecutor Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh well. Nothing to do but go to the crime scene, I guess!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all these electronic devices. I'm guessing they have something to do with sound.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why guess when we can fiddle? Hmm... let's see here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't touch that!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A healthy curiosity is the key to a good investigation! When in doubt, fiddle! That's what Daddy always says.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They should require parental testing, clearly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now that's a big instrument case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's a case for a contrabass, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could fit twenty violins in there, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It may look like a violin, but it's a completely different instrument!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could fit five Trucys in there, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! Are you comparing me to an instrument? Hmm. I wonder who left it sitting open like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, a ladder. I guess they need one to work on the lights and such.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why don't they use a stepladder? I prefer stepladders, really. ...Is that so wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not wrong, just... well, why do you prefer stepladders?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... They're so much more flexible than plain old ladders!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I prefer my ladders rigid and stable, thank you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, that piano looks much bigger close up! Machi played so beautifully...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, like a real pianist.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's just silly, Apollo! How can you call someone as good as Machi a "pianist"? Why, that's like throwing him in the same class as Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Good thing Mr. Wright didn't hear that one.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a big stage! It's on a whole other scale than the Wonder Bar!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The lights were so bright I couldn't see the whole first part of the concert.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'd love to do my act on a stage like this some day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just hold back on the lights, for my eyes' sake, please.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You'll be too blinded by my magic to worry about lights!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You probably don't want to blind the audience if you plan on showing them magic.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, it's you. I figured you'd come.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have to let us investigate the scene, please!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're attorneys, no? Shouldn't you wait until you have a client...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>LeTouse did tell me to ask the witness, the siren... ...With his dying breath, no less. Doesn't that count?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...G-Glare at me all you want, you'll get no snacks from me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Please! Think of poor Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmph. Oh well, I suppose. You did find the body with me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great! Let's get to it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just try not to touch anything!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's letting us look! And she's not munching her snacks! This bodes well. There are clues here, I can feel it! Leave no hanger unhung, no spot unspotted!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo? Your mouth is catching flies.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah? Um, nothing. It's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">"Maybe that's how the killer escaped." ...That's what you were thinking, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">When we arrived on the scene, the killer had already fled. He or she must have had a way out. And that air vent is one possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But it's much too small.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Not if the killer were about your size, Trucy...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was cutting up the dance floor at the time, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know! Of course I don't think you did it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's hard to tell with you, sometimes, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! What have I done?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, what a pretty brooch! Oh, Ema...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're not going to say, "Can I have it, please," are you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look you may be a cute little girl of fifteen... ...but that doesn't get you any special treatment with me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not healthy to envy the young, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's not about envy! It's about tampering with evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Note to self: Ema lacks a sense of humor. Use caution.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You need to learn to respect your elders a little!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Something seems so familiar about that brooch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy's still after that brooch, clearly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">No way! If you want one that bad, get your daddy to buy it for you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy always says: "Trucy, if you want something go find or borrow it." Oh, and "When in doubt, beg."</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Leave it to Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm a little concerned for Trucy's future... But I'm more concerned about the owner of that brooch.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are these... bullet holes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like it. There are two here in the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">From the look of it, the victim was shot once in the shoulder. The first shot must have missed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But there are two holes. Wouldn't that mean two misses?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The murder weapon is a 45-caliber revolver. It's very powerful. I believe what we're seeing here... ...is the mark left by the second bullet after it passed through his shoulder!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ouch... Sounds painful.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No kidding. I wonder about this murder weapon...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Apollo! Can I eat some of those, please!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Absolutely not!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know. I know! But still, I yearn!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look, you're not the only one eyeing that fruit here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well then, what are we waiting for? Let's eat!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa whoa whoa! Stop it! Are you two crazy? Ema, you of all people should know better...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But she tempted me! She's a... She's a temptress!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Please, grow up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, another ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Actually, it's technically a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well hello, Ms. Fancy Pants! Please forgive my lack of ladder discrimination.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! ......</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm less worried about the stepladder, and more worried about why it's there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why is the ladder there? Well, to climb, right? To reach something on the ceiling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... I still say it's a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this poster...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... "This Summer: A Legal Eagles Production of 'Case Closed'." ...Looks like a poster for a different show.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...One I wouldn't mind seeing real soon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's another Gavinners poster here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm just about sick of seeing those, personally. Maybe I'll tear it down! Ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No tampering with the crime scene, Ema!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmph. Maybe there's something else I can tear to shreds...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">D-Don't look at me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That speaker was blaring at the time of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, that's for monitoring the stage from this room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Monitoring?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It pipes in a real-time feed from the stage microphones. Useful for knowing when your set is coming up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I seem to recall it being loud and vaguely musical. <thought>It made it hard to hear Mr. LeTouse's last words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah, ah, Apollo! Look at that thing! It's huge! That... That's a TV!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, yeah, a wide flatscreen TV. I want one of those.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'll be wanting for a long time on your salary, junior. Wait till you're as famous as Mr. Wright was, then dream.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't think Daddy was ever rich, even when he was in law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great, just stomp on my dreams why don't you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What an amazing bouquet. I mean, it's giant.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not sure I approve. It'd be better if this flower was a bit more... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eek! The flower fell off!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What happened to preserving the crime scene, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's fine! Fine! I'll just put it back, see?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How scientific...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is one of those... uh, things, right? At the barbers?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A permanent dryer. Want me to curl those bangs of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, no thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Better not mess with his hair, Ema. It's part of his identity, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-That's a body, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure is. The victim, no less. Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeek! G-Go ahead, Apollo. You first.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me!? No, you should go first, Trucy, really...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Will you two stop bickering and get over here!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's munching on Snackoos again. Hope she's not too annoyed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, look at this hand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. He's holding something.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey! No touching!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can throw all the snacks at me you'd like, Ema. But sooner or later... you're going to run out of them.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm. You raise a good point. ...I'm a bit intrigued by this scene. Let's take a look.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah... see there? He's holding something! What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...A key ring?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You think it might belong to the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Certainly a possibility...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What an unusual key ring... And what unusual keys. This could be a vital clue.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The body was holding a key ring...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wonder what it could mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must mean something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It doesn't look like the kind Mr. LeTouse would use. So the question is, whose key ring is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, you're practically a detective there, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Practically!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>I'm glad it brings them so much joy to mock me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeek! Is that... blood? Umm... Why don't you examine this one, Apollo. You know more about, uh, red stuff than I do. Yep!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Says who? <thought>Something is strange about this blood, though... Is that what it looks like?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seeing these mirrors lined up like that makes me think I'm really in a dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You are in a dressing room. Hmm... This must be makeup. ...I've never heard of most of these brands.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe they're Borginian?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I haven't got a clue, and I doubt those are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all these presents. Lamiroir sure is popular.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I wonder what's inside? We... can't open them, can we?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Probably not a good idea. You never know what you might find in one of these boxes. Bombs, razors, ransom notes... It could be anything.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... I'm never having a birthday party again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the murder weapon, isn't it? This revolver...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. A big 45-caliber revolver.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. I wonder who brought this in here? I thought only police were allowed to have one of those.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why are you giving me that look!? I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Listen, I was out in the hall eating Snackoos when it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know! No one here thinks you did it, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's hard to tell with you, sometimes, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! What have I done?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait... If the killer brought a revolver... ...it must mean they had planned this from the start. That's right, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A 45-caliber revolver, very deadly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, Apollo, I was wondering... What's a caliber? And what does the "45" mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Heh, you want me to tell you? It's the size of the barrel. Simply put, the larger the caliber, the bigger the round. ...The bullet, in other words. Bigger bullets do more damage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, chalk one point up for forensic science.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You know it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...But it's not 45 inches, right? That'd be too big. What's the unit of measurement they use, Ms. Science? Well?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...... Hush. Kids shouldn't ask so many questions.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, there's a little window over here! Maybe the killer escaped through that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's barely big enough for me to get my head through.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not to mention it only opens a crack.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What? I was just saying it's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, right, no harm in that. <thought>Except I'm pretty sure it is impossible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You could peek into the room through it, though, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. "Romein LeTouse", wasn't it? He was Lamiroir's manager. And interpreter, apparently. This was his first time in the country.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... So I'm guessing he didn't know many people here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It doesn't seem likely. Nor can I think of anyone with a motive to murder him. ...Except for one person, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">One person...? Who?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lamiroir. No one here might have had a motive, but she's from...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! H-Hey, it was Ema's idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I said nothing. MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Always with the snacks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's a big man. Or was. I don't think even I would win in a fight with him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which is why whoever it was used a revolver, I'm guessing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We've sent a request to the Borginian Embassy for more info on him.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, you and I know more about the crime than anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Y-You do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's true. It was us who found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaa-!? Hmph. I guess that's what I miss for watching the concert.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I wish I was watching the concert. ...Anything would be better than this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, we know the crime took place during the concert.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And when we heard the shot and entered the room... ...the killer was already gone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? But that doesn't make sense! You came in when you heard the shot and no one was here? How did they leave the room?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, that window is a little too small, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The mystery of the disappearing killer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What do you think about this revolver?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... it's pretty big. And heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. It's a 45-caliber. That makes it one of the deadliest revolvers around. Even the police don't carry guns this big.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah. It doesn't make sense... You don't need so much power to kill at such close range. ...It's overkill.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not sure I see the problem. I mean, whenever I go out to eat curry... ...I order it "extra spicy". Just to be sure it's spicy. Of course, I can only ever eat one or two bites.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, and that's not a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There's another thing about a gun this big. It puts a lot of strain on the shooter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Strain...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah. Say, if you were to fire this revolver... ...the recoil would probably dislocate your shoulder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ouuuuuch! It's like the shooter's a victim, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yet, the killer used this revolver, and quite well. I'm guessing whoever did it was used to shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Used to shooting a high-caliber weapon? Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You always carry that around, do you? ...Just like Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's good to never let yourself forget who you are. I'm proud of you. Keep up the good work.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Come to think of it, why do I carry this around? Though I suppose that's one compliment it's got me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this... is the murder weapon? <thought>This revolver is incredibly heavy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's been fired twice. You can still smell the gunpowder... ...That's odd.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's odd?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm? Oh, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, no fair! Tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's just, something about this revolver seems... strange.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Strange...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm, sorry. I can't comment on anything not scientifically relevant. I am a forensic scientist after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A self-styled one, at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A sort of pin-fastener for attaching things to clothes. Not a safety pin-type, though.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So if it's not a safety pin... ...is it a danger pin!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I suppose if you stuck it in your eye, then yeah, sure. But you could do that with a safety pin, too, for that matter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Thanks for taking the fun out of my danger pin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Aw, you're driving a danger pin through my heart here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! Don't point that thing at me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry! I'm an old hand with firearms. I have one that shoots "Bullets".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't want it shooting any bullets, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not those bullets, silly! My gun shoots "Bullets, the Magic Cat".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A cat... comes out of a gun?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can tell your expression you've never heard of that trick. It's a great one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Honestly, That one sounds halfway interesting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The middle of the weapon is a revolving chamber. That's where you load the bullets. A revolver, see?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Revolver... Revolver... That sounds a bit like "Wonder Bar"! Especially if you say it really fast!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what I always used to think? I used to think the closest sound to "Wonder Bar" was "One Liver"! There's just so many words in the world, Apollo! Isn't it amazing!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... So many different words, so many different people. <thought>...People like Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are three keys on this heart-shaped key ring. Hmm? This middle key is shaped like... a guitar?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I get it! It must be the key to a guitar case!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A guitar case key... <thought>I'll bet I know who this belongs to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Thanks for taking the fun out of my danger pin.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Aw, you're driving a danger pin through my heart here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I know how you're feeling. It is hard to know when to stop. But anything more involved has to wait until the squad gets here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Argh... I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'll go report the evidence. Sorry, but could you wait here till I get back?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, actually, we have to--</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Great! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...She left.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do we do, Apollo? She told us to wait...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great. Now how am I supposed to investigate?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh well, I guess it can't be helped. Let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Go?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Time's a wasting, Apollo! We've got a lot of ground to cover!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's true, but... ...On second thought, why not. I'm sure everything will be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course it will! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... That air vent bothers me. If Ema and I came in through the door... That makes that vent the only exit from the room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But it's much too small.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Not if the killer were about your size, Trucy...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was cutting up the dance floor at the time, thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know! Of course I don't think you did it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's hard to tell with you, sometimes, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey! What have I done?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No snatching people's brooches.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Darn... Maybe there's another one lying around here somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If there is, you can't have that one either.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Don't be so stingy, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think the word you're looking for is "principled".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Are these... bullet holes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like it. There are two here in the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, if there are two marks, they must have missed twice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not necessarily... Some revolvers can put a bullet through a person. So it wasn't necessarily a miss.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ouch... Sounds painful.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Apollo! Can I eat some of those, please!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Better not. Ema will find out. Somehow, she will. "How could you eat those without telling me!?"</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah... I'll make sure to leave some for her to eat, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that's the issue here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, another ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Actually, it's technically a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well hello, Ms. Fancy Pants! Please forgive my lack of ladder discrimination.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">! ......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd say this ladder is used to climb up to reach things. ...Is there something on the ceiling?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I still say it's a stepladder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, there's another Gavinners poster. Ema didn't seem too happy about it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe I should take it down before she rips it up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You walk around with that thing and she'll sniff it out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Maybe I'll pass then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's probably wise to be wary of Ema...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That speaker was blaring when it happened. Apparently, it monitors sound from the main stage. ...Which made it hard to hear Mr. LeTouse's last words.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you know what I do at loud concerts? I wear earplugs! It really cuts down on the noise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And this would have helped me hear him how?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah, ah, Apollo! Look at that thing! It's huge! That... That's a TV!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, yeah, a wide flatscreen TV. I want one of those. Someday when I'm a famous attorney, I'll get one...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But Daddy never had one. I don't think he ever even had money when he was a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great, just stomp on my dreams why don't you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What an amazing bouquet. I mean, it's giant.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's super dazzle-frazzle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..."Dazzle-frazzle"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, it's super, and it makes you feel all dazzle-frazzle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Who taught you to say that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I knew it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is one of those... uh, things, right? At the barbers? It's one of those permanent hair things.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've never tried one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Want to?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... I think I'll stick with my top hat. We have an understanding, me and my hat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's... just a hat, Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The body was holding a key ring...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think it belongs to the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it's not Mr. LeTouse's, that seems like a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seeing these mirrors lined up like that makes me think I'm really in a dressing room. Look at all that makeup.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I haven't got a clue, and I doubt those are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess she's not into makeup yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at all these presents. Lamiroir sure is popular.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I got a present once, from a person in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's pretty cool.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Isn't it! Maybe you'll get one someday. ...From someone you defend!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's called getting paid, and I certainly hope I do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A 45-caliber revolver, very powerful. This is definitely the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder who brought this revolver in here? It's huge.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone unusual, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No one I want to meet, that's also for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me either. Unless it's in court, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, there's a little window over here! Maybe the killer escaped through that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's only big enough to stick your head through. And it doesn't even open all the way.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What? I was just saying it's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, right, no harm in that. <thought>Except I'm pretty sure it is impossible.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's there!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We... didn't just imagine that, did we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was wearing a silk hat. ...Friend of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hardly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoever that was, he sure looked suspicious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What is it with today!? Problem after problem! Achtung!</line>
<line speaker="???">You ain't kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's the two leading members of the Gavinners, Apollo! Klavier on vocals, and Daryan on guitar! They're so cool!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have a hard time thinking of "Klavier" as anything but a prosecutor, honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? What are they arguing about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Probably the case, I'd bet.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My hog won't start. My guitar case is busted... ...my guitar's been burnt to a crisp, and to top it all off, someone's dead! ...And then there was that performance just now. What was that all about!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Hey, man, don't blame me. You were the one who missed the cue.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Me? Miss a cue!? How could I conceivably get the most important part of that song wrong? How!? And what was all that tinny playing of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Who you calling "tinny"!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Sounds like they're having a spat. One of those "differences in musical direction" bands are always splitting up over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is hardly the time...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Hmm? What are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, um, hiya. ......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We were just discussing the investigation, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry. Wait... You were what?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Listen... You need to confirm that with the Republic of Borginia, Detective Crescend.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Right. Anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did he just call him? "Detective...?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah, greetings. Daryan Crescend... Criminal Affairs, Division 3.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... H-Hello. <thought>"Criminal Affairs"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">*sigh* Apollo... You really don't know anything  about the Gavinners, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something tells me that's about to be remedied.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Which crime do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder, what else!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, that. For me, today has been a hit parade of crimes, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prosecutor Gavin was singing the blues earlier, wasn't he? ...Something about his hog, and his guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Anyway. I'm afraid you know more about the killing of Mr. LeTouse than I do. ...For now, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You were the one who found the body, ja? While we were in the middle of a performance, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aren't you going to examine the crime scene, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'll leave that to Fräulein Detective. Wouldn't want to step on her toes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They're not exactly best buddies are they. Ema and Prosecutor Gavin, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, what to do next. We've already checked out the scene. <thought>Prosecutor Gavin may be right. We might be the most informed, for once.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe Prosecutor Gavin can shed some light on things we've found!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't believe you, Apollo! How can you come to this concert and not know about the Gavinners!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's not surprising. Why, even our ancestors knew nothing of America's existence once.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I know America exists.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Gavinners aren't just an average rock band, Apollo. Each member is connected to the police somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Police?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The real police! By day they pack heat, but by night they heat up the stage! By day those lips interrogate, by night they sing songs of unrequited passion!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They debuted seven years ago with "13 Years Hard Time For Love"... Then came "Love With No Chance Of Parole", and "My Boyfriend Is The Prosecution's Witness". The list of hits goes on and on!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This here's my right-hand man. ...Daryan Crescend. I make the melodies, and he attacks them with his guitar. He's a bit of a rogue, really.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Heh. And this guy's a bit of a perfectionist. When a performance goes the least bit wrong he goes into this funk... Just like today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd hope murder would be a bit more off-putting than a ruined concert...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The concert today? A disaster! I'll get to the bottom of this and then we'll see who missed a cue!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The missed cue... They were arguing about that before...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, I love nothing more than questioning tormented artists.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's this missed cue you keep talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha, you heard it, didn't you? From the audience?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, actually, I didn't notice anything...</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">See! No amateur is going to pick up on that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Can you guarantee an entire audience of amateurs? No! Now take a listen to this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's that...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A mixing board. We used it to record our concert tonight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Aren't we supposed to be investigating a murder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, we've come this far, might as well go all the way! I've always wanted to learn about the recording industry!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is but one of the devices used in recordings. We're a five-part band... This lets us record each member's performance separately. You use the sliders to adjust the volume for each part. Check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, neat! So, could you, say, hear only the drum part?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course. That's how we'll find the criminal guilty of missing his cue tonight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm more concerned with the other criminal. The one who kills people.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You want help on the case? Then help me with mine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess rock 'n' roll comes before prosecuting.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let's begin! First, we bring up the part of the performance in question. You simply choose the section of the song you wish to hear on the bottom-most bar. Like so. There it is. Now, listen.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Was something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You couldn't hear it? Listen again, closely...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah... the timing's a little off, isn't it!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You see? There! Right at the most important part! And even an amateur can hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">An amateur with a mixing board, maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You're missing the point! We'll never stamp out crime until we're perfect. Perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Here he goes again...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Right. Herr Amateur, you will prove my point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You will find the missed cue! You will tell us which instrument, which part, is the guilty party!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But how...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did I not just explain it? Use these sliders to adjust the volume for each part. Then you will find the part that hopelessly bungles the cue! You'll find it, with your untrained amateur ears!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Nothing to do but try, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess... I'll admit, this looks kind of fun.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">First, a quick review: use the sliders to adjust volumes. Press the section of the song you wish to hear on the bottom bar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sliders and the bar, got it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Once you've found the guilty part, press the corresponding number! Time to rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This part sounds a little off.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let's see............... ...Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let me guess... ...You got a D in high school chorus, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How'd he know!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This part is perfection. Absolute perfection. I'd bet all the royalties from my last platinum-selling album on it. The guilty part is elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, yeah, I know you sold a bazillion records.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Focus, Apollo! I'll cheer you on!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, it's probably better if you stay quiet... <thought>Let's give this another shot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This part is off.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Which is that? Hmm... 2nd Guitar.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was you Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...... Ah well, looks like the cat's out of the bag.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Ah well"? That's all you have to say!? That kind of attitude lets killers walk free, Daryan!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Here they go again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it wasn't such a good idea to ask about the concert. It's starting to feel like we're just wasting time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's all experience under our belts! That can't be bad!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I still can't get over the title for that song... ..."Guilty Love"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Best to avoid bringing up that topic again... I'm sure I can think of something else to ask about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were saying something about your motorcycle not starting?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And something about your guitar case being busted?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You're well informed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mentioned it a few times.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ach. Ach! It all happened this morning. It's all this key ring's fault.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The key ring...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's got all my keys on it, ja? My bike key, my car key... and the key to my guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, so this key ring...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It disappeared. I thought I'd put it in my jacket pocket...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Prosecutor Gavin's key ring... disappeared?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I had to come to the concert by taxi. How embarrassing! And in order to get my guitar out, I had to break the lock.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, this guitar wasn't the one that...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The very one. Up in flames... ...And right on stage, too.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I actually thought that was part of the show.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Crazy. ...And to top it off, Mr. LeTouse's life was taken. Nobody told me 'bout days like these.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Strange days, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...You think?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's wrong, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I was just trying to make sense of everything. First this heart-shaped key ring gets stolen. Then a very expensive guitar flares up on stage. Then Mr. LeTouse dies...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, and...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Could it all really be just a coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Coincidence...? Meaning...? Daryan, can you make any sense of all this?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Hey, don't look at me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you think, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I mean, either Mr. Gavin's having a really bad day... ...or all this was planned.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... You... aren't thinking what I think you're thinking... ...are you, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I am!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What? What!? Hey, don't leave me in the dark with Spike, here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...The name's Apollo, but yeah, I agree... Don't leave us in the dark! What are you talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Haven't you noticed a connection, Apollo? ...A curious connection between all of Mr. Gavin's troubles today?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, something was bugging me, too! That key ring, and the guitar, and the body...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Slow down there, Polly. You look a wee bit dizzy.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">He's bluffing. He hasn't figured it out. Fess up, if you're a man. You're as clueless as I am!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No, no, give Herr Forehead a chance. Let's see your evidence of the connection, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">E-Evidence!? <thought>Ack! I'd better think of something pronto!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">C'mon c'mon c'mon! Let's see it! What's the connection between all of Mr. Gavin's troubles?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The connection... is this! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, I would say you were close, but really, you're kinda far. Remote, even.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops. Try not to anger the Trucy, Apollo. No sudden motions... Just find that evidence slowly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's this, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You haven't!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I just don't see the connection. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well don't just give up! Give it a little more thought!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... You don't mean this, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">A lyrics sheet? ..."The Guitar's Serenade"...? What's that got to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It has everything to do with everything. Though I wouldn't have believed it if the Fräulein hadn't pointed it out.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">What are you talking about, man? Enough with the riddles!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Maybe it is a coincidence, or perhaps it means something. Don't you think, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I do. Everything that's happened to Mr. Gavin today... ...is predicted in the lyrics to this song!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Wh-Whaaat!? No way!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, just think about everything that's happened to Mr. Gavin. Let's list them in the order that they occurred... ...while reading this lyrics sheet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First, the key ring was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And not just any key ring! A heart-shaped key ring!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right here! "When you stole away the keys my heart held on to so tight." This is a "heart" holding "keys"!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And next, his guitar burst into flame.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Burning on in my heart. Fire. Burn my love away..."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And then Mr. LeTouse was killed...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Like a bullet of love. Fire. Take my life away..." But... But that's crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, no kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">So everything that happened today, here... ...This song predicted it all?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Or perhaps it was the other way around...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The criminal could have based his crime on the lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But who would go through all that trouble...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Someone who moves in mysterious ways, no doubt. I believe you've stumbled upon something quite vital... and quite annoying, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She looks pleased...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I was wondering if you knew anything about this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Th-That...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Does it look familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Familiar! It's mine! That's my key ring! I've been looking all over for it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaaaat!? This is yours, Mr. Gavin!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I knew it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! How can you make that "I knew it" face!? This is the key ring that was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Thanks, anyway. So, where did you find it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erm, actually, the victim was holding it. Like he was trying to keep it from the killer. Even if it meant his life.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Wh-Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!? The victim... you mean, Mr. LeTouse had my keys?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hrmm... When will my trials be over?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Speaking of trials, I've never heard Mr. Gavin whine in court like he has been today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema was right about the fop, I'll give her that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Mr. Gavin, maybe we can help. Tell us about your troubles today.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I really don't think that's...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tell us... ...and we'll keep mum about the key ring for now.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Are... you blackmailing me, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Anyway... Thanks for finding this. If you'd found it under different circumstances, I'd be even happier.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder why Mr. LeTouse was holding it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he was trying to tell us something? Maybe that Prosecutor Gavin is the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead, save your wild accusations for the court. I do so enjoy the penalties.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Sorry, but I'm not in the mood to talk about that right now. Even I can only take so much in one day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Funny, I always thought of Prosecutor Gavin as one of those cool, stoic types. The sort that never complains. How wrong I was!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Seems a bit more than just a coincidence to me.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I have to agree. The key ring, the guitar, and the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The key ring might have been dropped by accident.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet the victim was holding it. Hard to think that it was unconnected.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's true. <thought>Prosecutor Gavin's as calm and collected as ever...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So the criminal matched their actions to the lyrics?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">That sounds likely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would anyone do that?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...While we think about that, I'm going to get cracking on the biggest crime here. I'm going to talk to the Borginian Embassy about this Mr. LeTouse.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, right. Thanks, Daryan.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">I'll leave the pondering of mysteries to you. I'm outta here.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A foreign national, Mr. LeTouse was killed... It seems like that would have to be the "point" of all this. But they did more than that. They left us with not only a murder, but a mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin sure is irritable today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe this is the real Prosecutor Gavin we don't get to see in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I've had enough, frankly. If you find any more mysteries, do me a favor and keep them to yourselves, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ja... <thought>I guess this is all we're going to get from Prosecutor Gavin. That leaves Lamiroir to question.</thought> Prosecutor Gavin... do you know where Lamiroir is now?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, I had her go to my dressing room. With that pianist, Machi Tobaye, of course. She seemed rather shocked by Mr. LeTouse's sudden passing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The Gavinners's dressing room. Got it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't believe you, Apollo! How can you come to this concert and not know about the Gavinners!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's not surprising. Why, even our ancestors knew nothing of America's existence once.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I know America exists.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The Gavinners aren't just an average rock band, Apollo. Each member is connected to the police somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Police?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The real police! By day they pack heat, but by night they heat up the stage! By day those lips interrogate, by night they sing songs of unrequited passion!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, OK.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, just think about everything that's happened to Mr. Gavin. Let's list them in the order that they occurred... ...while reading this lyrics sheet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First, the key ring was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And not just any key ring! A heart-shaped key ring!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"When you stole away the keys my heart held on to so tight." This is a "heart" holding "keys"!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And next, his guitar burst into flame.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Burning on in my heart. Fire. Burn my love away..."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And then Mr. LeTouse was killed...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Like a bullet of love. Fire. Take my life away..."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this song prerdicted everything that was going to happen!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Or perhaps it was the other way around...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The criminal could have based his crime on the lyrics.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Someone who moves in mysterious ways, no doubt. I believe you've stumbled upon something quite vital... and quite annoying, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She looks pleased...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's there!? ...There he goes again. Who is that guy!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, he did look sort of familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So he is a friend of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, that's not it. ...Sorry, I don't remember.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Curiouser and curiouser...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are three keys on this heart-shaped key ring. And this guitar-shaped key was the key to a guitar case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wasn't he saying he had to break his case because he couldn't get it unlocked? I could open a lock like that in 10 seconds, easy! He should have given me a call.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So he could slap handcuffs on you after you opened it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Handcuffs? 20 seconds, tops!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm glad she's on my side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah... Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What... What has happened? I heard that Mr. LeTouse has died!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">L-Lamiroir! You speak? I mean, you speak English?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah... Yes. I was invited here from the Republic of Borginia... But I am not Borginian by birth.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But wasn't Mr. LeTouse your interpreter...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah that. Yes, well... It was Mr. LeTouse's idea. He thought it would add to the mystery, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then, your pianist is also...?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">No, Machi Tobaye is Borginian. He does not speak English. Now, please tell me! What has happened to Mr. LeTouse? Why did he...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Actually, Mr. LeTouse was...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Remember what Prosecutor Gavin said? "Not a word"!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But Mr. LeTouse is Lamiroir's manager! That's not fair to her! I mean, isn't she a related party?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Precisely who Prosecutor Gavin doesn't want to alert, I'd suspect.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">All we have been told is to wait here in this room. It is very unsettling.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, we're trying to figure it out ourselves. Do... you think I could ask you some questions?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Of course. I am always willing to help.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's as calm as she looked on stage... I can't put my finger on why, but I like this Lamiroir.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What is it, Machi?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What... but you'd be alone!</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, what seems to be the problem?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Machi... he is not good around strangers. He wishes to go out for a breath of fresh air. Would that be alright?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, sure, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">....................</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Very well. What is it you wished to ask me about?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! It's a postcard of Lamiroir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are these letters at the bottom? I've never seen these before.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It must be her native tongue, Borginese!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">"A landscape painter in sound"... This is how it would translate, roughly. Please, take one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"A landscape painter in sound"...? That's a nice image...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">You see the words written upon the postcard? They say "a landscape painter in sound".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"A landscape painter in sound"...? That's a nice image...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Republic of Borginia... that's in Northern Europe, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I've never even heard of it...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I started out singing in a restaurant... Then a producer called me. Before I knew it... here I am.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You don't say! You know, my daddy plays piano in a restaurant!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Producers tend to look for talent, Trucy. ...Lamiroir, you're not from Borginia originally? Were you born here?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, is that supposed to be a secret?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Image is everything when you're a star! I know a bit about that, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Ah, yes, it is something like this. A contract, you might say. I'm also not to speak anything but Borginese in public.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Image is important, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's not all image, though! Her songs are lovely! A real "landscape painter in sound"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A painter in what?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She travels the world, turning the sights she sees into music! That's the secret to your music's beauty, right?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">You're very perceptive.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I use your songs all the time in my stage act. ...I don't have to pay royalties for that, do I?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Stop while you're ahead, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">This "landscape painter in sound", too, is an image. Yet without it, my songs would not be so widely heard.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They even call you the "Siren of the Ballad", right?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes. In Borginese, "Lamiroir" means "the Siren". I fear that, perhaps, already I am not the siren I once was.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your pianist... Machi, was it? He's cute! Like a porcelain doll...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's very "European".</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I met him while singing in restaurants in Borginia. He is an orphan... yet his playing is exquisite. Soon he came to live with me.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's like a fairy tale, almost...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I noticed he hardly leaves your side.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, well, he is blind. At first, I hesitated at dragging him across the world.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He doesn't speak English, either, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">He had never left Borginia before we met. I made his presence part of  my contract. Machi and I together are "Lamiroir". Together, always.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. LeTouse... was my new manager.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">New?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes, from three months ago. Around when I received Mr. Gavin's invitation to come. I met Mr. LeTouse at my office. He was to be my manager and bodyguard... And, as it turned out, my interpreter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Interpreter... even though you speak English.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Yes... but we were to visit more places than just here. We had a concert in Japan scheduled after this one. Though I fear that may have to be cancelled now...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Was Mr. LeTouse from the Republic of Borginia, too?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Well... he was only with me for three months. I'm afraid there is much I do not know about him. And now, I shall never know. No one will even tell me why he has died.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm sorry... Prosecutor Gavin said we weren't to talk to anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. LeTouse... was a talented man. The "Siren of the Ballad"... That phrase was his idea, you know. I am happy for him that it has become so well known.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You are "the Siren", right Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">That is the meaning of my name in Borginese, yes. It was the name my producer gave me. But why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's very important. I had to know for sure if the "Siren" was you.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What do you mean, important?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'll tell you. You deserve to know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Siren"... It turns out that's a very important word in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">H-How?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When we found Mr. LeTouse... ...he was still alive.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I heard him say something... ...his last words.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. LeTouse! Can you hear me!?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">Ask... wi...witness...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hang in there, Mr. LeTouse! Tell me, who was the witness?</line>
<line speaker="LeTouse">The wi...witness...is ...si...si...ren...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He said "siren"... Really?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was the only one there to hear it... ...but I'm sure that's what he said!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Mr. LeTouse said that!? "Ask the witness"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you're the Siren, Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you see what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That reminds me... Does this brooch look familiar to you?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">My brooch... yes! Well... It may be mine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yours, Lamiroir...?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I was wearing a brooch earlier, you see. I must have lost it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well that explains the brooch we found. It was Lamiroir's!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Thank you. I was wondering where I'd dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this brooch belongs to her... That begs the question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is something wrong, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...What was this brooch doing at the crime scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I believe that brooch is mine, yes. ... I was wondering where I had dropped it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So it's Lamiroir's brooch, which begs the question... ...what was it doing at the crime scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you mind taking a look at this, Lamiroir?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">...... I'm sorry, I'm not sure what to say. I wish I could help you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, don't worry about it. <thought>Certainly one of the most pleasant refusals I've had.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Might I ask, are you with the police?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh! Uh, well, no. I'm a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">An attorney? Yet there have been no arrests, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is that a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">Does an attorney not work for a "client"? If you have no client, you should leave the investigation to the police, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But Lamiroir, we...</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I am sorry, but I cannot answer your questions. I'm afraid you lack the authority to ask them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack... <thought>Why...? If she witnessed the crime, why won't she tell us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I believe we are through here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I believe so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Who's there now!?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, it's you. ...Where were you!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! Ema! ...Is something wrong? <thought>She's looks grumpier than usual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You bet something's wrong! The impossible's happened! Arrgh! It's all your fault, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops. Maybe this is about us leaving the crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean by "impossible"?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well it's gone! Utterly gone!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...What's gone?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The body, stupid! What else?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. LeTouse's body has disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah... Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">From your vacant stare, I gather you've heard the news.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I heard Mr. LeTouse's body has gone missing...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Look for yourself. Quite the pickle. Quite. The. Pickle.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">How can you just stand there!? We have to start the investi...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There's no need for alarm, Fräulein Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">All entrances and exits have been sealed. The body will not leave the building. So, I suggest we go find ourselves a cadaver. There will be plenty of time to ponder the "whys" later.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you seem pretty sure of yourself, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, we'll find him. I'm rather enjoying this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How could Mr. LeTouse's body just "disappear"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you heard the man. Let's get searching!</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">...Hey, I don't know if this's exactly the right time, but...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, Daryan?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">See, Geeter's gone missing. It was in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Geeter? Who's Geeter!?</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">That's what I call my guitar! You like, man?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your guitar... was stolen?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This hasn't been a good day for guitars or geeters.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">OK. Body first, then guitar. And if someone finds that guitar, please bring it to our dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Daryan">Geeter's like a missing person, not lost 'n' found,  man.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There should be a body here. But there's not. How could this have happened? And why?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, this sure is a... what did he call it? A sausage? No wait, it was a pickle. And it's your pickle! I told you to stay in the room!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry. <thought>Not much else I can say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...It's alright. Top priority now is finding that body. ...You can make it up to me later. Ten bags or so of chocolate Snackoos should do the trick nicely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You should watch your sugar intake, Ema.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Just hold it right there. This is not time to be waving a bag of Snackoos in my face!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, it's not a bag of Snackoos.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look. What's important is that Mr. LeTouse's body is missing! And we've got to find it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She would be more convincing if she wasn't standing around eating her precious Snackoos.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. Does something seem different to you, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something is definitely different here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not sure that's all that important right now. Let's check out that thing in the middle of the stage!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That stage there must have been lowered before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's the tower that Lamiroir and Prosecutor Gavin were singing on.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone must have raised it. Hmm. I don't see a way to control it from here. Apollo, what about that ladder there against the wall? We could use that to take a look up top...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Maybe we should get Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you talking about? We have to see this sort of thing for ourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm... not so good with heights.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Stop whining and start climbing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It didn't look that high from below, really. But when we got to the top, I felt every one of those 20 feet down. Of course, I wasn't thinking about the height any more. Not after what we found up there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We found two things we were looking for, and one thing we never expected to find.</thought> ...The body, guitar in hand, and the pianist, Machi Tobaye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that concert last night sure went south in a hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No kidding. Why did they arrest Machi!? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't look at me like it's my fault! <thought>Machi Tobaye, the blind pianist... ...arrested on suspicion of murdering Romein LeTouse.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't believe such a cute little boy could do something so horrible!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess they had proof of some kind.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What proof could possibly prove that!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Mornin'.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What a night, eh? I apologize for being so upset...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mr. Gavin, do you know what's going on? Why did they arrest Machi!? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't look at him like it's his fault either.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was tough for me, too. We performed together that night, after all. Yet...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yet?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The powers that be say that, given the circumstances, it could only have been him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean by the "circumstances"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Lamiroir was invited from Borginia as an ambassador of goodwill. It is vital that this case be wrapped up swiftly. That's all the powers that be want, really.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well those are circumstances, alright. But what makes Machi the only possible suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead... You seem to have forgotten that you're talking to the prosecution... the enemy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah. Right. <thought>I think I like this side of Prosecutor Gavin better, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm not at liberty to discuss the particulars of the case. ...Especially not to the defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What... did you just say? Me? The defense attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's what I came to tell you. He's down at the detention center... He wants to request your services.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He...? You mean Machi? Machi wants me...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is what we've been waiting for, Apollo! Let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Right...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good luck. I'm off to question Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right. Later! <thought>I hope I'm up to this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I just don't get it. I refuse to believe a cute little kid like that could do something so terrible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You said that already.</line>
<line speaker="Machi">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Machi! Everything's going to be OK! We're here for you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, h-hi. Maybe you can tell me about last night...</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking].... [Borginese speaking]!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That was when I realized how tough it must be... A little kid like this... ...in a country so far from everything he's ever known.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, maybe Lamiroir can help?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But didn't Prosecutor Gavin say she was with him?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Good luck. I'm off to question Lamiroir.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, what are we going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's, um, a good question. <thought>I can't think of anything we can do but go with this. ...And hope for the best at the trial tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Machi">[Borginese speaking].... [Borginese speaking]....</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No clues here.</line>
</xml>