<xml>
<title>Turnabout Succession</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Welcome to court. Seven years... all leading to one verdict. A verdict which you must decide. Is the defendant, Vera Misham, innocent... or guilty? The courtroom doors are opening... the trial awaits. Are you ready to begin?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Vera Misham.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The nail polish Mr. Wright gave me. This must be the brand symbol. It's an "A", drawn like a flower. It's refreshing to see a brand with a simple, clear design like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This stamp... It's of the Gramaryes, Isn't it? Why did Mr. Wright give me this letter right before the trial? What could it mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's an address on here... And a name I've never heard of. At least, I think so... It's too blurry to read.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Prosecution's ready to rock.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin. How is the defendant... Vera Misham's condition?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Acute atroquinine poisoning. According to her physician... ...she could die at any time. Thus... her absence from the courtroom today.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!? They can't put her on trial without her being here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It... is unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They should wait for her to get better and do it then. ...It's so bureaucratic of them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's being a little harsh. <thought>They can't delay the trial any longer. ...Or they risk having no one left to try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A trial without a verdict can only cause grief... ...The records of this case, and experience, tell us this. ...Apologies to the defendant, but the show must go on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right... if Vera dies, the trial will be cancelled. ...I'm not going to let that happen! Mr. Wright told me everything that's been going on behind the curtain all these years. I'm going to get Vera her innocent verdict while there's still time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Your opening statement, Prosecutor Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The prosecution's case is unchanged by recent events. Why did Vera Misham succumb to poison? Because she couldn't live with the guilt of what she'd done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But Vera was poisoned with atroquinine! The exact same poison that took her father's life!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...What better confession could you ask for? Being the killer she would have had access to the poison. Significant, since it's rather hard to come by.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That is true.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In other words... I see no need for further discussion. We could have had our verdict... yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? If you have no objections, I see no reason to postpone a verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What we need to worry about isn't the verdict... but the trial itself! The defense holds that Vera Misham is the victim not the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If that's so... then you have to prove something. She was in court, giving her testimony before us. How do you propose her "killer" poisoned her? Oh... and incidentally, it would be nice if you told us who her mystery "killer" was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...The prosecution's objection is sustained. I ask the defense to prove its claims to this court. Tell us how Vera Misham was "poisoned"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I've got two things to prove here. Who did it, and how. Which to hit first?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How did the killer poison Vera Misham...? I will focus first on the method used.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Any comments before we begin, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not a bottle or container of the poison was found on the defendant's body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... So the vector of poisoning is unknown. Is the defense prepared to prove how the poison reached Vera Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. What method was used to poison Vera Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">From what I hear... ...atroquinine takes a while before it acts on the body.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. "Slow acting", it's called.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Also from what I hear... ...my penalties hurt more later than at the moment they're given. ...But let's find out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, I'm wrong, I get it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They've really made an art out of this penalty thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this...? My, what a beautiful bottle. I'd like to give whoever designed that a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is that... nail polish? Hmm, it's colorless. Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">N-No. Nothing. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the killer put poison in this bottle, and made her drink it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As Prosecutor Gavin has told us, this is nail polish.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nail polish...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's like paint for nails. Know any women with red nails?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! My wife has red nails! I see... so she's been painting them all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's recall yesterday's trial. Remember when Vera was testifying to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Vera seems pretty tense. She's practically chewing her fingernails clean off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whenever Vera became nervous, she had a habit... ...of biting her nails.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her nails... Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin? When the prosecution had Vera examined, did they check her nails?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I... Well I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Have them check the defendant's nails at once! ...Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you know who did this? Do you know who put poison in that nail polish!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That bottle... belongs to Vera Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why do you ask? Know someone else who might have a bottle like this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... No. Just checking.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice. You are about to accuse someone of poisoning that bottle of nail polish! Please dispense with the chatter. You realize the weight of this accusation? Here, let me show you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Understood, Your Honor. <thought>No problem. I know what I'm doing this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let us ask! Who poisoned Vera Misham via her nail polish!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm having a little trouble following your reasoning. Any insights, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is clear just who is poisonous here. Herr Forehead is poisoning the hearts and minds of this court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Then let's fight poison, with penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...No slouching now, Justice! This is my chance to drag the real killer out into the light of day! I know who gave Vera that bottle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this? Kristoph Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...What's your game? My bro... There's no way he could do a thing like that! You should know that better than anyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... ...He is behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I know. However... ...that doesn't mean it was impossible to do what he did.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ask yourselves "when" he put the poison in the bottle. It could have been yesterday. ...It could have been a month ago. Maybe it was a year ago? ...Or perhaps, it was seven years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But...! Kristoph Gavin had no motive for killing this poor girl!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just who poisoned Vera Misham? I have a name for you.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Just a moment, Herr Forehead. You are aware this is an accusation you're making? I think a bit of risk is in order. This much, to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I understand. <thought>No problem. I know what I'm doing this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's hear it! Who poisoned Vera Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm not sure I entirely understand. Do you understand, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It is clear just who is poisonous here. Herr Forehead is poisoning the hearts and minds of this court!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Then let's fight poison, with penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...No slouching now, Justice! This is my chance to drag the real killer out into the light of day! I know who gave Vera that bottle!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this? Kristoph Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...What's your game? My bro... There's no way he could do a thing like that! You should know that better than anyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed... ...He is behind bars.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I know. However... ...that doesn't mean it was impossible to do what he did.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kristoph Gavin had the opportunity to poison Vera Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Apparently, the defense has something in mind. Let's see what it is! How did Kristoph Gavin, currently in solitary confinement, poison her!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">From what I hear... ...atroquinine takes a while before it acts on the body.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. "Slow-acting", it's called.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Also from what I hear... ...my penalties hurt more later than at the moment they're given. ...But let's find out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, I'm wrong, I get it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They've really made an art out of this penalty thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this...? My, what a beautiful bottle. I'd like to give whoever designed that a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is that... nail polish? Hmm, it's colorless. Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">N-No. Nothing. Nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the killer put poison in this bottle, and made her drink it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As Prosecutor Gavin has told us, this is nail polish.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nail polish...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's like paint for nails. Know any women with red nails?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! My wife has red nails! I see... so she's been painting them all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's recall yesterday's trial. Remember when Vera was testifying to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Vera seems pretty tense. She's practically chewing her fingernails clean off!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whenever Vera became nervous, she had a habit... ...of biting her nails.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her nails... Aaah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin? When the prosecution had Vera examined, did they check her nails?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I... Well I...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Have them check the defendant's nails at once!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kristoph Gavin didn't have to "poison" that bottle the day of the poisoning, Your Honor! The moment Vera first held that bottle in her hand, her fate was sealed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But wait! This business about Kristoph Gavin giving her that bottle is only conjecture!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It's simply inconceivable!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Prosecutor Gavin doesn't seem to think so.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That face tells me one thing. Kristoph Gavin's own younger brother doesn't find it inconceivable at all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Prosecutor Gavin? If you feel there is a clear and pressing need... ...then we may have to summon Kristoph Gavin from jail as a special witness.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... Fine. I've known for some time that an impenetrable darkness lurked at the bottom of this. ...A darkness that has swallowed even myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...OK. The defense's wish is granted. Let prisoner Kristoph Gavin take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, begin proceedings to call a special witness! The witness is Kristoph Gavin, currently residing in Solitary Cell 13 at Central Prison!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Ah, Your Honor. How nice to see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It's been quite a while, hasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">To what do I owe the pleasure of your company? It's not every day I'm summoned from my solitary cell. In fact, it's never.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think you already know, Mister Kristoph Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah... Mr. Justice. ...I hear you've been doing quite well for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack... Why do I feel like somehow, he's still my boss...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Stiff upper lip, Apollo! You can do it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Does this bottle look familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ariadoney nail polish? ...Why yes, I use it myself. As did the late defendant, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's not dead yet!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">And...? Was there something concerning this bottle you wished to ask me about? I admit, I respect her for her taste in nail polish.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Her "taste" indeed! This nail polish was how Vera Misham was poisoned!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Atroquinine... was it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're well informed about the case, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Even in solitary, much comes to my desk. And I have nothing to do but read. ...Well, Klavier?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Maybe you can explain this?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... You're being accused again. ...By him. Again.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ahh. And? You agree with his accusation, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hold a proper trial, shall we? Kristoph Gavin... your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I'd be delighted.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The charges against you are quite severe, Mr. Gavin. You are suspected of the poisoning of the defendant, Vera Misham... ...Please testify on this matter to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Owning the same nail polish does not a murderer make.I have been in solitary confinement for half a year. How could I poison her?Her father died of the same poison... the meaning of which should be clear.The prosecution's case holds. She poisoned her father, then attempted to poison herself.Surely, you aren't going to suggest I was responsible for poisoning her father, too?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...I'm afraid the defense's claim is sounding rather unlikely.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Naturally. For one, I don't even know the Mishams. Isn't that so, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Justice, begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm accusing Kristoph Gavin, my ex-boss. But I know he poisoned the Mishams! The question is "when" could he have done it...? Not to mention... "why"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Owning the same nail polish does not a murderer make.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell me, is this nail polish expensive?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ariadoney is a nail polish of the highest order. Not only is it fabulously expensive, but it is made in extremely limited quantities.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you, and Vera, just happen to both use it? That can't be a coincidence!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm guessing it's not a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's simple. Ariadoney is the best nail polish one can buy, correct? Then, if one wanted the best nail polish, one would buy it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That makes sense! Why, it's a bit like my feelings toward my brand-name gavel here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And my silk top hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Are we all done showing off our refined tastes?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Please, continue with your tasteful testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I have been in solitary confinement for half a year. How could I poison her?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can't you still make contact with the outside world in solitary?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, so he had an accomplice on the outside? Is this your latest accusation?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I am allowed a certain modicum of letter writing.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But the contents of those letters are closely checked. It would be extremely difficult to send a hit request!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Prosecutor Gavin's on the warpath, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... You think so, too, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I bet I know why. He must be nervous with big brother watching!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... And maybe that's a weakness I can turn to my advantage...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Are we "cool" with that? May I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Her father died of the same poison... the meaning of which should be clear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defendant is not dead yet!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There are no known cases of someone surviving atroquinine poisoning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You seem to know a lot about atroquinine.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I know a lot about a lot of things. Which is why I suggest we pick up the pace. Or else, you'll be short one defendant, for what she's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will refrain from speaking ill of the... ill!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...My apologies. Shall I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The prosecution's case holds. She poisoned her father, then attempted to poison herself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Vera had no reason to want to commit suicide! And also... ...who would commit suicide by doing their nails!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The answer's quite simple. Basically...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Allow me to explain, beginning with, "Why did she do it?" The answer's quite simple. She couldn't live with her own guilt. Next, "Why did she use nail polish to poison herself?" This, too, is simple. So she could die doing something that she liked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Something that she liked"...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Once she saw that the trial wasn't going her way, she knew she would die. And, it's not easy to bring poison into a courtroom. ...Must I explain further?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I believe that's clear enough. Crystal clear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, the two brothers together is like a two-man wrecking team!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They could use a little more teamwork, though.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Surely, you aren't going to suggest I was responsible for poisoning her father, too?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Both Vera and Mr. Misham were poisoned with atroquinine. That really can't be a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defense is repeating fallacious statements based on conjecture! The prosecution requests concrete, unambiguous proof of the witness's crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Objection sustained. The defense will please present concrete proof.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Does Prosecutor Gavin seem strange to you, too? It's like he's all grown-up...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think that's how prosecutors are supposed to be, actually. <thought>Though he is acting different than usual... ...I'll bet it has a lot to do with his brother Kristoph being in the room...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's make this testimony count, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Quick and painless. <thought>...My bracelet should do the trick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK... I'm questioning my ex-boss. His testimony seems water-tight... but he's lying. I'm sure I'll be able to see something... as long as I focus!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was you who killed Drew Misham.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...A bluff worthy of your new mentor, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, really? ...But you see, I saw it. Right when you said "her father, too"! Your hand tensed unnaturally, and a little devil appeared to give me the news.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... And? Let's assume, for the sake of argument, that you saw me being "tense". What does that mean? Are all tense witnesses guilty? And tell me, was Drew Misham fond of nail polish, too?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry, but there's more than one way to poison a man. You don't need nail polish to get to someone's mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, then I must be very talented indeed. You see, Drew Misham was killed on October 6... ...while I was already in my solitary confinement cell at Central Prison. If that's not an alibi, then I don't know what is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But you found a way, all the same. And I found it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is how you poisoned Mr. Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...My, my. And here I thought you'd come so far.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I admire how you, lacking any confidence whatsoever, choose to barrel on. Your defense lacks even a shred of elegance. ...Much like Phoenix Wright, come to think of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Relax, Justice. I've come this far, I must know the answer... ...How did the killer get to his victim, when the killer was in jail...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure this commemorative stamp requires no introduction.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The night Mr. Misham died, he was seen writing a letter. Atroquinine was found on this stamp, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">So am I to understand this stamp was the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, you are. Oh, and yes... ...this stamp was found in your prison cell!!!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That is all, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! P-Poison on the back of that stamp!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After Drew Misham was killed, someone paid a visit to this witness's cell. ...Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's when he found the stamp. You made Drew Misham write you a letter! That's how you killed him!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">My, my. You've upset my poor brother to the point of uselessness. Allow me to clarify this matter, Justice. All you need do is recall witness Spark Brushel's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Well, that's the thing, see. After he put his letter in that envelope... ...Mr. Misham sat there searching his desk drawer for something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His desk drawer...?</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Yes! A stamp! A so-called "Postage Stamp", end quote!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">He was "looking for a stamp". Ergo, he had no intention of using this stamp.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What I'm arriving at is that this commemorative stamp was in a frame! It was mere coincidence that he used it that night!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would... seem to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Or perhaps you mean to suggest that I can somehow manipulate coincidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He does have a point. How would this witness know if the victim was going to use that stamp? Without that, he couldn't have planned the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Really, Klavier. You should be seeing through these weak-spined bluffs by now.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's right, though... ...How could anyone have known Mr. Misham would use that stamp that night? Least of all Kristoph Gavin locked away in his cell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...it seems that the defense has run out of things to say.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You assume he had something to say in the first place. I believe the defense's bluff... has been called.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The "defense's bluff"...? I'm not sure I agree with you there... Kristoph.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">K-Klavier...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Honestly, I wanted to believe you. But the defense wasn't trying to get away with a bluff. You were, Kristoph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What are you saying? ...Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Forehead. What was your accusation again...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh!? Oh, it was that...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">..."This poisoned stamp killed Drew Misham"... ja? To which my brother responded thusly: "There was no way to know "when" Misham would use the stamp."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's right. Which is why it couldn't have been planned...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Tell me. It needs to be "planned"... why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why couldn't it have been a "coincidence"? The defense's case is simply that Drew Misham died by that stamp. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Coincidence"...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Kristoph, you tried to slip out from under his accusation by changing the subject! If that's not bluffing... what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... What are you up to, Klavier?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I could ask you the same question, Kristoph.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Heh... ...I silenced the defense with the fewest words possible. It's called "efficiency".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But Mr. Gavin! That's impermissible testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Very well. I shall take his claim head-on, then. ...Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You accuse me of Drew Misham's murder, yes? Then, allow me to ask you: What possible reason could I have to kill a painter?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Motive! He's talking about a motive!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed. It's hard to see how an attorney could come to want to kill a painter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now here's something: why didn't he bring up the motive from the very beginning? ...Unless he was afraid it was a battle he might lose...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So... what does it mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It means there might be a weak spot! Maybe I have some evidence to prove a motive...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A motive for murder. This is a vital, if not the most vital element in this case. Please consider this when making your statement.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'd say it's about... this vital.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's... pretty vital.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm going through with this no matter what!</thought> ...Understood, Your Honor. I'd like to present evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, let's see what you have for us. What reason did Kristoph Gavin have for wanting to murder Drew Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... Bravo, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The way you present erroneous evidence with such numbing lack of skill. To think changing mentors would cripple you so.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Allow me to present you with a numbing penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hang in there, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Drew Misham had another "business" besides painting. Add a "lawyer" to that... and the puzzle is complete.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! I'm plenty numb now... Can I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kristoph Gavin's motive becomes clear... ...when we consider why the stamp came to Drew Misham's studio in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And why was that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Forgery, Your Honor. Go back seven years. Drew Misham accepts his first job creating forged evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've... seen that before! A page from a diary, wasn't it? Magnifi Gramarye's diary.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, when attorney Phoenix Wright lost his badge, yes. ...This was the "evidence" he presented. To his loss.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...This evidence is a fake, yes. But did Mr. Wright request the forgery be made? That was never proven!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The defense attorney on that case was Phoenix Wright. Who, other than him, drunk with the prospect of victory, could have done it? And why would they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Just out of curiosity... ...do you remember this letter? This is the first page. ...And this is the second.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Those were presented in court yesterday. This letter was sent to Drew Misham by the client who requested that forgery.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The "enclosed stamp" was none other than the poisoned commemorative stamp! Drew Misham drew his last breath just the other day. However! The motive for his murder was already seven years old!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Seven years old...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The client who requested this forgery was very cautious. He tried to erase anything... and anyone with connections to the forgery!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...To keep them from talking?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But he made a mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...The stamp was a picture of my favorite magicians... so I kept it...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Father took me when I was very young... ...It was a great magic show. I loved it so much...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The killer's "time bomb" was delayed. The poisoned stamp was sealed within a glass frame... ...where it sat for seven whole years.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Forehead. Do you understand what you're telling us?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The one who schemed up the forged diary page was the one who poisoned the stamp. And it was Phoenix Wright who presented the forged evidence seven years ago. Adding the two statements together, the one who schemed to kill Drew Misham... ...was none other than Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry, but that's not how this is going to go down.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? Then how will it "go down"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I checked through the records on that case... when I found this. ...Seven years ago, just before the trial began...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh... Old boy! Um, uh... Here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I dunno! I just got it over there in the hall. They told me to give it to the "old boy in the blue suit with the spiky hair".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And one more thing...</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">I'm... sorry to have sprung this on you so suddenly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I received the files from your previous attorney only yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">...I understand I am asking the impossible of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well, you haven't really told me what happened yet! All we did... was play cards.</line>
<line speaker="Enigmar">And that was enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Phoenix Wright was put on the case the day before the trial started. He didn't have time to request a forgery!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The day before...!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now here's a question. Just who was Shadi Enigmar's previous defense attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No... Th-This can't all be...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But it is all true. There was another man, a defense attorney with a badge on his collar... ...it was you! Kristoph Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! W-What is the meaning of this, witness! I mean, defendant! Er, former lawyer!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Let me begin by denying this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's easy enough to look up, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">And impossible to prove if you can't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Attorneys are registered with the court the day before the trial begins. In other words, no record remains in the court. How exactly did you intend to prove Phoenix Wright's claim?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That would be difficult. I'm afraid this line of inquiry won't yield...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Forehead. Are you sure you don't have evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong with Prosecutor Gavin? He looks clammy!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Evidence! Evidence that shows this man, Kristoph Gavin, requested that forgery seven years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Klavier...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Just... prove it! Clear up these doubts now, or I swear, I'm off this case!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...He must have thought of some evidence, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Prosecutor Gavin looks like he's in physical pain! That darkness... ...I have to pull that darkness out of him... And proof is the only way I can! What proves Kristoph Gavin's link to Drew Misham!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? You claim Kristoph Gavin requested a forgery of Drew Misham seven years ago! Prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It can be proven.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... Simply ridiculous. Why even discuss it? This "evidence" does not...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Are you... telling the truth, Apollo Justice...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I am.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Then... I say we give him the benefit of the doubt!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But, if you're wrong about this... ...be prepared for a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Your Honor. You do the defense an injustice. Mr. Justice is clearly passionate about his claim. Should the penalty not match his passion?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... haven't given a penalty like that in a long time. Well? Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Fine, Your Honor. <thought>All I have to prove is any kind of link. Something that ties Kristoph Gavin to Drew Misham... And... I have something that clearly does the job.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well, Mr. Justice. Present your evidence! Show us the link between our witness and Drew Misham!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... What say you, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, yes... What was your name again? Apollo Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Your point?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I was thinking you should have it changed to "Forgery". ...It suits you far, far better.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Forgery Justice...? That's not so bad!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>In other words... wrong evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Most unfortunate. Might I suggest changing it to "Penalty Justice"?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Way to go, Herr Pen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, a new nickname already. Time to rethink my evidence... carefully!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence proves there's a link!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">That... scrap of paper? I'm afraid I can't let you submit that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is there some problem?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">There is. How could you possibly have that? You couldn't.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! That's Daddy's handwriting...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Wright's handwriting!? What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah, I see now. Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean "of course"?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I just remembered I had a visitor yesterday. Phoenix Wright came to my cell... except I wasn't there.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Phoenix Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">When I returned, I saw he had something of mine in his possession. Of course, I had no intention of letting him get away with reading my private mail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mail...? You mean, this letter was in your cell?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...No. However, it appears Mr. Wright has yet to be cured of his bad forging habit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if it's a forgery, it's not a very good one. The handwriting's terrible!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is Mr. Wright's reproduction of what was written in the real letter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Reproduction"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When Mr. Wright visited Kristoph Gavin's cell... ...he brought with him a small video camera.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He recorded his entire conversation with you, Mr. Gavin. And the contents of your "personal" mail!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...! R-Regardless. This mockery of a piece of evidence will never be accepted by the court. Evidence based on a "video" a man with no authority whatsoever "claims" he took... ...A man who happens to be an ex-attorney suspected of forgery!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor... Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">As embarrassing as this is for me to say... ...I'm afraid my brother is incapable of making rational judgments at the moment. Your Honor. ...Your decision, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... The defense's claim is denied.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Only actual evidence is permitted in a court of law. Please remove the defense's "evidence" from the record.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Better luck next time, Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is... a commemorative stamp of Troupe Gramarye. But Mr. Wright wrote this letter himself. Based on the video, right? Did he go out of his way to find an identical stamp and put it on here? Seems like a bit of wasted effort if you ask me...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo. It's not addressed to Kristoph!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, you're right. ...I guess it makes sense. It would show a connection, if it was. And, for the killer, it's kind of the murder weapon. I doubt he'd give out his real name along with his address.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, good point. How sneaky!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Murder by mail... That's a scary thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we've certainly taken a detour from our cross-examination... ...but, the defense appears to be lacking proof. I'm forced to end the cross-examination of Kristoph Gavin at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Apollo! Do something...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm thinking! But... without evidence... ...I don't have anything I can use on him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. This ends the special witness's cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...The show's over, yet the crowd screams for more. Only now do I understand why.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Frankly, I'm relieved. This has been bothering me for seven whole years. And I'm tired of the whole youthful angst scene. ...Now's our chance. Let's clean out the family closet, eh, Kristoph?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Klavier... You're spinning out of control. Calm yourself before you say something you'll regret.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Spinning out of whose control? Mine? ...Or yours?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Take a moment to consider everything you've built. Your reputation as a prosecutor... your fame with the masses. You could lose it all, Klavier.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Did you see that? He's trying to press Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin! Try to remember... ...what's really important to you!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You amuse me, Herr Forehead. I couldn't forget what's really important to me, even if I tried.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In fact, I haven't. Not even once. Seven years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Finally. You just couldn't resist, could you, Herr Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Resist what? Presenting solid evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Might I request we put the current cross-examination on hold? The prosecution would like to call a new witness.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...State your name and occupation for the record.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm familiar with the trial. I've watched the video several times.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Didn't you find anything "unnatural" about it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unnatural?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, you did seem unusually well prepared. I mean, Mr. Wright had only just presented his evidence. And the next moment you call in Drew Misham. It was almost as if...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Almost as if"... what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Funny, it didn't even occur to me to wonder... ...But now that I do, I see there's only one possible explanation!</thought> Almost as if... from the very beginning... ...you knew Mr. Wright was going to present that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I knew that if I applied the usual pressure... ...Phoenix Wright would eventually come up with that forged diary page.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Don't do this, Klavier.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I knew because you told me, Kristoph!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh... Whaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was the night before the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Klavier.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Kristoph...? Odd seeing you at the prosecutor's office the day before the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Ah... I won't be appearing in the trial, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Huh? Why not...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I won't be facing off with you on your first trial, apparently. ...But in exchange, I brought information.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Information...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">The attorney who'll be there in my place tomorrow is not to be trusted. Don't even give him the benefit of your respect. Listen... ...I want you to call in a special witness. Then... ......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I wondered about it at the time. "How did Kristoph know so much?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Kristoph! We were supposed to face each other in that trial! A fair fight, brother to brother! I deserved that much! You let me borrow the victim's belongings... ...You showed me all your research on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The victim's "belongings"...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which would have included Magnifi's diary... wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">My, my, Klavier. You disappoint me. You find trees, yet miss the forest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're the one missing the forest, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You can't sweep this under the rug. Not anymore. Tell me what was going on behind that trial!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...... ...Why not? I've achieved what I came here to do. I see no harm in a little reminiscing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think we're finally going to shine a light on the black belly of this thing, Trucy. We've done everything we could. I hope it's enough.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Seven years ago... the day before the trial. I visited the detention center at the request of my client, Zak Gramarye.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...To be honest, I don't know what his reasons were to this day. As far as I could tell... ...he dismissed me as his representation... because I lost in a game of poker. I can come to no other conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy used to say something. "If you want to know a man, you have to compete"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Zak wasn't watching his points, or the cards. He was watching the man behind the cards... Kristoph Gavin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">I couldn't believe it. Phoenix Wright...? A second rate attorney who relies on luck and bluffs! He dismissed me... and went with that pitiful excuse for a man? ...He deserved to die for that error alone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> So, the one who requested that forgery was...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Oh, I'm not admitting to anything. My point is... ...these two men shamed me, and I could not forgive that. Phoenix Wright and Zak Gramarye both deserved what they got.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So you asked Mr. Misham to forge that evidence... ...so you could "win"! But then, when you were dismissed as Zak Gramarye's attorney... ...you used your forged evidence as a trap!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You fed me information about the forgery you made. ...Then you gave your dirty evidence to him!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">You're free to imagine what you will. My point... is that all I had imagined came to pass. Everything went perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ha ha ha... Incredible. If I wasn't laughing... I'd weep.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Perfectly"...? You're mad, Kristoph. Stop fooling yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">What are you talking about, Klavier?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Tell me, how did that trial end?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Cancelled... when the defendant vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah. I get it. So, Kristoph... ...you've been living in fear for seven years!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...What...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were afraid your forgery would be revealed, and your reputation trashed! You couldn't leave things to chance... ...so you watched everyone involved with the case, for seven years!</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">You know, he always felt like he was being watched? That's what he said. Every day, for seven years.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">But I felt it, too! "Journalist Sure He Is Being Watched", end quote. Don't you wonder why Zak Gramarye got rubbed out after seven years... ...right after coming into contact with me!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Wait just a minute! Zak Gramarye was seen by this reporter? How is that possible!? Was he alive after being gone seven years!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... <thought>Finally... I knew this moment was coming... I just didn't think we'd get here so fast. Zak Gramarye... gone missing for seven years... Trucy's father!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo! Go get him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Right. Leave it to me. Allow me to refresh the court's memory. Six months ago, Kristoph Gavin was charged with murdering a "mysterious traveler".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I remember him quite well. Shadi Smith, was it? Poisoned in a Chinese restaurant... Tragic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The details don't really matter right now. What matters is... that traveler was Zak Gramarye!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Keep going! We'll talk about it later!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Did... she already know?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Someone please explain this! ...Mr. Justice! Can you explain this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It all started seven years ago... ...The great magician, Magnifi Gramarye's death started it. Magnifi Gramarye's death, and his student, Zak Gramarye, the suspect. Whoever defended Zak in court successfully would be famous beyond belief. ...Thinking that, Kristoph Gavin did the unthinkable. He forged evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Drew Misham?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, it was his daughter, Vera, who really did the work. You took precautions when you had that forgery made, didn't you, Mr. Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Precautions...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...To keep people from talking, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's when you planned your poisoning of the forgers.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Atroquinine... ...applied to a commemorative stamp.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, luck was on Mr. Misham's side. The bomb didn't go off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His daughter...! She saved him by taking the stamp... I see!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...But that wasn't the only bomb he set up.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The Ariadoney nail polish, ...of course!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You noticed something when you requested that forgery. When Vera Misham is nervous, she has a bad habit... ...a tendency to bite her nails.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That nail polish... was her "good luck charm".</line>
<line speaker="Drew">She was almost kidnapped, once. Since then, she's been... Well, you can see for yourself. She refuses to leave the house.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">That person gave me... a good luck charm. For when I absolutely had to go outside. It protects me.</line>
<line speaker="Drew">Yes, apparently, she received something... a gift. She won't tell me what it was. It was from that client... the one who wanted that note made...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was his insurance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Insurance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As long as she lived quietly at home, there was no danger to her. But what if she had to go outside!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If she ran into any trouble, she'd become nervous... ...and the nail polish would do the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His time bombs sat there for seven years. And then... they went off almost simultaneously.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">If you're finished... ...may I return to my cell now? I'm not accustomed to standing for such long periods of time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin! Have you heard a single thing we've said!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Oh, I listened quite closely to your little tale. Quite an entertaining piece of fiction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Klavier. Surely you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...... We're back to the evidence. The lacking evidence. Nothing proves a link between him and the atroquinine that took Drew Misham's life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about the restaurant? You killed Zak Gramarye! To keep him from talking!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I killed no man of that name. Read over the report again, if you like. The victim was a traveler by the name of Shadi Smith, about whom we know little else. You can't seriously think I knew he was that particular fugitive...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">OK, then why did you kill him!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...I plead my right to remain silent. Remember, this court did not convene to put me on trial. The defendant's name is "Vera Misham", suspected in the murder of her father. ...My trial's been finished for six months now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid we have strayed considerably from our purpose here. This court concurs with the witness. It is defendant Vera Misham who is on trial here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No! But you were doing so good, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As long as there is no evidence to support the accusation against him... ...this course of inquiry cannot find Vera Misham innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! Phoenix Wright spent seven years collecting this evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...You still don't get it, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Let us assume there was poison in the nail polish. Who then, was responsible for causing Vera Misham to bite her nails?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">It wasn't me, I know that much. The one who brought that poison to her lips... was you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha... Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...Evidence is everything. There is nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I believe this discussion has reached its conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice... ...you have performed admirably well for a novice attorney. I respect your partner, Phoenix Wright's determination as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">However... ...without direct proof, you have nothing. Isn't that right, Klavier?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Unfortunately... yes, Kristoph. You're right. ...That is, you would've been right, until now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Did the news not reach your desk in solitary? The eyes of the nation are on this courtroom today. ...This is the trial case for a new judicial system.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! That's right! <thought>I'd totally forgotten!</thought> The Jurist System!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Jurists, you say...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The current judicial system has been deemed too "closed off" from society. This new system attempts to inject the wisdom of common citizens into the law.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Common citizens? Wisdom? Is this some kind of a joke? What could we possibly gain by doing this? Entrusting our judicial system to a mindless, emotional mob of irrational mouth-breathers?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Common citizens have something called "common sense". Common sense is not restricted by the law.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Nonsense! There is only room for two in this court: Me, and the law! Keep the riff-raff out! Out, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're not in the court, actually. They're watching everything by video camera.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">H-How can you... allow this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Incidentally, the one responsible for making this happen... ...was Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Phoe... Phoenix Wright...? So... Everything was leading to this. Of course... Right... Wright.. Wright... WrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrriiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiGGGGGGGGGGGGgggggggGGGGGHhhhHHHHHHHHHHhhhhHHHHhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhHHHHHHHHHHHTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTTT I won't accept... I can't accept... This is no court! Law...! The law is everything! Law is absolute! You'd let ignorant swine soil your courts?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Kristoph... It's over.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">K-Klavier!!!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The law is "absolute"...? You can't be serious.</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Odd. I thought you spent your life looking for loopholes? The law isn't absolute. It's filled with contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The law is the end product of many years of history... the fruit of human knowledge! Like a gem, polished to a gleam through trials... and errors. It is this fruit we receive, and pass on, and face in our time. And it is always changing, growing. Nurturing it is our task as human beings.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Except for you, Kristoph. You aren't changing. You've stopped. You're not needed anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I couldn't think of anything to say. Maybe... because I still haven't seen enough. But someday, I'll know what law is. And I'll fight to change it if I have to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see no need to further prolong this trial. This began as the trial of Vera Misham, accused of murdering her father... ...the painter, Drew Misham. However... ...several other incidents were reviewed, and we seem to have reached a conclusion. ...... Before this court declares a verdict, I await your decision. ...Jurists of the court. For the death of Drew Misham, how do you find the defendant, Vera Misham? Innocent...? Or guilty...? ...I turn to you now to consider this matter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If a decision cannot be reached today... ...it may never be reached. The factors involved are simple. Did the defendant poison her father that night...? If so, she is guilty. Or was there another reason for Mr. Misham's death? Did another person poison him? If so, she is innocent. A panel has been provided for each of you to input your decisions. That is all...</line>
<line speaker="No. 6">Please... Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, Jurist No. 6?</line>
<line speaker="No. 6">There's something in the Jurist's Handbook here: "Persons involved with the case may not be jurists."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That is correct. I've looked into all your dossiers. None of you were involved with the development of the case.</line>
<line speaker="No. 6">With the "development of the case"...? I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Does that answer your concern?</line>
<line speaker="No. 6">......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's time for your verdicts. Make your decision in the case against Vera Misham! After seven years... the truth is ready to be heard. ...... Judge wisely. Judge well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Vera!!! I'm so glad, I...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't cry, Apollo! ...I'm happy, too. And proud. You did well, Apollo. When I thought about... what if Vera... I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey now, don't you start crying, too! Um... sorry you had to see us like this.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">V-Vera...?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...Thank you so much. Apollo, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I'm sorry... I shouldn't have pressed you like that... If... If I hadn't you never would have bitten your nails!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">No... I was wrong. Staying locked inside like that... clinging to my "good luck charm"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Vera...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...When I opened my eyes, and saw you... I finally understood. It's important to be a part of the world... ...to see things with your own eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It looks like that poison had some effect after all. It killed off whatever was holding Vera back from life.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I knew you'd pull through, Vera! I mean, that's what Apollo was fighting for the whole time! Your future!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I won't forget it. Here, let me thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, really, it's OK...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooh! Look! It's me! I love it! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is that... me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She really captured your essence, Apollo! Well, I think so, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">That reminds me... ...do you know where the other lawyer is...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The other lawyer...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! You mean Daddy. 'Cept he's not a lawyer anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...It's my fault, isn't it? I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! No, no, no, that's not what I meant...</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...No, it's OK. I'm through looking away from the things I've done. I hope I can look him in the eyes again someday and apologize.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm sure he'd be happy to hear that.</line>
<line speaker="Vera">He... brought all those things for me... when he came to visit... earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean that stack of videos? <thought>...Mr. Wright finished watching them all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know, I knew my real daddy was alive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was there, seven years ago, remember? I was the one who helped him "vanish" from the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You did wha... How?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not telling! ...He promised me, that day he went away.</line>
<line speaker="Zak">We may not meet again for some time, Trucy... ...but know this, I will be watching. And, one day, I shall return. ...You're the next Gramarye, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... Trucy... <thought>In the end... he couldn't keep that promise, could he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's OK! Phoenix is my daddy now. Even if he can't really play the piano.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That he can't...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Oh, and I've got you, too! Even if your voice is kinda loud sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Glad I made your list.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! Come to think of it... ...where is Daddy? The one who can't play. Do you know, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think he said he had to meet someone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. I wonder... ...Maybe it's a new mommy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vera">Tee hee... Oh, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm? Yes, Vera?</line>
<line speaker="Vera">I was wondering... Could you show him to me once more? ...Sir Hat, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, he's not been knighted. ...Yet! Here goes... do us an impersonation, Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">...<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>!! ...Ahem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not loud enough. And I like Ms. Magic Underwear better, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's "Magic Panties", Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... Your memory's returned.</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright... was this all a part of your plan, too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="???">When I lost my memory, I was reborn... as Lamiroir. But, you knew my true identity, did you not? ...That is why you chose me as one of your jurists.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, you're thinking into it too much. ...Besides. There was no guarantee that regaining your memory would make you happy.</line>
<line speaker="???">Of course it is a happy thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="???">For so long, I thought I was alone... ...but now I know I have children. Two dear children. I'm so proud of them... This, too, I think, is thanks to you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you going to tell them?</line>
<line speaker="???">They do not know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. They don't know their mother. They don't even know they're siblings.</line>
<line speaker="???">I will go to them... when the time is right. Until then, I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't worry, I'll take care of them for you. They're... They're very important to me, too. ...A little annoying at times, but still. <thought>I have to keep an eye on her, at least. Because I'm the only one who knows how she really feels... on the inside.</thought> ...Your bracelet.</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've seen a lot of mysterious things these past seven years. ...But your bracelets were the strangest of all. I remember meeting him, half a year ago now, in Kristoph Gavin's office... ...and then I met you. Two fates destined to intertwine... and I was there when they crossed. I'll never forget that.</line>
<line speaker="???">...... Such a small thing, that bullet. Yet it tore who I was away... Ten years ago... During a simple rehearsal... It was a miracle no one died... but "I" didn't survive that accident. That is why I left the troupe... my family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......</line>
<line speaker="???">Now, my memory has returned. I am myself once more. For the first time... I am glad to be alive, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Speaking of miracles. Vera Misham regained consciousness this morning. I can only hope she's as glad as you are.</line>
<line speaker="???">It is... a strange thing, fate. Sometimes a life is taken. Sometimes a life is spared.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know what I've been thinking? People don't die that easily, really. ...As long as they've got something worth living for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And that's pretty much the end of my story. For now, anyway. I've still got a long way to go. And this power of mine... well, it needs some work. But... there's hope now. We'd lost it, but somehow, we found it again. That's why people are smiling again... Hope. Yeah, I think I'll keep at this lawyer thing for a while. Oops, training time. Gotta go. Chords of Steel... here comes Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm glad you're staying with the agency, Apollo! It's like.. like I've found my long-lost, big, little brother! Oh, and don't you worry about Troupe Gramarye! Trucy's on the case! ...Now that I've have this, thanks to Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Trucy Gramarye? Frankly, I got my doubts. But Hat Gramarye? Now that'll pack 'em in!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's not every day you get a trial that rocks harder than one of our gigs, ja? That's why it's over! The Gavinners are breaking up. ...The news caused a run on tissues at supermarkets nation-wide. You're the real stars, now! I look forward to our next jam session.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's finally over. You know, thinking about it... ...I've been a piano player longer than I was a lawyer. Now that everything's sorted, and I've got time on my hands, maybe I'll take some lessons. ...Or maybe I'll take the bar exam... again.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...So, I was standing around, eating Snackoos the other day... ...when I got this crazy idea! What if they were... golden!? You could augment the crunch, or better yet, make them ding! Ah... the power of science! ...Although the preservatives might not be 100% safe...</line>
<line speaker="Olga">In unlikely event you are wanting Russian feast, come to Borscht Bowl Club! The only thing colder than restaurant... is borscht! Dah, but if greater challenge is being required... ...then come to the Hydeout. You know who to ask for!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">So, Kitaki Pastries is getting back to its Eastern "roots". Spread the culture, and all. Yo, Boss! Culture time!!!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...This is how we write "root", capice?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">But we're still about giving back to the people! Yo, Boss! P.R. time!!!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...And this is how we write "people", alright?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Not that Wocky's paying any attention. Whoooh... Kids...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Bizzoy! Chinese characters on cake was a fly idea like 3,000 years ago. Believe dat! Man, you wanna make it today, you gotta keep it real, you know what I'm saying? Yo, that's why I made the "O. G. Cracker". Fo real! I KNOW it don't look like no cracker, G. What, you want me to call it the O. G. Muffin!?</line>
<line speaker="Eldoon">...I don't know where all this talk about food is coming from. You ask me, there's only one food, and that's noodles. Noodles forever! I got a new one, too. See this time, I just put a big chunk of salt in the bowl! Why pretend? Eldoon's Noodles is about the salt! Salt forever!!!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">My exceptionally inquisitive nature has won me unequivocal adoration in my department. You see, they used to call me Wesley Stinkler. And Wesley Stickyhands. But no longer. I have a new name, one that reflects my true academic nature... ...Wesley Sicko, reporting! Yes, curiosity is a sickness, and I am the cure!</line>
<line speaker="Lamiroir">I don't know how to thank you for all you've done. Light has returned to my life, and with it, joy. I may have lost years, but I have gained a treasure. ...Two treasures, in fact. I will think of them when I write my next song.</line>
<line speaker="Brushel">Brush-a Brush-a Brushel! Brush-a Brush-a Brushel! Brushel here, back on the beat with another interview! Eh? How do I feel about how things turned out? "No Scoop Yet But Journalist's Confidence In Mint Condition", end quoooooote!</line>
<line speaker="Vera">...I've decided to keep painting. Originals only, of course. ...I suppose I'll have to see a bit of the world outside to find what to paint. ...But, I know there are good people out there now. I've met them. ...The door is open. The world is waiting. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Gavin! You're nervous about something!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...There is that finger pointing at me so rudely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kristoph">...And that desperate gleam in your eyes. It's quite disturbing, actually. Perhaps because you have no faith in your own logic? ...Which is why you cling to your dubious "power".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Confident or not, I've come a long way, Mr. Gavin. Just a little more to go. ...I need a "word". There must be some word that sends shivers down his spine...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Vera Misham...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender herself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>