<xml>
<title>Turnabout Corner</title>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is it, the big day! Did you get any sleep?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I went to bed at 1:00 AM or so.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? What time did you wake up?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...3:00 AM.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's only two hours, Apollo... But, at least you have me! ...And the Amazing Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Here's looking at you, kid.</line>
<line speaker="???">Good luck today, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That voice...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heya. Get any sleep?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was going out of my mind with boredom, so I signed myself out earlier today. Somehow, that place makes fake piano playing at the Indochine pasta joint seem almost fun.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! Do you know who Prosecutor Gavin's witness is today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a guess!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... How about Little Plum?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha! That Sherman tank of a mom? Nope, guess again.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's too bad. You know, speaking of moms... You need to find me a new mommy one of these days, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's barely morning and you're at it already, Trucy! Ah ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, see, this is why I don't buy their "father-daughter" relationship.</thought> So, Mr. Wright! Do you know who the prosecution's witness is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Alita Tiala. Your client's fiancée.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's going to be a witness!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But that seems odd... Why would she testify against her own fiancé?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have to wonder what Gavin's up to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something's going down today, that much is clear!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, not to worry. I've got my panties back. If we can't find a killer, I'll pull one out of there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Wocky Kitaki.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Prosecution is warmed up, and it's a sold-out house.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, to recap... While yesterday's witness seemed more guilty than any other party...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guilty of panty-snatching!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">We did find out one thing for certain. There were three people in the park at the time of the murder: The witness, the victim, and the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Correct, Herr Judge. And today, I'd like to do something a little new age. I'd like to look at this horrible crime... from the outside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The "outside"...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The acquisition of the murder weapon... The preparation for the act... Our poor defendant told all, you see. ...To his betrothed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His... bee trove?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...His fiancée, Herr Judge. His partner for life... with no chance for parole.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, you may show the erm... "lucky" lady to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Your name and occupation, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Alita Tiala. My occupation... is future wife.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, traditional values! I respect that. Too many brides these days can't even weave baskets blindfolded... underwater. Yet you're here today as a witness for the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">To be honest, I didn't want to testify at first. But... I couldn't hide the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Honesty! Another admirable trait.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Fräulein, is it true that, on the day of the crime... ...the defendant, Wocky Kitaki confessed his plans? His plans... for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will please give her testimony to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">It was the day that the family health check-up results came back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, the pistol did belong to the Kitaki Family, then...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes. With regards to this, an investigation is underway at the Kitaki mansion... ...on charges of the possession of illegal firearms.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the bullet that took the victim's life? Was it...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Fired from the pistol the defendant procured? Yes, this has been proven.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How can you prove something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bullets carry marks from the barrel that fired them, called "rifling marks".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Rifling marks...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Think of them as being a gun's fingerprint, left on every bullet it fires.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And when did you first hear about Wocky's plan?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">It was the day of the murder. I... I should have stopped him! I just didn't think he would actually do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. The defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">It was the day that the family health check-up results came back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was the day of the murder, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes. Everyone in the Family received their check-up results that day. When Wocky looked at his, his face went so pale...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But of course. He had just found out he had a bullet in his chest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you were there at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes... Poor Wocky...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">When Wocky found out that Dr. Meraktis had lied, he flew into a rage.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must have been, um, quite frightening.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He was furious! He ripped his report up into shreds...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Incidentally, I had to request another copy to file as evidence. A bothersome chore, but one I performed without complaint.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wocky's at an age where he's hard to control when he loses his temper. Of course, that little bit of instability is so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, now he sounds like a psychopath...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">"I'll teach him!" he said. He took one of the Family's pistols...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, is it easy to take a pistol out from the house?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Not really, I think. There's a system in place to limit access. But Wocky's a special case, being the next-in-line.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps his treatment was a bit too special, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Well, maybe he is a bit spoiled... I hear he got amazing presents for his birthdays. Last year was a switchblade made out of chewing gum and a chocolate gravestone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like he has a taste for sweets... and danger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The point here being that Wocky had access to a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...And, you already know what happened that night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"What happened"... meaning the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I tried to stop him, I really did! But Wocky wouldn't listen...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Our defendant was nothing if not determined, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The last thing you should do is blame yourself, miss!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I... just don't see how anyone but Wocky could have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How can you say that for certain? How!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead, you will refrain from badgering the Fräulein. It was the defendant... erm, Wocky, was it... who took the pistol from his home. We know this for a fact now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose we do.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, how could anyone else have used this pistol to shoot the victim? They could not. Simple logic, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That does seem to be the case. Does the defense have anything to say regarding this point?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could someone else have used that pistol...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure there was another person who could have used that pistol... ...... I just can't think of who.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Of course. He was the only one with access.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh oh, this is bad if I leave it like this...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Was there really no one else with access to that pistol? Someone else with Family ties...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Based on your testimony, there was clearly another... One other person had access to that pistol!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What's this...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Interesting! Let's ask the defense then... Tell the court who this other person with access was!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaa--! The Boss and his wife!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, an unexpected ploy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! That can't be right! Why would they want to frame their only son!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">On his parents' behalf, I'd like to give you a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carry on, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...He's speechless, Apollo. The judge is speechless.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha... Herr Forehead, our judge is silent. Perhaps you will permit me to explain why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No thanks, I think I know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then you must have been expecting this penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yowch... That didn't go so well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Poor Ms. Tiala... I can't imagine what it would be like to be in her position!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I'm a little more concerned for her fiancé. Why would she testify against him like this...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, of course, I mean you, Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...! M-Me...? But why...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were quite clear when you told the court: You heard about the pistol from the defendant on the day of the murder. In other words, you knew what he was planning.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let me get this straight... You intend to tell us that this lady stole the pistol from her fiancé... ...and killed a man in cold blood on his behalf? I've heard of people doing strange things for love, but this...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does seem a bit... unfathomable, to be sure. I'm all for romance, and for supporting your partner in life, to be sure. But I think I would hesitate at murder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd hope you'd do more than hesitate!</thought> But what if a different connection could be proven? A connection between the witness and the victim? We might find that she had a personal motive beyond wanting to help her fiancé.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hmm, that would put things in a slightly different light. What possible connection are you suggesting here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what I'm starting to think? I'm starting to think that the police never looked inside that safe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have evidence showing a connection between the witness Ms. Tiala and the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, those are... flip flops?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Sandals", actually. Ms. Tiala, do these look familiar to you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Should they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would think so. These sandals were found in the Meraktis Clinic lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't mean to say those are the witness's sandals?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He doesn't. Those sandals could belong to anyone...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the fact is that they don't. They belong to you. We found toe prints on these sandals.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Requesting permission to match the prints with the witness's feet, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Tiala, are those your sandals!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...... What if... What if my sandals were at the Meraktis Clinic. So what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">You know, I've just remembered something. I hurt my hand a few days ago, and visited that clinic. I must have forgotten them then!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So you were there as a patient?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nice try, Ms. Tiala. But the defense is in possession of evidence... ...that proves a connection between you and that clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-Whaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Evidence? Very well, Mr. Justice...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence that connects her to the Meraktis Clinic is...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, I suppose I could see--</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead. This trail you think you have found, it doesn't lead to the truth. Nor to a long career in the legal profession, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gee, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you will allow me to do the honors?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Why not? It might be nice for a change.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Most excellent... Let's rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll take the usual penalty next time, thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. Try again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That looks like... a medical chart?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Found inside a safe at the Meraktis Clinic. I'd like to draw the court's attention to the names written on the chart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What!? Ms. Tiala! Whatever... Why is your name on this chart!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, care to explain the meaning of this, Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...... I'm not sure what you mean by "meaning", Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Our warm little fiancée just froze over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I was on staff at that clinic until half a year ago. It was boring. So I quit. That's all. Is there a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Tiala! You testified that you had no connection to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">And I don't. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Now"...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I quit half a year ago, didn't I? So there's no connection. Let me guess, you're the kind of guy... ...who can't rest until he knows every last detail of his girlfriend's past. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's not true at all! Why, I... I embrace the ones I love, past flaws and all, no matte--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"There's no connection now" doesn't fly in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Doesn't... fly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's one tough nut. She probably feels right at home with the Kitakis!</thought> You left your job at the Meraktis Clinic, true... But these sandals prove that you remained connected!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Ah...! W-Well, who knows? I'm sure there are lots of people with those sandals...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So sorry, Fräulein, but your act isn't working.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your moment of hesitation just now cost you.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What's with you? I thought you were on my side!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm afraid there is no side but that which the evidence supports, Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That looks like... a medical chart?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Found inside a safe at the Meraktis Clinic. I'd like to draw the court's attention to the names written on the chart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What!? Ms. Tiala! Whatever... Why is your name on this chart!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, care to explain the meaning of this, Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...... I'm not sure what you mean by "meaning", Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Our warm little fiancée just froze over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I was on staff at that clinic until half a year ago. It was boring. So I quit.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's all. Is there a problem with that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Tiala! You testified that you had no connection to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">And I don't. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Now"...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I quit half a year ago, didn't I? So there's no connection. Let me guess, you're the kind of guy... ...who can't rest until he knows every last detail of his girlfriend's past. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's not true at all! Why, I... I embrace the ones I love, past flaws and all, no matte--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"There's no connection now" doesn't fly in a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Doesn't... fly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's one tough nut. She probably feels right at home with the Kitakis!</thought> You left your job at the Meraktis Clinic, true... But you remained connected somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. Show us evidence that proves the witness is still connected to the Meraktis Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Well, I suppose I could see--</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead. This trail you think you have found, it doesn't lead to the truth. Nor to a long career in the legal profession, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gee, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you will allow me to do the honors?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Why not? It might be nice for a change.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Most excellent... Let's rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll take the usual penalty next time, thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. Try again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These sandals were found in the Meraktis Clinic lobby. ...They're yours, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Ah...! W-Well, who knows? I'm sure there are lots of people with those sandals...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So sorry, Fräulein, but your act isn't working.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your moment of hesitation just now cost you.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What's with you? I thought you were on my side!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Perhaps you are unaware that toes leave "toe prints"? A simple analysis of these sandals will reveal all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I fail to see exactly what sort of connection this shows.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, see, that's because... <thought>...there isn't one?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I believe I understand. And I believe your wildly wandering eyes deserve a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...One more try! I'll get it this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">... Well, now we see your true colors. I was wrong to cooperate with you from the beginning! I just wanted... I just wanted you to help get Wocky back on the straight and narrow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This court thinks you need to worry less about Wocky and more about yourself. It sounds as though we need to hear a bit more about your story.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your sandals were found in the entrance to the clinic... Which means you went there on the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Well, there's little point in denying it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will tell us about this visit. Why did you go to the Meraktis Clinic that day?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I did go to the clinic that day. My first time in half a year, since I quit in January.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By "mistake", you mean... ...the mistake we heard about from the defendant? The botched operation?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He was a timid, small man... but I never wished him harm. I just thought I should let him know, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, but there is still one thing which does not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The sandals left in the lobby, of course. We can assume she wore these sandals to the clinic, ja? Then why did she not wear them home? If it were me, I would have worn them home.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would have worn those sandals home, too.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, why were the sandals left behind?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! He pointed out the contradiction before me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...There's probably a good explanation for this. Right, Ms. Tiala? ...Say, for instance... There happened to be a similar pair of sandals there which you wore home by mistake?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">... Actually, that's right. I'm impressed, Mr. Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, it is nothing. There is, after all, no other possible explanation. Ja, Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, what the...! No fair! He's filling the holes in her testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I did go to the clinic that day. My first time in half a year, since I quit in January.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Around what time did you go to the clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I don't remember exactly, but it was after 9:30, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that was the first time you had contacted Dr. Meraktis in half a year?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Of course it was. He wasn't the kind of boss you made "friends" with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, why did you go to the clinic that day?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I went to warn him. After all, I knew Wocky had the pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you want Dr. Meraktis to run away?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Well, after I failed to stop Wocky... ...I thought that was the only other way to avoid the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Couldn't you have called? Why go in person?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I called several times that evening, but no one was in.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim was busy driving home until after 9:00 PM that night, remember? This was proven by this mirror yesterday, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I thought if I warned him, he would run away for sure. Knowing the doctor...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">The doctor always was a timid man... too timid to admit his own mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean that act of malpractice on Wocky, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">If he had just told Wocky the truth in the beginning, none of this would have happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">True, that operation was the start of this whole affair.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh. Of course, if he'd told him... ...he might have been "erased" by the Kitakis much earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A disturbing thought!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We know that the Meraktis Clinic had ties to the Kitaki Family. He probably couldn't have gone to the police, even if he wanted to.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's why I knew I had to warn him!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Why else would I have gone? I'm not hiding any dark secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No "dark secrets", eh?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What? Look at me however you want, Mr. Justice, you won't find a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's hiding something, I know it! I must have some evidence that proves it, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">You're free to think whatever you like. I went to that clinic with only one thought in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This chart was found inside a safe in the doctor's office.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would this one chart be in that safe? Ms. Tiala, you know why it was, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mind filling me in?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dr. Meraktis didn't have the leisure of making "mistakes". That's why he wrote up a false report, and kept the truth locked away.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Bad Herr Doktor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this is where you come in, Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The nurse who filed this chart was you, which means... ...you knew about Wocky's failed operation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were in the same position as Dr. Meraktis! Kind of makes it hard to claim "no connection", doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">You're bold for a novice, I'll give you that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Mr. Justice, you must know I was only a nurse. The doctor is responsible for the chart's contents.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This chart business seems to be quite important. Please amend your testimony accordingly.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Too bad, little attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>My bracelet's reacting again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I felt my bracelet vibrate just now...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your bracelet...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just like yesterday. Like you said!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But... I can't see anything, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...? <thought>Then what's my bracelet reacting to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, maybe... Yes, that has to be it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What has to be it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your senses, Apollo... They must be sharper than mine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't see it, but you can sense it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know about that, Trucy! I don't have some kind of special power or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Listen to me, Apollo! There's a weak point somewhere in Ms. Tiala's testimony! But we don't know what her nervous habit is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, then what do we do!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You have to perceive it yourself, Apollo! With your eyes... and your senses!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Then it's up to me and my bracelet... I don't know why, but the bracelet helps. Somehow, touching it helps me focus. Let's give it a shot and bring down that testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Why would I go to the clinic now for a half-year-old chart?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But your signature was on that chart.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">So? What does that have to do with this case? If there was something in that chart to make me look bad, I would have dealt with it. The only one responsible for that chart is the presiding doctor... Dr. Meraktis.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's hiding something, I can smell it... And I bet she's got a habit that gives it away! I just have to focus to find her nervous habit! Maybe it's time to give my bracelet a rub...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why go to the clinic for a half-year-old chart now, you ask? But, you know why you would go "now", don't you.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I don't know what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It was quite clear, Ms. Tiala. You have a nervous habit. The moment you said the word "now"... ...you used your right thumb to fiddled [sic] with your ring.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She was unsure... I saw it! "Now"... That's the key word!</thought> The chart wasn't a part of your past... It was a clear and present threat!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's ridiculous, why if that were the case... ...I would have had six months to do something about it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which means something happened quite recently... Something to make that chart a problem for you now.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've got her on the ropes now, I can feel it! Time to strike the killing blow... with evidence!</thought> ...Ms. Tiala. There's no use trying to hide it. The chart became a threat to you now... because of this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Because of what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">The eyes of a hawk... and the brain of a toad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ribbit! I mean, ack! I can't lose this now! C'mon toad brain, one more try!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A health check-up report.. belonging to the defendant. The Kitakis are trying to get out of the business. The health check-up this month was their first ever... ...What did you think when you heard about this?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Eh? Oh, n-nothing. Why should I think anything?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? I would think you were positively beside yourself. Because you were afraid. You knew what Wocky's chest X-ray would reveal!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A full half year had passed since the operation. You thought you were home free... ...when the chart came back to haunt you!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's all, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Wh-What just happened? Did... the witness just admit to lying?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I sensed it. There was a great "aura" emanating from Herr Forehead. ...Very cool. So, the lady was lying, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's correct. She said she had no connection to the Meraktis Clinic. But her connection was deep indeed... A bit too deep. If the Kitakis got a hold of this chart with her name... ...she'd be finished. Isn't that right, Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">... You guessed it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I-I did it! I broke her testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Amazing, Apollo! I didn't see it at all! Daddy was right about you!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">It's true, that chart was bad news for me. That's why I went to meet the doctor that day! But that's all! I told him about Wocky and went home!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...It appears this cross-examination is far from over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She hid the truth from us, this is clear, yet... It is not clear that this truth has anything to do with the case at hand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. The witness will add this to her testimony. And... we'll have a bit more cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr! I was so close!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're still close! Keep on her, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We already know you're lying about having no reason!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I know you know! Don't look at me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Like I'm some two-bit washed up good-for-nothing... You scared me!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I concur. Even I am rarely treated to such a... hot gaze.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry... <thought>Maybe I need to do some face training, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I wanted to tell him to be careful, as an old friend.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, then you'd be betraying Wocky, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">No, I did it for him, for us!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She went to warn him, so that her fiancé would not have to commit such a crime, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I didn't want them to take my Wocky away...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Nothing happened at all. I warned him, and left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How did Dr. Meraktis respond to the warning?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh, he was quite surprised. Panicky, even. Who wouldn't be scared to learn a Kitaki was after them?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Incidentally, this court is not afraid of any mobsters! Why, we had a life-threatening situation just yesterday right here in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, real impressive the way you stood up to the attack of the Amazing Mr. Hat, sir...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...After which I carried you back to your chambers.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Sounds like the judge had quite a fright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>"Nothing happened" in Dr. Meraktis's office that day, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But what about the mess we found? Something definitely happened in that office, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, I know... But we can't prove "when" it happened. Nor that Alita Tiala was in any way involved...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's try putting some evidence up anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's no way she went to that clinic just to "warn" him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you know why she went, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to figure out what really happened at that clinic... and fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You say "nothing happened" in the doctor's office. I disagree. Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What's that? It looks like a squished-up ball of clay. Kind of like you, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This bullet was found in the Meraktis Clinic office. Something did "happen" in that office, Ms. Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Enough of this joking around. The police investigated that clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, but this was stuck inside the doctor's safe.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Inside the safe...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess the police didn't check that far.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...But there is a problem. How can you say that bullet was fired on that day?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Weren't you the one who explained rifling marks to us?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The pistol was taken from the Kitaki Mansion that day. If the marks on this bullet match the murder weapon... ...then that proves a firearm was discharged in that office on the day of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">... Not bad, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Have this bullet analyzed immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... It seems as though the bullet in the safe was fired from the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps the defense would like to state their position?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The bullet in that safe proves one fact: A pistol was fired in that office on that day. And at the time of the firing, the safe was open. The safe which contained the top-secret chart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you think someone was threatening Dr. Meraktis? In order to open the safe?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only one person was in a position to do such a thing. Our witness, Alita Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Mr. Justice! Where are you going with this? Are you accusing the witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alita Tiala knew about Wocky Kitaki's botched operation! She got engaged to him without telling him about it! As long as that bullet remained in his chest, his days were numbered. What if she married him, and then the bullet finally reached its destination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That reminds me. Apparently, the Kitakis have been asserting themselves in lawful business practices... They're making quite a great deal of money... a fortune, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nefarious! So she planned to marry him just to get her hands on this fortune?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You keep talking trash about my Alita... ...and I'll sue you, lawyer-man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh? Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yeah! You said... You said you'd... You'd... You'd abuse my Alita!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I think you mean "accuse"...!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Same difference! Well you can't have her! She's mine! It was me! I shot that doctor! Me! He left me to die, so I left him to die, too, there in that park!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W... Wocky! Just cool down a second, please!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You keep your hands off my Alita! Or I'll...</line>
<line speaker="???">...Tee...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Tee... hee hee ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M... Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I-I'm sorry. I just... It's been so long since I've laughed so hard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something funny?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Wocky. Wake up and smell reality!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">A... Alita-baby?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">The signature on the chart, the engagement... I mean, come on! It's so obvious. Even for a brainless, spoiled brat such as yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Alita...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your honesty is like a breath of foul air, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Hey, I wasn't getting out of this clean, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... The Family fortune is what you're really after!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's right. I wanted the money.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">No way! That's wack! I ain't trying to hear that!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Should have done the wedding earlier. Oh well. ...By the way, can I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who, me?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I believe you said you were going to abuse me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Accuse.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Of what crime, might I ask?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh, I'm a bad girl. Sure. I got close to that brat because I wanted his money. But he was the one with the pistol. He could've fired it into the safe after I'd already left the clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I would never do a thing like that. It was definitely that silly brat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, but...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T-Trucy...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You had the most to lose if that chart was found!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...But I didn't have a pistol, now did I?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">W-Well, you could have taken Wocky's!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">You'd think he'd have mentioned that, no? All I've heard him say is, "It was me! I shot him!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's only because he's trying to protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Sorry to intrude in this lovely conversation...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But the two of you are forgetting one critical point.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What... What point!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Certainly, the Fräulein wanted that chart. You assume she threatened the doctor into opening that safe. But then... ...wouldn't she have taken the chart?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You see? That chart wouldn't have been left in that safe!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He... He's right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is clear to this court that you are not a very good fiancée.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh, I'm flattered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it's time you told us the truth? Tell us about yourself, including your actions and whereabouts on that day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't forget! We've proven that you were at the Meraktis Clinic on the day of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">......</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes, I went to the clinic that day to speak to the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You went back "later"...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That chart was dangerous, you understand. I needed to get rid of it, that's why I went that day...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">But you couldn't get the chart then, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...And later that night, Dr. Meraktis was shot. I heard about the shooting, waited a day, but then I had to go back... ...No easy feat with the cops all over the place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ah! Th-That was you!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">......! Ah... Apollo! That sound... It came from behind this door!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Someone's in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A break-in! They left through that window!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you were the burglar...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That was you two? If only I had one more minute... ...then I could have opened that safe and gotten the chart!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? That's trespassing! And brazen, at that!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Oh, is this a trial for trespassing now? Besides... You can't blame a girl for wanting to protect herself... They are gangsters, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, Mr. Justice, your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Admitting the little crime to avoid the big one, eh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes, I went to the clinic that day to speak to the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why "that day"?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That brat was uncontrollable. He was ready to kill! And that would bring in the police... And that chart would become evidence... And I'd be hung out to dry... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But the police didn't check the safe, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, they thought the crime scene was the park.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'll make sure the responsible parties feel the heat... Such sloppiness won't be tolerated, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm kinda thankful for that sloppiness myself, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I wanted that chart, but I failed to get it. So I went back to the clinic later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Later"...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">When I heard what happened, well, I was too scared to do anything that day. So I waited until the day after... The 16th, was it? ...Of course, you and that meddling kid had to get in my way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But why did Dr. Meraktis keep that chart around? It was clearly dangerous for him. He could have burned it.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Because he's a coward. The chart was his insurance.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Insurance...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">My signature on that chart, to be more specific. That made sure I couldn't betray him.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">In any case, I didn't shoot him. You don't even have proof I stole that pistol, do you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you could have stolen it!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">"Could have"? Is this some new definition of proof?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll ask Wocky. He'll tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Might I remind you this is a cross-examination? You might want to keep your baseless theories to yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mmmmmnk! <thought>He's right, isn't he...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">And that brat was spotted in the park at the moment of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah, but... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">But what? You have nothing to say. This case is over. It was over the moment that brat was seen in the park! What's the point in dragging it out any further?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Frankly, I don't think it matters if Dr. Meraktis was shot in the temple or not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think we're seeing her true colors now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's trying to push all the blame on Wocky! And she's getting away with it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>My bracelet didn't react to anything this time... I guess that means there's nothing worth perceiving... Time to get old school!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor was shot in the right temple, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">So it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Let's review the facts again, shall we? If the killer shot from this location... ...the bullet would've struck our victim square in the forehead. However! The entry wound... ...was in the right temple.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, we heard testimony on this yesterday. At the time of the shooting, the witness was standing here. Just before the gun was fired, he shouted. The victim turned his head to look... and was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that testimony was proven to be a lie! Our egregious panty-snatcher, Mr. Stickler, did witness the crime... But he was standing to the north, next to the trash can where he tossed those panties! If Mr. Stickler shouted from this location, the bullet couldn't hit his right temple!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Silly, silly attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Do you remember what you had for breakfast that morning?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Do you remember, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I always have a glass of milk for breakfast.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What matters is one thing: The doctor was shot in his right temple. If that's the case, there can only be one explanation! The panties guy was mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But his location was proven! You can't write that off as him being "mistaken"!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Then why don't you show us, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Show you... what?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Must I explain everything? Very well, let's recap: If the witness, panties guy, was standing to the north... ...then where was the shooter standing? From what location did the killer shoot the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But wait! If the witness was standing there... ...how could anyone shoot the victim in the right temple?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ah ha ha ha ha! I merely laid out the facts for us. It is up to the one possessing the shiny forehead to show us. ...If you can, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wocky Kitaki was standing at the "Killer" mark... Wesley Stickler at the "Witness" mark... And of course Pal Meraktis was at the "Victim" mark...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear what the defense has to say. Where was the killer standing when they shot the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">At the "killer" mark, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In one fell swoop, we are back where we were yesterday, ja? How do you explain the wound in the victim's right temple?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Uh, that is a problem, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you, Mr. Justice, for pointing out the obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That would make Wocky the killer, Apollo! Geez!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One more time, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The killer was standing at the "Witness" mark!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would explain the wound in the victim's right temple.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So, once again, you are accusing Wesley Stickler? ...As the murderer of Pal Meraktis?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I would be, wouldn't I...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Finally, a glimmer of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Very well, Herr Forehead. Show us proof! Have you evidence that incriminates Wesley Stickler?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess he really is the most likely suspect... Do I have some evidence that shows Mr. Stickler did it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Apparently, you lack this promised evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... That wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You'll never succeed if your base assumption is faulty. Perhaps you should rethink this from the top, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe he's right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">In fact, you may want to rethink your choice of career.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hey, that was a bit uncalled for, don't you think!?</thought> Your Honor, the defense would like to reconsider!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. This penalty should help keep you on track.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As the facts stand now, we can't explain this crime... ...without contradicting ourselves at some point. But I know why. The real killer shot from an entirely different location!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What are you talking about!? I don't see any other place...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Apparently, Mr. Justice does. ...Let's hear it. Where in the park did the killer shoot the victim from?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's time to raise the roof! ...And the stakes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Penalties are such frightening things, don't you think? But what if they were a bit more... terrifying? ...Like so.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Double penalty?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Forehead wishes to take us in a new direction? Then he must be ready for the challenges ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Challenge accepted. <thought>It's Justice time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Are you sure, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The key is the witness, Mr. Stickler's testimony! If we believe that, and we know where he stood... ...and the victim turned when he shouted... ...there's only one place the killer could have been!</thought> The killer shot the victim from... here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is where the killer shot from!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But then the killer couldn't have shot his right temple.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So young, and already senile. How unfortunate...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll have you know I'm not senile! Why I remember exactly what I ate the morning of the crime! .............................. Ahem! Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...No fair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You seem intent on digging your own grave. Here, have a shovel and try again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is where the killer shot from!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. I hadn't thought of that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">None of us did, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And this explains the wound in the right temple how?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... I hadn't thought of that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An amusing diversion, Mr. Justice. Penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, amusing... like your career, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Fine, rub it in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps you would be so kind as to try again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe we all owe a debt of gratitude... ...to Ms. Alita Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks to you, we had a chance to review the crime... ...and this time, we were prepared. We know that Wesley Stickler was telling the truth! We should have listened to him from the beginning. Wesley Stickler was standing next to the trash can when he saw the two men. ...He shouted, just as he told us in his testimony. ...And the victim turned to look in his direction. A shot was fired! The victim was hit in the right temple.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh yes! Which direction was his right temple facing at that moment? That's right! Toward the noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! S-So you're saying... ...the killer was inside the noodle stand!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Let's think about this a bit more, shall we? You say the killer was "inside the noodle stand". Which would mean the victim, Dr. Meraktis came to the park... ...wheeling his own murderer in the cart behind him!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">This is the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard! I'd think you'd notice if you were pulling someone along!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something we should worry about before that! Why was he pulling the noodle stand in the first place!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let's deal with our problems one at a time, shall we? Someone was hiding in the stand... We have not come this far to talk about "possibilities". ...Let's talk about "proof", baby. Show us evidence that proves someone was in that stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Can I prove that...?</thought> You want evidence that someone was in that stand...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I've got it right here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Intriguing! Let's see what you've got.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, too bad!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Kidding! Just kidding! I've got it! <thought>...Whew, close one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Then let's see it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Show us proof that someone was hiding in the noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Thoughts, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We have a choice between Heaven... or Hell. Either our brains are damaged, or Herr Forehead's is. I wonder which it is?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...This court finds Mr. Justice's brain faulty. ...By majority vote.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... Time to pick something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">How about showing us the right evidence this time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"The Meraktis Clinic"... And they're covered with paint. These slippers were found in a trash can near the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A single slipper print was found at the scene... ...Right next to the noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Ack...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, and Ms. Tiala. Your toe print was found in the left slipper!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In other words... ...this is proof you were inside that noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet there was only one slipper mark found at the scene... ...Can this be called a footprint, in good faith?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Observe the diagram! A park pathway runs right next to the slipper mark! A slipper wouldn't leave a trace on a cobblestone path!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Yet you still cannot say this is a "footprint", ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why not!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You have an impression left by a single slipper... What if it was on the stand and simply fell to the ground?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's... That's just dumb!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">One more thing. A noodle stand is typically cluttered with the tools of the noodle-making trade. There's no room for a person to ride in there!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You have a point. Could someone have hidden in that stand?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! I think I might be on to something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think I've figured out one of our pieces of evidence! In order to make room in the stand, some things would have to be...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you have proof that someone could have hidden in the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can prove one thing. Someone did scheme to clear space in that stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I don't see how that evidence relates to the matter at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! ...That wasn't it. Maybe if I submit another piece of evidence while he's thinking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Stop right there! I think someone's "scheming" to avoid a penalty. ...We'll have none of that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oops...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Again, Mr. Justice, if you would. Your evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is a noodle bowl from the stolen Eldoon's Noodles noodle stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and what about it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We discovered a large quantity of these bowls yesterday... ...in the lobby of the Meraktis Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A large quantity of noodle bowls in the victim's clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon was very clear about those bowls.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Well, I don't care who did it! Without that stand, I'm finished! All my noodle bowls were in there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet the bowls were removed! That night, there was space inside that noodle stand! Space created at the Meraktis Clinic, no less. Right around the time that you were there, Ms. Alita Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Stooooooooooooop! I won't listen to any more of these wild fantasies! No... not fantasies... They're worse lies than that spoiled brat's pickup lines!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would like to remind the witness of her current status. This court does not consider you entirely innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Show me an innocent... I'll show you a fairy tale.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...In any case. The defense has, somehow, made its point. The witness had both a motive and an opportunity to kill Dr. Meraktis.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">More fairy tales! This whole trial is a fairy tale!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then please, pull us back down to reality, Ms. Tiala. I'm giving you one last chance to explain yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is it! Why was Dr. Meraktis pulling that stand that night...? ...And what was Alita Tiala doing inside it? Time to get to the bottom of this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">That night, I went to ask Dr. Meraktis for the chart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You knew about the botched operation... So you tried to get rid of the chart, to save yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I won't make excuses. ...And I did warn the good doctor. I gave him a chance. I told him that brat got his health check-up report. ...And that he was coming to settle the score.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. Very well. Mr. Justice, begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor. <thought>This is the last testimony! Either I perceive the truth, or it's over!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">That night, I went to ask Dr. Meraktis for the chart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you did go to steal that chart!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Were you listening? I said I "asked" him for it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The victim was a man in good health... I don't see how she could have coerced him.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">True. It would have been impossible without a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But what if she did have a pistol...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">I'll admit I wanted the chart. That much is true. ...My reason was simple.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I had no intention of ever letting that chart fall into the Kitaki Family's hands.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It certainly would have put a damper on your wedding plans, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Not only that. If the Kitakis had gotten that chart... ...I'd probably be with Dr. Meraktis now, pulling that great noodle stand in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It seems our witness was in a fix as well.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Who would want to die pulling a noodle stand?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When I die, it will be by disappearing mysteriously in the middle of a magic act!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could we be a little less morbid!? Please!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">So you see, I needed that chart.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">But Dr. Meraktis didn't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He didn't understand...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He wouldn't listen to a word I was saying! The moment he saw me, he started to tremble... Hah, I thought, what a sad excuse for a man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Please don't smile like that anymore... It's creepy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">He was practically delusional!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">For some reason, he thought the Kitakis had sent me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They "sent you"?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He thought the Kitakis had sent me to get the chart.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It makes some sense. You are their son's fiancée.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Don't make me laugh! The Kitakis? Send me? They don't play that way. If they'd known about that chart, they would have gone in there with guns blazing. But I couldn't convince the trembling doctor otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">So I gave up and went home... All I did was talk to him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If that was really all that happened... ...what were all those noodle bowls doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">How should I know? There weren't any bowls when I went, I know that much! Why don't you let me be and go look for your killer someplace else, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Do I detect uncertainty there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...This is my last chance!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo... any word from your bracelet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, actually... <thought>I felt it respond...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I couldn't see a thing! It's up to you, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Time to perceive the truth! ...Here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"All I did was talk"... and lie.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What? Show me proof!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm pretty sure about this one... I think I'm getting the hang of this. A little slip in confidence, and they give it all away.</thought> The proof... is you, Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"All I did was talk to him", you claim... Yet you can't hide your own nervous twitch when you say those words!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">My "twitch"? What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have a habit of scratching the area of your neck around the edge of your scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wha--! Wh-Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is working better than I'd hoped! Her unconscious actions tell the truth she won't say. Habits and lies... Two dots... Connect the dots and find the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">D-Don't look at me like that! I t-told you the tr-truth...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It seems that when you recall what really happened in that office... ...you can't keep your hands off your neck, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... It seems that nervous habits... ...are unconscious reactions that manifest when someone is trying to hide something!</thought> You can't hide behind your scarf, Ms. Tiala! Something happened between you and the victim in the Meraktis Clinic office!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I've got proof that shows exactly what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Alita">...I knew you were bluffing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I could tell by the way you fondled your spiky hair!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! She found my habit! I'd better rethink this... OK, when we found the Meraktis Clinic office... ...there were signs of a struggle, and a bullet in the safe. Ms. Tiala was willing to do anything to get that chart. So something happened... But what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What's that...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You're touching your scarf again.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...There's something unusual about this lamp. The bulb is broken... and there's a red splotch on the cord.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seeing how you hide your neck... I think I can come up with a plausible explanation for the lamp's state.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Well spit it out! This talking in circles nonsense is killing me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Very well. The answer is very simple. Ms. Alita Tiala... Please remove your scarf!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">! ........................ Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is a trial to determine what happened in that park. Yet we seem to have drifted off target.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We'll find out soon enough if we're drifting... As soon as the witness removes her scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I... I won't do it! This is insane! I'm a... an unrelated third party! You can't order me to remove my clothing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ms. Tiala. I'm afraid you've forgotten what's already been proven.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're hardly "unrelated". ...Please remove your scarf.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">No. Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I knew it. So I was right, wasn't I, Ms. Alita Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your neck... That isn't what I think it is!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something did happen that night at the Meraktis Clinic! You needed to get that chart back, no matter what it took. Even if you had to steal your fiancé's pistol to do it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But wait! Looking at this lamp, and the witness's neck... It looks like the very opposite happened!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. The victim in the clinic that night... ...was this witness! Specifically... ...you tried to threaten Dr. Meraktis and he attacked you! That's what happened that night at the Meraktis Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Urk......!!! Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek......................................................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Will someone please tell me what really happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I told you the truth already! I went to the clinic that night to warn Dr. Meraktis!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...That gangster knows everything! He's coming for you!</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">...Looks like my clinic's seen its last patient.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">We have to get rid of that chart! Quick, open your safe! Give it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">...So you can save your own skin?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">I know what you're up to. You want in with the Family... And if they see that chart, you're finished.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">......</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">...Leaving me holding the short straw. But if I'm going down... I'll want some company. You!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And what happened next!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He jumped at me, and knocked me to the floor! Then, he took that cord... ...Pal Meraktis was serious. Deadly serious. He really tried to strangle me. I... I must have blacked out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... you were the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And the red splotch on the cord... was your lipstick.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I... I didn't want to remember that night. That's why I didn't bring it up. There... Are you happy now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I was out cold, almost killed! And you claim I then snuck into that noodle stand... But how could I!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, one thing is clear. We now know what really happened at the Meraktis Clinic. And it would seem that our victim was not entirely without blame himself!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I... I'm sorry. I get so nervous just thinking of it, it's hard to breathe. I've told you everything. Can I go home now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You bear some responsibility for events that day, true. Yet, if you were also a victim... ...this court would owe you some sympathy. ...Well, Mr. Justice? I believe this clears up the remaining questions for Ms. Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>When did this happen!? Suddenly, everyone's sympathizing with her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't know what to think anymore, Apollo... I mean, is that it? Do we know everything we need to know about Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! This finishes the cross-examination of this...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Heh. Heh heh heh. Not so fast. This party's just getting started! Now, we rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Those spikes on your head are softer than they look... Or do you not have the stomach to go all the way?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Gavin...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Pal Meraktis choked Alita Tiala... ...She fell unconscious. But what happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's right! There is more we don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... she was choked hard enough to leave that mark! She would have been out for a while!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Even still, what if it was her in that noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Alita Tiala, half-dead... Dr. Meraktis pulling that stand... And a bullet fired from inside the noodle stand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What if it's all true!? We might have already figured out what truly happened that night!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Alita Tiala, as you can see... ...we're not through with you just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...You really want to blame me for this murder, don't you? You, too, "Prosecutor" Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Me? Fräulein, I only wish to know the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, let's go back over what we've learned up till now. On the day of the murder, Wocky saw his check-up report. ...From which he learned about the bullet still inside him. So, he took a pistol from the Family stash... ...with the intent to give Dr. Meraktis some of "his own medicine".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And Ms. Tiala heard about this from Wocky. So she went to the Meraktis Clinic ahead of him! ...In order to get rid of the chart with her signature!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But then... something happened.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Sounds like you've figured it all out. But remember, I was the victim! I was out cold.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, what about Dr. Meraktis?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That does seem to be the problem... He had just strangled Alita Tiala, perhaps, he thought, to death. What did he do after his crime?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I was just knocked out! Not dead!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">From the state of his clinic, and the scene in the park... ...I think it's clear what the good doctor did next. Well, Herr Forehead? Care to guess?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? What did Dr. Meraktis do!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe he did think he killed Alita Tiala... Do I have evidence to show what he did next...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence shows what he did next!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Shows what, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your smile has a sort of sick desperation to it, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What, this smile?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Let's try again, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...As his next move, Dr. Meraktis... ...stole Guy Eldoon's noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">What, "killing" me disturbed him that much? So much he randomly stole a noodle stand!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It wasn't so "random". Remember all the bowls in the clinic's foyer? Bowls that belonged inside that stand? I think it's pretty obvious, don't you? That stand was at the clinic. However, the question is why did he remove the bowls?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe... because the stand was heavy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or he wanted to put something in the stand in their place...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Wait, you don't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do. Dr. Meraktis did replace those bowls with something... ...your "corpse", Ms. Tiala!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">M-My "corpse"!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dr. Meraktis panicked. He thought he'd killed you...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...His next move would be to dispose of the body!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Th-That's crazy talk! You're all crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then let's think about it... logically. The doctor had a place to dispose of you in mind... ...But on the way there... ...who should he run into but the defendant, Wocky Kitaki!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I question your "logic".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The park is a dead end. Why would he head in that direction to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's right! He had no reason to go there! ...Oh, now I get it! It was a trick! That spoiled brat made him do it! He made the doctor steal the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell me... Why would someone go to a "dead end"? ...Unless the park was his destination!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Apparently, the defense has an idea. Tell us where Dr. Meraktis was heading with the stand! Here, please show us on this diagram. To where exactly was the victim dragging that stand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim was heading here!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah yes, of course. There. ...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ I'm young, Your Honor. I'm still making up my mind about a lot of things.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Perhaps you should leave the court until you grow up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Ugh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">There? That's a... a river!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. I scarcely need to explain why.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A perfect place to dispose of a body.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">H-He was going to throw me into that river!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He didn't have many other options, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe this clears up all of the remaining questions. The victim pulling the stand, and the defendant before him. ...And inside the stand, you, Ms. Alita Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And then, the denouement. Wesley Stickler, of panty-snatching fame, walks up. Seeing the two men, he shouts! In that instant...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">So... I shot him?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were the only one who could have stolen Wocky's pistol. It had to be you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, Ms. Tiala?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...... Hmph. ...Nice work.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You mean, I'm right?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I mean you've done a fine job dreaming up a story... ...to get that spoiled brat off the hook!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You're the one who's dreaming! Apollo's backed up everything he's said with facts! If you're so sure he's making it up, give us another reason! Why was Dr. Meraktis pulling that stand through the park!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Who knows? But there's one gaping hole in your logic. I think Mr. Gavin knows whereof I speak!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whereof what!? <thought>I can't believe she's still trying to deny this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Must I always be the one to point out Herr Forehead's errors?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Ack, maybe there really is something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe the Fräulein speaks of... Herr Doktor's car.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His car...?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">That's right! The Meraktis Clinic has that big garage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In which sat... a green sports car, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Why would he steal the stand in the first place!? If he wanted to carry a body, he would have used his car!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And so we find our victim without probable cause to steal that stand... ...and our defense without a case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... I have an idea! You know that green car? I bet it wouldn't run! It was broken!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, what an excellent counter-argument, Fräulein. Too bad you're quite wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Don't tell me you've forgotten what happened to your daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's right...! That night, the car that hit Mr. Wright... ...was that green sports car!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, yes! I-I'd nearly forgotten about it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Afterward, he drove it back to that garage. It ran fine.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...That's right. So why didn't he use his beloved sports car, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A glaring contradiction, to be sure. More glaring than your forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... Nooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! Well, Mr. Justice? Why didn't Dr. Meraktis use his car to carry the "body"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is that a groan of surrender I hear?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some advice: Now's a good time to review all you know. ...Everything you've learned over the last two days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Everything I've learned...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, this contradiction casts doubt on your entire case! This is truly your last chance! The defense will explain to us what happened that night!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually... It was someone else who stole that stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But then why was the victim pulling it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... Um... He would have had to steal it from someone else!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... We're back where we started, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Without an explanation for why he didn't use the car.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'll ask you again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The victim... used the car to carry the body!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, so you're throwing out everything you've proven up until now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, if the car wasn't broken...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I admire your adaptability in the face of impossible odds. Yet this does not explain why he was pulling that stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's going on...? Is Prosecutor Gavin trying to tell me something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps we need to ask you again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I have an idea... It's all coming together!</thought> ...That night, Dr. Meraktis couldn't use his car.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Hah! Now you're making even less sense than usual!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not according to my information, Ms. Tiala. Put one and one together, and the explanation is simple!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If it's so simple, perhaps you can show us some evidence? Show us proof why the car wouldn't run that night!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is proof of why the car broke down that night!? Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, it's proof of a malfunction, alright. ...A malfunction in Herr Forehead's brain.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hah, hah, very funny, guys.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! You will mend your malfunction and present evidence that makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see now... Panties!? Again!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All sorts of things come out of my panties! ...Even the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Another crime was committed the night of the murder. The theft of these panties! The latest in a string of similar thefts, actually. But that night, the snatcher was caught in the act! A brave young girl chased the thief until they hid... ...in the Meraktis Clinic garage.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh-Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The snatcher hid the panties there before running... ...Perhaps someone in this court remembers where he hid them?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why... weren't they found in the car's exhaust pipe?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Exactly. By the way, I learned something yesterday... ...A very important piece of information. ...And I learned it from you, Prosecutor Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, so you were here investigating?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And I was on my way home... when my hog gave up the ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your hog...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">My motorcycle won't start. A clogged exhaust pipe...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad! It looks like such a nice bike, too. Hard to believe that it could break just from that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Cars, motorbikes, they're all the same. Clog the exhaust, and they won't run.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">My, how interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">While Ms. Tiala and the doctor were struggling... ...the panty-snatcher snuck into the Meraktis garage. From that time, until the time we found these... ...that car wouldn't start.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Wh...What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's why Dr. Meraktis had to use the noodle stand! It was the next closest thing he could think of!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well, Ms. Tiala? This wraps your doubts up quite nicely, I think!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">... So it does.</line>
<line speaker="Alita"><thought>Where... Where am I...? So dark... Can't see... ...Cramped...! The pain... my throat's burning...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">Wh-What's your problem!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You, Doc! I know what you did!</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Alita"><thought>...Wocky?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...You lied to me! So you know what I'm gonna do? I'm gonna give you a taste of your own medicine, man!</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">W-Wait! Let me explain!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">F-Fine. I'll give you your last request.</line>
<line speaker="Meraktis">Listen, you're being tricked! But not how you think! It's not just me...</line>
<line speaker="Alita"><thought>No...! He'll ruin everything! ...I have to stop him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">C-Cease this at once, y-y-you two!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Funny. This isn't the way it was supposed to turn out. Oh well. Too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's still one mystery... How did you manage to disappear from that stand?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">In the silence after the shot, I heard the witness running...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I believe we heard as much from Wesley Stickler. He went to use a public phone to inform the police.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Which is when I made my escape.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Which is when you left that slipper print!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Dr. Meraktis didn't bother taking my slippers off. I threw them out after I stepped in that paint, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That was your mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">No. My biggest mistake... ...was coming to you for help, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I believed in you! You and your "Anything Agency"... If anyone would get Wocky declared guilty it was you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we've reached a conclusion of sorts. ...Prosecutor Gavin. How is Ms. Alita Tiala doing?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She's confessed to everything. We're processing her arrest now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prosecutor Gavin sure seems calm for someone who just lost...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think he already knew... He'd figured out she was the killer a while ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some advice: Now's a good time to review all you know. ...Everything you've learned over the last two days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He lost... but I didn't exactly win, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Hmm? Something the matter, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Looks like it's time to announce a verdict...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Great job, Apollo! You did it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, we did, somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wocky's off the hook... ...free to become the gangster he's always wanted to be! And he has you to thank...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey! Attorney-man! You're gonna pay for what you did to my Alita, homes!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Or to blame, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You give my Alita back! Stupid pointy-head attorney with a death-wish!</line>
<line speaker="???">Enough, Wocky!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Mr. Kitaki...</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...It's high time you opened your eyes, Wocky.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">What do you know, old man! I think it's 'bout time you opened yours! Givin' up the life, tryin' to become some kinda businessman!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Don't talk about what you don't understand, Wocky!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I'm afraid the guard is going to throw them both out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...If not in jail. Wouldn't that be a happy ending.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, maybe we can help them out! We know why Mr. Kitaki needs to make so much money... Maybe we should tell Wocky. Oh, Wocky? Apollo has something to tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I do? <thought>Way to put me on the spot...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Eh? Whazzat?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Show him the reason why, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why is Mr. Kitaki trying to become a business man...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about it, Wocky... Think about your condition.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I talked with your mother, Little Plum, yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">It pays... but we need a lot of money right now. Clean money, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...She doesn't mean... You aren't really... are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...Eh? You're bugging.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think that means I messed up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Wocky, I don't care what you think of me... But you should know how your mother feels.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Little Plum?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What was that she said...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">It pays... but we need a lot of money right now. Clean money, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, could she mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Wh-What's this about, old man?</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...I searched the globe. And I found one. A doctor who can take that bullet out of you, Wocky. But it's an expensive procedure.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">M-Man! B-But you got plenty of money already, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">I won't use it.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">...!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">It was the gangster life that did this to you, Wocky. ...I want to help you, and I want to do it clean. Please understand. Wocky...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">D-Dad... M-Man, I see how it is, old man! Always you looking out for... out for...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wocky...?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Listen good, old man! One day... One day... I'm gonna take you out! Then we'll see who's the O.G.! You try to hide in your business suit, I'll find you! Stupid ol' geezer!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My! Wocky!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...No, it's as it should be.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Kitaki! <thought>I liked him more without the puppy dog eyes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">I'm glad... to have met you. I'm not so good with words... But I know a professional job when I see one. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who? Me? I don't think...</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Someday... I'll bake you one of our latest... The Kitaki Lime Pie.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...He's opening a pie shop!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...So long.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And he was gone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, let's head back, Apollo! To the Wright Anything Agency!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, since when do I work at your agency!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aw, we make a good team! Don't just stand there, let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Huh... Why not. She did help me out. And there's a few questions that still need answers... Like this power of mine that she showed me... And my bracelet... If anyone can help me figure it out, it's her. Though I can't say I care much for what her father has become...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that's right! We have to go someplace first!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why, to claim our reward from Mr. Eldoon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ah, salty noodles. Right. He got his stand back already?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, and after that, you can come see my show! With a special appearance by the Amazing Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Oh, it's special alright!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please... anything but him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Tiala! You're unsure about something, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">...Not as unsure as you are.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, she sure showed you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grrr...! <thought>I've got to focus and find her habit. Find that... ...and I'll find the weak spot in her testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Gotcha, Ms. Tiala!!!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I heard you just fine the first time. What, I wasn't aware we were playing paintball.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's one cool cucumber, that Alita.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Hmm. Maybe I spotted the wrong spot. But my bracelet reacted! There must be something in this testimony! I'll find your weak spot, Alita Tiala...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Wocky Kitaki...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>