
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Academy</title>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no! I'm gonna be late! *huff* *puff* Whew, finally. So, this is it... the illustrious Themis Legal Academy. <thought>This is the place where many distinguished lawyers and prosecutors got their start. When news spread that Mr. Wright had gotten his attorney's badge back... ...he received a call from this school, asking him to pay a visit. Mr. Wright brought us along, hoping we'd learn something from the experience. But no, I had to go and blow it by getting here thirty minutes late. At least it's not all business today! After all, today's their school festival!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow! This place has school festival written all over it... literally! But why all the cold stares? Is it because everyone's in a school uniform except me? Well, I like the way I dress! Wonder where Mr. Wright and Apollo are?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sounds like a mock trial is about to start, but where's this Lecture Hall? Looks like all the students and faculty are heading that way. Might as well join them. Maybe I'll find Mr. Wright and Apollo there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>This must be the Lecture Hall. Wow, they spent some serious money on this place. The District Court can't even compete.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, Mr. Wright! Apollo! I've been looking for you two. I'm so sorry I'm late.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's okay. Sorry we couldn't wait for you. But we didn't want to be late for our meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Lucky for you, the person we're supposed to meet also seems to be running late.</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright, Mr. Justice, it seems Prof. Courte has yet to arrive. How un-professorial of her to keep visitors to our esteemed institution waiting like this! I shall make her write "I will not--" ...Oh, who do we have here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. You haven't been introduced yet.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, yes. You must be the young lady Mr. Wright was telling me about. I am Aristotle Means, a professor at this hallowed hall of teaching. I oversee the lawyer course here. It is a pleasure to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm Athena Cykes! I just recently got my attorney's badge myself! It's nice to meet you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Means">How wonderful! So vigorous and vivacious. You just earned yourself a gold star.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, thanks! <thought>That big smile of his is kinda scary, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like the mock trial's about to begin. What are we going to do about our meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, speaking of the mock trial, do either of you know what it's about?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Oh, but I thought we had sent a pamphlet to your office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, the pamphlet... Whatever happened to that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You won't be seeing it again. Trucy used it for the old rip-it-up-and-restore-it trick. ...Unfortunately, it didn't work as advertised.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, it seems I had better explain the situation, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, does anyone have any questions?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I do, professor! Could you tell me all about your school?!</line>
<line speaker="Means">What an excellent question. Here's a gold star for asking! Our academy has three courses to choose from. Students seeking to be lawyers take the lawyer course. Likewise... ...budding prosecutors take the prosecutor course, and future judges, the judge course.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, you have everything here for someone who wants to seriously pursue a career in law!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes, well, that's what makes our school special, and today even more so. After all, today we are to be treated to a lecture by the legendary attorney Phoenix Wright. We can't wait to hear all about his return to the legal profession</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're giving a lecture, Mr. Wright? But you're not even a professor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. Yeah, well I'm just giving them what they want.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh, did you even know you were meant to be giving a lecture here today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, sort of. But I came early because I was supposed to have a meeting... ...with the head of the judge course, Constance Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's been a whirlwind of a morning. Let's leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Prof. Courte... She is a wonderful instructor, but quite unpunctual.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, so that's who's late.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">From what I've heard, our esteemed Mr. Wright here... ...is scheduled to hold a training seminar tomorrow, in addition to today's lecture.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A training seminar? For lawyers? What exactly does that involve?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Why, it involves the very skills that make a lawyer, a lawyer! The arm angle when shouting, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" The proper way to strike the podium... How to project one's voice... And most importantly, how to bluff your way to victory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Um, who exactly do you want me to teach stuff like that to again?</line>
<line speaker="Means">What a wonderful question. You just earned yourself a gold star! The great honor of taking a seminar by a famous lawyer and a famous prosecutor... That is what is at stake in the mock trial, the crown jewel of the school festival.</line>
<line speaker="Means">The mock trial in question is a prestigious event that every student aspires to win. The top student in the lawyer course and the top student in the prosecutor course... ...face off in a simulated court case set in this very school! As for the case itself... ...we select the best script written by a judge course student and base our case on that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! A one-on-one battle?! How thrilling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, if the student studying to be a lawyer wins, they get to take my training seminar? But what if the other student wins? I'm not a prosecutor, so...</line>
<line speaker="Means">There's no cause for alarm. We have a famous prosecutor ready for just such a case. But exactly who it is, well, that is a special surprise!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A famous prosecutor? <thought>No, it can't be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">What magnificent presentation technique! Both your timing and speed were impeccable.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Speed?! You mean speed's important when presenting evidence, too?</line>
<line speaker="Means">Absolutely! The speed and approach angle theorems are the first things we teach here! I believe Mr. Wright and others like him already make extensive use of them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You do, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... to some degree, I guess, ah ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It never even crossed my mind. <thought>This lawyer thing is deeper than I thought!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Prof. Means, forgive me for interrupting you and your guests. I'm Juniper Woods, a third year in the judge course. Professor, the trial will begin shortly. Since you'll be delivering the pre-trial speech... ...would you mind waiting up in the balcony until we're ready for you?</line>
<line speaker="Means">My, how very organized you are, Juniper. You just earned yourself a gold star, too. But what about Prof. Courte... Well, I suppose she'll eventually arrive. Now then, I trust you will look after our visitors, Juniper?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, of course, Prof. Means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Juniper? Juniper Woods? Is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hm? ...Then-- Athena?! I almost didn't recognize you. I didn't know you were back from Europe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, you two know each other? Now that's a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We've known each other since we were kids. We're like best friends, right, Junie?!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... Well, we lived close to each other, so we used to play in the forest together.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, like a lot a lot. <thought>Why won't she look at me? I guess I shouldn't be surprised since we haven't seen each other in a long time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway... we're supposed to go wait in the waiting room, right? Not that I wouldn't mind taking in the mock trial you're putting on today.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Unfortunately, the mock trial is only for students and faculty. There is one seat reserved for Mr. Wright, but no other exceptions are allowed.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Yes, I'm very sorry, but it is part of the student curriculum, after all. I hope you won't mind remaining in the waiting room until the trial concludes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, that's too bad. I was hoping to learn something new today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'll tell you what, Apollo. Why don't you take my place?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure. Besides, I'd like to meet with Prof. Courte as soon as she gets here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aw, no fair! I wanna see the mock trial, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, I'm going to let Apollo pull what little rank he has. ....If it's okay with Prof. Means.</line>
<line speaker="Means">But of course, Mr. Wright, if that is what you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's settled, then. We'll expect a full and detailed report, Apollo, so pay attention!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, being the new kid sure stinks.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">If you would please follow me. I'll escort you down to the waiting room on the first floor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Still no Prof. Courte... It's been over thirty minutes. And Mr. Wright's snoozing away on the sofa. This is so boring. I should've hid in the Lecture Hall and spied on the mock trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eek! Wh-What was that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*yawn* ...Athena. I could've sworn I just heard something fall down and break. If you go running now, they'll think it was you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well it wasn't me. I think it came from somewhere outside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Well, we better go have a look, seeing as everyone else is in the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is this stage for some sort of concert? It kinda reminds me of a courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Athena. Behind the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Eeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prof. Courte! Can you hear me?! Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, that's... that's who we were supposed to be meeting with?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... It looks like our meeting's been canceled for us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! This... This can't be real...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I called the police. They should be here soon. ...I'll go tell everyone in the Lecture Hall, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, wait. They'll find out soon enough once the police get here. Let's do our own crime scene investigation before it gets too crowded around here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?! Are we even allowed to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no big deal, as long as we leave it exactly like we found it. Plus... No, never mind. Anyway, we should look around while the scene's still fresh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But...... Okay, you're the boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In addition to checking the body, we should also check the area around it. But we don't have much time, check only what you can. ...Nervous, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yes! I mean, n-no! <thought>Apollo didn't bat an eye at the alderman's body during that case in Nine-Tails Vale... I can't let him show me up. I can do this. Just take a deep breath and focus!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, Prof. Courte was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep, the professor I was here to meet with. Turns out, she wasn't running late after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>How awful. Here she was lying dead and we thought she was late.</thought> What was that you were saying before, Boss? You never finished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? Oh, that. Don't worry, I'll fill you in... later. But right now, let's focus on the investigation, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Okay, sure. <thought>Ugh, the suspense is killing me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, a shiny new attorney's badge. Brings back memories...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've heard that countless people live in dread of your pointer finger. Were you really that scary back then, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. Strike one. I've always been just as you see me here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A harmless sheep in wolf's clothing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Strike two.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you have an old picture of yourself? Wait, never mind! I'm not sure I want to see it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Strike three, you're out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen, Athena. There's a certain amount of etiquette involved in presenting evidence. You're free to shove this or that into my face, but... ...at least get my attention first or give me some sort of a warning.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>In other words, do as I say, not as I do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should start by studying the body. Hmm, I wonder what's the best angle for this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. I guess I really do have to examine the body... Well, guess I'd better get used to stuff like this if I want to be a full-fledged lawyer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh... There's an arrow stuck in her side. Gunshot wounds and stab wounds are pretty common, but arrow wounds?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is a homicide any way you slice it. In other words, we have a murder on our hands.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>A murder?! Here?!</thought> S-So, that makes this arrow the murder weapon. Well, that and the bow that shot it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, but where could the killer have shot her from? The stage is a sea of obstructions? I'm no expert on archery, but it can't be easy to hit a target with this much stuff around.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Would it be possible to kill someone by stabbing them with an arrow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure. Guess we better do some more investigating before jumping to conclusions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do we have here...? A book? I'm guessing it fell out of her chest pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! What if it's her diary?! That's the most private thing a girl has!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True, but considering the situation at hand, my apologies to the late Prof. Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, don't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, looks more like a planner than a diary. Every page seems to have the same sword mark printed on it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still think a girl deserves her privacy, but this may help us solve the case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Notice anything strange about the body? Take a deep breath, and then take a good look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... well, now that you mentioned it, there's no blood around it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yet the victim's body is cold and rigor mortis has already started to dissipate. It would appear that quite some time has passed since Prof. Courte was murdered. Thing is, the quad was packed with students up until the start of the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, then doesn't that mean she was killed at a different location? Ooh, I know! The killer moved the body here while everyone was in the Lecture Hall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a definite possibility. Notice anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... Her arms are raised over her head and there are dark bruises around her wrists.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. The professor was probably tied up with something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eventually, her wrists were unbound, and as she reached up to stretch, she was killed? ...Actually, I'm not so sure about this theory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... Well, there's not exactly a lot to go on...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nice work, Athena. Your face only turned five shades of pale. I was expecting fifty. We should probably take a picture of the crime scene, just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, I'm on it! Say cheese!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Cheese? And I thought I was the one with the twisted sense of humor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think that should do it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, let's take a better look around the area while we wait for the police to arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This pile of rubble sticks out like a sore thumb. Looks like broken pottery or plaster. Maybe this is the source of that noise we heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, there were supposedly two statues on this stage. I seem to recall hearing that a coed from the Fine Art Club had made them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There were two? Then that thing over there is the remains of another statue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This could be related to the case. Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's definitely something here, but there are other pressing issues to take care of. Like doing a careful search of the area around that broken statue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wonder what this was a statue of. Whatever it was, it was reddish-purple in color.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When Apollo and I first got here, both statues were already here, but they were covered up. I bet they were waiting to unveil them when the school festival moved here to this stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean this duffle bag-looking thing was actually being used to cover the statues? I guess that just leaves the question, were they broken by accident or on purpose? Hmm... What a puzzle this is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's something buried in the rubble. ...The Themis Herald?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, we shouldn't disturb it. Let's just read what we can.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Final Act in Torrid Love Triangle Centered on Campus She-Devil Juniper Woods" "Level-headed lawyer course genius and hot-blooded prosecutor course student... ...will go head to head in a mock trial battle for the she-devil's black heart! Hugh O'Conner has declared that he will confess to her if he wins!" Wait, whaaaaaaaaat?! I seriously wish I hadn't read that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You find that more shocking than discovering a murder victim's body?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-B-But, we're talking about my friend Junie here! She'd never lead guys on like that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, you don't believe everything you read, do you? This article is clearly written with malicious intent. I'm not buying a word of it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You're right. But it's still disturbing, even if it's third-rate tabloid material.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, here comes Apollo! I've never seen anyone move so fast!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*huff*... *huff*... Listen! Something big's happened! I was at the mock trial when the police announced a body had been found on campus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. And we're the ones who phoned it in. We found Prof. Courte dead behind the witness stand over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WH-WHAAAT?! Can you show me?! ...What the--?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We've already had a quick look at the body. It's definitely a homicide. Once the police get here--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I know it's a homicide! I'm shocked because it's the same! Exactly the same!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa there, Apollo. Take a deep breath and explain what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the same! The body, that is! It's just like it was in the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? It's like the mock trial?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know! It sounds crazy, b-but... The body's location and position, the murder weapon, the lack of pooling blood... It's all exactly like the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're kidding, right? It can't really all be the same... can it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The whole school's in an uproar. There won't be any more classes today.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A murder on campus... That's the last thing I expected at a legal academy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll go tell Prof. Means what we observed when we discovered the body. You two wait here until you've spoken with the police.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* I can't believe this is happening.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe we have to wait around here. I can't stay still at times like these. <thought>I hope Junie hasn't fainted from the shock of this whole thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Ah! Thena... er, I mean, Athena. There you are.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie! Am I glad to see you! I was worried that--</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Don't worry about me. I am Student Council President, after all. I need to be strong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Student Council President? Wow, I'm impressed. <thought>She's really changed. She used to be kind of sickly and shy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Juniper was it? You mind if we ask you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, we're stuck here waiting for the police. And there's really not much to do.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Sure, what would you like to know?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I haven't seen you in ages, Junie! What's it been, seven years or so?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, and I remember how you were always there for me, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, maybe it's just me, but I wanted to ask why you seem so distant. Remember how you used to call me Thena? I liked it better that way. It felt like we were sisters, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, but I'm Student Council President now. And as the student representative of Themis Legal Academy, I have to act properly.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She was never this stiff and formal before.</thought> I knew you wanted to be a judge, but I didn't expect this. It's such a prestigious school. And you're in the judge course to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. And Prof. Courte had been in charge of it until... well, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, right. Prof. Courte was the professor in charge of Junie's course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What sort of teacher was Prof. Courte?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">If I had to sum her up in a single word, I'd say she was "amazing." "A judge must always seek the truth." That was her mantra, and she used it in trying to... ...fix what was wrong with our school. She was a beacon of hope in this dark age of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's wrong with our school? What did you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, uh, nothing! Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Am I imagining things or did I just detect something in Junie's voice?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Prof. Courte chose my script for the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh? You mean all of the students in the judge course had to submit a script? And yours was the one she selected? Wow, that's amazing, Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, th-thanks you. But now, Prof. Courte is... Who would do such a thing? Just yesterday we were working together, trying to get things ready... *cough* *cough* *cough* Excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you all right, Junie? Maybe you should take it easy for a while. <thought>So she's still got that cough... Guess she's not as strong as she pretends to be.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why do you need a script in a showdown between a lawyer and a prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, we were simulating a trial, so we needed a script as a framework. All the details about the incident and the people involved are included in the script. We also prepared a crime scene, photos, a murder weapon, and other kinds of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you guys think of everything. Must be hard getting all that ready.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, well... it was only Prof. Courte and I. After all, we didn't want the script or other elements of the mock trial to get leaked. We were the only ones in the entire school who knew all of the details.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Must've been a big pain in the-- er, I mean, that must've been really difficult.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I wrote the script so that the case could go either way. That way, the defense and the prosecution both had an equal chance of winning.</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh, if you think that's all she's capable of, you've got another thing coming.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Who said that?</line>
<line speaker="???">Juniper's genius doesn't stop at her brilliant script.</line>
<line speaker="???">YEAAAAAH! She gave an award-winning performance as the defendant, maaaaaan!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I think I found a rival to my Chords of Steel.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Hugh, Robin, aren't you going to introduce yourselves to our guests? As Student Council President, I won't have you treating them rudely.</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh, you're right. I heard Mr. Wright was bringing a couple of guests with him. That would be you two? Apollo Justice and Athena Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yep! I'm Athena Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'm Apollo Justice. Nice to meet you.</line>
<line speaker="???">...I'll pass on the handshake. I'm studying to be a lawyer. The name's Hugh O'Conner. ...But some call me Mr. Perfect because I never score less than 100% on tests.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. Most... pretentious... introduction... EVER. And what's with his hand? Is it glued to the inside of his pocket or what? Yeesh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Lemme be the first to apologize for Hugh's totally rude introduction! SORRRRRY!!! Now, here's my intro! I'm Robin Newman!!! I'm studying to be a prosecutor! Like the really cool kind that nails the bad guys! NOOOOOO!!! Where's the sincerity?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So he makes pottery, too? And what's that brace-like contraption for...? Junie sure has made some... unusual friends.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">These two were the lawyer and the prosecutor in today's mock trial. And even though I wrote the script, I also played the part of the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Final Act in Torrid Love Triangle Centered on Campus She-Devil Juniper Woods" "Level-headed lawyer course genius and hot-blooded prosecutor course student... ...will go head to head in a mock trial battle for the she-devil's black heart!" <thought>Wait, THESE two are the guys who supposedly have a thing for Junie?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Juniper, come on. Your role's way beyond just that.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">That's riiiiiight! The mock trial's just the start! She's also in the school festival's main event! Live on stage, Juniper Woods! And the crowd goes bananas! WOOOOO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">......... I'm... I'm supposed to sing at the school festival. All of the other girls were too embarrassed to try out, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My Junie singing? On a stage in front of people? <thought>Wow, she really HAS changed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was responsible for making everyone's stage costumes. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's amazing, Junie, but then again, you were always good at that kind of thing. These constellations in particular are really something.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh! Um, thank you. One of my favorite things to do is to look up at the stars in the middle of the forest.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh, so you're a fan of the night sky then?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow Apollo, didn't know you were such a romantic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-It's not like that! I have this friend -- he and I go way back -- who got me really interested in space.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, you had friends when you were young? Color me surprised!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">As Student Council President, I cannot allow such mean-spirited teasing to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eep.... <thought>I think she's angry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">The costumes were no problem, but as for singing, I'm not sure I--</line>
<line speaker="Newman">NOOOOO! YOU CAN DOOOOOO IIIIIIT!!!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's right. And anyone who says otherwise will have to answer to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It's like a chivalrous love triangle -- a damsel in distress and two knights in shining armor. Maybe that Themis Herald article wasn't too far from the truth. Speaking of the latest news, I wonder how the mock trial turned out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, how did the mock trial end?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">We were just about to reach a verdict when the police arrived. Now we'll never know how it would've turned out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess that's what happens when there's a real murder during a fake murder trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It ended right before the verdict? Talk about bad timing...</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">.........</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I was THIS close, maaan! I bet I woulda won!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I bet the defense wasn't doing too badly either, right?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">We'll settle this some other time. And I assure you, I WILL win when that time comes.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Like I'm gonna let that happen! I DON'T THINK SO!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hope they don't end up hurting each other.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, don't worry. The three of us have been good friends since we enrolled here.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. We even have proof of our friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Proof? Like physical evidence, proof?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes. We're studying for a career in law, and in the legal world, evidence is everything.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeaaaaaah!!! As long as our friendship lasts! You can bet we'll be carrying them around!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, the famed "Themis Legal Academy ingenuity" at work! So, what exactly is this proof of friendship, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">.........Well... It's a secret. And if I show you, it would be bad luck.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, okay... <thought>I knew it. There's definitely some discord in Junie's voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Our friendship is sacred and inviolable. It's not something to be put cheaply on display.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Proof?! We don't need no stinkin' proof! Us three are friends foreveeeeeer!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I can hear discord in their voices, too! But they're talking about their friendship. What's going on here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something wrong, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, it's... it's nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... All right, then...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's your attorney's badge, isn't it! I really envy you, you know. That gold sunflower really suits you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks. But I know you'll make a fabulous judge someday, Junie.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-Thank you... But... Even if I become a judge, I'll never have one of those sunflower badges.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wait, so she only envies me for the badge?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, th-that's...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh. Sorry, but I couldn't help reading it. You always were popular with the guys.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-That's not true! I... I was never...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You just didn't realize it. But that made you even more irresistible. It's been seven years, but I still remember how all the boys wanted to be near you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I bet you used to get all excited when a guy handed you a love letter... ...and then got really bummed out when he's say, "Could you give this to Juniper for me?"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Agh! <thought>How'd he know?! I'm sure it was just a lucky guess, but why'd it have to be Apollo of all people?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Athena, you know it's against school rules for you to have such things in your possession. As Student Council President, I'm afraid I'll have to confiscate that. Hand it over, please.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But this is important evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Oh, well, then I suppose we can make an exception just this once.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, she's one tough law-and-order type president, all right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, isn't that--!</line>
<line speaker="???">Everyone, stay right where you are! Don't move a muscle!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Detective Fulbright? Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Why, if it isn't my little lawyer friends! Sorry, but the small talk will have to wait. Juniper Woods, you're under arrest for the murder of Constance Courte!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...I'm what?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Wait a second! What's going on here?! Why are you arresting Junie?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, Detective Fulbright. We're involved in this case, too.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ah-ha! So, you're the lawyers the dispatch said were first on scene! I can't tell you everything, but I will say this. There are two major reasons for her arrest. Number one! The suspect led someone to where the body was.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I-I didn't--!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">And number two! The crime scene is exactly how the suspect portrayed it in her script!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But...! You can't arrest her on just those grounds!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">True. But there's more! However, Prosecutor Blackquill specifically told me to say no more than that!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So Blackquill's the prosecuting attorney on this one, too...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Detective Fulbright! We found this in the suspect's pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? Wh-Why there's...! There's blood on this!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-That's evidence we made for the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">A mock... trial? Never heard of such a thing, but it sounds fishy to me! Real fishy! Now, if you would, officers.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">B-But... *cough, cough* I... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie! <thought>I have to do something! I... I can't let them take her away like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Anime cutscene</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> I refuse to believe that she's the killer! Junie! I've decided, I'm going to defend you! I'll fight with everything I've got!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-Thena...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie... It's good to hear you say that name again.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hate to interrupt your bonding time, but... Aren't you rather new to all this? You're barely even a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I don't have much experience, and I may need Apollo and Mr. Wright's help at times... ...but nobody believes in Junie as much as I do!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll help you, too, Juniper. There's no way you murdered your professor.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Thena... *cough* Apollo... Thank *cough* you both. I'm counting on you! *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We've got your back, Junie!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Guess things worked out after all. Now that you have your lawyers, Ms. Woods, it's time for us to head back to the station.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I can't believe Junie's been arrested for murder. And I can't believe I accepted her case without asking Mr. Wright!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a deep breath and relax, Athena. I'm here to help with whatever you need, so let's get right on the case!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. I won't have this case left in the hands of rank amateurs. If anyone's going to solve this case, it'll be me. Time to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why that smug little--! <thought>He hasn't even finished law school!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">HUUUUUUGH!!! That was totally ruuude!!! And you're not the only one on the case, maaaaaan!!! I'm in, too! Big time! JUUUUUUUUUNIPER WOOOOOOODS!!! I'm gonna save yooooooooou!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Now that those two are gone, let's get back to what I was talking about in front of the stage. ...About the mock trial, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right! You said the victim's location, position, and so on were just like in the script!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. But without the script or any props, it's kind of hard to explain.</line>
<line speaker="???">Perhaps I could help... Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Prosecutor Gavin! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You two seem to know each other. Is someone going to introduce me?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why, I do believe we have a fresh face here. Greetings, Fräulein. I am Klavier Gavin. Some know me as a prosecutor, but I'm most famous for my former rock band. We were quite popular you know, but regrettably, the band went kaput. Perhaps you've heard of us? The Gavinners? I was the lead vocalist.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Never heard of your band. Then again, I was out of the country till only recently. But... can I get your autograph?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You just met him like three seconds ago and you want his autograph?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Forgive me Fräulein, but I've retired from the music biz. But I'd be happy to offer my autograph as rock star prosecutor, Klavier Gavin.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, okay. That one, then!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She's a lively one, eh, Herr Forehead? Didn't know she was your type.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........She's the newest member of Wright Anything Agency, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nice to meet you! I'm Athena Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A pleasure to meet you too, Athena Cykes. Now that the intros are out of the way... ...I'm sure you have some questions for me, ja, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what are you doing here, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I'm here for the same reason as your boss -- to give a lecture and a training seminar.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So HE'S the famous prosecutor they invited!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And... I have another crucial role to play. The Gavinners are getting back together for a one-time special performance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even though you guys disbanded? ...Which was a shame, by the way. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ja, I know how much you... adored our music, Herr Forehead. Anyway, I studied abroad in Germany to get my badge early, but I did graduate from here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, so that performance Junie mentioned...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see you've already heard about that. One student representative was selected to sing with us onstage. And the stage was supposed to look like this tomorrow. Two big banners and a pair of wicked statues. This is just an illustration, but it's not half bad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wicked statues...? Wait are these supposed to be you and Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Bingo, Fräulein. And they were so big and magnificent, too! What a terrible waste. But the worst part of this whole thing is... ...my long-awaited reunion with my mentor never came to pass.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, don't tell me your mentor was--!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Prof. Courte. She was the one who taught me how to think about the law.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, Constance Courte was your professor here at the academy...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">She may have taught the judge course, but she had a huge impact on me. She was fond of saying, "The end is only justified through proper means." She wouldn't tolerate dishonesty and always revered what was right beyond all else.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I can feel Prosecutor Gavin's sadness. Oh, no, I think I'm gonna cry... *sniffle*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena? Are you tearing up? Though I can't blame you... Prosecutor Gavin owes a lot of who he is to Prof. Courte.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Exactly. So, as you can see, we are both joined in purpose, so to speak, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">May I ask why you people present your attorney's badges like that? It seems like Herr Forehead and Mr. Wright always want to show theirs off, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, let me ask you, Prosecutor Gavin. Why do you play air guitar?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It would seem the answer we seek can be found in much the same place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I never gave it that much thought, actually. I always just whip it out.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did I ever mention I'm a graduate of this fine institution? The mock trials... They sure bring back memories. So many unforgettable battles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? So, you stood on that stage, too?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ja, I waited on my air guitar, rocked out to the beat, and exposed crimes for all to see. You could say this is where my hard-rocking prosecutorial style made its debut.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hard-rocking prosecutorial style? How did your mock trial turn out?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung, baby! I brought the house down and had the crowd on its feet! Ever since, the academy has held a live concert in conjunction with the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>All I wanted to know was how the trials turned out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why, Fräulein, what a wonderful piece of evidence you have there. But I imagine no matter what you present... ...it would be impossible for it to be more persuasive than your beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Too bad it doesn't work that way in court, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Now, let's rock this place hard!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I don't follow. Let's rock what?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Forget already, Herr Forehead? I said I'd help you explain the mock trial. We're going to reprise it right here in the Lecture Hall! It might help us catch her killer!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Right. the stage is ready. And you, Herr Forehead? Ready to rock?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, no, the defense is not ready to rock.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You saw the actual mock trial earlier, right? Just relax, you'll do fine. Besides, we have the script right here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie's masterpiece?! The one everyone's been talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ja, and there's only one in existence. I "borrowed" it, if you will. Now, Fräulein, we'll need you to play the part of defendant and judge as per the script.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, got it!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I've only read the case outline so far. I don't know how it actually turns out, so I'll treat this like I'm prosecuting a real case. You, Herr Forehead, will play the part of a fledgling lawyer, a role you were born to play. All the evidence is also here with us. We have everything we need to reprise the mock trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Très bien! Let's get started. Defendant-slash-judge Athena Cykes, is psyched and ready to rock! Court is now in session for our reenactment of the mock trial... ...or what I'd like to call the mock mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ja, a double mockery, perhaps, but a trial is still a trial. Achtung, baby! It's no holds barred! Let's rock!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aw, can't we take it easy today?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great... A judge that voices her own objections AND abuses her judicial powers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now, then, Prosecutor Gavin, your opening statement if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You got it, Fräulein Judge! Our case is set in a school very much like this one. The victim -- a professor, female. The defendant -- an Archery Club member, also female.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh me, oh my... I'm innocent! Innocent I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's some seriously bad acting, Fräulein. Anyway, the victim's body was discovered in the middle of the quad. Here's a shot of the crime scene. Ironically, it was Prof. Courte who posed as the corpse. Herr Forehead, how did the mock trial participants react to this photo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Newman was surprised by what Prof. Courte was wearing. He reacted with, "Oh, the green sweat suit."</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's not exactly what I would pick to focus on, so why would he care about that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, too much of a fledgling to know what's important, that one. In any case... ...both in the mock trial and the actual case, Prof. Courte was wearing a sweat suit. Moving right along--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's right. And therein lies the significance of this mock mock trial. So let's keep rockin' it hard, just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Before the crime occurred, the defendant was to meet the victim in the quad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, ahem... Let's see here... "When I arrived at our meeting place, I found the professor with an arrow in her stomach! But... it wasn't me! I didn't kill her!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't have to ham it up like that, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's called getting into character, Herr Forehead. Don't be such a wet blanket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Um, let's see... Oh yeah, then Hugh said... "A frail coed used her bare hands to stab her professor with an arrow? I don't think so. At the time of the murder, a male student was seen... ...holding a bow in the Archery Club room, which has a clear view of the quad. He shot the arrow into the victim before my client even got there!"</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Nein nein, Herr Forehead. That feigned swagger does not suit you in the least.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Order! Order!!! ORDER!!! Especially you, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me?! But I was just trying to get into it like Mr. Euro Rocker said.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, the victim was shot from the Archery Club room before the meeting even took place. Hence, the defendant could not be the killer. That seems to be the defense's assertion. Prosecutor Gavin, do you have any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The autopsy report notes that the edges of the victim's wound were unusually ragged. Could such physical trauma possibly result from an arrow shot from a bow? Nein! I believe the victim was impaled with the arrow by hand... postmortem. In short, the real murder weapon was not the arrow at all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When Robin was prosecutor, he had a tough time determining the real murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, he's just a student, a warm-up act, while I am the real deal, the headliner, so to speak. The true murder weapon was most likely the awl that was left in the art room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">An awl, what's that? Er, I mean... Hmm... An awl, you say? What might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It's a kind of tool used for poking holes in paper, wood, and other materials. It's kind of like an ice pick. I have a photo here if you're interested.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gross.. It's all bloody up to the handle. Please tell me it's just paint.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Most likely, Fräulein. Pretty realistic, ja? Let's pretend it's real blood for now. The defendant's prints were lifted from the murder weapon. Furthermore, traces of the victim's blood were discovered in the art room. That's where I believe the murder actually took place.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, the question now is, how did the body get from the art room to the stage?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The murder took place in the third floor art room, but the body was found in the quad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It must've been quite a chore moving the body all that way.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not at all. There's a maintenance area and storehouse right outside the art room. And a cart used to carry balls around was found there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I think I've seen one of those before. But that's a pretty big one.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A jumbo, ja? Big enough to fit a person -- or a body -- in it. The defendant dropped the body from the art room window, then moved it with the cart. That is how a high-school girl could easily move a body all by herself!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You don't saaaaaaaaaaay!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Klavier:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes... It's almost scary how similar this whole case is to the mock trial proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sounds like he has only high praise for Junie's script.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Were there any further arguments from the defense?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nope. It seemed like the teacher who was playing the judge was satisfied, too.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Time for the finale, then. Your verdict if you please, Fräulein Judge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh, right, that's me! Very well, this court finds the defendant, Juniper Woods-- Wait a second. Even if this is just a mock trial of a mock trial... ...I don't want to declare Junie guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yeah, perhaps that's not such a good idea. Let's end our mock mock trial here. Besides, it's about time I get back to my investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, you two! That little run-through of the mock trial cleared up quite a few things!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung, baby! The prosecution's already got a witness sized up, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was quick. <thought>Prosecutor Blackquill's almost too good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're in such a helpful mood today, Prosecutor Gavin...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, like I said, I just want to catch whoever killed Prof. Courte. And there's no reason for me to start butting heads with you two. Anyway, I won't say goodbye, as I'm sure I'll be seeing you later.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I always thought prosecutors were all a rather scary bunch. But Prosecutor Gavin seems pretty nice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, he's not so bad as prosecutors go. We should get back to investigating, too. We don't have nearly enough information yet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we also have to tell Mr. Wright that we accepted Junie's case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Looks like we have our work cut out for us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The most prominent feature of this case is how closely it resembles the script. That makes it a tough one because we have to have a firm understanding of them both.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No sweat! We can reenact the mock trial as many times as we want by reading the script! I'll check it out in the Court Record and commit it to memory later!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good. I bet the script and the mock trial are going to be the centerpiece of the real trial. Make sure you know them inside and out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, sir, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Justice? Careful, I could get used to that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, any advice on how to investigate this case?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh... Start by interviewing people about the basic facts.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Interview people! Got it! Hey, you there! What can you tell me about the--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, hold on, Athena! The trial's tomorrow, so try to limit it to people with some relation to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, got it! Limit the interview pool!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... You might also want to take it down a notch, otherwise you'll be dead by tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He wants me to calm down?! At a time like this?! Junie's fate rests in my hands. I just HAVE TO win this one...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, nice. Your attorney's badge! That's the first thing you want to present when you meet someone new. I heard that's what all lawyers do.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You heard that? From whom?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who else, Mr. Wright. Just remember, your badge comes first! See, Athena! Check it out! This is my attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ooh! That's so intense! I want to present mine like that, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A torrid love triangle? Juniper sure is popular with the guys.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course she is. She's pretty, plus she has such a sweet and caring personality.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know what you're thinking. Why can't Athena be more like that, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh! N-No, no! The thought never crossed my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Let's see... Panic... Sorrow... Yep, that's exactly what crossed his mind. *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mock trial was quite the heated battle.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, Mr. Wright didn't even hear me when I said I wanted to see it. That was so unfair. We should've done rock, paper, scissors to decide who got to watch. I know I would've totally beaten you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How could you know that? The game's totally random.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I can tell you favor scissors. I mean, the proof's sticking right out of your head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What're you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Like I said, it's right there on your head!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! Nice one, Athena. Keep it up! I don't care if it's totally unrelated to the case or just plain annoying or even embarrassing. Just keep presenting evidence without any regard for others! That's the first step towards becoming a successful trial lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leave it to me! I'll one piece after another, and then another!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Hey, what do you think you're doing? The crime scene is off limits to students.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk, I'm no student. I'm a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Yeah, right! Just because you're in law school doesn't mean you're a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You should see what she did to the last cop who said something like that her.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Why you--! Are you threatening an officer of the law?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! N-N-No, it's not a threat! It's more like a friendly warning!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>...*sigh* Guess we should go before I get myself arrested for assaulting an officer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A school festival? Why didn't you take me with you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, um... Only Mr. Wright was officially invited. Apollo and I are just tagging along, but we ARE lawyers, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, my magic act would've made a great warm up for the mock trial. They'd have seen how even the most crucial evidence could vanish in the blink of an eye!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's probably precisely why Mr. Wright didn't invite you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Athena, don't you think the Wright Anything Agency has about run its course?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Isn't it obvious? It's time for the Wright Anything Academy! And you, Athena, I want you to be the head of our Psychology Department.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh... What other departments will we have?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I'll be the head of the Magic Department... ...and we'll have a Chords of Steel Department and a Bluffing Department!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>But then who'll be the head of the Toilet Cleaning Department?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, that's an attorney's badge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Promise me you won't make it disappear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! What a mean thing to say! Do I look like someone who'd do something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I didn't mean it like that. Anyway, I hear they reissue badges that get lost, so...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, isn't that great! That means you have nothing to worry about!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! ...But seriously, please don't make mine disappear. I wouldn't want to have to explain.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, is that the morning paper?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Something like that. It's a school paper. I was thinking, your magic tricks would make a great article.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really?! A newspaper article about my tricks? That would be so cool! The moment the interview starts, I'd suddenly disappear, shocking the interviewer! Without an actual interview, they could call the article, "The Interview that Vanished"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'll just leave it at that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, thanks, Athena! That'll make a great new prop for my magic act!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? But that's--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, what kind of trick should I do with it? Make it disappear? Burn it? Rip it in two?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ha ha ha. Let's just save that fun little detail for later.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aww, you're no fun.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I heard they arrested your friend Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, Detective Fulbright just took her in.</line>
<line speaker="Means">I refuse to believe that one of our students is capable of murder. We must prove her innocent by any means necessary! The end justifies the means!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean, the end justifies the means?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I, Prof. Means, always say what I mean, and mean what I say by all means! Here at our esteemed academy, we train our students to produce meaningful results. You believe in Juniper's innocence, do you not?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, I do! Junie wouldn't even hurt a fly!</line>
<line speaker="Means">Precisely. We have justice on our side. The only other thing we need are results. It is the height of folly to endanger your client by failing to pursue all means possible!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... sure I want to prove her innocence, but... <thought>I don't like the sound of that "end justifies the means" part.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Well, you are still young and idealistic. It's no wonder you fail to see the wisdom therein. There is but one thing to do now. I must personally take up Juniper's defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're going to take her case, Prof. Means?</line>
<line speaker="Means">I may be a professor, but I am still licensed to practice law. In fact, I have even battle Prof. Courte in... well... in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No kidding?! So you guys were rivals or something?</line>
<line speaker="Means">No, nothing of the sort. She was an esteemed colleague at the academy and in court. You see, both Prof. Courte and I graduated from this academy at the top of our class.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, I bet they both used to really bring it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, if you would excuse me, I had best go discuss the case with Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prof. Means, please, wait! I didn't want to say anything, but Apollo and I already agreed to take her case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's true. Juniper is counting on us to prove her innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Means">Really now? You two?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And when were you planning on telling me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry, Boss. I know we should've asked first, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. Relax. Your friend was just hauled away in front of your eyes. Sometimes you just have to make snap decisions. And I think you made the right one.</line>
<line speaker="Means">How wonderful! Very well, Athena Cykes, let me ask you just one thing. As a lawyer, what is it that you treasure beyond all else?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh! That's any [sic] easy one, Professor! Seeking justice for my clients!</line>
<line speaker="Means">What a wonderful answer. Juniper must be overjoyed to have a friend such as you. As her professor, I too, shall do whatever I may to help her. And if you decide to take the-end-justifies-the-means strategy, come see me at once!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Let's hope it never comes to that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Means">Now, if you would excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, time's a wasting. You better start investigating and fast. But first, how about I tell you everything I know so far?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, please!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Have you learned anything new about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I ran into Prosecutor Gavin, and he told me something interesting. Seems the murder took place in the art room. There's traces of a large pool of blood there. So the police believe the body was moved from there to the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? Really?! <thought>Just like the mock trial again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The police are searching the art room, but whether they'll find anything, well...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well what? <thought>Come to think of it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's do our own crime scene investigation before it gets too crowded around here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?! Are we even allowed to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's no big deal, as long as we leave it exactly like we found it. Plus... No, never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Now, where was I again?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there's really no need to talk about it right here, right now. I want you two to find out for yourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, were you shocked by your conversation with Prof. Means?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, umm, I guess so. <thought>Actually, that was pretty shocking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The dark age of the law... I'm sure you've heard those words before.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure, a number of times. Prosecutors file false charges and lawyers fight back by fabricating evidence. There's a lot of that going around these days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the question is, how is it related to the case at hand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Training students to produce results... That is the school's policy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that in and of itself isn't a bad thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. ...As long as those results come by fair and honest means.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, but what was it that Prof. Means said?! "The end justifies the means"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To survive the dark age of the law, you must use any means necessary. Fabrication of evidence and false charges are unavoidable in the quest for results. That's what they're preaching here at Themis Legal Academy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But... What'll happen to our legal system if results are all that matter anymore?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha, relax. It's just a rumor. I'd take it with a grain of salt if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, that's a relief. <thought>He had me going there for a minute. Wait a second! What if Mr. Wright examined the victim's body for a reason! Maybe he was worried someone might actually tamper with the evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Things like that sure scream out "school days," don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Were you involved in any extracurricular activities like school papers or mock trials?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah, that wasn't my thing. I was an art major.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">An art major? Then how did you become a famous attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's kind of complicated. And when I say, kind of, I mean really, really complicated.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh... <thought>...He must really mean it. I'm picking up a lot of complex emotions in his voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that about wraps up what I know so far. The fact that this case closely resembles Ms. Woods's script is obviously important. Knowing that, you should probably try and identify what's the same and what's different.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay! I'll try talking to as many people as I can on campus!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, there's Hugh! Hey, Huuuuugh!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Oh, it's you two. Do you want something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you find anything? You said you were going to do some investigating of your own.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Nope, nothing yet. I'm afraid it's not looking very good for Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't really think Juniper could have done something like this, do you?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Only the author and the victim knew the contents of the script. Both the stage and the art room were in the exact same state as described therein. Nobody could mimic the crime like that unless they'd already read the script... or... wrote it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Look, Prof. Means is better able to handle this than you two, so just leave it to him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There it is again. I'm picking up some discord in Hugh's voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hugh, would you mind telling me a bit about yourself?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, whatever. I'm 6'1" and under this uniform, I'm one hundred percent lean muscle. My grades are outstanding and I'm the ace of the Archery Club. Needless to say... ...I never miss my mark. Oh, and I'm incredibly humble, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>How can he even say that with a straight face?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Those around me call me a genius, but I pay them no mind. But when it comes to tests... I always get a hundred percent, so I suppose it's only natural for them to say I'm a genius. But, as I said before, I pay them no mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I heard you the first time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But what about the mock trial? It sounded like you were about to lose to Robin.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. There's a very good reason for that. You see, right before the mock trial started... I saw the body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You saw the body?!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Right, and I was so distraught that I basically handed Robin a victory.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hugh, would you mind telling us a little more about that?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Right before the mock trial, the campus was empty. Everyone was here in the Lecture Hall.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That's right... There was that announcement and the everyone came in here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">The only exceptions were the mock trial participants. Juniper, Robin, and I were in our personal dressing rooms next door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, your own personal dressing rooms? That's total VIP treatment.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Actually, they're for student-teacher meetings. They don't even have windows. The other two waited patiently in their rooms, but that's not my style. So, I headed over to the archery range on the other side of the quad. I did some meditation while I waited. That's the best way to relax. Then, just before the mock trial was about to start, I headed back toward the main building. As I walked across the quad, I passed in front of the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, that's when you saw the body?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Right. It was quite a shock. As much as I hate to admit it, my legs were shaking. I could've easily beaten Robin if it hadn't been for that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, hold it right there. You went through with the mock trial even though you had just discovered a body? Why didn't you tell anyone? I mean, we're talking about someone getting killed here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think I know why... Was it because of this?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Ah! Where'd you get that?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, this article in the Themis Herald IS true. The winner of the mock trial would get to make his confession to Junie.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Right. But if I reported the body I'd found, the whole thing would be called off.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He really wanted to win that bad? Bad enough to ignore a dead body? Sorry, but that's not normal. ...Or could their love for Junie really be that strong?</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Your attorney's badge? Looks brand new. That just shows how inexperienced and useless you are.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, when you get your badge, it will be new and shiny, too!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. You mouth-breathers just don't get it, do you? My badge will be a symbol of my genius. From the moment I get it... It will be chipped, bent, and worn as if it's been through a thousand courtroom battles.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>He's like some hipster doofus.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">That's from the Archery Club. We let the school use it for the mock trial. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course, the real murder weapon isn't an arrow at all.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">I know. But the fact remains that it was used in this whole insidious plot. But a mouth-breather like you couldn't possibly understand. You see, archery is a sport that demands advanced mental focus. And the killer's actions have done harm to its image.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know exactly what you mean, except for that mouth-breather remark.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Well, let's hope that someday you will because it couldn't be any more self-evident.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I like him less and less every time he opens his mouth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it just me or is this your name here?</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, that's my name, but how should I know what it's doing there? But being that the whole campus looks up to me... ...I'm not surprised to find my name mentioned here and there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>And I'm not surprised he said that, being the narcissist he is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, you really declared that you'd confess to Junie if you won the mock trial? <thought>Because he's definitely not the shy type.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh. Yeah, well, that's just the genius that is me. My thoughts and actions are on a whole other level from you mouth-breathers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>No, it's your vanity that's on a whole other level.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">...I get it. This is your way of mocking my defeat. You like shoving people's shame in their faces. That's your modus operandi.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, that wasn't my intention. Besides, you were never actually defeated.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Oh, I suppose you're right. ...Or is this a trick intended to provoke me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That wasn't my intention, either!</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Then what WAS your intention?! I know! You're trying to toy with my emotions!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow, this guy can't take being humbled, old country style.</thought></line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Random junk from some mouth-breather? What makes you think I'd want to see that? Heh. The least you could do is make it more interesting, like by telling me how cool I am.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Who does this guy think he is?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks for sharing that important piece of information with us. It may prove useful at tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Good. Because that's all I have to say about the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks. And don't worry, we'll prove Juniper's innocence, you'll see.</line>
<line speaker="O'Conner">Heh, I can't say you two inspire much confidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, Athena, what next?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So this is the maintenance area. Let's see... During the mock mock trial, Prosecutor Gavin said... ...that the art room is right above here on the third floor... ...and that they body was dropped from there onto a high jump mat from the storehouse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. And then he claimed that the body was transported to the stage in a ball cart. And then... Hm? There's someone else here...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, it's Robin!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Whoooooooooa! You scared the crud outta meeeeee!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! Right back at you! ...So, what are you doing out here?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">I'm working out so that I can become strong enough to save Juniper! But I'm so worked up... my training brace is almost breaking at the seams!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right... The girl you like got arrested, so you're psyching yourself up to rescue her?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yes! Because! I'm the manliest of manly men! ...That's why I work out with my manly brace!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Except that I hear some discord in that manliest of men's voice of yours...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't mean to be rude, but can't you talk without shouting?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Sorry! I'll try not to shout so much! If at all possible, that is!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>...Which is "not at all possible" by the sound of it.</thought> Um, so do you mind if I ask you some questions as Junie's lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">No problem! Ask away! Keep 'em coming, maaaaaan!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ouch... My ears ache already.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Robin, could you tell me a little more about yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">You wanna know about meee?! I'm a second-rate member of the Fine Arts Cluuub!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Fine Arts Club?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like broken pottery or plaster. Maybe this is the source of that noise we heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, there were supposedly two statues on this stage. I seem to recall hearing that a coed from the Fine Art Club had made them.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Two big banners and a pair of wicked statues. This is just an illustration, but it's not half bad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wicked statues...? Wait are these supposed to be you and Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Bingo, Fräulein. And they were so big and magnificent, too! What a terrible waste.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Say... Did you create those stage statues by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">You bet I did! Both of 'em! Put my blood, sweat, and tears into those things, maaan!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It must've been terrible seeing them all smashed up like that</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Nah! I couldn't face Prof. Courte if I let something like that get me down!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Prof. Courte was the Fine Arts Club advisor! She was all about truth and beauty, maaan!!! She always said, "The only good result is the truth"! That and... ..."Only lawyers who seek the truth through legitimate means produce worthwhile results"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeees! I'm totally on your guy side! She must have been an incredible woman!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeesh, and you call ME loud when I practice my Chords of Steel...</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Aw, maaaaaaaaan! Why'd I have to take the prosecutor course! I mean, how am I supposed to save Juniper if I'm studying to be a prosecutor?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry. I'll clear Junie's name, you'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The three of us had a dream! We swore we'd make it happen TOGETHER!!! Prosecutor! Lawyer! Judge! The three of us would hold fair and honest trials! The dark age of the law? Ha! We were gonna put a nail in its coffin, maaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, you guys swore to do that?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">But, noooo! That stupid school rule had to ruin it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">School rule? Which one?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Anyone with a prior conviction, no matter how minor the offense, they won't...! They won't be allowed to graduate from this stupid, holier-than-thou schoooool!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A tough legal academy, with even tougher rules...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Junie will never become a judge unless I can prove her innocence. And if I fail, the three of them will never realize their dream. ...It's like someone put pressure on my pressure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Whooooooa! Check out your badge!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you think? Nice and shiny, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">Yeah! It's AWESOME!!! If the plating ever starts to peel or it gets all bent up, lemme fix it up for you!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Newman">No problemo! I'll have some primo clay and glaze at the ready, just in case!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wait, what does clay have to do with my badge?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Ah! That paper!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, Robin, is this article true?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">The author of that article has been gunning for the three of us for some reason! It's been nothing but trashy articles like this as long as I can remember!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Maybe the author just wants your attention?</line>
<line speaker="Newman">No waaaaaaay, maaan! The venom in those articles is waaay beyond that!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm, I wonder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Newman">Whoooa! Déjà vu, maaaaaan! It's like I can almost taste my near victory again! But noooooo!!! The final showdown was canceled because of that murder!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This topic sure seems to strike a raw nerve. I hope it doesn't come between you guys.</line>
<line speaker="Newman">You kidding?! Our friendship...! It's like a diamond, only tougher!!! It's like a powder keg before a spark!!! It's like the calm before the storm!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>In other words, it's under a lot of pressure and ready to blow at any moment...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought the area was cordoned off. Hey, the police are discussing something over there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, I know! I'll just quietly sneak over for a listen. Here goes...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Athena, watch where you're--!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Eeeeeeeeek! Ouch! Who put this stupid box here? Wait............ Eek! A-A-Apollo! This box, there's...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-Th-There's! There's someone or... *gulp* something inside!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't let it be a SNAAAAAAAAAAAAKE!</line>
<line speaker="???">............Sss, sss, sss. You morons just blew my cover.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--? There really is someone inside...</line>
<line speaker="???">Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss! That someone is me, Myriam Scuttlebutt. And I'm a senior in the judge course.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What's with the box?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. It's the fate of we who live in the shadows. There's a very good reason why none may see my face by the light of day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, if you're taking the judge course, did you write a mock trial script, too?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. You really want to see my script that bad? Well, you better watch out. Read it without my permission and you'll wish you hadn't!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Who cares? I'm sure it was rejected for a good reason.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so you're studying to be a judge, too? You must be classmates with Juniper. Are you a friend of hers?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Juniper? Sss, sss, sss. Sure, she's my friend. That's why I'm gathering info. Now, tell me all you know. You know, for tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">For tomorrow's trial? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. I'm going to take the stand, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, the witness for the prosecution is... some weirdo in a cardboard box?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! This disguise is how I get my scoops! ...But you're right. It's me. So tell me everything you know for Juniper's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait a second, Myriam. Repeat what you just said.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">A lawyer with brains as bad as his ears. Poor Juniper! I'm taking the stand tomorrow. Tell me everything you know for Juniper's sake. Clear enough for you this time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought so. Athena, my bracelet's reacting.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really?! That means...! <thought>A lie, already? That was quick</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Think you can see through me with your silly little guesses? You're wasting your time! My box is impenetrable! Nobody sees the real me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gah... I blew that one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're completely boxed in now, Myriam! And Apollo's power is like a box cutter with x-ray vision! Prepare to be exposed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't exaggerate, Athena. I'm a lawyer, not a superhero.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's strange. You suddenly tightened your grip when you said, "for Juniper's sake." It's like you subconsciously tensed up because you're lying.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! Wh-What're you talking about?! When did I ever lie?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, then let me ask you this... Why were you selected as a witness?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. That's an easy one. I'm the editor-in-chief of the Themis Herald. I know everything there is to know around campus, even the darkest of secrets.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Editor-in-chief, huh? Pretty impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, yeah well, it's a lonely, one-woman operation. I do it all myself, from reporting, to editing, to publishing. Still impressed? I'm a perfect storm of journalism because I bring it all to the table, sss, sss, sss, sss! ...And this is the evidence. Here! An extra edition of the Themis Herald, published to coincide with the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Myriam. You've revealed who you truly are: As someone who's never had Junie's best interest in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">What?! Are you questioning our friendship?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, you may want answers, but... No can do, because what you're saying conflicts with this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Scuttlebutt:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Scatterbrained? If I'm wrong, just say so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's nothing iffy about it. You're way wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss! Scatterbrained, scatterbrained! Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss! Now, out with it! Tell me everything you know for Juniper's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">That's the Themis Herald, the paper I publish. What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Are you really that dense? This article is full of malicious lies about Junie! It's definitely not something a true friend of hers would write!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kahk-kahk! Y-You got it all wrong! Another staff member wrote that one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't think so, Myriam. You even said it yourself just a moment ago. "It's a one-woman operation." Or did you forget already?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Kaaahk kahk-kahk-kahk! If you'd just give me the info you have--! Stupid pawn! Juniper's just using you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now, I want the truth, Myriam! You hide in your box in order to collect gossip for your sleazy paper, isn't that right?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're not really friends with Juniper, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. No duh! She's the target of my scoops, and my readers demand dirt! Extra, extra! "The Dirty Little Secret of the Squeaky Clean Student Council President!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dirty little secret...? All right, what are you planning to say in court, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">I'm a witness to her part in the crime. I'm going to tell it all in a shocking exposé! The end justifies the means. That's my brand of tell-all journalism!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The end justifies the means? Wait a second!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">In this dark age of the law, many of us embrace Prof. Means's methods, even future judges. I've even adopted an end-justifies-the-means brand of journalism, which includes... ...tape recorders secretly hidden all over our campus... ...secretly recording every last word without anyone being any the wiser!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Doesn't she realize that's totally illegal?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">And one of them was at the scene of the crime -- the art room!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You put a tape recorder in the art room? What did it record?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. You wanna know? You really wanna know?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, please! That's so nice of you to--</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! Like I'd really tell you now! The big scoop comes out in court tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tsk! You're so mean, Myriam!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">According to my evidence, a fatal fissure had opened between the three of them.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who? Junie, Hugh, and Robin? And what do you mean by fatal fissure?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Juniper, Hugh, and Robin used to be the best of friends.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Used to be? They still seem to get along fine to me. <thought>I did sense some discord, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. You don't know anything. Prof. Means has his followers and Prof. Courte had hers. Their influence is inescapable!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you implying that one of them adheres to that extreme idea you and Prof. Means have? <thought>But why would anyone follow that philosophy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. How could you possibly understand. You're new around here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Myriam, wouldn't you feel better if you came out of the dark and into the light?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. I can see fine in here. You'll be the one's [sic] seeing the light in court tomorrow. Then you'll realize how guilty Juniper Woods really is! Sss, sss, sss! Sss, sss, sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! I love this newspaper! The paper quality, the printing method, the smell of the ink... Could it be more perfect?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... Is it really that amazing?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Meh! You just don't get it, do you?! Toilet paper, hamster cage lining, window wiper! My paper is so awesomely versatile!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Am I to understand that the contents run the entire spectrum of fecal matter as well...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">My script was way more popular than Juniper's.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Wow, was that the majority opinion?</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Yep. My behind-the-scenes maneuvers, threats, and deceptions worked like a charm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Myriam, this may come as a surprise to you, but that's called "cheating."</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss. Says you. I didn't break the law. Besides, the end justifies the means. That's what they teach us here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently, some people are already thriving in the dark age of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Scuttlebutt">Sss, sss, sss! If you wanna give me a present, slip it through a hole in my box. Or if it's too big, you can open the top and gimme it that way! So, which way is it gonna be? Sss, sss, sss!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Either way creeps me out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. We're going to have cross-examine [sic] her tomorrow, but I don't know where to start.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, let's at least take care of whatever we can today.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right. Let's see what else we can find out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, maybe it's about time we wrapped up our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh, wait. We haven't met with Junie yet.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's head over to the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-Thena. Thank you so much for coming.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She called me "Thena," like she used to. Maybe she's finally letting her guard down.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie, the crime's unfolding exactly like your script. Any idea what's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">We wanted to make it fair, so the script was kept secret until the day of the mock trial. And the only people who knew the details were Prof. Courte and I.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... Nothing we haven't heard already so far.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">However...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes?! What is it, Junie?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, there was this one article in the school paper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean this one? It's more like a tabloid piece than a newspaper article, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I've... been worried that the trial would wreck the friendship between Robin, Hugh, and me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She wants to stay friends, but both of the guys are hoping to take it to the next level. Oh, the passion of high school drama...! Wish I could've experienced it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">And I know I shouldn't have, but... I revised the script to favor the prosecution. But Prof. Courte noticed it immediately and changed it back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ahh, so if Robin had won, Hugh wouldn't have been able to confess his love to Junie. That would've kept the trio's relationship the same. Never knew Junie could be so devious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Sorry. I guess my personal problems won't be of any help in court, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You never know. Help often comes from the most unexpected places. Thanks, Juniper.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was wondering about that awl you had on you when you were arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Detective Fulbright! We found this in the suspect's pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Hm? Wh-Why there's...! There's blood on this!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Th-That's evidence we made for the mock trial!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">A mock... trial? Never heard of such a thing, but it sounds fishy to me! Real fishy!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It was the murder weapon from the mock trial. Prof. Courte and I were prepping it in the art room until the day before the trial. I didn't even realize I still had it on me until I was arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then we've nothing to worry about. There shouldn't be any way to link it to the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Still, that blood-red color on the awl bothers me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wasn't it just paint or something? I mean, I was looking at it from pretty far away, but...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It probably was just paint, but that's what bothers me. It wasn't on the awl when we were prepping it yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It wasn't? Then how and when did it get there?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, before the mock trial began, I showed Thena and Mr. Wright to the waiting room... ...then I went back to my dressing room to get the trial props we were going to use. That's when I found the art room key and the awl with what looked like blood on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A key... and the awl?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Prof. Courte normally has the art room key since she's the Fine Arts Club's advisor. And since that key was there in the dressing room... ...I thought she was the one who had painted the awl to look like it had blood on it. After all, she always insisted that the props should be realistic, so...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The awl suddenly shows up on the day of the trial with what looks like blood on it? I have a really bad feeling about this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Me, too. But let's not jump the gun on this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You and Prof. Courte were busy preparing for the mock trial together yesterday, right? Was that the last time you saw her?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">...Yes. I left school at around 6:00 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you notice anything different about her?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">No, I didn't notice anything out of the ordinary. She looked and acted the same as always. I would've never guessed she'd end up like this.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Um... I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't go around showing that to everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How come? I mean, it's so well made. Aren't you going to wear it when you sing?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*sigh*... Yes, unfortunately, I've been chosen to sing. But I don't think I'm up to the task.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Reminds me of the old Junie when you talk like that. Makes me want to protect you.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I can't let you do that. After all, I'm Student Council President! It's my job to look after our entire student body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So what if you took that can-do spirit and applied it to your singing?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*sigh*... But we're talking about me singing in front of a huge crowd.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Maybe she is in over her head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I wish the mock trial had ended better than it did...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but to have three good friends all play leading roles? It's pretty amazing if you think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's true. And it's thanks to the strength of our friendship. There's nothing we can't do if we help and support each other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know... Is that really the issue here? <thought>But whenever I bring it up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes, that's what it's all about! The friendship between the three of us is absolute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena, it's obvious that they're friends, so let's leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, I know that, but... <thought>Her words seem kind of forced.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll do everything we can to prove you innocent tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I know. And I believe in you, Thena. Well, I should go now. Bye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is she gonna be all right? She's like a shadow of the girl we met back at the academy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Junie I knew was always like that -- a little weak and sickly. But the fact that she's lifted her façade shows that she trusts us. Even still...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, when Junie and her two friends were talking about their friendship... ...I sensed some discord in their hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seriously?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but it was really faint. I might've been mistaken. <thought>There's no reason to doubt their friendship... is there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry, everything will be fine! You and Juniper are friends, right? You know that friend I mentioned to you earlier? Well, get this. Whenever something's troubling one of us, the other can just feel it. That's real friendship.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I suppose you're right... Might as well forget about that and concentrate on the trial!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yup! Tomorrow's the big day. Let's sort out what we know so far.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay! The victim Constance Courte was murdered in the art room on the third floor. Then, her body was moved to the outdoor stage in the quad. Also, the location where we found the body was just as the mock trial script described.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wish those were the only similarities they shared.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What I mean is the script and this case are exactly the same in almost every respect. So it follows that the actual trial may very well unfold just like the mock trial did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no! <thought>The mock trial ended right before the prosecution was about to win! Well, that's not gonna happen! This time, Junie WILL be declared "not guilty"! Of course, I intend to get our results the honest way. We can do this! We'll be fine! After all, I have Apollo and he's the king of being fine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nothing of particular interest here.</line>
</xml>