<xml>
<title>Turnabout Goodbyes</title>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey, Nick! Do you know if there's any good waterfalls around here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Waterfalls...? Dare I ask why?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Duh, Nick! Isn't it obvious? I need a waterfall to stand under! Preferably a freezing one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Oh... Is that part of your spirit medium training?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! Except, I've been slacking off lately... I need to brave the elements and be forged anew under the rushing spring waters!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Okay... I don't know about any falls per se, but Gourd Lake is pretty close...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. Darn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but them's the breaks. Couldn't you just take a cold shower or something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Good idea!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So much for the rushing spring waters...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="TV">Next in the news... A large, unidentified animal was sighted at Gourd Lake! The town is buzzing with excitement! Locals are calling it "Gourdy" in a tip of the hat to Nessie, the Loch Ness monster. Though its namesake, Nessie, proved to be a hoax... locals are confident their Gourdy is the real deal. ... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The water pressure's kind of low in that shower.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You want more pressure, huh? Why don't you go down to the fire department and have them spray you with the hose?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Good idea, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apparently, E.S.P. is no aid in detecting sarcasm...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="TV">We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin! Strange occurrences continue at Gourd Lake... But this time, it's murder! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gourd Lake again?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="TV">The body of a man was found in the lake early this morning. A suspect was apprehended. Sources inside the police department revealed... that the suspect's name is Miles Edgeworth, age 24. Edgeworth was an up-and-coming prosecution attorney, known for his skill and connections. He was guaranteed a long and rewarding career... has he thrown it all away? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...? E-Edgeworth!?</thought> What's going on!? Edgeworth would never do something like--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yipes! M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The fireman yelled at me when I called him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We've got bigger things to worry about than that! They arrested Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? You mean, the prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he's a suspect... in a murder!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaat!? When? Where? Whom? Why? How?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go find out, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Difficult-looking legal books stand in a formidable row. They mock me. I tried reading one, and it made my head hurt. When I closed it, it slipped out of my hand. Then my foot hurt too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's favorite plant. Its name is "Charley." Maya's gotten the knack of watering it lately. Charley's been perking up these days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. If we had more clients, I would probably sit here more often. Lately, I've been spending more time on the couch, watching TV.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya brought in a poster of the Steel Samurai the other day. We had a big fight over whether to put it up or not. I know she's just waiting for a chance to sneak it up on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it's cleaning day again at the hotel across the way. I hear they're planning a second branch outside the city. I can see the bellboy, getting the angle of that screwdriver in the drawer just right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean!? Let's investigate! We should talk to Mr. Edgeworth, and check out the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're right... We need more information! Save aimlessness and confusion for later!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? Got any good ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not really. I do my best thinking when I'm standing underneath a waterfall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I think it's developing a nice luster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll look at your badge later, Nick. We've got work to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose you're right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, Nick... We've all been in here one time or another, haven't we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it comes with the territory.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not sure it's something we should mention to too many people... Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Hey! Edgeworth! Come back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I don't think he's in a very good mood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he is in detention. Were you in a good mood when you were here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you've come to laugh at the fallen attorney? Then laugh, laugh! Well? Why aren't you laughing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Should we be laughing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah. It's a trick. Laugh and he'll get mad... or burst into tears. Edgeworth. We don't have so much free time we can spend it coming down here to laugh at you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Yes you do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, he's right.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I hoped you wouldn't come. I didn't want you to see me. Not like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey, I didn't want to see you either, believe me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile for the camera...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He hasn't moved an inch since I came in. A real pro. Or maybe he's just nervous with Edgeworth in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth. Tell me what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Why should I? What are you going to do about it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Duh! We're going to help you, that's what!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! ... Help me? You? Don't be ridiculous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're a novice! You've only been in three trials!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sure, you got lucky and won all three... But your luck's bound to run out some day! You need real skill, Wright. Experience!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! He's insulting you! Nick? Why am I always the one who has to get angry!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder took place at Gourd Lake, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... late last night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The lake is a long way away from your offices and the court... Why were you down there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I see no need to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-Mr. Edgeworth! You... you didn't really...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Gourdy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I went to see Gourdy.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Gourdy"? What's that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll... tell you later. <thought>Why won't Edgeworth talk to us?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your attorney's badge...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth. Let me defend you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Hah! Hah hah! Good one, Wright. But I'm not that hard up. Not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Me? Trust a wet-behind-the-ears lawyer with only three trials under his belt? Never!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My case is near hopeless, Wright. Every defense attorney I've talked to has turned me down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Simply put, they were afraid they'd lose. It occurred to me that it might be my fault that they lack confidence. After all, I did get every single one of their clients declared "guilty."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Regardless, I don't want you involved in this. You in particular I cannot ask to do this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth... this is really hard for me to ask... But... you didn't do it, right? Right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Think what you will. I have only one request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stay out of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why!? B-but Nick is trying to help you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know...! I know that! But I don't want your help, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">!!! Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Look, just go away, and leave me alone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Mr. Edgeworth did it, didn't he.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Let's go investigate elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He hasn't moved an inch since I came in. A real pro. Or maybe he's just nervous with Edgeworth in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is where it happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Gourd Lake is in the middle of this park.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can see some police walking around in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Questioning people, probably.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Isn't that Detective Gumshoe over there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal!? There's enough of us here! Anyone found anything?</line>
<line speaker="Police">S-sorry, sir... Nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Idiot! The trial's tomorrow! We need clues, on the double!</line>
<line speaker="Police">B-but, sir... There weren't any clues... that's why we arrested that attorney, Mr. Edgeworth! It's clear, sir. He's the one who--</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Shaddup! Just you try saying that again! I'll... er... I'll make you sorry if you do! I mean... just, get outta my face, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Police">Y-yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe's kinda scary today!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Recruits... peh! ... Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're that Harry guy! Harry Butz!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wright! Phoenix Wright! <thought>Will he ever learn my name!?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And just what are you doing here, pal? Investigating!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Um, well, yes. I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'm here to help! Ask me anything you want! Bring it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He seems different than usual. I wonder what's up? Umm... Mr. Edgeworth hasn't actually asked us to defend him yet...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Oh? Y-you don't say...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I feel winter's chill from the bare leaf trees today... *sigh* What is it about winter that turns people into poets?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know, but my toes are starting to feel numb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes... my poetry has that effect on some people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sign says "Gourd Lake Nature Park." This place is full of families picnicking on the weekend.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... no waterfall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not many picnickers come here for spiritual training, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe? Do you know what happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? You don't know, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wow, okay, Mr. head-in-the-fluffy-pink-clouds Lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Head-in-the... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Never mind, I'll tell you. It happened last night, about 15 minutes after midnight. There was a boat out on Gourd Lake. In that boat were two men. One of those men shot the other with a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And... the shooter was Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A cop who arrived on the scene arrested him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How did he get there so fast?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... There was a witness. When the report came in, we raced to the lake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A witness?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You don't think Mr. Edgeworth is a... murderer!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Absolutely not! It's impossible! I don't care if there's a witness either! I don't believe a lick of it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-right! Who cares what the witness says!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I care!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... You really believe in him, don't you, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Course I do! But... the police are pretty sure he's the killer. Nobody's even really taking this investigation that seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">After all the help Mr. Edgeworth has been to us... Hard to imagine that no one's standing up to take his side.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, at least you are, Detective. At least you are.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know who will be Mr. Edgeworth's defense attorney in tomorrow's trial?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He hasn't got one yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? The trial IS tomorrow, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I don't know the whole story... But apparently no one he's been talking to will take his case.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-why not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth won't tell me! When you guys showed up, I figured he'd asked you to defend him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">U-unfortunately not...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, pal, then you got a job to do! Help out Mr. Edgeworth! Prove that badge you wear isn't just some fancy piece of metal! Prove it to me, pal! Show me you're an attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-is it true? No one will take Mr. Edgeworth's case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... He's a bit of a celebrity. If you defended him, and lost, your reputation'd be sure to suffer. What's more... The case against him is... well, it's pretty solid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose it would be if they have a witness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Pal! Don't tell me your going to turn your back on him too!? Remember the Steel Samurai! Mr. Edgeworth helped you get your client declared innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I know. I went to Edgeworth. I tried. He really doesn't want us to represent him. Especially not us, he said.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? W-well, that doesn't make any sense, pal! You should have heard him talking about you after the Steel Samurai case! He kept saying "Wright, Wright, Wright" over and over.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Nick? I'm not sure that's a good sign.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Neither am I...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why wouldn't he want your help? I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who was this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Er, sorry, pal. That's confidential. Anyway, the witness saw everything, apparently. I'm sure they'll turn up at the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was there only that one witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep. It was pretty cold out on the lake last night. And, it was Christmas Eve after all. Still, we're being thorough. You never know when you're going to turn up another witness. That's why we're here today, checking things out. So far, we're coming up empty...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! It's Christmas today! I'd forgotten. What are you getting me for Christmas, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Talk to Santa.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That badge! You're showing that to the wrong guy, pal! You gotta show that to someone who needs it!</line>
<line speaker="Police">Detective Gumshoe, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What? Find something!?</line>
<line speaker="Police">Um, no, sir. Not yet. But there was a call from the precinct. They want to hold an investigation briefing...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A briefing? Right! I'm off! Oh... Sorry, pal. I guess you heard. I gotta go. Any last things you want to ask me about before I head back?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, yes. Do you have any information on the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry... They haven't worked up the autopsy report yet. I'm still waiting for it myself. Actually... Say, if you get the time, drop by the precinct! We can talk more there, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're not coming back, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Erm... Probably not, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what should we do if we have something to talk to you about...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, right. Here, I'll show you how to get to the precinct. Come down and see me anytime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, hey! Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, we'd like to take a look around in the park. Can we walk around?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! No problem, pal. You got my permission.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, Nick. I think there's something to be said for talking to people when they're busy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. They don't have time to think about not giving you information...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Now, let's get investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Looks like Detective Gumshoe isn't here.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Something wrong, miss? Hmm? Turning yourself in? Okay, what did you do? Shoplifting? Larceny? Public indecency...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no! None of those things! We're looking for Detective Gumshoe... is he around?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Gumshoe? Oh yeah. He's in a meeting right now. I don't think he'll be out any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, we'll come back.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">You do that. Oh, and go straight home and stay out of trouble. No more shoplifting, you got that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Do I look like a criminal or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of a female police officer... Wait, no. That's the latest "Babes in Uniform" calendar. My bad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"...your mama could see you know she'd be crying'... ...a break and spit it out, you lowlife scumbag..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for interrogations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These are the detectives' desks. There are computers and files on each one. Funny, they're a lot tidier than I'd expect. I guess the detectives don't spend a lot of time at their desks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, is that the police department's mascot...?</line>
<line speaker="Chief">That's the "Blue Badger"! It was my idea! I made it! It's my mascot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... see. How nice.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">I'll get him assigned mascot of the Criminal Affairs Dept. if it's the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Wha...!? "Gourd Lake...!" "Gourdy sighted"!!! I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Shouldn't you be reading something more important...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wowsers! This is "Gourd Lake"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup. I'm not sure it warrants a "wowsers," though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. Probably not. But hey, look at that snack stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Samurai Dogs"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wanna Samurai Dog! Please! I bet they're great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">With a name like Samurai Dog, how could they not be?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They're a little behind the times, though. The kids are all into "The Pink Princess" now. I mean, like, y'know!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nope.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. Gourd Lake is really big.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick. Why is it called "Gourd Lake"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Well, a long time ago, they used to grow gourds here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! No way! I was sure it was because the lake looked like a gourd when viewed from above! You know, like an hourglass shape?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it is shaped like a gourd, actually. But that's just a coincidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. Okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trashcan is empty. At least the place is well maintained.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lineup of plastic benches. I guess the idea is you buy a dog and eat it here. I doubt anyone would sit here and eat on a day like this. Except maybe Maya... if she had a Samurai Dog.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh... I almost didn't see that signpost. "Left - Boat docks" "Right - Exit"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A hotdog stand. It's closed... The Christmas fringe looks a little half-baked. The banner reads "Samurai Dogs"... Somebody needs to redecorate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh. Someone left one of those poppers here. You know, you pull the string...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...and it goes "pop." Yeah, I know the ones. You see them a lot around New Year's.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! It might be a clue! Let's take it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">C'mon, admit it. You just want to pop it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Was it that obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A popper... hmm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nah, let's leave it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, listen to your inner child a little, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe if you outer child would be quiet for just a moment, Maya!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I suppose it couldn't hurt. Huh? Where'd it go?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I already put it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! If we don't hurry Mr. Edgeworth will get the death sentence!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! O-okay! Let's go check things out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's that? I'm not in the mood for idle banter, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... what is this place?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A boat rental shop. Closed for Christmas it seems. I guess a murder taking place on one of the boats won't be good for business, either.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boats... I've never ridden on a boat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Well, how about we go out on one when the trial is finished?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, good idea! You bet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's more forest off that way. I doubt I'd find any helpful clues in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A small boat rental shop. Doesn't look like anyone is around. They're probably closed because it's Christmas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are some boats floating at the dock. Was one of these boats used in the murder, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I changed my mind. I don't really want to go for a boat ride.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I like it here, Nick. Look... someone's camping!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They've got guts, camping at the scene of a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey, Nick! If they were camping here last night, they might know about the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true...</thought> Good call, Maya. Let's go talk to them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Check out this camera!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... what's with the big mic and that box on top, I wonder? It looks like some sort of automatic system for taking a photo when a noise is heard.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Hey, let's see if it works! *cough* "Hi, I'm Nick!" ... Maybe I'm not saying it loud enough. "YO! I'M NICK!!!" ... Huh. NIIIIIIIIII......IIIIIIIIIICK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Will you stop that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think it's broken, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-don't kick it! <thought>It must not be set up to respond to voices.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trees grow quite thick here. Further back, the trees fade into the shadow where the sunlight can't reach them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The trees grow quite thick here. Further back, the trees fade into the shadow where the sunlight can't reach them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sign says "No Camping." Funny place to pick to pitch your tent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait, what if the sign said "No Setting Tents on Fire"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I don't think they have signs like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's food and some magazines on the sheet. It takes a pretty tough skin to camp in this cold.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, don't tell me you're hungry again?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, no. I was just wondering, why are camping pots and pans made of aluminum?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... They didn't talk about that in any of the law books.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, there's no law saying they have to be made out of aluminum, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not having this conversation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This SUV has seen better days. It's dented all over. I can't believe anyone would drive their car down here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This camera has a mic and some sort of attachment. It must take pictures when triggered by a noise.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Cool! Let's try it out! *cough* "Hi, I'm Nick!" ... Maybe I'm not saying it loud enough. "HEY! I'M NICK!!!" ... Huh. NIIIIIIIIII......IIIIIIIIIICK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Will you stop that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it's broken?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-don't kick it! Maybe it isn't set up to respond to voices?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well what then? I know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The party popper...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Yep. It responded.</line>
<line speaker="???">Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaw! Hey, you! Git yer hands offa' that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="???">What in the Sam Hill...!? Look what ya done now! There goes a whole roll of film!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah? Wha... huh? S-sorry!</line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry's nice but it don't pay my bills! Y'all know how much a roll of film costs!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I'll pay you back!</line>
<line speaker="???">What were ya'll thinkin' settin' off a party-popper in a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh... well...</line>
<line speaker="???">What! Don't try to play stupid with me just 'cause you think I'm some country bumpkin! Yeah, I know how y'all Yanks think! "I say, those southern folks talk with that exaggerated drawl, why they must be dumb!" Well let me tell you, just because I might be dumb don't mean we all are!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick, help!</line>
<line speaker="???">And who are you, now? Her chaperone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, uh, no, rather, uhh... we're sort of... friends?</line>
<line speaker="???">Jus' figure out what y'all are gonna say and say it for bejeezum's sake! Gawd, I'd rather sit through one of papa's drawls than listen to you stutter all day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy... I guess we should pay her for the film...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Watch it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes ma'am. <thought>On second thought, I'll pay later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm really sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This camera is rigged to respond to noise. But it only responds to loud noises... like a party popper.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ummm...</line>
<line speaker="???">What!? Can't ya see I'm changin' the film on my camera here! Someone--I'm not namin' any names--but someone used up a WHOLE ROLL.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't work... I wonder if I have anything to show her that would get her attention...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, er, this is my badge.</line>
<line speaker="???">Huh? Aren't badges supposed t' be all shiny and impressive? You a cop or something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="???">Wh-what!? Y'all ain't gonna try and pull one o' them lawsuits on me over that film now? Cause I'll have you know I'm a fighter and I wrassled meaner looking' things'n you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, that's not it at all. We're here investigating a murder that took place here, on the lake.</line>
<line speaker="???">A murder...? ... Sounds cool! Why didn't y'all say that in the first place! Go ahead, ask me anything ya like!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finally! Some cooperation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You too. Y'all can come out of hiding now. I won't bite. Hard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Come to think of it, where did Maya get to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-sorry... I-I was feeling a little overwhelmed. The culture gap and all...</line>
<line speaker="???">Never you mind, honey. I kin' talk Yank for ya if... ahem... if it pleases you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-thanks. I think I'll be okay.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Great then! I'm Lotta, Lotta Hart, but y'all can call me Lotta! I'm here photographing meteor showers for a research project. Mighty pleased ta meet ya!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh yeah, when was that murder, anyway? I ain't seen much television lately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It happened late in the night on Christmas Eve.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That so? Christmas Eve?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A man on a boat was shot... Did you see anything?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, lemme see. A boat, ya say? I reckon I mighta seen one... not sure though. Y'all gotta remember I've been watching this here lake for a good three days now. I seen enough boats to choke a mule. Kinda hard to remember which I seen when.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what is it you do, Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh? Me? Hah hah. Y'all don't really want to know that, do ya? Actually, I'm a research student at Country U., right in the heart of the heartland.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Neat! Nick! She's a research student at a university! Country U.!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... so I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, when did you come up here?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hmm, lemme see... I guess it was 'bout three days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you photographing?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">D-didn't I tell y'all that already? Meteors! Yep, meteor showers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Falling stars...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's quite a camera you have there.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all better know it! It's German-made. A genuine Solingen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Isn't that where they make knives...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... So, what's that device you have stuck to the camera?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh? Device?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It started moving all by itself when I fired my party popper...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh that? That triggers the shutter whenever it detects certain sounds. It's programmed to pick up loud noises right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A programmable camera! Neat!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">So yer a lawyer, huh? Tell the truth, yer badge is a lot more impressive than you are.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hah... hah... oh. Ahem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, your camera... it triggers on loud explosion noises?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Ayup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, the victim in the case we're researching--he was shot with a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">A pistol...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Now wouldn't a gunshot make a similar noise to our party popper...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I guess it would.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your camera... didn't get a picture of the murder, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">... Hey! Y'all are pretty bright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I see what yer sayin'... Tell ya what, I'll have a look-see at my film.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would have been a photo taken late last night...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I checked 'em once, don't remember if there was anything on 'em though. But what if I got sumtin'! I could be witness to a genuine murder! Yeehaw! I'll go check that film. Y'all come back now, y'hear?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She went inside her SUV. I guess we should come back later...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who was that with the camrea...? Lotta something? Let's go talk to her about that photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I guess Detective Gumshoe is still in that meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Thanks for coming down, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">We just finished the meeting. For better or for worse...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get the feeling we're in for some bad news...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"All right, hands against the wall, all o' you... Don't even think about escaping! I got eyes in the back of my head!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for arrests.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you know anything about the victim yet?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No, no... Still can't I.D. him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Has Mr. Edgeworth said anything?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not a word.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how did the meeting go?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I can't tell you, pal! You're a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-true...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Y'know... I don't know what to believe anymore. Sure, Mr. Edgeworth's human like you or me. Still... I get the feeling that if he'd done something wrong, he wouldn't go hiding it. That's just the kind of guy he is. Why can't anyone else see that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, they think that Mr. Edgeworth did it...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, the trial's starting tomorrow, as scheduled.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... hey, in the end you did tell us about the meeting!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Don't go telling anyone else, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And... do me a favor! Stand by Mr. Edgeworth! He needs help, and you're the ones to help him! I'm sure he's got some reason why he won't talk to us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe... How come you trust Mr. Edgeworth so much?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I'd think that was obvious. We got a strong working relationship, us two. We trust each other, and that's how it works.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A "working relationship"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">See, Mr. Edgeworth always gets his defendants declared "guilty" every time. Yeah, his methods right be a little extreme at times. But... there's a reason! He trusts our investigation, see? He trusts us to get the right man! That's why I work extra hard, pal. We've got to earn that trust he places in us.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth is a man you can trust... And you have my word on that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering, did you ever get that autopsy report?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that? Yeah, I made a copy for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you show me that photo of the victim? ... That face...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone you know?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... I don't know. I just have this feeling that I met him somewhere a long time ago. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya seems lost in thought.</thought> You remember anything?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess not.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I hope it helps you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry, I'm drawing a blank right now.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. Nothing... just, something's been bothering me. ... Could you show me that autopsy report once more? ... ... ... Hey! I-I remember now! This guy! This is a lawyer that was at that office Mia worked at! I met him once when I went there to hang out with Sis!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That office...? Wait! You mean Grossberg's office?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! That guy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was the last name I expected to come up... Maybe I should go talk to him... for old time's sake.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... The police have pretty much made up their minds that Mr. Edgeworth did it. And Mr. Edgeworth won't tell us anything. I guess we could go look for clues down by the lake?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? Penny for your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thoughts... Thoughts... Yeah, why won't Mr. Edgeworth tell us anything? And... and... And why did he refuse to ask for our help? What a jerk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... This person was a lawyer at Grossberg's office. Let's go talk to him! Mr. Grossberg, I mean, not the dead guy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been a while since I was here last. Mr. Grossberg is out as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Look at the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That painting is still missing... Mia must have known about the deal with Mr. Grossberg and Redd White... She kept track of all of White's extortion and blackmail rackets.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Expensive-looking mahogany bookshelves, filled with expensive-looking books. Hmm... funny... they don't look like they've ever been read.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well then let's take them back to our office! He won't miss them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, we don't need them.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then, can we take that wooden bear?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. It is kind of cute.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A solid mahogany desk. The wood's been polished to a deep luster.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! I want a desk like that in our office too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. I don't think I'm ready to sit at a desk like that yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? I meant for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd better start saving your allowance, then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why is the wall there a different color?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A big painting was hanging there until recently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh. What happened to it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... well, he gave it to someone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet he gave it to some romantic interest! Love blooms eternal, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An expensive potted plant. No idea what kind of plant it is, but it's probably the most expensive one available.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think our Charley is cuter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. He's a really cute... plant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A table for clients. Hmm... an elegant ebony case, and if I'm not mistaken, that lighter's made of solid gold. Even I can tell someone here's got money to burn.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We should put things on our client table too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not really into smoking.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We could put out candy, or gum.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Classy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'm sorry. I can't think of anything I want to say about that.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey y'all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wait up a sec! We got bingo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bingo...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">My automatic camera took two pictures last night!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">This is them. Take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait...!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">See? See? He's shooting him with that pistol!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-it looks like that, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But you can't really tell who that is shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, well there was enough fog out there last night t' strangle a bullfrog. But, y'know... Seeing these photos reminded me of something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I saw the murder happen. I'm a witness!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaa!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-are you serious!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Course!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How do you forget... never mind.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all reckon I should tell the cops?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... reckon so!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What's that? Now don't y'all go tryin' to mock my accent! I'm a sensitive lady!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... reckon no!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What's that? Now don't y'all think y'all can pull one over on me just cause you speak the lingo! I know enough to know that when you see a murder, you'd best tell the cops! It's my obligation as a citizen!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, so, I'm off to talk to the cops. Y'all can have this photo. Later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-w-wait! Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What? Can't y'all see I'm kinda busy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">T-tell us what you saw, too! Please?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nice try, honey, but I wasn't born yesterday. I'm a witness, and that means I'm on the side of justice, and that means the cops! I'd sooner eat the south side of a north-bound skunk than tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Don't let it get your skivvies in a bunch. Friends today, enemies tomorrow! Or was that the other way round? No matter. I'm gone! Hey! Maybe they'll let me do some testifying! Hot darn!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She left... ... Well, that's one more witness. What do we do now, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, if she saw something, there's not much we can do about it. The question is: what exactly did she see...? I guess we'll find out in the trial tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An expensive-looking camera faces the lake. Next to it is a large microphone and a blue plastic sheet. Hmm. Looks like a computer is attached to the camera.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Looks like the police have given up their questioning.</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah! N-Nick! I think Santa's mad at you!</line>
<line speaker="???">Long time no see, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... you know Santa!? Wow... Nick and St. Nick... Hey! I see the connection!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't be ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="???">Dude, it's me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L... Larry! What are you doing here!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Isn't it obvious? I'm working my day job! I sell Samurai Dogs! Want one? Gotta get money for dates, you know, My girl Kiyance deserves the best!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>K-Kiyance...? Not another model, I hope...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, Kiyance's a fine, fine woman, Nick. It was her idea that I wear this costume! She was all "You go girlfriend!" Y'know? She bought this costume for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That... that's great, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! A Santa costume! She must be really nice!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoa! Cute! Nick! Who's she? She's not your...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not my... what? N-no, she's not!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm his partner, Maya Fey. I'm, uh, the little sister.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sister...? ... Wow, Nick, must be tough. Working nine to five, having to take care of a little sister...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no, I'm not Nick's sister, I'm my older sister's little sister...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh. Sounds great!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't worry, Maya, he's not listening...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick, benches! Let's take a break... maybe have a dog?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think not. It's too cold to sit and eat hotdogs out here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wimpy city boy! You should try standing under a freezing waterfall some time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't get over the Samurai Dogs...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "Original" Samurai Dogs, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, man, whoever calls their product the "original" first wins!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't you add "world-famous" to the sign?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, good idea!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What have I done...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Larry. There was a murder here last night... You work here. Have you heard anything?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you're wasting your time. Last night was Christmas Eve! He was with Kiyance, obviously! He wouldn't have been standing out here in the cold!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think what you just said caught him off guard, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">N-no, it's just... Kiyance's not in town right now. She... she's in Hawaii on a photo shoot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A model. I knew it.</thought> Well, anyway, there was a murder here on the lake. The trial's tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh. Neat.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant is Edgeworth. Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick? Why would Larry know Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoa, Nick! You don't mean THAT Miles Edgeworth!? Old Edgey!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. He's a murder suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-whoa! Murder?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? You know Mr. Edgeworth, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! Of course! Edgey was in the same class as us in grade school!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... umm... tell me about the dogs!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Oh, you mean the Samurai Dogs?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-why are they Samurai Dogs? I... I mean they kind of look gourd-shaped.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, well originally, they were Gourd Dogs! Y'know, like "guard dogs"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ouch...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The Samurai thing was Kiyance's idea. Oh, she's my woman, y'know. She was all "change the name and you go girlfriend!" She made me that banner! Man, the kids can't get enough of those Samurai Dogs!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Err... Something about that just seems... wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, and guess what? We're getting a ton of customers here at the lake, what with the big news!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "big news"...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">G-"Gourdy"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, Mr. Edgeworth was your classmate, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah, Nick, him, and I used to hang out all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... I never knew.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Don't get me wrong. He's always been kind of a stick in the mud. Studying all the time, trying to "be like father."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Like his father...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. Edgey's pop was a famous defense lawyer back in the day.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. Wait... You said "defense lawyer"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait a second! But Mr. Edgeworth is a prosecuting attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">What? Edgey's got a proboscis on his knee!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, no--he's a "prosecuting attorney." That's like the total opposite of a defense lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Huh. Go figure! He always used to talk about defending the "weak" who were "unable to defend themselves." Man, he used to go on and on about man's duty to society and all that. What a bore! I wonder that changed his mind, though? Do you know, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... what's "Gourdy"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? You mean you don't know? It's here, in this very lake! A giant, mysterious monster! Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A... monster?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. Check it out. This is an article from yesterday's newspaper. There's a photo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! It's r-really real! Nick! A monster! A real monster!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... yeah. <thought>It's probably just a log or something... right?</thought> Hey... there's a quote here from the person who took the photo. Hmm? What's this? "I set the camera to automatic, and when we got into the frame... I heard a loud 'bang'! Like an explosion... followed by the sound of something slipping into the water..."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish I could have seen it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would there be a sound like an explosion...?</thought> Larry. Could I borrow this article from you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sure, no problem. That'll be one million dollars!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-one million...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grow up, Larry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Nick, show me that article once more. "I set the camera to automatic, and when we got into the frame... I heard a loud 'bang'! Like an explosion... followed by the sound of something slipping into the water..." How romantic! And cool! I mean, to think, a real monster!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah. I'm just glad I'm selling more dogs!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Oh, that's your attorney's badge, isn't it? Dude, you really helped me out back in that trial. S-sorry, I can't really pay you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Cause you blow it all on "Kiyance"...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">But... you can have all the dogs you want!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-really!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... If you let her at your dogs, you won't have any left for the other customers.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, no problem. If that's what makes her happy, y'know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How many times do I have to remind you that it was ME who got you off the hook!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whazzat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a camera. You take pictures with it.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">L-Larry! You mean you don't know what a camera is!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">C-course I know! Hey, you're looking at a bona fide junior high graduate! I was talking about the weird contraption on that camera!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that. Well... it's hard to explain. Just forget about it.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well don't go showing me it, then! Geez!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey Larry, you know this guy?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Who's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. That' why I asked you.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Who's this, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">W-what's this? You know, my eyes have been getting pretty bad lately, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, the photo's blurry, Larry. It was taken last night.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Last night...?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sorry, Nick. I don't know much about that. I'm just a simple vendor of Samurai Dogs, dig?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Not a Gumshoe in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Police">If you're looking for Detective Gumshoe, he's in the questioning room. Apparently, an important witness turned up. He'll be in there for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lotta Hart... it has to be.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"...move in the crowd. Wear drab clothes... Never enter the target's field of vision..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for trailing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Who would have thought there'd be a photo...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth... Did you shoot him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... What do you think, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think you're the kind to point a gun at anyone, no.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you didn't shoot him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I didn't. It wasn't me.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah-HHHHEM!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ah, that old familiar clearing of the throat!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah hah! You're Mia's... something, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was her understudy, yes. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah hah! And you, you're Mia's... something too, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her little sister, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You've grown! You've come to look a lot like your sister, you know? It takes me back. "Ahh... the days of my youth... like the scent of fresh lemon..." you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Mr. Grossberg, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm...? Ah, yes. I beg your pardon. Of course you came here to discuss something. What is it then? Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a murder last night...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">A murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You haven't heard...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I, er, just got up, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Miles Edgeworth shot someone with a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Edgeworth!? What!? W-who!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the identity of the victim is still unknown.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">T-this is terrible news indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he hadn't heard anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg? Whatever happened to that painting?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh, yes... I do not think it shall ever be coming back home to this office. I can't exactly claim it as stolen... I suppose it's my just desserts. Old, bitter desserts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who is this Hammond guy, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mr. Hammond... He was the defense attorney in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"That case"...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, the "DL-6 Incident."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"DL-6"...? <thought>Why does that sound so familiar?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Perhaps you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm sure someone mentioned it during the trial for Mia's murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That was the incident where the police were so at a loss they used a spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Wait... you don't mean? Was that medium my mother?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, my dear. The spirit medium, Misty Fey, your mother, contacted the spirit of the victim. But... the case was a loss. No conviction was made.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">The DL-6 Incident, yes... Happened 15 years ago. A very strange case, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They never caught the criminal, right?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Correct. Misty Fey used her powers to talk to the spirit of the late victim. Her testimony led to charges being laid against one man. But Mr. Hammond won the case and the suspect was declared innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... And the police blamed my mother, calling her a fraud. You were the one who helped her out then, right, Mr. Grossberg?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Er... y-yes. Yes, quite.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">N-no... please. D-don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>DL-6... Never thought I'd hear that name again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">But wait... What does this case have anything to do with Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It has everything to do with Mr. Edgeworth, my dear! The victim in the DL-6 Incident was none other than his father, Gregory Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what!? His father!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... If you want to know more, you should ask him yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You've really grown up in the past few years, my dear! How proud Mia would be if she could see you now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She said she was more worried about me than anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aww, just go on and take the compliment, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So, this camera on the lake takes a photo whenever it hears an explosion sound?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's what she said.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">And it just happened to be set up on the beach, pointing out on the lake?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes... she said it was to photograph "shooting stars."</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm. Shooting stars... explosions... what's the connection? I'd be suspicious of this witness of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm? Strange... I feel as though I've seen this man somewhere before! ... Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you remember!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He was a lawyer! Here, in my office! That's Hammond! Robert Hammond!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Hammond...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">And you say this is the man Miles Edgeworth shot?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So this is the moment the crime took place, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You can't really say for sure that's Edgeworth. I'm not sure whether that's a good thing or a bad thing. Not sure at all...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Misty Fey. Mother of Mia and Maya Fey. Show this photograph to Miles Edgeworth. He'll have something to say to you then.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Er... my apologies. I'm not sure I can help you with that.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Show him this... I'm sure he'll talk to you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait... This is a photograph of my mother!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My mother... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I've shown her the picture, I can't think of anything to say... That probably wasn't the best thing to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's this? I was hoping you'd gotten my message the first time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, what about your defense?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! It's no concern of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess he hasn't found anyone yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I ask you about the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright. I'll ask you again, just leave me alone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please try to understand. I'm not doing this to prove I'm tough, or because I look down on you. I just don't want you anywhere near this case. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you go to Gourd Lake?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no intention of telling you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nor, apparently, would you tell Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective Gumshoe was really worried about you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The "DL-6 Incident"... was when my father died. Right before my eyes... He was shot and killed, and I saw it all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My memories from that time are... foggy. I suppose it's a self-defense mechanism. In any case, a suspect was arrested... a man. It's pretty clear he was the only one who could have killed my father. The spirit medium they used to talk to my late father said the same thing. It was an attorney by the name of Robert Hammond that cleared the suspect's name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And Hammond... is the victim in the Gourd Lake murder?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... That spirit medium... that was my mom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? You mean you're...? ... It's strange. I thought that terrible incident was about to end, and now... this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"About to end"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The DL-6 Incident happened 15 years ago. 15 years ago... on December 28.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">December 28?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The statute of limitations on the case runs out in three days.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick? What odes that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When a case's statute of limitations runs out, legally, the case never happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Three days from now, DL-6 will be closed... forever.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What happened to the suspect? The one who got off innocent?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know... He disappeared from public view. Nobody knows where to. If he's still alive, he'd be about 50 years old now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I can understand why he'd go into hiding... It'd be hard to live a normal life after being a murder suspect in such a big case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... so, was your father a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was... Gregory Edgeworth. He was quite famous at the time, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, you were sort of trying to follow in his footsteps.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I'd rather not talk about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your attorney's badge...? I can't say I really want to see one of those right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's only been a matter of hours since you last visited. Yet you've made incredible progress in your investigation. I'll admit it, I'm impressed, Wright. You were always single-minded in your work, though. Once you start on something, you always see it through, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the "DL-6 Incident"...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Right... DL-6. I didn't want you to find out about it. That is why I refused your offer to defend me. I'm sorry if it sounded like I thought you weren't up to the job. I just wanted to keep you away from DL-6.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... do you still think it would have been better for me to stay away?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't know. But... I see no point in hiding anything from you now. Very well. Ask whatever you like, and I will answer to the best of my abilities.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It pains me to ask you this now...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know! You want us to defend you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... Will you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, who could have guessed this day would come?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, charley! No way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...!? ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey, don't look so serious, guys! I was kidding! Just a little joke!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was nothing little...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...or joke-like about it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought it was funny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Do it over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. How could I refuse you, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is my chance to finally pay you back.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pay him back...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Pay me back? For what? I don't remember ever doing anything for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Never mind... I guess you don't really need to know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh... My letter of request. Please give it to Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess we should... ... W-what's that!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">E-earthquake! Nick! It's a big one! Whaaaaa! I-it's calming down... ... Whew... that was scary!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? Huh? Where's Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... There. He's on the floor in a ball, shivering. I guess he doesn't do so well with earthquakes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've heard of running, but curling up in a ball?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I guess we're done. Mr. Edgeworth doesn't seem like he's going to stand up any time soon. Let's go, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh.. right. We have to give Edgeworth's letter of request to Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what's wrong, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This wild lady comes in here just a while ago... Says she came "to talk to y'all after hearing what Mr. Wright had to say"! What's this all about, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Lotta Hart...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why are you going around finding more witnesses!? You want to give Mr. Edgeworth the death sentence, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, not at all... Just... I mean, she did see something. There's nothing I can do about that. I can't go around covering up evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Er... You trying to say something about the way I do my job?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No sir!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"Never talk to people in the neighborhood... Turn all the lights in the room off, and close the curtains..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for a stake-out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what did Ms. Hart say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She says she saw Mr. Edgeworth fire the pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She even had a photograph to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. I saw it too... But you really can't tell from the photo who it is shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's why she said she's going to enlarge the photo. She said "it'll drop the quality a mite, but should let us see who's who!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She can do that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, so there's going to be an enlarged photograph that shows Edgeworth in the act. Great. Just great.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">In any case, she's going to be the one testifying tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What happened to the other witness?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... Apparently, there was a cancellation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A "cancellation"...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm afraid tomorrow is going to be life or death for poor Mr. Edgeworth. We got a witness who says she saw the very moment of the murder. And we got a photo taken when the shot rang out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd say that sounds like a pretty unwinnable case... But wait... What did Mia used to say? If he's innocent, there's got to be something I've overlooked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It sound like Mr. Edgeworth is going to ask the state to assign a public defender. I was just asked to file the paperwork. But you still got time, pal! Go talk to him again, for me, please! You have to convince him! You have to make him let you defend him! Please! I know you're the only one who can do it, pal. You're the only one who can save Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal, there's only one thing I want to see from you! And that's a letter of request from Mr. Edgeworth for you to be his defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look what I got.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Hey, you did it, pal! Glad I waited till the last minute to file those papers! I'll rip 'em up and start new ones for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Detective. Well, see you in court tomorrow, then.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Good luck, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You guys feel that earthquake a little while back? I was worried!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Worried? We're fine! I've lived out here my whole life. I'm pretty used to them by now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, I wasn't worried about you two. I was worried about Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, right...</thought> He did seem to over-react a little, now that you mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, well, I'm not surprised. It was a pretty big quake. I'm going to go check on him. You two go eat and get your rest for tomorrow's trial. Later!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I wonder what it is with Mr. Edgeworth and earthquakes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder... He was never that scared of them when he was in school.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then again, I was only in the same class as him for 4th grade. He transferred to another school after that. I wonder what happened to Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>