<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Today will be the final day of this trial. I hope both the prosecution and the defense will be able to present decisive evidence. Very well, Mr. Edgeworth. Your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In yesterday's session, the defense presented us with a new theory for this case. He claims that the scene of the crime was, in fact, Studio Two. Today, I will call on people present in the Studio Two trailer that day. From their testimonies, the truth will become clear.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... very well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth seems a bit on edge today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may call your first witness, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution calls Ms. Dee Vasquez to the stand. Ms. Dee Vasquez is a producer who was present in the Studio Two trailer that day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Will the witness state her name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Dee Vasquez. I am a producer for Global Studios.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the day of the murder, you were in the trailer in Studio Two...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">As everyone here knows, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I dislike needless banter. If you must pontificate, do it when I'm not here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mrrph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-very well, Ms. Vasquez. Please give the court your testimony concerning the day of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I know she did it! Make her pay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right! <thought>If she's guilty, I'll catch her with her pants down... So to speak.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I entered the trailer, oh, a little before noon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I have a question about one part of your testimony. You were "fatigued" so you had Sal "take" you...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The van.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">There's a van at Studio Two. I had him take me in that. I thought it might be risky to walk, what with that monkey's head toppling over.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I see! Very well. Mr. Wright, your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is the final battle, Nick! Let's do it!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I entered the trailer, oh, a little before noon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you didn't stop in at the Employee Area?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">No.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Are you always this... terse?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The meeting began at 12:00 sharp. It ended at 4:00..</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did no one leave during the meeting?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">No one. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... C-come on... let's talk a bit more about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The witness did not come here to engage in idle conversation! Stop interrupting the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The same could be said to you, Mr. Edgeworth. And please stop banging on your little desk. It hurts my ears.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">There was to be a rehearsal afterwards, so we went to Studio One.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And when exactly was that?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I've forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you could try remembering?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">No.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The meeting ended at 4:00, and the rehearsal was scheduled for 5:00... I would think it was between those times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You "would think"!? C'mon, all you did was state the obvious, Edgeworth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I was fatigued, so I had Sal take me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on! You had Sal "take" you? What does that mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">It means what I just said. I had Sal take me in the Studio Two van.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh... oh, right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">At 2:30, we took a 15-minute break in the meeting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what were you doing during that time...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Don't hit your desk. It irritates me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yeah! Mr. Wright...! Oops.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... It was a 15 minute break...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Sal and I ate t-bone steaks on the table in front of the trailer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have someone who can verify this?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Sal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no... I mean someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">One person is enough.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If she committed murder during that break... She wouldn't have had time to eat a t-bone steak! If I had some evidence that proved she didn't eat that steak...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? Find anything?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I kind of wish she'd said a little more...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's hard. I think she's pretty used to being the boss. But I'm sure you'll find some contradiction in what she said... somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah! As I thought!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You claim you ate a t-bone steak! But I say you did not!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-what's this, now, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's... a plate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This plate was on the table in the employee room. As you can see, a large bone has been left behind.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright. Need I remind you it was a T-BONE STEAK!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly my point! Remember if you will... Ms. Vasquez and Mr. Manella ate at a table outside the trailer. Yet there were no bones left on the plates! The plates were bare!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Vasquez? Tell me, how can a person eat a t-bone steak... and not leave the bone? I think I know how!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You ate the bone, too!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick... are you sure? I mean, I love steak, but even I don’t eat the bone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I don’t eat it either!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I, too, leave the bone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, can I try that again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Elementary! You were eating a boneless steak!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Wright, say you are right... What would that prove?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, right, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Remember her testimony? She said she ate a "t-bone steak"! She said "bone"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Correct! I was... testing you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, sure, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry... Can I try that one more time?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't eat any steak during that break! You took your steak and threw it somewhere... like that incinerator!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">! ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I... I see! Then what was Ms. Vasquez doing during her break?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn’t it obvious, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was picking on Mr. Manella!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... Sometimes this court finds it hard to tell whether you are joking or being serious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would prefer it if you remained serious!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor. I'll do my best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She was meeting with the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! A-are you saying...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor! As Ms. Vasquez left the trailer to eat her steak... She ran into the Steel Samurai! And then you did it. You killed him with your own hands!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! I-isn't that a little presumptuous!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of stunt are you trying to pull, Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Let him claim what he wants.... You say I did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Fascinating! And here I was worrying that today would be as boring as all the rest. ... Very well. Let us have a battle of wits, you and I.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Any day, Vasquez!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good luck, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Let's see... What was that murder weapon again? Oh yes, the "Samurai Spear."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I am, as you can see, a woman of petite stature. How could I possibly use that heavy spear as a weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, maybe it's not impossible, but--</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Silence. I'm speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmmph!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The victim was stabbed through the chest from the front, yes? I believe this would indicate that the victim was aware of the killer's presence. Now, the Steel Samurai costume is quite light and mobile. Compared to the victim, I am weaker and slower... I couldn't possibly win such a fight! Not to mention, there is proof I did not have the spear! The photograph of the Steel Samurai shows that the victim himself was holding it! Or do you mean to suggest that I could have wrested it away from him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-yeah! Take that, Wright! If you still think she did it, show us proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... er...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. Look at the data we have on that Samurai Spear in the Court Record. Isn't there something in there that gets to you...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something odd about the Samurai Spear...? ... Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something the matter, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-sorry, Your Honor. I'd like to take back my previous claim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, I won't hold you to your claim. But I'm afraid I will have to penalize you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What’s this? You're taking back your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's backtrack for a moment. I want to consider whether the witness could have used the Samurai Spear or not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you would have a great deal of difficulty using that as a weapon. Pretty much anyone would.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hah. You see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You "don't know"!? What kind of a lawyer are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Quiet. I'm speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">M-m-mmph!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">You "don't know"!? What kind of a lawyer...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know whether you could have fought with the Samurai Spear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, that has no bearing on this case!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Samurai Spear was not the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of this!? The spear was found lying next to the victim's body!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have proof, Your Honor. I can prove that the Samurai Spear was not used as the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wrong, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I haven’t said anything yet...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know you well enough by now to know when you’re going to present the wrong evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can sense it too, with my Fey blood...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, okay, so I picked the wrong evidence! Enough with all the sensing!</thought> Right. Okay, here’s the real evidence, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I present my proof: the so-called "murder weapon"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-but, that IS the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not so fast. Remember that this spear broke during the morning action scene run-through? But, someone fixed the spear. It was the security lady! She fixed it with duct tape! Now tell me, how is it possible... for someone to stab a man who is wearing a thick costume with this!? Through the chest!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright! What are you driving at!? Think about what you're--</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Silence! I’m the one testifying here and I will be heard!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmmph...!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Are you quite sane? Are you even aware of what you're saying? If the Samurai Spear was not the murder weapon, then pray tell what was!? How was Hammer killed?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Can you tell us what weapon was used to kill Mr. Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I can't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"O-of course"!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Can the antics, Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to agree, Mr. Wright. At least pretend that you think you might know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk. Note to self: think before speaking. Tough crowd...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Would I make a claim like that if I couldn't tell you what the weapon was?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I’m afraid your confidence can sometimes be unfounded, Mr. Wright... Very well, let's see this murder weapon, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Think about this some more!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please! How could that possibly have been the murder weapon!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. She has a point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, Your Honor. Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-what is this? Why, that's Jack Hammer standing at the top of the stairs! O-order! Order! If I cannot have order this trial will be suspended! Mr. Wright! What is this all about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This photograph is from five years ago. There was an unfortunate accident at Global Studios. This is a photo of that very accident. Not a word of this was leaked to the outside. It was a close-kept secret at the studios.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What does this have to do with the current case!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Edgeworth... You still can't see it? See the fallen man in this photo? See how the fencepost pierced him through the chest?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh... what!? Are you saying...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. What happened five years ago... has happened again!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Continue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's 2:30 PM on the day of the murder! Ms. Dee Vasquez meets Jack Hammer outside the Studio Two trailer! Then she did it! She pushed Mr. Hammer off the stairs onto the fence! Just like Mr. Hammer had himself done five years ago! Though whether she did it on purpose or by accident, I cannot say.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-in other words... th-the victim, Mr. Hammer... He died in the same way that he caused another man to die... five years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Precisely. Ironic, isn’t it?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Hoh hoh. Very creative, Mr. Wright. I could use a man like you on my script writing staff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You deny that what I say is true?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Mr. Wright. Let's say, for the sake of argument, that Hammer died at the trailer as you say. Yet the body was found at Studio One, was it not? And in the Evil Magistrate's costume, no less. Are you then claiming that I carried the body to Studio One... And returned to the trailer all in the space of a 15 minute break? How could I have disposed of the body!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The break in the meeting at the trailer lasted 15 minutes, from 2:30 to 2:45. Could Jack Hammer have been pushed off the stairs to his death... then carried to Studio One and placed inside his costume? There wasn’t enough time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... indeed. Well, Mr. Wright? How could she have dealt with the body?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">15 minutes is kind of a short amount of time...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">You see? Even I cannot do the impossible. Therefore, Mr. Wright. I didn't do it. Agreed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not agreed!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You’d be surprised! I bet she could do it! When people think their life depends on it, they can do amazing things!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, this is not an episode of "That's Incredible."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you claim she did everything in 15 minutes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let me guess: "Show Me Proof!"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct! Show me proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How am I supposed to do that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then I won't have you making any unsubstantiated claims!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Wait a second, how does he know what I'm thinking!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! I need only look at the cold sweat running down your face to know what you're thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Perhaps you’d like to reconsider your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if she had another way to carry the body, other than with her own hands?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">For instance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, for that matter, there was no need for her to do the deed in 15 minutes! And there was a way for you to carry that body.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">!!! I-interesting! Let's hear it then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Please show us how she carried the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Dee Vasquez used this to carry the body to Studio One!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, how can you carry a dead body with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please rethink your statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Vasquez. You carried the body to Studio One. And you used the studio van to do it!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Recall your testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">There was to be a rehearsal afterwards, so we went to Studio One. I was fatigued, so I had Sal take me. There was a van there, right? I had Sal drive me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You used the van to carry the body to Studio One! Then, before everyone else got there, you put the body into the Magistrate costume!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on, Wright! Don't forget, it was Sal Manella that drove the van! Are you suggesting that Mr. Manella was a conspirator?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course he wasn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! So, without Mr. Manella noticing anything, she put the body in the van... Then managed to put the body into the costume...? Are you seriously suggesting that is possible!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Of course I'm not serious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ha... hah!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was kidding. To, er, lighten up the proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Li..light... Lighten!? Y-you can't lighten up a murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. The court requests you refrain from making claims in jest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, Sal Manella has to have been a conspirator! The body had to be placed in the van, and put into the costume. There's no way Ms. Vasquez could have done that alone! Also, don't forget that they had to dispose of the Steel Samurai costume. They had to... because it was covered in Mr. Hammer's blood! They probably burned it in that small incinerator. Well, Ms. Vasquez! Shall I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... No need. You're smarter than you look, Mr. Wright. Hmph. I lose. You win. It... was fun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... win!?</thought> ...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... So... what happens next?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't "?" me! Don’t you have anything to say!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">What would you like me to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? "I lost"? Something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I just said that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait, so you mean... Dee Vasquez! So, it was you? You killed Jack Hammer! ...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Who can say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Are you sure I did? Mr. Wright... We just engaged in a battle of wits. And the result of that battle? You proved the possibility that I murdered Hammer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">But... that is only a possibility. Proof is another thing altogether. You lack decisive proof, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wha... wha... wha... wha... WHAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Mr. Edgeworth, your thoughts?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... uhh... mmmph. O-of course, it's as the witness says! ... Certainly, it does seem very likely she did it... but, uh, there's no proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...! Edgeworth isn't sure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Well? I came here as a witness today. If you've no more questions, I'll be leaving.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk! What do I do now!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Vasquez! You did it!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... That wasn't a question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Um, did you do it?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">No.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure that question helped this court get any closer to a verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'd like you to testify again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Testify... again?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Know when to give up, Mr. Wright. Think about it. Even if I were to testify again, what's the point? I can only say what I said before. The truth, Mr. Wright. I've already said all there is to say. What would happen if I said it again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">You'd ask the same questions, get the same answers. A waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was hoping I'd come up with a question while pounding on my desk. I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... You have my sympathies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Damn... damn! To come so far, only to fail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As it seems there are no further questions... I would like to end the cross-examination of the witness, Ms. Vasquez.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was hoping I'd come up with a question while I was objecting, Your Honor... I didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! I request that the witness testify again!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">You are the prosecutor, are you not? Why are you badgering me? I'm your witness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I just want to hear your testimony again.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Does this make any sense to you, Your Honor? I don't see that we have anything to gain by repeating the last several minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth... I, too, see little point in making Ms. Vasquez repeat herself. What exactly did you want her to testify about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmmph! Well, yes, um... ... Indeed! Verily, I say... Ergo! I want to hear about what happened... after they found the body!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">After they found the body...? Very well. The witness will testify to the court concerning this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Why did Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows? He probably realized she did it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... but! Wasn't he the one that said he always gets a guilty verdict...? After all that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I was with Sal and Oldbag, the security lady, when we found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see no issues raised by this testimony... Mr. Wright, your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick, we're close, real close! She may be acting tough now... But if you put her on the spot she's sure to falter! Find the key you need and twist the truth out of her, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I was with Sal and Oldbag, the security lady, when we found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What time was that?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">We were to meet at 5:00 for the rehearsal. So I'd say it was then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When exactly did you and Mr. Manella arrive at the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">About 10 minutes before. I wasn't stuffing any bodies into costumes, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where were the other employees when you got to the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">They weren't there yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well!? Then you could have put Hammer in that costume, with Sal Manella's help!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Oh? What did I just say? Did I not just say "I wasn't stuffing any bodies into any costumes"...? You should try to listen to what people are saying, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>B-boy!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will continue her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better leave this one be. I'm sure she'd see through anything I had to throw at her, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The assistant was there, too. Only Powers was absent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers was taking a nap, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">So he says.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did no one go to call him?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Remember...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Remember... what?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">There was a dead body lying in front of us. Yet you expect me to be calm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You certainly seemed calm enough when I accused you of murder! *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! Wouldn't that be the other way around!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The other way around?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You discovered a murdered body, and one person was missing, right? Wouldn't you normally go looking for the missing person!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I have to agree with the defense on this one. Well, Ms. Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph. Logically speaking, perhaps. But no one there was thinking very logically, I assure you. Also. Without his Steel Samurai costume, Powers doesn't really stand out. We often left him on the bus when shooting at location. No one noticed he was missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Powers...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, I suppose that explains that. Very well, Ms. Vasquez. You may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll hold off. She'd just blow off anything I had to say, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I immediately called the police. Then Powers showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was everyone else doing at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">No one said a thing. It was silent. Completely silent. So we stood there until Powers finally arrived on the scene. "Sorry! Sorry I'm late!" Then... silence. Dead silence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Silent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey... Hey, Nick. Why's everyone so quiet? Someone should do something to lighten things up!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">The security lady, Oldbag, was quite agitated. Pointing at Powers, saying "he did it!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oldbag... the security lady.</thought> Why did the security lady think Powers had done it?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">She said because she saw him going toward the studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... the Steel Samurai.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did the detective arrest Mr. Powers based solely on the security lady's word?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Perhaps not. She seems to have given the detective that photograph... Of course, I heard all this after the fact.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That photograph... meaning the one taken by the security camera.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">She's not known for exhibiting the best sense of judgment when it comes to Hammer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm. I don't think there's anything in there I can use.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll hold back, I think. I'm sure she's already anticipated anything I could throw at her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I asked to be left out of the proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "asked to be left out"?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Yes. It seems that everyone else was questioned. And I'm really not fond of that sort of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, you can't decide who the police will and won't question!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Thankfully, the studio thinks otherwise. They were nice enough to understand that, since we were in a meeting... There was no way we could be involved. Thus, they covered for us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Covered for you... or covered it up for you? There must have been a lot riding on it, with all those bigwigs at the meeting... I'm sure her "professionals" helped convince everyone they didn't require questioning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I went back to the trailer to get my script and direction notes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The script and your direction notes?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Yes, they're quite valuable. It wouldn't do to have them stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I guess not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! I thought you came to Studio One for a rehearsal! Why didn't you bring your script and notes!?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Well, I was under the impression that we wouldn't be able to rehearse anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">There was a murder, after all! Who could think of rehearsing after that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, yeah, I guess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Ms. Vasquez, please continue...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor!!! I have an objection to the witness's last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think! Ms. Vasquez said she didn't bring the script because there wouldn't be a rehearsal. Don't you see what that means? She would have had to know about the murder before going to Studio One!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What you have just said... is a reasonable observation. However, I find it hard to understand why the prosecution would make such a move! Or are you thinking of a career change to defense!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I... appreciate the concern, Your Honor. I will stand by my statement, however, regardless of how the court sees my role here. Now, Ms. Vasquez... Do you have an explanation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe Edgeworth is helping me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph. So the prosecution is in cahoots with the defense? What kind of court is this? No matter. I think you misunderstood me. I had a perfectly good reason to believe there would be no rehearsal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, the witness will change her testimony to reflect this reason.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"Then I went home." to "I knew that Hammer was injured and couldn't do any action scenes, so I left them behind."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll hold back, I think. I'm sure she's already anticipated anything I could throw at her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Then I went home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you weren't questioned?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">That's correct. I find these things... distasteful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thinking back to when we first began this trial... We were under the impression that there was no one in the trailer at all.</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Well, we were in a meeting the whole afternoon. What's the point of talking about that to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She has got to be the least guilt-ridden guilty person I've ever met...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll hold back for now. I'm sure she's anticipated anything I had to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I knew that Hammer was injured and couldn't do any action scenes, so I left them behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did you know about the injury?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">H-how did I know!? Sal. He told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sal the director... Hm...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You have to find something to peg this on her here... Or everything we've done till now will have been wasted! I believe in you, Nick! Go get 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "knew that Hammer was injured"...? Don't you think that's a little funny? I mean, it was the Steel Samurai who was injured! It was Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Wh... what!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Explain yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Mr. Hammer is dragging his leg in this photo. But that's because he was pretending to be Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">P-pretending...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One person was inured in the run-through that morning. That person was Mr. Powers, not Mr. Hammer! Now, why did you think it was Mr. Hammer who was injured?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...! I-I already said it was Sal who told me! Th-that's right! He must have gotten it wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think not. Mr. Manella was at the run-through that morning. He would have known it was Mr. Powers who was injured. He saw it happen! Why would he tell you the wrong person? Ms. Vasquez!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You must have heard Mr. Manella wrong! Even though he said Mr. Powers was injured... You thought he was talking about Mr. Hammer!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Now that you mention it... Yes, I believe you're right. I'm sure that's what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You're supposed to be putting her on the spot, not helping her out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right... I kind of talked myself out of that one, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Quick! Start over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, you didn't hear anything from Mr. Manella. You saw Mr. Hammer limping with your own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but... Wasn't it Mr. Powers who was injured...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but remember! Mr. Hammer was dragging his leg, too! He was pretending to be Mr. Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And when was he doing this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well... It would have been after he put on the Steel Samurai costume... and went to Studio Two. Where he was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly! Ms. Vasquez! You met him, didn't you? You saw the Steel Samurai limping! And Mr. Hammer was in that Steel Samurai suit! That's why you were confused! That's why you thought it was Mr. Hammer who had been injured that morning!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! I will have order!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Witness! Can you refute this claim?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hrrmmmm... hmph! ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, let's see you sneak out of this one, Vasquez!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Very well! I have a question for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... Why are the real killers always so... persistent?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Why in the world would I want Mr. Hammer dead? Yes, he'd fallen on hard times, but he was a star! I had nothing to gain from his death! Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Yes, you would need a motive. Why would she have killed the victim? If there is a reason, it is unclear to this court. Does the defense have anything to say on the matter? In other words, can you prove she had a motive?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, no! Saying you can't prove it now would be admitting defeat! She'll get away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... but what proof could I possibly have!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't care if it's impossible, you still have to fight this one!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. I have proof, and I'll show it to you! I present to the court evidence as to Ms. Vasquez's motive in this murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Psst, Maya, look. This is it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Why... are you showing that to me, Nick? And why are you whispering?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just testing it out on you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh. Well, I'm afraid your test results are negative.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hurry up with it! We have a certain tempo we have to maintain here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... yes, Your Honor. Right. Here goes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is... the photo from before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This photo reveals the motive in this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm right, aren't I, Ms. Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hrrrrrrm... hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Five years ago, Mr. Hammer was at the height of his fame. With Dee Vasquez's help, a terrible accident was swept under the carpet... Ladies and gentlemen, the case currently up for trial... It began on that day, five years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ironically enough, that accident precipitated Mr. Hammer's fall... His fall from stardom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">His guilt weighed him down, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However! You, Dee Vasquez, used Mr. Hammer. You made him work for you for petty change!</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bringing us to the present day... and Mr. Hammer's last role as the Evil Magistrate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes! Undoubtedly, it was a constant source of shame for the ex-star...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One moment, Mr. Wright. We are talking about motives, here... yet you have only talked about Mr. Hammer. It almost seems as if... As if it was Mr. Hammer who had killed Dee Vasquez, not the other way around! What motive would Ms. Vasquez have?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Y-yes, that's right. According to what you say... I would have no reason to kill Hammer. He was a good source of income for me! And I never get rid of useful men. It's a policy of mine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Please explain Ms. Vasquez's motive for murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay... Allow me to present to the court evidence proving Ms. Vasquez's motive!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is my proof!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And... this tells us why Ms. Vasquez wanted to kill Mr. Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">I’d say all it proves is that the defense attorney has completely lost his marbles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! The court requests that you find your marbles immediately. And, I'm afraid I have to penalize your [sic] for this waste of the court's time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We’re so close! Think this one through, please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, I'll ask you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She had no motive, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was Mr. Hammer who was out for blood! All Ms. Vasquez did was push him off the stairs... in self defense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's that now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple! Mr. Hammer was intending to kill Ms. Vasquez!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wha-!? WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Jack Hammer drugged Mr. Powers with sleeping pills! Jack Hammer snuck into the dressing room and stole the Steel Samurai costume! Jack Hammer wore the costume to fool the security lady into thinking he was Powers! Then Jack Hammer made his way to the trailer! And for what purpose, you ask? To kill Dee Vasquez, who had so cruelly taken advantage of him all those years!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you did do it, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">... Yes. I am guilty. It was me...</line>
<line speaker="Vasquez">Congratulations, Mr. Wright. I lose... again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth... Where's Dee Vasquez?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In the waiting lobby, Your Honor. As calm and collected as ever...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears you have brought about yet another miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think not, Your Honor. Will Powers was innocent. That he should be found so is only natural... not a miracle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Yes. Yes, you're right. Very well. This court finds the defendant, Mr. Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Will">I... I don’t know what to say! Thank you so much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I’m just glad you’re okay.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes... but... it's sad. I know now that Mr. Hammer stole my costume. It's bad enough that he wanted to kill Ms. Vasquez... But to think that he tried to frame me for the murder! It makes me sad... Tell me why, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-huh?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Tell me! Why did Mr. Hammer want to blame me...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we'll never know.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whew... I'm not sure I wanted to go down that road.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, this is what I think. Mr. Hammer wanted to put the blame on you because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's because you were the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Because I was the Steel Samurai?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Hammer was a big star, once. But he was reduced to acting in a kids' show... and as the villain, to boot! The kids love the Steel Samurai. And so, he hated you.</line>
<line speaker="Will">I... I think I understand. H-he could have just told me. I would have changed places with him any time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think you’re missing the point...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">... Thank you. I'm just glad it's all over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So am I... so am I...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Will">... S-sorry? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, what does that mean, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Nick? You know that problem of yours? That problem where you present evidence that makes no sense? You're doing it again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Congratulations, WP!</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh? Oh! Heh heh. Thanks to you, I'll be able to don the Steel Samurai outfit once more! I can't wait to get back into that sweaty costume and... ...? Is... something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no! O-of course not... Aah! N-Nick! Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Say something, Wright. I'm not good at small talk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What? ... Umm... that was too bad, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't waste any time gloating, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... I really wanted to thank you. Vasquez would have gotten away if you hadn't stepped in.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Ah, uh, pleased to meet you. I'm Powers. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, er, Edgeworth. I'm a big fan of your work, Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Liar!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright. I must say, I hadn't expected to meet you again after all these years.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Meet "again"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However. In retrospect, it would have been better had we not met. Thanks to you, I am saddled with unnecessary... feelings.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unnecessary feelings?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Unease... and uncertainty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aren’t those kind of necessary?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They only serve to get in my way. You listen to me, Phoenix Wright. Don't ever show your face in front of me again. That's what I came here to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Umm... Mr. Wright? Is... this guy your friend?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Friends? As if! They’re rivals! Rivals! Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For now we are... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh!? Why do I get the feeling I'm missing something? C'mon, Nick! Tell me! What’s the deal with you and Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so the curtain closes on another trial... I caused quite a stir by revealing that accident from five years ago. It was the talk of the town. Thankfully, Global Studios rethought its programming change. They went back to making kids' shows again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! This is it! The new show starts today! You're going to watch it with me, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll admit, I was kind of surprised... I didn't think they'd seriously go through with it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You have to buy trading cards too, okay! We have to trade with Cody and that assistant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Fine, fine. I'll do it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't it great that WP gets to play the lead again? I wonder if they'll show his real face this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno... I don't think the world is ready for the real Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court see no reason to further prolong the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Mr. Will Powers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>