<xml>
<title>Turnabout Corner</title>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Two months have passed since Mr. Gavin's arrest. My first trial, and I lost both my mentor and my job. Yeah, I'll admit it. I was screwed. But even when I hit bottom, I told myself I'd never come here. Honest. Here being the legendary Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices. OK, Justice, time to stop trembling.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Ah! You must be here for the interview. Right this way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello there! You've found the Wright place! Welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Ah... <thought>What's with this girl!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Well now, shall we begin?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Begin... what?</line>
<line speaker="???">Right, first things first... Any special talents?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erm, talents?</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes, well, you must have at least one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... Uh... I guess... Defending?</line>
<line speaker="???">"Defending"... An unusual talent, but it'll do. With a little jazzing up, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You think so...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Let's give it a go, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">Go ahead! Show me! Defend! Just give it all you've got. Don't hold back now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What are you talking about? I can't just "defend" here!</line>
<line speaker="???">First lesson: A professional can perform anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="???">We want people to be laughing with us... ...not at us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thanks. But I'm not sure why they should be laughing at all.</line>
<line speaker="???">What...? What exactly do you think you came here to do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Um, defend... No?</line>
<line speaker="???">... Excuse me, but do you know where you are?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh!? The Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices, right?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Oh. I was afraid of that. Don't worry, you're not the first.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, what's going on here? Who are you? I came here to meet with the person in charge...</line>
<line speaker="???">Well, you've apparently made no fewer than two mistakes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mistakes? But I got a call from Mr. Wright this morning!</line>
<line speaker="???">Perhaps you should go read the sign out front again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's there to read!? Look, it says right there... ...Oh. Why does it say "Wright Talent Agency"...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Welcome to the Wright Talent Agency, where you've "always come to the Wright place!" I'm Trucy Wright, CEO. I'm a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It all came flooding back... The trial... That girl...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hello, sir. Please, pick a card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. She's my daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy... Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Here, check out our flyer! So... what's your name?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo... Apollo Justice, attorney at law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All these legal books must be Mr. Wright's leftovers... ...There's a lot of unrelated books in here, too. "One Trick a Day"... "Magic for Idiots"... You'd think a pro magician would aim a bit higher.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ack! Don't touch Mr. Charley!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Mister" Charley...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's been in this office much longer than I have! Daddy's mentor had a great fondness for Mr. Charley. He's lived here since Daddy was a rookie attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh.  <thought>Mr. Charley... riiight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now I take care of him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's one of those hula hoop things everyone was crazy about way back when.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I had no idea these were that popular!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not so bad with one myself, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh!? I-I'm still learning... So you can really make someone levitate with it? Show me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh!? I-I have no idea how! <thought>It's just a normal hula hoop, isn't it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A strange, split box leers at me from the wall. Um, is this one of those boxes for cutting people in half?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! This cabinet is used for an illusion called the "Zig-Zag"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've seen one on TV... But why is one just sitting here in your office?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, it's a little big for me, you see. So I'm using it as furniture. Hats in the top, shirts in the middle, and pants down below! I think it's a nice touch... don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's not exactly what I'd call a "welcoming" decor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An old, sepia-tinted photo of a man in a silk top hat.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's my favorite magician! I want to be just like him someday!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sure, nice... Guess it's good to have a role model. Even if he's gotta be well over 100.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How rude!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are all sorts of strange paraphernalia sitting on top of the piano.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Those are my magic props! Practice, practice, practice! A professional never leaves their weapons far from reach!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you can't play the piano with all this junk on it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, no one plays here anyway. And the neighbors complain.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess Mr. Wright really can't play...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A blue silk hat, just like the one Trucy is wearing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, that's just for show. Don't wear it, please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Last thought from my mind, honest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I put it there so clients can see it and know who I am. Nothing says "magician" like a silk top hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! That fork is floating! ...Not. Why do you have a plate of plastic spaghetti here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That right there is the whole reason I became a magician!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do tell.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I saw a plate just like that in a restaurant once. The floating fork looked so real! That's when I knew... Someday, I'd make magic more amazing than that spaghetti!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That table... doesn't look very sturdy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You've never seen one of these? It's a magic table!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, like, you make this teapot disappear?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So you might think! But that's not it... Before your very eyes, the contents of the pot change! ...From Earl Grey to Darjeeling!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kinda hard to see the difference, I'd think...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's up with this "Wright Talent Agency"? Guess I'll talk to her and find out what I can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... Is this really a talent agency?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You bet! Daddy started it seven years ago, when he quit law. Of course, we only have two people signed up right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Two people... Does that include you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Trucy Wright, Magician Extraordinaire! I've done a lot of stage shows! Paid, too! I am a professional, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er... right.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Promise you'll come to one of my shows, OK? Let's see... Oh, and the other person our agency represents is... Phoenix Wright, Pianist Extra Ordinaire!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your dad, in other words. Didn't he say he couldn't play the piano?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Our agency doesn't see that as a problem. Why, there are many magicians who can't do magic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">At least you're optimistic, I'll give you that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're his, er... you're Phoenix Wright's daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! After Daddy quit law seven years ago... ...I promised I would keep him fed! So I'm kind of his sugar daddy! Get it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm in charge of this whole office, too. Pretty amazing for a young lass of fifteen, wouldn't you agree!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">F-Fifteen? Uh, how old is Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy? Oh... he's 33 this year.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm sure there's a good explanation. <thought>I hope...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, about Mr. Wright giving up law... It was because of that incident seven years ago, wasn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh? You know about that!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not the details. I remember the news, though. It was a big deal.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So I hear. I was too young to understand what was going on. I'll ask Daddy about it next time I get a chance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Daddy, right... That reminds me. About Mr. Wright... He gave me a call this morning to come in.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy's not here right now. He's in the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The hospital!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah. He's on strict bed rest until he gets better.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh... What!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I've seen one of those before! That's an attorney's badge. It looks just like the one Daddy used to have. Now if I take this badge... And do this, and this... See! It's gone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Hey! My badge! What'd you do with my badge!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No need to worry! Just look in your pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh! No way... My pocket? <thought>Wait a second... There's something in there!</thought> ... It's a flyer for your agency!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And here's your badge. You can have it back now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's the last time I let her touch anything of mine. Period.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a number inscribed on the back of the badge. There are many numbers like it, but this one is mine. Proof that I'm an attorney. To tell the truth, I get a happy feeling inside just looking at it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, the Hickfield Clinic. It's quite close.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Well, I'll be going now. And I'll, uh... give this showbiz gig some thought, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait! I'll go with you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So... this is Mr. Wright's hospital...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Eh? Visitors are ya? Hrmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, yeah. Are you the... doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Hickfield">Ayup. Dr. Hickfield's the name. Eh he he.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good morning, Doctor!</line>
<line speaker="Hickfield">Oh, hiya there, Trucy. Cute as ever! Eh he he.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is... this Daddy's room?</line>
<line speaker="Hickfield">Oh yah. 'Cept he's gone for a mornin' checkup. Be back soon. How're you, Miss Trucy? Got any places you'd like... examined? Eh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doctor... the nurse was looking for you.</line>
<line speaker="Hickfield">Why, if it isn't the Daddy o' the cutest lil' thing in town! Hrm. Hrmm. Guess I'll be off then. Eh he? Later, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, what an odd bird that guy was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning. Didn't expect you so soon, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aaaah! Daddy! You snuck some grape juice in again!? The doctor said you weren't supposed to drink that here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy. Look at the label.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... Oh. "Deep Sea Mineral Water". That's fine, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I switched the labels. Don't tell Trucy, 'kay?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What can I say, the man loves his grape juice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A swaying, spiraling stack of DVD cases. "The Steel Samurai", "The Nickel Samurai"... "The Pink Princess", "The Zappy Samurai: Electric Bugaboo"... They're all children's action hero shows...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This "kid" I know keeps sending them to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh. Like a niece or nephew?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Quite the collection. This kid's parents must be really generous with their allowance. <thought>Funny, Mr. Wright doesn't seem the type that kids would like.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright's bed... It's really messy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look how messy this is! You're just hopeless without me, aren't you, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes! She's attempting to clean up! Look out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha. You got me. What can I say? I was raised in a barn. Try not to let word get out, Apollo. If you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, it might ruin your illustrious career pretending to play the piano.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This looks like a child's toy piano.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gotta practice. Wouldn't want my fingers to get stiff. A pro always keeps his weapon close at hand. Shall I play you a tune?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... no thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, how unfortunate. I so rarely get a chance to play.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that on TV? Looks like some sort of action hero show...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I know that one! That's the Sniffling Samurai! His "Booger Flick" attack is a big hit with the grade school crowd.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I had no idea you liked this kind of stuff, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what else is there to do when you're stuck in bed? Besides, the episodes will just keep piling up if I don't keep up, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... yeah. <thought>Try not buying them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now's the only time I get to watch and write up my reports.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your... reports?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a long story. Like a lot of things, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Who could have imagined it? Me, victim of a hit and run...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A hit and... You were hit by a car!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, he tried to swerve, I'll give him that. Picture me tossed thirty feet through the air... ...only stopping when my head hit that telephone pole.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You hit a telephone pole with your head!? Are you OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thankfully, my only injury was a sprained ankle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He really is as lucky as they say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something that, well, it just doesn't sit right. I just can't believe you have a daughter, Mr. Wright! And... she's so big! Not fat, but, er, you know what I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Trucy's still a child.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! How many times do I have to remind you! I'm not a child anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha ha! But you'll always be Daddy's little baby girl to me, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ah ha ha, my foot. I'm not buying it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, something you should know about Trucy...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's a magician, right? She told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not a mere stage magician... She's a genius.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tee hee! Aw, Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'll soon come to appreciate her "talent".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could just tell me things instead of insinuating them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, why did you contact me? What could the Wright Talent Agency possibly want with me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No need to get prickly, now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, I didn't ask to be dragged in like this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? But didn't you come into the office of your own free will anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, yeah, of course. "Help! We're in big trouble here at the office! Big!" ...I thought someone was dying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you don't think this is big trouble? My talent agency represents only two people... and one of them is in the hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right, Daddy! How are we going to pay this month's rent!? And the groceries!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... That's the problem with such a tight operation. It's a symbiotic relationship. When one of us falls, the other, too, must fall...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! This isn't exactly a suitable conversation to be having with a 15 year old kid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, if Apollo here can't help you... ...you'll have to transfer to a new school. Again.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No! I can't! I only just made friends... How could you do this to me... to us!? Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What? Now it's my fault?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On that note, how about you come work for us? I've got the perfect client for you already lined up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... A client? <thought>You mean I get to do my job? I get to defend in court!?</thought> ...Alright. I'll hear what you have to say.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You got him, Daddy! Hook, line, and sinker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah ha. Now it's time to reel him in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's official: I'm scared.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Alright, so who's the client?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, yes. Here, take a look at the map and I'll explain. Last night, I left the office just before nine o'clock... I was going to that Indochine pasta joint, Alden Tae's. I play piano there, of course. ...That's when it happened! The car sent me flying, nicked a telephone pole... ...and zoomed away. Creepy, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just a tad. It's almost as creepy as hearing you tell the story like it was no big deal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The car sped off in this direction... ...So, good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You wanted a client, didn't you? Well, I'm your client! Find the guy who knocked me into that telephone pole!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, hold on! I'm a defense attorney, not a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. Once you've found the guy, I intend to sue him. Then you can stick it to him in court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm not a prosecutor either! I'm sorry, but... this is crazy. I'm going home.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's that? Looks strangely familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How could you not recognize an attorney's badge!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been seven years. I've forgotten... a lot of things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess some seven years are longer than others.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't get so worked up. It was just a joke.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Daddy. Sorry, Apollo. He just loves jokes, you know. Even the ones that aren't very funny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your real client should be stopping by the office any time now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The office... You mean the talent agency? <thought>No harm in going. It's not like I have anything else to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...One more thing. Do look into my accident too, would you? I marked the scene of the tragedy on this map. It's right in front of this park. Should be easy to find.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So, he's going to make me investigate this after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've marked the location of the accident on your map. Find the criminal who knocked me into that telephone pole!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey hey hey! How long you planning on making me wait, eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey there, Trucy-doll. Sounds like your pops had a bit of a rough spot, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">All's well that ends well, I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This... is our client?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! So this is that Pollo fellow, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, y-yes? <thought>The name's "Apollo".</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Look at 'im there, arms all crossed-like. Ready to fight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, sir! ...You don't mean that literally, do you?</line>
<line speaker="???">The boss told you what I need, right? Don't let me down now, Pollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't worry about your defense sir, I'm on it!</line>
<line speaker="???">Defense...? Your noodle half-cooked? It's too late for defense! My castle's been stormed! My keep's been kept! My noodle stand's been stolen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-Noodle...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know Mr. Eldoon from the noodle stand, don'cha, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No nicknames, please. And no, of course I don't know him!</line>
<line speaker="???">You new in these parts?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not really...</line>
<line speaker="???">Then you know the best noodles in town: Eldoon's Noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, whose noodles?</line>
<line speaker="???">My noodles! Er, help me out here, Trucy-doll.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is Mr. Guy Eldoon... our client! Maybe you can tell us what the problem is, Mr. Eldoon?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Anything for you, Trucy-doll!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... You run a noodle stand, Mr....</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Eldoon. Guy Eldoon's the name! And noodles are my game. The secret's in the soup! I've been searching for the perfect soup for a year 'n' a half.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh. That's... not that long, really.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">My family's been noodle men for generations. Got a lot of expectation on my shoulders. Fifteen fathers passing the noodle to fifteen sons.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's a pretty old noodle!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Aye, and fool that I was, I pushed it away. I rebelled against my pops, and picked another livelihood. But... that didn't turn out so well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">There was no denying it... Salty broth runs through these veins, boy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, it was like destiny that you became what you are.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Right, destiny's the word! Oh, I fought it... ...but in the end I was bound by the twisted noodle of fate!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not a mental image I care to linger on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">So, last year, I started my noodle stand. The 15th generation of Eldoon's Noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... So tell me more about Eldoon's Noodles.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You don't know the genius that are my noodles!? I make 'em so salty, why, they're saltier than... salt!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now I really don't want to find out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy's a regular at his noodle stand.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">He frequented my pops's stand back during his attorney days, too. Yep, him and his assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry... I'll be sure to drop by your stand soon.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Wish you could, sonny!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Heck, I wish I could! I'd give anything for a bowl 'bout now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">It was stolen! My stand! Gone!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Stolen...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">It was last night... I was doing my rounds, blowin' my whistle.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's like an ice-cream truck's bell but louder! He even gets complaints!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Eh heh, now you're just trying to butter me up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That sounded more like the blues than a whistle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">I closed up my stand for the night and parked by the house. Then, this morning, dark 'n' early... It was gone! My keep! My castle! Oooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe some bum carted it off? ...Just guessing here.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Well, I don't care who did it! Without that stand, I'm finished! All my noodle bowls were in there, too.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Yee haw! Attaboy! Way to flash 'em! Ol' Phoenix used to do that to my pops all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your father...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Yup, he'd whip that bad boy out 'n' say "Put it on my tab, you know I'm good for it."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A tab at a noodle joint?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">Sorry, fellah, but the only business I'm concerned with is my business. You gotta help me out! Get my business back!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the saddest thing I've heard all day.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You know it. Anyhows, that's the deal. Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good... huh? Wait... What exactly is your request?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">My noodle stand! Find it! And the day you bring my baby back is the day you feast on as many noodles as you want! Course I make it so hot 'n' salty, two bowls'd kill a man. Then I'd really need defense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Speaking of defense, that's what I do. I'm a lawyer. Not a detective...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">This is where I live, you drop by if you need any info, 'kay? Get it back today if you can, Pollo! I got noodles to make!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Things have certainly taken a turn for the bizarre. Traffic accidents... and noodle stand thieves.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um, actually... There was something I wanted to ask you about, too, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>I have a bad feeling about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">Ah, listen to the lady's problem now. Don't be cruel!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I lost something last night. That is, something was stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Hey, what's this? More thieving and skullduggery!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, um... Someone stole a pair of my panties.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Panties?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erm, so they were, um, stolen, your, er...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My panties, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah, er, right. Panties.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">That's a cryin' shame, that is, Trucy-doll.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I was alone in the office last night. I had hung my panties out the window there to dry... ...when a thief came and took them! My favorite panties! I ran after him. "Give those back!" I shouted. "Wait!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that was certainly brave of you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...But I lost him. Without those panties, I don't know what I'll do...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">A darn cryin' shame, yup.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, at least the scene of the crime is convenient. I'll mark it on your map!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">I'll be headin' home now. Remember, find my stand or there's an empty bowl in yer future, Pollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, right.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">And you help out Trucy-doll here, too, y'hear?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Things have certainly picked up, haven't they! We had no work yesterday, and now we have three cases!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see where we stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not in a courtroom, that's where.</thought> Well, the first item on our list...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Phoenix Wright... Daddy's hit and run accident. We have to find the one who hit him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Who's going to pay us for this again?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And the second item... Mr. Eldoon's request.. to find his stolen stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For which we stand to gain... a bowl of salty noodles...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And the last request is mine! To find my stolen panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That bowl of noodles is looking better and better.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's go, Polly! To the streets!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aren't you enthusiastic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How could I not be!? Let's crack these cases, you and me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Guess we might as well get started... Let's see. A hit and run... a stolen stand... And last but not least... stolen panties.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe I should ask her more about her... uh... This is going to be difficult--</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your [sic] going to have to press me for information! Go ahead, do your worst!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, no thanks, I pass.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You can't "pass"! This is your job! Look, I had hung them outside the window there to dry... ...when a thief came and took them! My favorite panties! I ran after him. "Give those back!" I shouted. "Wait!" ...But I lost him. I can't live without those panties! Please find them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well? Do we have any leads?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... One moment... ... Allakazam! Allakazing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! Where'd all this evidence come from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... So what happens next?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's it! Pretty neat, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah. Neat. <thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's that, Polly? Oh, I know! You want to see a magic trick! Well, you've come to the right girl! Watch as I make that evidence disappear, forever!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! No, don't! Sorry, my bad!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Mr. Wright's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe he's gone for an examination?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He'll probably be back soon. Let's wait.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think it might take some time. Daddy always loves his examinations!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Don't ask, Justice. You don't want to know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why don't we come back later?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A bottle of Mr. Wright's favorite brand of grape juice. After that trial, I'll never drink grape juice again. Clearly not a problem for Mr. Wright, however.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A swaying, spiraling stack of DVD cases. It looks ready to collapse. Better keep my distance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright's bed. Wow, what a mess. Trucy must be in charge of cleaning at home.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A small, children's piano. I guess the man likes pink.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The television's been left on... to an episode of the Steel Samurai. That's the same episode as before. Must be his favorite.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is where Mr. Wright got hit by that car?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">According to the map, this is the place!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What a huge mansion... Feels like Chinatown.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! There's a nice-looking lady over there. Let's question her!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, OK. <thought>I'm a little curious about the park over there, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Excuse me! Um, can we have a few words with you?</line>
<line speaker="???">You want something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! That husky voice... Why am I suddenly sweating?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's quite a house you've got there! You must have a lot of money...</line>
<line speaker="???">Whoooh. "Money" sounds like something my son would call his friends. This is the Kitaki Family mansion, little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="???">You, kid with the hair. You want something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! M-M-Me? No, not a thing! Bye!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! We can't leave without questioning her! What if she knows something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But th-the Kitaki Family...! <thought>They're the biggest organized crime syndicate in town!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">If you're going to ask something, ask it. If you're man enough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Waaaaugh! R-Right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yay! Way to whip him into shape, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Does she know no fear!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">I'm Plum. Plum Kitaki. Wife of the fourth head of the Kitaki Family business. Friends call me Little Plum.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm l-little Apollo Justice, attorney at law. *gulp* <thought>If looks could kill, this woman would be a mass-murderer by now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, what a big house! And the gate is so big...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Kitaki Family is pretty big around these parts.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I like the fox! It's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Ah, that. That's our family crest... from the old country.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your family "crest"?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">We're clever as the fox... and our teeth are sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So it's like a motto! You need a crest, too, Apollo! Ooh! How about the scales of justice? Or a lunar lander!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I'll pass, thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A brightly painted dragon. Why do I get the feeling he's glaring at me? Those paints must have been to repaint this wall.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">That's right. I called in an artist to do the job right. ...He's the third so far.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The... third?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">The first spilled paint all over the entrance here, the second on my kimono... So I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, don't tell me. It's better that I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's paint splashed all over this gate. <thought>What a mess...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Was this paint knocked over by the car that hit my Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">That's right. Feh. And I'm left to clean up the mess. If you find whoever did this, bring the scoundrel by, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course! Then you can make them clean up their own mess!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Ah ha ha ha! You're cute. Naïve, but cute. When I find whoever did this, you can bet I'll be doing some "cleaning". There's nothing I dislike so much... as a mess.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! I wish I could say cool things like that!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">I'll bet you do! Wa ha ha ha ha!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd laugh if my teeth weren't chattering so hard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Little Plum? That's a really cute name for someone so...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is it, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about you go through me when talking to her, OK, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? That seems like a bit of a needless procedure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm a lawyer. I live for needless procedures.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Oh little girl, you should know... We're gangsters.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Gangst... Oh! That means you're the bad guys!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! Through me! Please! I'm begging you here!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Wa ha ha ha ha!!! The bad guys... I like the sound of that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I'm going to need some warm tea after this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">It takes a lot of hard work to protect a family fortune. Things aren't as easy as they used to be for us "bad guys".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, you're saying that business is in a slump?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let's not ask about "business if we can help it, please?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There was a car accident here last night?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Last night...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of c-course you wouldn't know about it! S-Sorry to bother you!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Wait.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">You're talking about that man, aren't you? The one who flew thirty feet and just walked away?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's my daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Ah ha ha! I should've known! One of our Capos thought he'd make a great point man...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Capo? Point man...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, could you avoid using too much, er, industry lingo?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">In any case, it's been nothing but trouble. I've been cleaning up this mess since morning! Bah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Cleaning up this... paint?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Was this paint spilled at the time of the accident?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">It was around 9 last night. I heard a crashing noise... ...and found your father drowning in a sea of paint.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So you came to his rescue?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">You've my husband... the Boss to thank for that. The car that hit your father knocked over this paint... ...then turned the corner, and sped away. We're in the middle of repainting our wall, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm sure that dragon is glaring at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But, why are you out here cleaning it up?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I mean, aren't you a gangster? Don't you have any "goons" to do your dirty work for you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please! Go through me when you want to...</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Wa ha ha ha ha!!! Don't be such a stiff, lawyer-boy. I suppose we gangsters do have a certain image...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urm, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">But we're community-oriented gangsters, you see. ...The Boss likes to give back to the people, see?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How noble of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">I availed myself of the public facilities to get rid of all the garbage... Now there's just the paint on the street to deal with.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Public facilities...? I wonder if she means that trash can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Sorry, kid. I got no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's pretty. I bet she has a story, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There is something about her... Too bad she seems to be in a bit of a rush.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Looks like there's some trouble by the park gate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I smell an incident!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ma'am! There's no entry to the park!</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">Now don't you tell me where I can't go, young fella! I always walk through this park on my way home!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Please, get down from there! You'll hurt yourself, ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's quite the determined old lady.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">People Park... Huh, kind of an odd name for such an empty place.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder why it's named that? Hey! There's something written on the gate post...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh yeah... It says, "Donated by Big Wins Kitaki".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean the Kitaki Family built this park? It's so nice of them to give to the community like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Let's not get too friendly with them, shall we? <thought>A gangster building a park...? Odd move for a crime boss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Personally, I'm a little more interested in this park.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what I think? I bet they're filming a movie. Let's go take a look! Maybe we'll see someone famous!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Hey, Miss! Stay out of the park!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...He got mad at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, did something happen here, officer?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Huh? Uh, no, move along, nothing to see. Why don't you kids go play someplace else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're not kids and we're not playing! I'm an attorney!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah, Detective Skye! We're fine ma'am, nothing to report!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Detective...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why's she wearing a lab coat?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're hardly one to comment on how people are dressed.</line>
<line speaker="???">And... these kids are?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Curiosity seekers, ma'am. They claim to be "lawyers".</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah. Why don't you kids run along and play someplace else?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, we're not...</line>
<line speaker="???">Or I might spill something on that pretty face of yours. Want a dose of experimental Hydroxyacelunodosetrase?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Come again? What's Hydroxy... stuff?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whatever it is, it doesn't sound good. Let's go, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="???">Try to keep out the riff-raff, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes ma'am!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grr... How are we going to get more information like this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why don't we ask that nice woman across the street?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh yes, that nice woman... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I gotta say, I'd really like to know what happened here...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Hey, I said no one goes in! Unless you want a face-full of hydroxyadayadawhatzit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... No dice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a big trash can on the way into the park. I guess we could check it out...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A detective's life sure is a hard one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm an attorney, actua... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. Two pieces of garbage with paint on them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These... are slippers. They look like those slippers you get at the hospital...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look at this, Apollo! Doesn't this go on a car...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a side-view mirror! Looks like it was torn off when it smacked into something... or someone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, you don't think...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do. This could be from the car that hit Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, and he took off its mirror? I never knew Daddy was so strong. I only have room in my pocket for one of these, though. Which do you want to take?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a side-view mirror with some paint on it in this trash can.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can only carry one thing at a time in my pocket, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Should I swap the slippers for the mirror?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, let's swap the evidence. Trucy, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm on it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...On second thought, let's not and say we did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's some paint on the slippers in this trash can.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can only carry one thing at a time in my pocket, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Should I swap the mirror for the slippers?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure, let's swap the evidence. Trucy, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right-o!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually... let's not and say we did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Can I ask you a question?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What happened in the park across the street?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Oh, yes, quite the commotion. "Chicago Lightning", as the Boss would say.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Chicago... huh?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Gunfire. Someone was killed. Strange circumstances, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">What a morning! Trouble everywhere. The park, the gate, even our house...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Did something happen at your house, too?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">A crime without honor! Without remorse! It's a private matter... Wanna hear about it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Somehow I don't think "no" is an acceptable answer, Polly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... what happened at your house?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Bloomers. Last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh. <thought>I got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Me, Little Plum Kitaki, the victim of a panty-snatcher!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaaaaat? So it wasn't just my panties that were stolen!?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Got you too, did they? Poor thing. Like I said, whoever did this is a hardened criminal. It wasn't you, was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No! Of course not! Mercy!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">I've heard word that panties have been disappearing lately. ...And the missing panties all have something in common.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's hard to imagine Trucy's and Mrs. Kitaki's panties having much in common... I just imagined Mrs. Kitaki's panties... *gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know! We'll find your bloomers, too!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Great! Show me what you're made of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What have you gotten me into this time, Trucy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell me anything about this mirror?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">That's probably from the car that knocked that fellow across the street.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right! That makes this a valuable clue!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Let me know if you find that car, would you? You splash Kitaki paint, you pay the price.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? This spot here is black.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I wonder what that is...? It doesn't look like paint...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The bottom is covered with paint!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What's this weird shape here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It looks like a leaf was stuck to the bottom when the wearer stepped in some yellow paint.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the outline was left when the leaf was removed! Ack! I got paint on my hand!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Apollo! I saw you try to wipe your hand on my cape!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's cut clean off! I wonder what's in there...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't. There are bare wires hanging out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's see... Zzzzzzaaaaap! Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--!? A-Are you OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hee hee! Just a little joke!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Don't scare me like that!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You mean, don't "shock" you? Zzzzzzaaaaap! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...That girl from before!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Plum">Oh! Welcome home, sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, uh... hello, m-mother.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's a Kitaki, too!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Uh, um, Miss! Miss!</line>
<line speaker="???">...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Here, our flyer.</line>
<line speaker="???">The... Wright Anything Agency?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-Anything Agency?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! Do you like the new flyer? So, um, this is our defense attorney, Mr. Apollo Justice!</line>
<line speaker="???">Attorney...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Drop by our office! We'll be waiting!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah... Good-bye.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why did you give her our flyer?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I dunno. She seemed like she could use some help.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's the heiress to a gangster dynasty! She doesn't need our help!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I wouldn't be so sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... what's this place?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This would be Mr. Eldoon's house, silly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so this is where his stand was stolen from. I can see a piece of evidence lying on the ground already.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Hey! Look, there's a police car parked over there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right... What's with the sparkly... entrance? What is this place? A hospital? There's a sign... "Meraktis Clinic".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Oh! That's where the thief went!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The thief...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The one who snatched my panties! He ran into this clinic last night! Wait, maybe that police car is here to find my panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I doubt it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, there's only one way to be sure! Let's investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Ah, there you are, sonny! Well, you find anything yet!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, um, no. Not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">The longer you loaf around here the saltier your victory bowl gets, just remember that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This bowl of noodles is sounding less like payment and more like punishment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That doorway sure is sparkly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The "Meraktis Clinic", huh. Looks more like a casino parlor than a hospital. They must be quite profitable.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Funny, it looks closed. Maybe they're on vacation today?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like they have a special offer going on...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Three shots for the price of one!" Ooh, now's our chance, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Chance for what!? I don't need any shots, thank you. Whoever runs this clinic, they seem pretty business-minded.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'd understand if there was an ambulance outside... But a police car?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe they're tax evaders!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah, sorry miss. No going into the clinic today.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Did something happen?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Huh? Oh, no. Nothing to see here. Move along. You'll have to find someplace else to play doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Do we look like the right age to be playing doctor!?</thought> We need a little more info on this Meraktis Clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We could ask Mr. Eldoon. He is their neighbor and all. And we should check out that garage! What if the thief who stole my panties is still in there!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Guy">That's the place! Right there! That's where I kept my stand. Covered all nice 'n' purty with that blue tarp there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you used this plastic sheet to cover your stand at night? ...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You see? What? Did you figure out why it was stolen!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well no, but it does suggest that the thief knew what he or she was looking for. They clearly knew what was under that sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">So it wasn't one of those casual drive-by stand snatchers, you mean? Not bad, sonny-boy. Not bad at all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this yours, Mr. Eldoon?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Hey! That there's the heart and soul of Eldoon's Noodles! The bowl absorbs my salty soup... Pretty soon it's gonna taste just like noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! It does smell like noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">All my other bowls got taken away with my stand! Get it back for me, sonny-boy, I'm beggin' ya!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This house is... well, it's old!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">It's been well-loved, that's for sure. I've lived here with my wife for many years now. It's got character, though, just like my soup!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I always thought character was a positive thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's quite a sign. I take it that's "NOO" as opposed to "OLD"?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Ah, you like it? Made it myself, I did. I meant to write "Noodles" but ran outta space.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Prior planning prevents poor performance!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Lucky for me it spells a word all by itself! And spruces up my image, it does!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It does have a certain power of willful denial thing going for it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like the oil drum is connected to that sink over there...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Collecting rainwater to do the dishes! How environmentally conscious!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... don't think he uses rainwater to cook his noodles and to make the broth, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh I'm sure he finds the best water money can buy! Taste is his business, you know. Look, that sign over there! "Eldoon's only uses water from all-natural sources!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... <thought>I think I'll take a rain check on eating here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a hand-written sign here... "Save the light!"</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">"Save the light!" indeed! Mr. Eldoon's house is practically in the dark here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess the hospital clinic next door blocks the sunlight.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Everything's gone wrong since they built this monstrosity! Broth needs sun or it rots! What's a man to do? They just want my customers to get food poisoning so they can turn a pretty profit...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That seems like a lot of trouble to go through for a few extra patients...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! A doggy! Good boy, good boy, Salty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sure the dog has a real name, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Yup, sure does! Name's Spoon. And it's a she, by the way.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Spoon doesn't seem so lively.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">She didn't get her bowl of salty broth this mornin', that's why. Poor lil' thing. *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Let's find that stand soon! For Spoon's sake!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm pretty sure dogs aren't supposed to eat noodles...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, your stand... "Eldoon's Noodles", was it?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Aye! Passed down from father to son. That stand's seen its share o' salt, mmm-hmm. Salt runs in the family, you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I bet high blood pressure does too.</thought> So... your stand, Eldoon's Noodles, was stolen...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Oh, it wasn't just the stand that was stolen, sonny-boy! I lost those wobbly wheels, my salt-crusted stewpot, my stained sign... I didn't just lose a stand, I lost a legend!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No one steals a legend and gets away with it on my watch! Let's find that legend, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Isn't it about time he bought a new one anyway?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are there any more details you could give me about the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You bet, sonny-boy! It happened last night... I was blowing my whistle like always, crying the town, I was. The smell of broth filled the streets... thick 'n' salty. I got home, well, right before 10 PM, I reckon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess he's not aiming for that late-night market.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">I washed my bowls and gave the wheels a squirt of grease. Then I went inside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When did you notice it had been stolen?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Early this morning. Before the sun rose. Work starts early!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Do that many people eat noodles for breakfast!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">I'm washed up on the salty shores of ruination! That stand had my whole life in it... nay, my whole being!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They took everything?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">All my soup stock, my noodles, my bowls... and my dreams!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">At least they left one bowl. Look, there, on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">If you don't find that stand today... Then I'll be forced to walk the streets, peddling that bowl... my last bowl.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, I'm under enough pressure here as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's it! That's where the thief who snatched my panties ran to!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">It's a crying shame, that is. If they have to steal, make it my loincloth! Not some pretty girl's panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The garage, right. You don't think the thief lives here, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Feh! I wouldn't put it past that good-for-nothing doctor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... Do I detect a little animosity here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's make sure to check out that garage thoroughly!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, do you think something happened next door? There's a police car out front...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Feh! Probably gave someone food poisoning, I'll bet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If anyone's at risk of giving someone food poisoning...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">That police car got here this mornin', actually. I asked what they were up to, but they wouldn't even tell me, the neighbor! Feh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Guy">Not that I was surprised much. That doctor works for the wrong crowd. It was just a matter of time 'fore he got what was coming to him. Feh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The "wrong crowd"...?</line>
<line speaker="Guy">...Never you mind about that.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You can tell my bowls by the Mr. Salty logo!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The mascot of Eldoon's Noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Guy">They come to the stand, they sit, they drink deep from that bowl... ...and when they see the  bottom, their face looks jus' like Mr. Salty's! Genius, no!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Very high-concept.</line>
<line speaker="Guy">You can't ply a trade if you don't love the tools. Remember that!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes sir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy has a thing for professionals, clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guy">Sorry, sonny-boy. My interest is for my stand and precious little else. Get cracking on that case! Find my stand, I'm beggin' ya!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's the Eldoon's Noodle's mascot! Mr. Salty! He's so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not a very endearing mascot, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know... Come to think of it... ...It looks a lot like you, Apollo. Especially the red parts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I help if I like red?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, look! I love these little personal touches!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seems a shame to hide it on the bottom of the bowl. ...Huh? When I touched it the paint flaked off.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He must have painted it on by hand with warm, professional care!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After buying the cheapest paint he could find with cold professional thrift.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is the place! This is where that panty-snatcher ran!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe! Let's look for clues! Clues... to a panty-snatching! Clues... like a pair of panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, Trucy? Could you try not saying "panties" so many times?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something about this car...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's take a closer look!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look... a cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone dropped it beneath this tire! If the car moved, it would be crushed for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I wonder if it belongs to the doctor here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We should bring it to him later!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! Look at that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mirror's been broken off! <thought>Now THIS is a clue!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!? You're smiling like you know something I don't... You aren't keeping a clue from me, are you, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A clue? Let's see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. Not that I can think of.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No? Then what were you smiling about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I wasn't smiling. It was the dust in here. I thought I was going to sneeze... Ah... ah... ah... WAACHOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, don't make faces that ah... AH-CHOO! ...are so misleading then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know yawns are contagious, but sneezes...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Mmm. Well, I'm sure there's gotta be a clue somewhere! Let's keep checking things out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I do have just the clue you've got in mind...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... That's your clue? Sorry, but that leaves me feeling kind of... clueless.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Like father like daughter with the humor, apparently.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's no need to bluff here, Apollo! Save that for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Thanks for the advice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">My clue is... this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa! It's the same color and size and everything! A perfect match!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess we could check it out...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm. Two pieces of garbage with paint on them. Look at this, Apollo! Doesn't this go on a car...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a side-view mirror! Looks like it was torn off when it smacked into something... or someone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... looks like we've just solved a case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So the car that hit Daddy last night...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is sitting right in front of us, yep.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. You put the "pro" in "professional", Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gee, thanks, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That reminds me... I once read a record of a case that Mr. Wright worked on many years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently, there was this car with a piece of cloth shoved into the tailpipe! That piece of cloth turned out to be a vital clue to solving the case!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I remember that case record whenever I'm checking out a car... And I always check the tailpipe!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Everyone's gotta have a hobby, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wouldn't it be funny if... ...Hey! There's something in here!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait a second... Are these your...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! My panties!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaat!? Already!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, thank you, Apollo! You're a genius! Amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no, really, don't mention it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, I'm serious, I'm really impressed! You must have a nose for finding girls' panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Um, what are those?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My little panties, of course! They've come home to mama! I can't wait to use them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You're going to put them on? N-Now!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Watch closely now... See? Nothing in the panties... ...Ta-da!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Wh-Where'd that come from!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How did that bowl get in your panties!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My panties are an extra-dimensional space... Anything can fit in there! ...They're my Magic Panties! It's one of my best tricks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Magic... panties?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They love them over at the Wonder Bar. I do shows there nightly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You mean those panties are a prop!? You could have told me a little sooner!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's once case closed, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you saying!? We still have to catch the sly devil that ran off with the tool of my trade!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something tells me we're not finished searching this garage, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This mirror fits this car door perfectly...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So the car that hit Daddy last night...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is sitting right in front of us, yep.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. You put the "pro" in "professional", Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Still, I'm glad. If I hadn't picked up that habit of looking up tailpipes... ...I might never have seen your panties. I mean, found your panties. Magic panties.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I know, it was amazing how you slyly peeked up there! I think you have a successful career in peeking up tailpipes ahead of you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm so glad all of this makes sense in context.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You gotta wonder why my panties were here, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That is a mystery...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something tells me we're not finished searching this garage, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This car belongs to someone at the Meraktis Clinic... and it hit Mr. Wright. Mr. Wright sprained his ankle, and the car lost a side-view mirror. This car vs. Mr. Wright... Not quite the match of the century.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! A kitty-cat! Here, kitty kitty kitty.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...It's not coming down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We do look kind of suspicious, you have to admit.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's OK kitty-cat! His hair won't hurt you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's OK kitty-cat! She won't make you disappear in her hat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, it's a folding ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Polly! That's called a "stepladder"! C'mon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...A stepladder? How is that different from a regular ladder then?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's a much more complex piece of machinery. It's like two ladders stuck together!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So you admit that basically it's a ladder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have to look past the  form... at the essence of the thing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Er... Can we talk about something else?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeek! Someone's there! ... Oh, it's just a gold-painted human skeleton.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just a human skeleton!? ...And painted gold?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There's a mannequin hand waving to us from the box behind the skeleton. This place just screams "hospital storage", don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It screams something, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look at this cute little watch-strap! I want one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's kind of odd, though.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I mean, if you wanted to know the time, you could just look at the phone itself.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, you're right! Sharp, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-Thanks. <thought>Finally, some respect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, what does that tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, the owner of this phone doesn't think through the details, for one.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They did drop their phone, after all. I kinda figured they were a little spacey already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... good point.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... I was just wondering if there was, like, a switch on these...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh. Mysterious.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? Do you want to know the secret of my panties?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! N-No! No thanks! <thought>Who uses magic panties in a stage show anyway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now that we've solved this case, we should go report to Daddy! He'll mope if we leave him alone too long, knowing him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, OK. ...He doesn't seem the type to mope, though. <thought>And this is hardly a case worth reporting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What, you want to see them again? Well, if you must...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No no no, I'm fine, really. Let's just put them away, shall we? Case closed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you talking about!? The case isn't closed until we have our thief! Just find him on the side while you work on the other cases!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it were that easy we wouldn't need the police.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If we don't need the police... then we don't need defense attorneys, either, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Fine, fine. I'll look for your panty-snatcher...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm so glad we found my panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I had no idea they were so important to you.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And in time for tonight's show, too! A lot of people come just to see my panties, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... might not want to advertise it like that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a big waste basket by the park entrance.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...? You aren't going to search through the trash?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think we need to.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, no, please, knock yourself out. Don't mind me, I'll be waiting over here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just so we're clear, searching through trash isn't a hobby of mine, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I found out who this mirror belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Ooh. You're tougher than you look. Spit it out. Who was it? Where do they live?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! I j-just forgot! Heh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I remember, Apollo! It was the Meraktis Clinic!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Shhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why? I'm right, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">...Meraktis, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, yes. <thought>Why's she so quiet all of a sudden?</thought> ... Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">Erm, no. Pay me no mind. And thanks for the info.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yo! How goes it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! How do you feel?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not bad, Trucy, not bad. It's good to have you young'uns on the case. Lets ol' Daddy-o get some well-deserved R&amp;R.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The elderly need their rest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh... isn't he only 33?</thought> ...Um, we've cleared up most of the cases...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was right about you. Competent. Capable. Tell me what you found out. If you want to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Your enthusiasm is over-whelming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this was the thing that led you to the car.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, sir! The mirror you knocked off was just the clue we needed!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good work, Apollo. Of course you might say... ...I was the one who made solving that case possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...You don't get points for knocking off a car mirror.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look! My panties! They came home to mama!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Apollo. I was worried about them, too. Trucy special ordered those...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A startling display of parental concern!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd hate to have to buy a  new pair... *shudder*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Make that a not-so-startling display of cheapskatedness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's actually a relief to be so thoroughly ignored.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Little Plum's not here. She's not finished cleaning, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe she went to get a paint scraper?</line>
<line speaker="Plum">OK! Who's the wise guy who spit gum out on the street!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Her voice carries all the way out to the street from inside the mansion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's a neat freak! How cute!</line>
<line speaker="Plum">You there! It was you, wasn't it!? Fess up! I hope you've said your prayers. You're gonna need them...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tr-Trucy? Let's leave. Now.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An impressive gate befitting the Kitaki Mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look at the name plate! "Kitaki"...! That's so cool! Short and blunt, like any good gangster! Ooh! Let's change our name! How about... "W. A. A."! ... Maybe that's too short and blunt. What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No comment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A colorful dragon turns its baleful gaze in my direction. As if to say, "Abandon all hope ye who enter here." Don't worry, Mr. Dragon. Me and hope haven't been on speaking terms for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Several colors of paint have been splashed across the gate. It's almost all dry. This is going to be tough to clean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like that woman's still causing trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Look, no one goes in! That means you!</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">Oh, what's the difference? Let... me... go! Ow! Ow ow ow ow ow ow!!!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah! S-Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">That's it, I'm suing! ...But I might change my mind for five bucks...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is she, some kind of con artist?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently, this park was the gift of the Kitaki Family. The friendly "People Park", brought to you by organized crime... A very naughty part of me is tempted to write "We Kill" on the left side of the sign.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They're not letting anyone into the crime scene. The guard at the entrance is humming a song. He's got rhythm, actually. Maybe he plays in a band.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I certainly didn't expect you back this early.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Polly's amazing! He found my panties so quick! Almost like he was the one who stole them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You have an interesting concept of praise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And? Did you find the mad driver who gave me that 30-foot toss?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apparently... it was a doctor. From the Meraktis Clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Meraktis, eh? I've heard of him. Nothing good, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That reminds me, a police car was parked outside the clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe something happened?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is this Meraktis Clinic anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I've heard are the rumors. That clinic's been making good money... in a bad way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bad...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ties to organized crime... The Kentucky Family.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... the Kitaki Family? <thought>He did that on purpose!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some injuries you can't take to a public hospital, see. They use the Meraktis Clinic for their patch-up jobs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It looked like something had happened in that park.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah. A body was found there in unusual circumstances...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something more unusual than being dead?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...It's not our concern, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! Let's ignore that and find that noodle stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What ever happened to professional curiosity?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... I was wondering when I get paid? We solved the case of your accident, and um, found a missing article of clothing.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">My panties!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That leaves the noodle stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Feel free to drop in if you get stuck. I'd be happy to help with anything not involving money.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Good-bye, quid pro quo. Hello pro bono. *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! Back to the office to plan our next move!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... You're the woman from the Kitaki place!</line>
<line speaker="???">Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I knew it! Something's the matter and you want our help, right? Well, you've come to the Wright place! This way, please...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Um... Thank you. My name is Alita Tiala. I... have a request.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your request... let me guess, something's been stolen?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Um, your flyer... It says "now defending" so I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaat!? You mean, you mean you want me to defend you? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe you can tell us what happened? Were you hit by a car? Did someone steal your stand? Or your panties?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">No! No... I'm not the client, actually. The client would be my... well, my fiancé, I suppose you'd call him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fiancé...? What happened to him, then?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">He was arrested this morning. The charge... was murder.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Murder...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Have you heard about what happened at the park?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what's your story? You frequent the Kitaki Mansion, yes? Are you a member of their, um, organization?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">No... Not yet.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not yet?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">You see, I'm to be married next month. To the boss's son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The boss's son...? So he's a, uh... *gulp* <thought>A gangster...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes, but the Kitakis are locally responsible gangsters. I thought it'd be nice for a change... Quit my boring job, live the good, gangster life.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think you're on to something! "Ms. Kitaki"... I like the sound of that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not sure your daddy would care much for that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What happened!?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I haven't been told all the details. But I do know a body was found in the park. Near the Kitaki Mansion.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There were a lot of police cars there.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Apparently, the victim was shot with a pistol... But I hear the circumstances of the shooting were... rather unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And your fiancé was arrested for this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um... what sort of person is your fiancé?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your fiancé is the Kitaki Family's only son, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Alita">His name's Wocky. Wocky Kitaki... I brought a photo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well. That's... quite the photo.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I know! Oh, he can be powerful and menacing, but so cute!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But, if he's the boss's only son...</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Yes, I'm sure he'll take his father's place some day.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Say, I'm a boss already! Of this agency!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">Please help my Wocky! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Right! My first solo defense case! Crime boss's son or not, I'll prove he's innocent!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Alita">An attorney's badge... So you really are a defense attorney. Please, I'm counting on you. I need your help.</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I'm not sure I understand... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no, it's me who's sorry, really! Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Right! Let's go check out the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Alita">I hope that's OK? I've never written a letter of request before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, it's fine. <thought>I should hope it's your first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">If we take this we'll be able to investigate the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why does this envelope say "Hit Request"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... it's a bit of lingo. Like "call in a hit", or a "hit man"...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, you mean gangster-talk!? So does "hit" mean "to defend" in gangster-ese? Well, "hit man"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I certainly hope not... <thought>Something tells me she used the wrong envelope...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? Where's Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe he's getting an examination again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How many does he need!? <thought>Wasn't it just a sprain?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Too bad, Polly! You wanted to show off your request to Daddy, didn't you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Me? No!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh? That's a surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">L-Let's just come back later, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Polly! You look as happy as a clam in its shell.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">For a lawyer this is it, the place where the battle begins!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">...Ahem. You need something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaah! Yes, we're attorneys. I was hoping we could see Mr. Wocky Kitaki?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Sorry, he's in questioning right now. Could take a while.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Drat. Oh well, guess we'll have to come back later then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So much for that battle...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That security camera is looking at me. I wonder if they tape all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A security guard. He stands here, watching this room. I have no idea if he's listening to us talk. I'm not even sure he's breathing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this is it... My first murder crime scene!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah, it's you kids again. Look, can't you find some other place to play...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We're not playing! We're um, "investigating"! Aren't we, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sir, I have a letter of request here.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Letter of... huh? Why does it say "Hit Request" on it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ms. Tiala must have used the Kitaki's stationery...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Excuse me, coming through.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ah! It's you! Mr. Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Who's this guy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">I must say I'm used to being inspected by the ladies... But this is the first time I've felt this way with a man.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr.... Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, Fräulein. What is a sweet morsel like you doing in such a dismal place? Can I help?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... Y-Yes! The police man officer fellow here won't let us in! We even have a letter of request!</line>
<line speaker="???">You must be exhausted, standing out here! I will take you to the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooh! R-Really!?</line>
<line speaker="???">...By your leave, Officer.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Ya... Yes sir! Of course, sir!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah ha. Very well. This way, Fräulein...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whee!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Hey! What about me!?</line>
<line speaker="???">...On that note, enjoy your investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thank you! Will we see you again...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ask the wind, Fräulein. I'll be riding on it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Who was that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eeeeeeeeeek! Apollo! Look! A c-corpse!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaat!? ...Hey, it's just a mannequin.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow. It sure got me.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahem. Might I ask exactly what it is you're doing here? Oh, it's you. How did you kids get in here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! This guy, well, he was more like a prince really. He let us in...</line>
<line speaker="???">Him again. That glimmerous fop, always getting in my way... Anyway! This scene is off limits.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Excuse me? We have a letter of request!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Hmm. One moment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why is she holding that big magnifying glass...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">.............................. I'd recognize that handwriting anywhere. Scientific analysis says this was written by Alita Tiala.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thanks. <thought>It took you thirty minutes to figure that out!?</thought> So... what's up with the mannequin there?</line>
<line speaker="???">It's taking the place of the body, preserving the scene of the crime as it was found.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The body... was pulling the stand!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, you're a defense attorney, are you? Detective Ema Skye. I'm in charge of this crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She doesn't seem that happy about it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...She doesn't seem that happy about many things.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I trust you know how to stay out of the way. I always carry two pairs of handcuffs... just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey there! No messing with the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But we need to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Look! That stand! ... It says "Eldoon"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I've noticed. Well, we've solved the case of the missing stand at least. ...Though the circumstances could stand to be better.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey there! No messing with the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But we need to investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Investigations are to be carried out by professionals, scientifically!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's not going to let us check out the crime scene, is she...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Apollo. My very un-scientific analysis tells me something here is very suspicious...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I think I know what you mean. It's kind of hard not to notice. <thought>I'd better check out what we came here to find at least.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Detective Skye...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Quiet, please. It's snack time. MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH. MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH. MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We're not making much progress here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She must not be very busy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">*sigh* I never seem to get a lucky break. Back after nine years, and they won't give me the position I requested... ...And then I hear he gave up the defense attorney life...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He? Who's he? An ex-defense attorney...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, if you could spare a moment to take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Can't you see that I am extremely, extremely busy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Eating snacks, yes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Busy eating snacks, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is going nowhere fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Mr. Eldoon...! Hello?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like he left.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And we found his stand and everything! What about our free bowl!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, too bad, looks like we'll have to wait a little longer for that bowl. So sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Aw, what a bummer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The front entrance to the Meraktis Clinic. The walls and posts are so highly polished I can see my face in them. ... Hot dang, my hair looks good.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like this is a banner for some campaign. "Three shots for the price of one"... Somehow I don't see people lining up for that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A police car is parked in front of the Meraktis Clinic. It's empty. The police must be inside investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The blue tarp Mr. Eldoon used to cover his noodle stand. Robbed of its purpose, it blows in the wind... alone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A lone Eldoon's Noodles bowl lies on the ground. The lone bowl, tipped on its side... It's kind of surreal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Eldoon's house has seen better days. And I'm betting I've eaten better noodles.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This must be his business sign. It reads "NOO". Maybe that's how the kids are spelling "new" these days. Another failed attempt at hipster marketing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An oil drum for catching rainwater. ...Ack! A sparrow just flew over and... Aw man, that was just disgusting! Something tells me this wasn't the first time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a hand-written sign here... "Save the light!" It's hard to make out the sign in the shade from the clinic next door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guy Eldoon's dog doesn't look too lively. They say dogs and their owners resemble each other... I guess there are exceptions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, you're back! Run into some problems?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Polly, didn't you want to tell Daddy something?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who? Me? No! I'm fine. Really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? So there is a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no problem. Actually, I got a defense request.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A defense request! That is a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've given up the court. I'm not a lawyer anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... The request was for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. You're a lawyer, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's doing that on purpose! I know it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what about this defense request?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's related to the murder in People Park, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guess what! We found Mr. Eldoon's noodle stand at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you now. That's unusual indeed. Never heard of a noodle stand being used as a murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Uh, I think the murder weapon was something else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean you don't know what the murder weapon was?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That funny detective lady won't let us on the scene! What kind of detective wears a lab coat, anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A lab coat? Hmm. Didn't think she'd be involved with this...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You know her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... you know her, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I met her on a case... this was about ten years ago. She was still a high school student at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That would make her about the same age as me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's my daddy! He knows all the police types. Oh, wait! Maybe you know that other guy, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That other guy...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That shining prince on the motorcycle!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Prince?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo. Tell me about this "prince" of Trucy's. Indulge a concerned father...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was at the crime scene... He looked just like Mr. Gavin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Did he now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You know him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My guess is he's Kristoph Gavin's younger brother...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His brother!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're acquaintances, after a fashion. Klavier Gavin... rock 'n' roll god incarnate.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Klavier... What a lovely name! He's so dreamy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I didn't know Mr. Gavin had a brother! And what was he doing out there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have a feeling you'll be crossing paths again soon.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah. That detective woman won't let us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Go to the office. Under the silk top hat you'll find a bottle of white powder. Try taking that to this detective.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"White powder"...? <thought>I hope it's not what I think it is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just take it to her. It'll be fine, you'll see. Oh, and tell her I said hi.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... I think we should focus on finding more information about the case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You seem to be having fun.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course! This is my first criminal investigation! And it's so mysterious! A noodle stand pushing a dead man along...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Uh, I think it was the other way around. The dead man was pulling the stand. But you're right about it being mysterious.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I knew it! More information, that's what we need!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this must be the "silk top hat" Mr. Wright mentioned. Let's take a closer look... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know what this is, Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I... remember finding some in Daddy's dresser when I was little. I thought it was sugar, so I licked it... He got mad at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is getting more and more suspicious...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's go talk to that detective! She's sure to know what that white powder is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm. The bottle has a label on it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Can you read it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, not a word. I'm not sure I speak whatever language this is written in.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's too bad. I guess we're stuck with this mysterious bottle of white powder...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Does this ring any bells?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah! Is that--!? It couldn't!? Where'd you get that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I brought it from the office.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You... work at the Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, yeah, sort of...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Detective Skye! How do you know my daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">D-D-Daddy!? I'm sorry, who did you say you were?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Trucy Wright. Phoenix Wright's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!? Mr. Wright has a daughter!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You seem shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">W-Well, if you're Mr. Wright's daughter and you're his apprentice... ...then I'm available to help you in any way I can!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, thanks. <thought>You can start by not calling me Mr. Wright's apprentice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This powder is used for detecting fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fingerprints...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I guess you might call it a memento... from the time I spent with Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>White powder memories...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">If you find any evidence with fingerprints on it, please let me know! We'll dust for prints!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, she's quite the eager beaver all of a sudden...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Benches line the river running through the park.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ahh, a little urban oasis. I bet children come here to splash around in the water.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That river's a little deep for splashing... and a little dirty.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, they could listen to the water and pretend they were playing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blue tarps have been placed on the ground around the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! I bet the victim was going to have a picnic here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I guess he could have eaten all the noodles he wanted.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't touch those! Those are preserving the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, I guess the police put these tarps here after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's... a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A "shiv" to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh... lingo!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defendant, Wocky Kitaki, is the son of known gangsters. The police are assuming this belongs to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, but wasn't the murder weapon a pistol...?</thought> Huh? Look at this, there's a handprint on this shiv...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A handprint? Then there might be a fingerprint. Let's investigate!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right! First, choose the fingerprint you want to examine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Choose a fingerprint?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look closely at the handle. See? There's more than one fingerprint there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Those black spots?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. Pick the one you want to analyze.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right! Let's get detecting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow, she's practically glowing with excitement...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">First, sprinkle some aluminum powder over the print. Just touch the screen, like this. See? The oil left by the print absorbs the aluminum powder, so you just dust it on... ...and blow it off!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-Blow?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's like whistling. You know how to whistle, don't you? Just put your lips together...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow! Amazing! It's like magic!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Heh heh. Isn't it though?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right, let's give it a shot!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally, it's important that you cover the entire fingerprint with the powder.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm, good... clear... Quite impressive! Next, to match the print. The police office has samples so you can tell whose finger this print belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... That doesn't sound like as much fun as actually finding the print.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">OK, pick the person whose print you think this is. You probably have a good idea whose knife this is already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... the fingerprints do belong to the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes! Isn't it amazing? Ah, the power of science. It's my life.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo, she's... sparkling.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And I'm dimming.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Look sharp, spirits up. The real fight is yet to come!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Chin up, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The trial hasn't even started and I'm already losing...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A knife is sticking straight into the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">With the defendant's fingerprints on it... Which means... You think he stuck it into the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't know what he did with it but I don't like it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This mannequin is dressed up to look like a police officer. I've seen one at the station. <thought>A mannequin in place of a body...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The body of the victim has already been removed.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think the victim was the noodle stand thief?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, you think someone killed him because he stole it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! Taking care of business, Little Plum Kitaki style!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Try not to sound too eager about that, please...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...And this is Mr. Eldoon's noodle stand, obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It does say "Eldoon" in big letters, doesn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that mark on his paper lantern there looks familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's going to be a little weird telling him... what with the corpse and all...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Anyway, that wraps up three of our cases.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! Congratulations, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And leaves us with one case that's worse than all three put together... Murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's got to be a good clue or two around here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You and your trash cans! Go ahead, knock yourself out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, can't you see I'm doing my... Huh? L... Look! Another pair of underwear!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, Apollo! You're a genius at finding panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Stop saying that. Wait, these aren't...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-They're not mine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could these have been stolen, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll always remember this trash can as "the place where Apollo found those bloomers"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't you have more important things to remember? Wait, these aren't...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-They're not mine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could these have been stolen, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The report came in late last night. The body was found much as you see it now. ...Except it was a real body.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But... why?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why was a body pulling a noodle stand? If I knew the answer to that, I wouldn't still be here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, what was the cause of death...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A bullet wound, to the temple. ...He was shot by a pistol.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A pistol?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not the easiest thing to come by in this day and age.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Unless you're a cop... or a gangster.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Incidentally, the victim's name was Pal Meraktis. I just received the autopsy report, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I mean, really! What's up with this case!? It's enough to make me want to run off, pulling a mysterious noodle stand behind me...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not so mysterious, actually... We should tell her, Apollo! After all, we know where the stand came from!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A likely story! I didn't come here to play games, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, we do know where the noodle stand came from. The noodle stand's owner is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Look, I have better things to be doing. I'd make more progress eating snacks than listening to this drivel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>You could try actually investigating, rather than just standing around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">... Who's the old guy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the proprietor of Eldoon's Noodles, Mr. Eldoon himself!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's famous in this part of town.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not bad. I guess Mr. Wright picked the right kids for the job. That saved me a lot of work. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What sort of person was the victim, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean what did he do? He was a doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A doctor...? <thought>I'm starting to see a connection here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Who? Me? I'm just a supervisor for this crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Detective Skye... Hmm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">I was out of the country for a while. I came back to be a forensic scientist.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! Were you studying abroad?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Something like that. I was studying in Europe. Forensic sciences, mind you. But when I got back here, they threw me in criminal affairs! Just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why didn't you just become a forensics expert in Europe?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I suppose that was an option, but... I had a lot of favors to repay to people back here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Favors? Wasn't she in high school when she left?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? What's that look for? I was involved in an... incident before I left. But Mr. Wright and his people helped me out. I owed them.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really? I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If she's been out of the country for a while... ...she probably doesn't know about Mr. Wright's current, erm, "state of affairs".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Could you tell us a bit about the defendant? He's the only son of the Kitaki Family, yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wocky Kitaki. I don't know if he is the boss's son, but he's certainly throwing his weight around... ...Violently. In the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why was he arrested in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... You are a defense attorney, aren't you? You're not his, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, a-actually, yes, I am.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well... We have a witness to the moment of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The witness called the police. They'll be testifying during the trial tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whaaaaaaaa--!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could you tell us a bit more about the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, let's see... Apparently he's the physician at a clinic in the area. Quite well off, too, from the sound of it. The clinic's name is... The Meraktis Clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... Maybe that's why the cop car was parked there?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What? You've been to the clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I told the detective about the case of the stolen noodle stand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I see... So that means... ...Dr. Meraktis stole the stand and pulled it all the way here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would seem to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">... But why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't ask me!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ah, an attorney's badge. It reminds me of when Mr. Wright was still defending. Everything I have now is thanks to him. Remember, help as many people as you can. That's your job!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She's right, Polly! Let's make a difference! ...Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Ah, no! N-Nothing. <thought>I... I actually felt inspired for a moment there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Fingerprint analysis is the very basis of modern forensic science! Doesn't just talking about it leave you breathless with excitement?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh yes. Breathless. <thought>Actually, it does sound kinda interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let me know if you find any evidence that might have a  print or two, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The defendant's fingerprints were found on that knife.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Which means that, at the very least, he was here at the scene of the crime...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's highly possible, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. This doesn't look good.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No use worrying about what's out already! You just worry about what's yet to come!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Why did Dr. Meraktis die like this...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Pulling a noodle stand... Very strange.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Inconceivable! I just don't get it! Some people just can't die normally!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's dead, give him a break.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry... I don't think I can help you with that. I think you need more than just scientific help. But ask me anything you like! ...Just ask scientifically.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The label reads "Fingerprint Powder" in some strange language.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How do we know for sure? What if this is really a jar for something else, like jam, or honey?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would anyone go through the trouble?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, so the police don't find out, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hardly think possessing fingerprint powder is a crime. </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, huh, I guess. That's boring.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">These bloomers sure have a... distinct design!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You certainly know who they belong to at a glance.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That way, she doesn't have to write her name on them! Genius!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I would think writing your name would be easier than drawing a plum blossom.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, the defendant's prints are on this knife...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That would mean he was here the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's what I call irrefutable scientific evidence! Neat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not so neat when it happens to be evidence against our client...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh? Look at this, Apollo! Mr. Eldoon spelled his name backwards on this side!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I think that says "Noodle". As in "Eldoon's Noodles".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Huh... Oh, I get it! So the name of his store is the same whether you read it forward or backwards!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... I guess it would be. Well, except for the last "s".</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... Then, how about a store called "Team Meat"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, close, but that would be "Taem Maet" backwards. And what kind of store is that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why, a store that sells meat! "It's not meat, useless it's Team Meat!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah. Uh... No.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Visiting hours are almost over at the detention center. You might think about wrapping up here and heading over.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good idea. <thought>I don't know what good it will do. We have a witness, and a knife with prints... Have I mentioned I've got a bad feeling about this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Don't worry, it's like a Wright tradition.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Some traditions I can live without.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Guard">I'm sorry. Meeting hours for the day are all done.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But we still have three minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">I'll put in your request, but don't expect anything. The father's talking in the private room with him.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The father? You mean like a priest?</line>
<line speaker="Guard">I mean the suspect's father, Mr. Winfred "Big Wins" Kitaki himself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Not someone I care to meet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">...Die you--!!!</line>
<line speaker="???">...You're the one on your way out, old--!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">.........</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Ah. They're here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! This guy radiates power! Power.. with a cute apron?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You Wocky's lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Well, I'm Big Wins Kitaki, fourth head of the Kitaki family... capice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er... Actually, I came to speak to your son.</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">... Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">My son's innocent. He killed no one. If he were found guilty... it wouldn't be good. ...Capice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes! I'm all about capicing! Capice'd loud and clear!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">You gotta do more than just understand to make it. You'll learn, though. Even if the lesson comes at the end of your short life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't feel so good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">What's the big idea, old man! You can't treat me like a kid no more, not now! You know I... I... I wanted to go to the clink! I like it here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... must be Wocky?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">A G's not a G till he does hard time! Bizzoooy! You'll see. When I get out of here, things'll change!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Silence! My apologies, Mr. Justice... He's usually such a nice boy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Forgive me if I have a hard time believing that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Ha! You can't take me under your wing this time, old man! You heard me! I don't need no trial! I did it!</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">...I think that's enough for today, Mr. Justice. Don't let me down tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So much for talking to our client.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But we made so much progress today! We even found my panties! I had fun, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course, the biggest mystery of all remains... <thought>How am I supposed to build a case for the trial!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, almost forgot, it's time for my show! Tonight I'm performing at the Wonder Bar! You should come check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No clues here.</line>
</xml>