<xml>
<title>Turnabout Goodbyes</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it... judgment day. Today, things are gong to get settled at last... a lot of things.</thought> Waaaaaaaargh! Wh-what's the big idea!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-s-sorry, Nick! I only touched your shoulder! I guess the "shock" hasn't worn off from my run-in with the stun gun yesterday. Anyhow, today's the last day of the trial! Good luck, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... thanks, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth is looking glum as always. I hope von Karma doesn't push him too hard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Whooooooooaa! Wh-wh-what are you doing!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry! I'm sorry! I just thought I'd ch-cheer you up with a pat on the back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... Maybe you should go outside and discharge?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right. Good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Try not to electrocute anyone on your way out...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's gotten into that girl?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Morning! Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Uh... good morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How did it go, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Have no fear! As promised, I've captured our runaway caretaker! I just brought him in. Took all night, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Detective Gumshoe. You must be tired.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Actually, after that shock I got on the way in, I feel pretty good.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yogi says he's forgotten his own name... But that has to be a lie! Why would he want revenge on Edgeworth if he couldn't remember his past!? He does remember... and I'm going to prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Mr. Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... The prosecution... is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... U-uh... right, very well. We have reached the final day of our proceedings in this trial. I ask that the prosecution submit decisive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Understood.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C'mon! Don't be awed into silence by every little thing he says!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. von Karma, your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Right. Thanks to Detective Gumshoe's efforts, the boat rental shop caretaker has been arrested. In yesterday's trial, the defense asserted that the caretaker was the murderer. However, the caretaker has yet to confirm this. I would like to ask the defense to cross-examine him as much as necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well! Please bring the witness into the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Ladies and gentlemen of the court... I believe you all remember our witness. He lives in the boat rental shop on the lake, from where he witnessed the incident. In addition, he has currently lost memory of his name and identity.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! Why did you run away yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">The witness was not running away, as he will now testify.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see. Very well, please begin your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Zzz... mmph?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er, I'm really sorry about just leaving yesterday like I did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Let's begin the cross-examination, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He has to know his name! Yanni Yogi! You're Yanni Yogi and I'm going to prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er, I'm really sorry about just leaving yesterday like I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd call what you did "running away," and not "just leaving." You heard Larry's testimony, and realized you were in danger!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Now, Mr. Wright, there's no need to rush to conclusions. As I said, the witness was not "running away." Listen to the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He sure seems relaxed! In fact, they both do--von Karma and Yanni Yogi!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">But, I wasn't running away or nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why did you leave!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">He's just about to say why! Is it so hard for you just quietly listen when someone is talking!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I sat quietly, Edgeworth would be guilty in three minutes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I, uh, went to buy some food for Polly, see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Food...?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Well, Polly is a bit of a gourmand, you see. She only eats these high-quality bird pellets from France. They only have them in the big pet shop downtown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you weren't arrested until this morning! Why didn't you go back to the caretaker's shack?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er... well... I kind of got lost, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">The witness has trouble remembering things sometimes. When the police apprehended him, he was on his way back to the shack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, right! Nice try von Karma! No one's going to believe that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see! So he was lost!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please! Your Honor, come to your senses!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I figured I got nothing to do with this incident anyhow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've lost much of your memory, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er... ayup, seems like it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then how could you know that you didn't have anything to do with this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or... Or maybe you're lying about not having your memory, hmm? You know exactly who you are!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">The witness has testified quite clearly that he has no memory of who he is. If you claim he's lying, then show the court proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... How am I supposed to prove what's going on in that old codger's head? That's impossible!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph! I'm glad you've come to your senses, Mr. Wright. Very well, witness. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er... I mean, I'd need one of those "motive" things, right? And I don't got one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How can you say you had no motive? I say you do! You had a grudge against Edgeworth and the victim, Robert Hammond! That's why you took revenge on them! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Please don't make me repeat myself, Mr. Wright! This witness has no memory of anything beyond several years ago! He can't hold a grudge! It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to prove he's lying about his memory... Otherwise, it's going to be the same thing over and over until the trial ends!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>First things first, I have to prove this man is who he is! Do that and the motive will prove itself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Might I say something, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You've been saying the same thing now over and over. You've been calling the witness's memory of the past or lack thereof into question. But, does this really have anything to do with the current case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, Your Honor. The witness has said he has "nothing to do with this case" and "no motive"... Both of these statements are lies!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Mr. Wright! There is a serious problem with your claim! Or... are you saying... Are you saying you know who this witness is!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Ho hoh! Now, this is interesting. I would like to know myself! So, who is he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't play dumb von Karma!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please tell us this witness's name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name... is "Gregory Edgeworth"! ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Er... Mr. Wright? All of us here remember what Gregory Edgeworth looked like. And he looked nothing like this, believe me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... that's pretty harsh, Your Honor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm going to have to penalize you for your wild claim! Now... let me ask you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name... is "Robert Hammond"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Wright. Robert Hammond is the name of the victim in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Generally, the victim in a murder case is no longer living.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's true...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, try again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His name is Yanni Yogi, a former court bailiff!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Yogi...? That name seems familiar. ... Oh! Yanni Yogi! From the DL-6 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I thought the judge would have heard of it... it was such a famous case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, what does this mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! If this man is Mr. Yogi, then he has a clear motive!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Jumping to conclusions again, Mr. Wright! This man, this witness, is Yanni Yogi? Fascinating! However... How do you propose to prove this to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">This is a court of law, as you may recall. You need proof! And, allow me to repeat, once more, that the witness has lost his memory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is it... I have to do this now! If I can't prove he's Yogi right here, right now... Then I've got nowhere else to go!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! How are you going to prove it!? How can you prove that he's Yanni Yogi?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's okay. It's actually quite simple. Your Honor! Please take this man's fingerprints! Then, we'll compare them to the fingerprints on file for Yanni Yogi 15 years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... that makes sense.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">I'm so very, very sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-why?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">The witness... has no fingerprints!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What!? No fingerprints!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Er... you see, before I worked as a caretaker, I worked at a chemical plant. I burned my fingers working with the stuff. Ayup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!? <thought>Yogi, you sneak! You burned your fingerprints off to hide your past!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, if the witness has no fingerprints... I guess we will not be able to prove his identity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Well, what will you do, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmm? It seems that the case has been decided, no?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No!!! I know what happened! I know everything! I... I just can't prove it! But no... I can't let it end like this. I can't lose! There has to be another way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">There is no one who can testify as to who this witness is! No one!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What are we going to do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I didn't even consider that he might have erased his fingerprints... <thought>What do I do!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Well, Mr. Wright? Perhaps you'd like to cross-examine the parrot for a little comic relief, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, yeah, very funny. You're a sore winner, von Karma. ... Wait a second... "Cross-examine the parrot"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what is it, Nick? No... you're not going to...!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense would like to take Mr. von Karma up on his proposal!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Take Mr. von Karma up?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">On his... proposal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor! I would like to cross-examine the witness's pet parrot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order! Uh... well, what do you think, Mr. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Need you even ask!? This is a farce! I object!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! You were the one who suggested I cross-examine the parrot, von Karma! I have a right to do as you suggested!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mmph... ... Well, if you're so desperate, then please, be my guest.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Of course, should you go through with this... And nothing comes of it, then I hope you're ready for the consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... this is crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Well? Still want to go through with your little game!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let the parrot take the stand. I will cross-examine her, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">This is the most ridiculous thing I have ever heard!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>von Karma's rigged every person's testimony, every piece of evidence... Except the parrot! She's my last chance! At least... I think so.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You know, come to think of it... This is a really stupid idea.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... I've heard of desperate men grasping at straws... But this is the first time I've heard of men grasping at macaws! Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think! von Karma is a perfectionist in all things. He's probably rigged every piece of evidence and all the testimonies... If I can't do the unexpected I've no chance of winning!</thought> Your Honor. I've thought about this proposal... And I'm going to do it. I'm going to cross-examine the parrot!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Bring in the parrot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's... quite a bird. Please tell us your name?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Name!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness is ignoring me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It must be hurt... to be ignored by a bird.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. Very well, witness... Who is your owner? Please, er... testify for us.</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Certainly the most concise testimony we've had so far. Very well, begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you going to do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I... I don't know! What do we do, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness! You can't just say "hello" and expect us to get anywhere! I want you to testify! Maya, you talk to her.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-right! Uh... What do I say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Remember... two days ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pol-ly, Pol-ly. Have we forgotten something?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">*squawk* "Don't forget DL-6!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If I can get Polly to say that here...! That will prove that the caretaker had something to do with DL-6!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Polly? Have we forgotten something?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"... ... Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Th-that's not what you're supposed to say! Forgot! Something we forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh oh. It's not working, Nick! She won't say it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is ridiculous! Why won't she say it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Something the matter, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... Don't tell me von Karma expected this! He couldn't have retrained the parrot... could he!? Did he train her not to respond when we asked if we'd forgotten anything!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should get her to say her name?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly! Polly! What's your name?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Pol-ly! Pol-ly!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... I think we've established that this parrot is named "Polly." Does this have anything to do with her owner's identity?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, I guess it doesn't really have anything to do with that, no.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Please only ask questions pertaining to the matter at hand. Very well, witness. Continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes it does!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hah! Fascinating! You claim that the parrot's name will prove her owner's identity? Then show us this proof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't you think you're taking the bluffing a little too far?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen. We've not here to answer the question of "who is the caretaker." We're here to prove that he is Yanni Yogi! All we have to do is tie the name "Polly" to Yogi!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. The proof that the parrot's name reveals the caretaker's identity is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I had hoped you would have learned this by now... Making random guesses here is a waste of court time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... wrong again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all! Witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The DL-6 Case File?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">That's quite a large file you have there! Which page is this "proof" on, then? Show us, or stop wasting our time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Mr. Wright, please show us the page. Where in this file is the information connected to this parrot's name?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Case Summary" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry... But I don't see anything here that relates to the name "Polly." At least, not on this page.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph! A bluff! As I expected!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I have to deny your claim, Mr. Wright. The witness may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Victim Data" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry... But I don't see anything here that relates to the name "Polly." At least, not on this page.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph! A bluff! As I expected!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I have to deny your claim, Mr. Wright. The witness may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Suspect Data" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This page has all the information about Yanni Yogi! Right after he was arrested, his fiancee committed suicide, see?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed, it does say that, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was his fiancee's name?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Polly Jenkins"... "Polly"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor! He remembered the name of his fiancee who committed suicide. That's why he named his parrot after her!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see! I guess that is possible.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! A mere coincidence, that's all! My granddaughter has a dog she calls "Phoenix." Well, Mr. Phoenix Wright? Does this make you my granddaughter's fiancee!? She's only seven years old!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed. Alone, it is a little weak for evidence in a murder trial. We would need some other corroborating evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where am I going to find that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We're getting closer! One more! If we can just get one more piece of evidence...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, witness. You may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I'll get her to say the number of that safe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? The safe? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's just try to get her to say anything, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly! What was the number of the safe in the shack?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"1228... 1228..."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... My, what a reckless parrot. Well, Mr. Wright? You aren't claiming that this number has something to do with the caretaker?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, I guess it doesn't really have anything to do with that, no.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Please only ask questions pertaining to the matter at hand. Very well, witness. Continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually it does! That's why I had her say it!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hah! Ridiculous! How can the number to a safe tell us who the caretaker is? Show us your proof! What could possibly link this number to the caretaker's true identity!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Admittedly, I didn't think you had anything to show us. And now I see I'm right. How could a safe number reveal someone's identity?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... I think that was the wrong thing to show them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph. I hope you're happy now, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness may continue her testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">The DL-6 Case File? What is this obsession you have with that case?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Where in this file is something relating to the safe number?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Victim Data" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. This file is from a case 15 years ago. I don't see anything about a safe in here at all!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">I believe this is another one of Mr. Wright's bluffs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Very well, witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Suspect Data" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. This file is from a case 15 years ago. I don't see anything about a safe in here at all!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">I believe this is another one of Mr. Wright's bluffs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Very well, witness, continue your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's on the "Case Summary" page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Case... Summary?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Specifically, the date on which the DL-6 Incident occurred!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The date of the incident? December 28...? Why, that's today's date. Fifteen years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the number on that safe is 1228!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He used the date of the DL-6 Incident as the number for his safe, Your Honor! That's how important that date was to him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... it certainly is an interesting coincidence. People often do set their secret numbers to dates.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! This is not tangible proof! I set my ATM card's number to "0001" because I'm number one! This has nothing to do with a date! Nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed. Alone, it is a little weak for evidence in a murder trial. We would need some other corroborating evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where am I going to find that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We're getting closer! One more! If we can just get one more piece of evidence...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... but what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, witness. You may continue.</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Witness, you're here to speak! You must speak to me!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Frankly, I can't believe that you're speaking to the parrot.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-well... I guess we should try to get some information out of her! We need to show the judge that her owner is Mr. Yogi!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I think we've reached a conclusion here.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">This is a mere coincidence, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">True, that is a possibility. However, two coincidences at the same time seems more like a "pattern" to me.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh... what are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Summon the caretaker of the boat shop. Immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness... Tell us your name.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wait! This witness, he doesn't remember...</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">No... it's okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I've accomplished what I wanted to do. I'm done.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! He looks totally different!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the real Yogi, I think. Finally. He's been acting feeble to hide his true identity. Acting... for 15 years!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-well...! Let me ask you again. Please state your name for the court!</line>
<line speaker="Yogi">My name... is Yanni Yogi. 15 years ago, I served as a bailiff in this very court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Yanni Yogi! So was it you who killed Robert Hammond...? And tried to frame Miles Edgeworth for his death?</line>
<line speaker="Yogi">... Yes.  It was me. I did it. ... They put me on the witness stand 15 years ago... Robert Hammond... he said I was mentally unsound. He told me it would make me innocent. Get me off the hook. So... I pretended to have brain damage... I was innocent, really! But he didn't believe me! We won the trial... But I lost everything. I lost my job, my fiancee, my social standing... ... Then, this year, 15 years later... A package arrived. It was a letter... and a pistol. The plan was written out in careful detail. It was a plan to take my revenge on the people who ruined my life. I didn't care who had sent it. I thought this was my chance, after 15 years, this was it! Finally, a chance to have my revenge on Robert Hammond and Miles Edgeworth... I have no regrets.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-wait a moment! Revenge... against Miles Edgeworth? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Yogi">I'm not at liberty to speak on that matter. Why don't you ask Mr. Edgeworth yourself? Anyway, I admit it, I was the one who killed Robert Hammond.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">von Karma... Where is Mr. Yogi?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Under arrest, Your Honor. I saw no room for error in his confession.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then... the defendant, Miles Edgeworth is...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Innocent. In this case, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Very well. Will the defendant please take the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are a few mysteries left unsolved. Still, you are cleared of suspicion for this particular case. So I would like to pass judgment on the murder of Mr. Robert Hammond. Any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe it! Why isn't von Karma saying anything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. This court finds the defendant, Mr. Miles Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-did someone just say "objection"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It wasn't von Karma...! Wait, but that means...</thought> No... Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. I object to your judgment.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not innocent at all! As we have heard, Yanni Yogi killed Robert Hammond in revenge. But, revenge for what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Edgeworth is trying to confess! He's going to say he's guilty! He's going to tell them he was the murderer in the DL-6 Incident! He's going to tell them he killed his own dad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh! What do I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The judgment has already been passed! I object to Edgeworth's outburst...</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Didn't something like this happen yesterday, too? I believe a certain witness raised an objection after a guilty verdict was passed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would be Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">We must hear this new statement! We must hear Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's right. We have a duty to hear Mr. Edgeworth out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No... I'm sure Edgeworth thought about this one long and hard. This isn't my place to interfere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, are you sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing we can do about it. This is his problem, now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For fifteen years... I have had a recurring dream. A nightmare... it's only a nightmare. That's what I told myself. But now I know, it wasn't a dream. Yanni Yogi wasn't the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean... in the incident where your father died?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From the distance of the shot, it wasn't suicide, either. Everything was as clear as day. The murderer... The criminal in the DL-6 Incident... It was me! Your Honor! I confess my guilt! I am guilty for DL-6, the statute of limitations of which ends today! The culprit... is me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! This is certainly unexpected! The defendant, declared innocent, is confessing to another crime! A crime for which the statute of limitations runs out today! I'm not really sure how I should deal with this...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! It's obvious. We hold a trial. Right here. Right now. We try this man for his crime of fifteen years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think... I think I would like to take a five minute recess. During this time, I will consider the appropriate course of action to take. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sorry, Wright. I've just wasted all of your effort.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Mr. Edgeworth... I just don't believe it, pal! I mean, you... kill your dad?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I didn't want to believe it myself, Detective! But... it's the truth. I deserve to be punished. Murder is murder, no matter what the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is crazy! Just crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ...? Nick? What are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh... I was just reading through the Court Record once more. I'm getting my case ready.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your case... for what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Isn't it obvious? I'm going to prove that Miles Edgeworth is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...! Wh-what are you talking about, pal! He just admitted to it! He confessed that he did it! In court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Edgeworth. But I don't believe in your "nightmare."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just a dream. It's not real. The truth is right here in this Court Record. In any case, tighten your belts. The real fight is just beginning. I'll prove you're innocent. Trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then, I would like to resume our trial.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Judge! Miles Edgeworth has admitted his own guilt. He has confessed his crime. Let us begin by hearing his testimony. Then, though pointless, let the defense do their cross-examining. The statute of limitations on the DL-6 Incident runs out today. Though it's unconventional for me, I'd like to run this one by the book.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Does the defense have any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor. <thought>von Karma... you knew this was going to happen from the very beginning, didn't you!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Will Miles Edgeworth take the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Will the witness state his name and profession.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Miles Edgeworth... I am a prosecuting attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mr. Edgeworth. Fifteen years ago, you mistakenly killed your father, Gregory Edgeworth. Is this correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... It is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Then testify about this matter to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>When Edgeworth was telling me about his dream yesterday I noticed something... One detail didn't quite fit. That will be the key... but only if I can get it to work!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That day, I had gone to the courtroom to observe one of my father's trials.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And, until now, you thought this memory was a "dream"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We were stuck in that elevator for five hours. The oxygen in the elevator ran out, and I lost my memory of the events.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! The same claim Mr. Yogi has made!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Wright? Your cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That day, I had gone to the courtroom to observe one of my father's trials.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was the trial your father was involved in on that day?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't remember things very clearly. Only two things... I know my father lost, and Mr. von Karma was the prosecuting attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. von Karma? You were handling that case?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">It was fifteen years ago. I don't remember the details.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That was when Edgeworth pointed out the problem in von Karma's evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As we went to leave, an earthquake struck, trapping us in the elevator.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, there were three people including yourself trapped in that elevator?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Myself, my father, and Yanni Yogi. We were fine at first... But then as time passed, and no one came to help...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My father and Mr. Yogi lost their composure, and began to argue.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you do then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was a nine-year-old boy at the time. What could I do? I was scared... Trembling, in the corner. But then...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just then, something heavy fell at my feet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pistol. I assume it was the bailiff, Yanni Yogi's. The safety must have come off when it fell from his holster.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">And you picked it up. What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I picked it up, and threw it at Mr. Yogi. I wanted them to stop fighting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know it was a pistol when you threw it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think I knew. I knew it was dangerous. But... the air was getting so thick. I panicked.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">So, you're saying that you threw the pistol at Mr. Yogi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was... in a daze.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A moment later, there was a single gunshot, then a scream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The gun fired once?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I think... after I threw it, I lost consciousness. Since then... They've echoed in my head, every day. That gunshot, and that horrible scream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The scream...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure you only heard one gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I'm sure of that. I heard the shot, and the scream... Then everything faded. I was unconscious until the rescuers came.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that doesn't make sense! Look at this file one more time. This plainly contradicts the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">You do enjoy dragging out that file, don't you? I don't accept this evidence! Unless... you can tell us what page it's on! Which page contradicts Miles Edgeworth's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Looks like your luck has run out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... This page has no contradictions that I can see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait! There is a contradiction in the file!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Then show us the right page! Even my grandchild could do better than you!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Looks like your luck has run out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... This page has no contradictions that I can see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait! There is a contradiction in the file!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Then show us the right page! Even my grandchild could do better than you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the "Victim Data" in this file! It says quite plainly: "the murder weapon was fired twice"! Miles Edgeworth only heard one gunshot! Yet, the murder weapon was fired twice! The first shot was the accidental firing when the pistol was thrown. So... who fired the remaining shot!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Was there, perhaps, another shooter who fired that second shot?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Your Honor. As I'm sure you're aware... This incident occurred fifteen years ago. The evidence is dated... The pistol did fire twice. However, we do not know WHEN that second shot was fired. It might have been fired the day before the incident! There is no proof that the second shot had anything to do with this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see, I see. You do have a point. Mr. Wright? The murder weapon was fired twice, as we have heard. One of those shots was fired by the defendant, a boy at the time. Do you have any proof that the other shot fired had something to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... I didn't think of that.</thought> I, uh, don't have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hah! As I suspected!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Given that all this happened fifteen years ago, it's doubtful any proof remains.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Court Record...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look... doesn't this make you think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa! <thought>She's right! That is strange!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. I think I will be able to show you proof.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh-what!? Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now, Mr. von Karma. Save your surprise for after you've seen the evidence. Very well, Mr. Wright. Show us your proof. Do you have evidence that the second firing of the pistol is related to this incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... Please, think how we feel having to look at this evidence time and time again. Every time you show us ridiculous evidence, I feel, well, mocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah hah... Uh, I mean, I really don't mean any harm by it, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Not meaning any harm"... and "not doing any harm" are two different things, Mr. Wright. Try again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is a photograph of the scene of the crime, fifteen years ago. I can see that the victim lying there is Gregory Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This proves the murder weapon was fired twice, at the time of the incident! This photo proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... So, let me get this straight. This photo proves two shots were fired? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Y-Your Honor, please... Please get a clue! Show the judge the contradiction in the photo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's here... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the victim... Gregory Edgeworth? Gregory Edgeworth was shot once... and he died, as we can see here. What's strange about that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Er... Maybe I need to be more specific here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once more, please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think... it's here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your eyes have a habit of shifting back and forth when you're uncertain. Try taking a deep breath, and think this over once more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As should be obvious, the contradiction is here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... a bullet hole in the door...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Gregory Edgeworth was killed by a shot from the pistol! Yet, there is also a bullet hole in the elevator door! We also know that the murder weapon was fired twice! Thus... Someone other than Edgeworth fired that second shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, there was only one gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I'm sure of that. I heard the shot, and the scream... Then everything faded. I was unconscious until the rescuers came.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It must have been scary.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take a look at this. This is a photograph of the scene of the crime, fifteen years ago. And in it, lies a clear contradiction to Mr. Edgeworth's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I can see the victim, Gregory Edgeworth, lying there... But what do you mean, a "contradiction"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Just as I thought, the judge is clueless... as always. Show the judge the contradiction in the photo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's here... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean the victim... Gregory Edgeworth? Gregory Edgeworth was shot once... and he died, as we can see here. What's strange about that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Er... Maybe I need to be more specific here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Once more, please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think... it's here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your eyes have a habit of shifting back and forth when you're uncertain. Try taking a deep breath, and think this over once more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As should be obvious, the contradiction is here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... a bullet hole in the door...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! Miles Edgeworth testifies that there was only one gunshot! However, according to this photograph, not one, but two shots were fired! One shot hit the victim, the other hit the elevator door. I ask you, then! Why did Miles Edgeworth only hear one gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">This photograph does seem to confirm a second shot. However, when was the hole in the elevator made? It might have been there before the incident occurred! If it was there before, it has nothing to do with this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mr. Wright! Do you have any proof that this bullet hole was caused at the time of the incident!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... I didn't think of that.</thought> I, uh, don't have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hah! As I suspected!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Given that all this happened fifteen years ago, it's doubtful any proof remains.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Court Record...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look... doesn't this make you think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-whoa! <thought>She's right! That is strange!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. I think I will be able to show you proof.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh-what!? Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now, Mr. von Karma. Save your surprise for after you've seen the evidence. Very well, Mr. Wright. Show us your proof. What do you have that proves the bullet hole in the door was related to the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor... The answer is in this file.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">You do enjoy dragging out that file, don't you? I don't accept this evidence! Unless... you can tell us what page it's on! Which page contradicts Miles Edgeworth's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at the "Victim Data" in this file! It says quite plainly: "the murder weapon was fired twice"! Miles Edgeworth only heard one gunshot! Yet, the murder weapon was fired twice!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... Please, think how we feel having to look at this evidence time and time again. Every time you show us ridiculous evidence, I feel, well, mocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah hah... Uh, I mean, I really don't mean any harm by it, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Not meaning any harm"... and "not doing any harm" are two different things, Mr. Wright. Try again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was a terrible scream. I remember it to this day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"To this day"...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I can practically hear it now. I doubt I will ever forget that scream as long as I live.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There it is! One part of the testimony that clearly contradicts the evidence... But I don't know what it means...! I'd better find out, and quick...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-order! Order! Mr. Wright! What are you driving at?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's simple, Your Honor. At the time of the incident, two shots were fired. One went into Gregory Edgeworth's heart. The other hit the elevator door. Remember that the defendant lost consciousness after the shot he fired rang out. In conclusion... We must agree that the second shot was fired by someone else!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! But who could that someone else be!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murderer, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">... I knew I should have stepped in before your wild fantasies got out of hand. Mr. Wright... Look once more at the DL-6 Incident case file. Look closely. Try the "Case Summary" page.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The "Case Summary"... that's on page 1.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Look what is written there! "Not a single clue was found on the scene."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">If the pistol had indeed been fired two times... Then the other bullet would have been discovered on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He does have a point.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">That second bullet has never been found! Why? Because the second bullet does not exist! The bullet that claimed Gregory Edgeworth's life was the one fired by his own son! That is the truth of this matter. The whole truth. It was undoubtedly something else that made that bullet hole in the door.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! I will have order! ... Mr. Wright has proven one thing to us quite clearly... That the murder weapon was fired twice at the time of the incident. However! As Mr. von Karma says, the second bullet was not found. It is highly unlikely that the police merely overlooked this second bullet. So, all we have is the single bullet fired. I'm afraid I have to discount the defense's claim.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... I praise the judge for his wisdom in his matter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gah! How did this happen!? I don't believe that the second bullet didn't exist! Was I wrong? Have I been wrong about this whole incident?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you doing, Nick!? Why aren't you raising an objection!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... It looks like I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the second bullet wasn't there, then all my conjectures are for nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no... But you said you'd do it, Nick! You said you'd get Edgeworth declared innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I'm sorry... It's just, when I saw the photograph, I thought that two shots had been fired. I was so certain of it. I thought I'd won! I thought there was another person, someone else who fired the killing shot. But now... I was wrong to think it could be that simple. This case has stood unsolved for fifteen years!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it seems that we have finally cleared up this incident. Only one bullet was found at the scene of the crime. That shot was fired by Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would like to ask one thing of Miles Edgeworth before passing my verdict. Have you been paying attention to the trial so far?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... No, I do not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you killed your father, though that was not your intention?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Yes, I did.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Oh no... He's confessing... ...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The statute of limitations on the murder of Gregory Edgeworth runs out today. Therefore, I must pronounce a verdict on the defendant, right here...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Right now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Does anyone have any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've been here before... It's just like my first day in court... There are so many things I know I should be saying... But my mind's gone blank, I can't find the words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Every lead I thought I had has been squashed. This is really the end. Edgeworth... I'm sorry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-huh...? Maya...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-are you okay? Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's happening to me...? I have to think...! Wait... don't think... act!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I... I object!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk. Mr. Wright, on what grounds do you object, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I don't know! His case is perfect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what? What did you just say?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The second bullet must exist? But where!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... It seems waiting is not going to produce us any answers from Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh... Th-the second bullet! It, uh, it exists!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? But we've just heard proof that it did not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I realize that, Your Honor. <thought>I'm really grasping here!</thought> I-it's just, someone took it from the scene of the crime! That's what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... Who!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-th-the murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">The murderer? Then tell us, just who is this "murderer"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... still thinking about that one.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the criminal took the second bullet? Why would he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">First of all, how would he have found it? It's not easy to find a stray bullet, Mr. Wright! Was there some pressing need for the murderer to search for that bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-of course there was a need. That's why he took it!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! What possible reason could he have had!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-well... The reason the murderer took the bullet away from the scene with him is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... Maybe he thought that the bullet would be used as proof?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Proof...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was a special bullet, so he took it with him...</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Well, the murderer was a very cautious sort, you see. That's why the murderer had to search for that bullet...</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">It that was the case, then he would have taken the bullet from inside Gregory as well!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Why would he only take one of the two shots fired!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Have you really thought this through? I'm going to have to penalize you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh... This isn't going so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would the murderer have spent the time to look for that stray bullet...? I haven't got a clue!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's wrong, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah! The murderer had no reason to take that bullet! You don't want to admit it, but it's true!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Had to take it...? The murderer? What does that mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor! <thought>I have no idea what I'm doing...</thought> U-uh, well, the murderer had no intention of taking the bullet from the scene. But... uh, the murderer HAD to take that bullet.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Had to," Mr. Wright? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, for instance... <thought>For instance WHAT!?</thought> Uh, maybe the bullet, uh... hit the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The bullet... hit the murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">J-just saying, for instance. I mean, if it hit you, you would have to take it with you, wouldn't you? It's not like you could perform surgery right there. Y-y'know?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second... I was just talking off the top of my head, but what if that's really what happened?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me get this straight. So at the time of the murder, the murderer himself was shot? And he left with the second bullet still inside!? Thus leaving only one bullet at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yes... I guess that's how it would work, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But there's a problem with that! The other two people rescued from that elevator... Miles Edgeworth and Yanni Yogi were both unharmed! So that would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murderer came from outside, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Mr. Wright. You are truly the most unpredictable defense attorney I've ever known. I can tell you're grasping, yet I cannot deny the possibility of what you say.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">What are you saying! Deny it! Deny it! No one involved with the incident was wounded! There was no "murderer"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No one was wounded at the time of the incident... He's right. I can't think of anyone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I just thought of something really crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Crazy?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember what Mr. Grossberg said yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Gregory Edgeworth dealt a blow to his perfect trial record.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It must have been quite a shock for von Karma. He took a vacation for several months after that, you see. Yes, an unusual event for the man. That was the first, and last vacation he's taken in his many years of prosecuting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What if von Karma didn't take that vacation because of shock...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But took it because he was injured!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Which would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It could only mean one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He was the murderer in the DL-6 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was the man who shot Gregory Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It was... von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something wrong, Mr. Wright? You seem... dazed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, n-no, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? You have indicated the possibility that the murderer came from outside. Can you give us the name of your suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. Should I come out and say it now!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... I don't have enough proof yet. This is my trump card, I'd better save it for the right time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright? Something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm fine, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Shall we carry on with the trial then, hmm? That said, we have no farther to go. All that is left... is the finish. In other words... the verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what! Not yet!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Think, Mr. Wright. You have said that someone from the "outside" was the murderer. Yet you cannot suggest anyone as a possible suspect! Which means your conjecture... is worthless. And will be rejected. Of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Now's no time to be holding on to that trump card! The trial's almost over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-alright! I may not know what I'm doing... but here goes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! There is a suspect... one lone suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this is certainly interesting news. Very well, Mr. Wright. Who is your suspect?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">V-V-V... <thought>Urk! My h-hands are shaking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">von Karma!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean, THE von Karma? The prosecutor? Sitting right there?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Bah.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... don't object?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph. I see no need. Why honor this ridiculous outburst with my objection?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because you took a vacation for several months starting the day after the incident! Yet you pride yourself on a perfect record! Why would you take such a long vacation without any reason!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">So you're claiming that I took a vacation to heal my "injury" from the incident? Fascinating! Prove it. I would have needed surgery, no? Where did I go under the knife at, Mr. Wright!? Bring the doctor that operated on me! Have him testify!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Let's find out who his doctor is!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's no use.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know von Karma. Perhaps too well. He's perfect. He wouldn't leave clues. He probably didn't undergo surgery. That would leave a doctor as a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Grr... Nobody's that perfect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... so what, Nick? Did von Karma pull the bullet out by himself!? That's insane!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... he couldn't have. You can't just pull bullets out of yourself! ... <thought>Wait... What does that mean...? That bullet has to be somewhere! But... where?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Well, Mr. Wright! Can you produce evidence to prove that I was shot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It would be impossible to find the doctor who operated on von Karma now... Even if von Karma did undergo surgery!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph! It seems you have finally come to your senses. You've realized the truth: You can't prove something that didn't happen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The Court Record...? What could be in there!? Gah! There's no time! I'd better think on it as I go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright, von Karma. I'll prove it. And I'll even use evidence... I know how you like it so much.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The evidence that proves von Karma was shot is...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Karma">What exactly is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Judge, if you would?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Right. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm really not sure how I've managed to make it this far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please reconsider your evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">von Karma is perfect... He wouldn't risk surgery, leaving an evidence trail. So then, I ask, where is that bullet now? I think it unlikely that von Karma performed surgery on himself!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! You... you don't mean!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I do. There is the possibility that the bullet is still inside von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-is that even possible? For all these years!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, there's one way to find out. We could use this metal detector! Well, von Karma? I'm going to run this over you, and see what we find.</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">... I... refuse!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-you refuse...!? But, refusing this means... You acknowledge that the bullet is still inside you? Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! The defense requests that we be allowed to use the metal detector!</line>
<line speaker="Karma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Judge! I call for a suspension of this trial! This is an invasion of privacy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The statute of limitations runs out on this case today! It was you who said we had to end it right here, right now!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mm... mmmph!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough! I permit the use of the metal detector. Mr. von Karma, you will submit yourself for testing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What does this mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... but we have to give it a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It reacted! Something's inside his right shoulder! The bullet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Mr. von Karma...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You! It was you!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... I was afraid this would happen. And so, I remained silent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Indeed, there is a bullet in my shoulder. However... it has nothing to do with this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">I was shot in the shoulder long before the DL-6 Incident! I claim that the bullet in my shoulder has no relation to DL-6!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-but, Mr. von Karma! Can you prove that?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">"Prove"? I have no obligation to prove anything! It is you who must prove something here, Mr. Wright! Not I.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright? Well? Can you prove it? Can you prove that the bullet in von Karma's shoulder was from DL-6?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Of course he can't! You don't have any of the DL-6 evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's because you took it out of the Records Room yesterday!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">With no proof, you cannot convict me of any crime! So sorry, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No... I'm the one who's sorry, Mr. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were close... one day away from freedom. You see... I have proof!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who would have thought you would have dug your own grave trying to convict Edgeworth! I can link that bullet in your shoulder to the DL-6 Incident... And here's my final proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick...? Umm... If this if your final proof, don't you think you should choose a little better?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean, that was the wrong evidence? Everyone looks kinda puzzled...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, he's really mad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think you'd better dig out the right evidence, and quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right! You got lucky, von Karma, but this next one is the real evidence, okay!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-that's... A bullet?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Where did you get that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the bullet used in the DL-6 Incident. This was taken from the heart of the victim, Mr. Gregory Edgeworth. The bullet is preserved quite nicely, with all the ballistic markings intact.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ballistic markings...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You may recall the term. It came up in the first trial, two days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ballistic markings are the fingerprints of a weapon. All bullets fired from a gun are marked with that weapon's unique pattern. By examining the markings, you can tell which weapon fired the bullet. It's quite accurate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have two bullets in our possession. One, the bullet removed from Gregory Edgeworth's heart. The other, Mr. von Karma, is the bullet buried in your shoulder. We could analyze both bullets... Then, if the markings matched... We would know that both bullets had been fired from the same gun! The very same pistol... in other words, the murder weapon that killed Gregory Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mmmph... mmmph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. von Karma? You will let us remove the bullet from your shoulder. Then we'll compare the ballistic markings to those on this bullet... And solve this case once and for all! Well, Mr. von Karma!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mmmrrrrrrgggh! Uuaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That scream... I've heard that scream before... Wait... I know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's that scream I heard in the elevator! Fifteen years ago... von Karma! It was you who screamed!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Wooorrrrrrroooorrgggh Eh...Edgewoooooorrth......... ...Ehh...Edgewoooooorrth...... Only...you would... dare...defy me...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So... it was you!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">You and your father are my curse! Your father shamed me with a penalty on my record! And you... you left a scar on my shoulder that would never fade! I... I'll bury you! I'll bury you with my bare hands! Death! Death!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Mr. Chief Prosecutor... I am sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">I... was careless.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...! Edgeworth!!!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tsk tsk tsk... Who would have thought another man would have come to open that elevator door? Judge!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-what?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">What are you doing!? Do your job! Bring an end to this miserable charade! Now! End it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">V-very well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears that we have come a very long way to the end of this maze. Fifteen years later... Mr. Miles Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were innocent. You are innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you said, it was all a "nightmare."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Mr. Miles Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Nick! We did it! Did you see his face!? von Karma looked even paler than usual! He's pretending to be all cool, but inside you crushed him, Nick! Crushed! I gotta say, I'm impressed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heh... It was pretty close, though. I was sure we'd had it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know, I was on the verge of tears the whole time, myself. But now it's all just a good memory!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, it's finally over, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I... I'm not sure how to say this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I know! I know! Try "thank you."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I see. ... Th-thank you, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you're welcome.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think you could have done better than that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oof! S-sorry... I'm not good at this sort of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You got a lot to learn, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dear, dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoooooooooooooop! Amazing, pal! You pulled through just like I thought you would! I'll never forget this! I owe you one, pal. And tonight, let's party! Dinner's on me! Yeah, my salary went down again a bit this month... But who cares!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See, Mr. Edgeworth? You should take a lesson from Detective Gumshoe! That's how you say "thank you"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmm. I... I see. *ahem* Whooooooooooooop! ... I... I feel foolish.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry. Take it a little at a time. You'll get used to it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been fifteen years since I've seen Edgeworth this... unguarded.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, y'all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all were great in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yo, Edgeworth! Congrats!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Er... thank y'all very much.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I knew you were innocent from the start, of course. Just look at you! You wouldn't stick your hand in the cookie jar even if no one was there!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You... were the witness on the first day of the trial, weren't you.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, well, let bygones be bygones, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of which, what are you doing now, Lotta?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Who, me? Aww, I went back to college. I gave up trying to be an investigative photographer pretty quick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? That's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Isn't that the hotdog guy from the park?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's over, Nick! My life is over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-why the sad face, Larry!? What happened now!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, Nick... I'm not long for this world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... you don't look sick...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It's Kiyance! Sh-she's goin' to live in Paris! Paris, Nick! She's leaving me behind!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Larry, Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo, Edgey! There you are!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, yes, here I am.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Congrats, Edgey! Here... a little gift from me in celebration!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Celebration? That's unusual for you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Harry Butz! You come along tonight too! My treat, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Uh... thanks! Looking forward to it! <thought>Yo, yo, Nick! That's the suit that questioned me! When he says treat... that's not police-talk for prison food, right? Right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I think you'll be fine, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah? What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That envelope that Larry gave me. It's got money in it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah. That's not that strange. People give money away to celebrate sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's $38.00, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh. What a weird amount. I mean, it's not a little, but it's not a lot either. ... $38.00 exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-N-Nick! Wasn't that exactly the amount of lunch money that was stolen from Mr. Edgeworth in school!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">$38...! No... No!!! Larry, it was you!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you so surprised about, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Larry was absent that day from school, right? But that doesn't automatically rule him out as a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think back to that day, fifteen years ago. Larry took the day off, but he was bored, he came in to school anyway. Then he saw the money lying there... and the rest is history.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I never was good at History! Heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Edgeworth... you didn't know, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suspected. I just couldn't picture Larry protecting you like he did that day. Everyone else was saying you did it. The whole class was against you, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... too well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, you may not know this, but we used to have a saying back in school. "When something smells, it's usually the Butz."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really, Wright. I'm surprised you didn't figure it out!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, this is sure an unexpected turn of events, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You should have told me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now, now, Nick. It was fifteen years ago! Don't you think the "statute of limitations" has run out, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd say so, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">There you have it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr... Where does that leave me!? I became a defense attorney because of what you two did!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I'd call you a goody-two-shoes to the extreme.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah! And you get worked up too easily, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-death! The death sentence for both of you! Man, if only I had known, I'd have become a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The same goes for me, only the other way around... For the longest time, I thought that I might have killed my own father. I thought I might be a criminal. I became a prosecutor in part to punish myself. If I had known the truth, I might have become a defense attorney after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Want to switch, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey, y'all! Line up, I'll take a photo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, photo time! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And after that, dinner on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe took us out on the town that night. We celebrated Edgeworth's new found freedom. Although, Edgeworth was still in detention.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa... I went a little overboard yesterday. My head hurts... Huh? It's still only 5:00. Maybe I should go back to sleep... Hmm? <thought>What's this? A letter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Good morning, Nick. You were really impressive yesterday. Seeing you... It made me think about what I'm doing here. I'm a spirit medium... in training, of course. I wanted to help Mr. Edgeworth too. I wanted to help you. But I couldn't. I was useless. So, I've decided to go back to my training. I'll become a full-fledged spirit medium, for starters. I couldn't say it to your face, so I left this letter. Goodbye, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>G-goodbye!?</thought> What time is it? Gah! The first trains for the mountains have already left! To the station!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I guess I'm too late... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! N-Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... you're leaving?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. It's hard being a spirit medium who can't talk to spirits. And... I think you'll do fine without me, Nick. Be good... okay!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I never could have saved Edgeworth without your help.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the last day of the trial... I heard her. I heard Mia's voice!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You heard my sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... only her voice, but still... It was at the very end when I thought we'd lost everything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, that's my sister for you. Detective Gumshoe helped, and Mr. Grossberg, and even Larry... I'm the only one who couldn't help. I was useless, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you were the one who stopped von Karma, Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? I-I didn't do anything! All I did was wander around in a daze...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I have evidence that you helped!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">E-evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Show Maya some evidence to cheer her up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">A bullet...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">von Karma was convinced he had taken all of the evidence pertaining to DL-6! But you were the one who rescued the last piece of evidence we needed! This was the bullet that put an end to von Karma! And you were the one who gave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Maya. I couldn't have done it without you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...  ... I'll be back soon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm going to complete my training, and come back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Okay. I'll be waiting. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course you will. You can't run that office by yourself! You're hopeless!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I don't know about that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Huh? S-sorry, Nick. I guess I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh! Now that I think about it I don't understand this evidence either!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's okay. You don't have to try and cheer me up. But... One day, I'll come back and be useful, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... bye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! Don't think you've graduated yet, amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Perhaps you'd like to rethink that claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... yes, Your Honor. <thought>Uh oh... I got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Mr. Edgeworth came down to the precinct to wish me a happy new year! Talk about a pleasant surprise!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whoooooooooooooop! Detective Gumshooooooooooe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then he hung his head low and went right back outside. Kind of like he was embarrassed or something. Strange, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Nick? Nah, haven't seen him lately. Who, me? I've been working at a cheese shop! That's Missy's a nice lady, but she's not exactly what you'd call a "cheap date". Huh? Oh, she's in Hawaii right now, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Who? Wright? Yeah, I remember him. I hear he's busy lately. You know, not to ring my own bell, but I sort of taught him everything he knows. I'm sure he's grateful.</line>
<line speaker="Bellboy">Phoenix Wright...? Hmm... Ah! The defense attorney for whom I wrote that affidavit for, yes! Oh, you should know, I've taken over management for the Gatewater hotel recently. Should you be in the area, please, stop by...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Phoenix Wright...? He an actor? Well, I'm not buying it! You can't be a star with a name like "Phoenix"! Did you finally know they're putting out some of Hammer's old movies out on DVD in one of them box set thingies that you can buy now-a-days and all not that I know what a "DVD" is or why they use three-letter words for just about everything these days how am I supposed to keep it all straight anyhow, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Will">I'm pleased to announce the Pink Princess is a hit! I sure owe that Mr. Wright a great deal. *sniff* Oh, and I'm keeping my face out of the public eye until the show's over. I wouldn't want to ruin any kids' dreams, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, I got a letter from Maya the other day. It sounds like she caught a cold standing under a waterfall. I wanted to visit, but didn't have time, so I sent her some Pink Princess trading cards. She says she can't buy them where she is. What kind of place is she living at anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Cody">Wright? Who's that? You wanna talk? Let's talk Pink Princess! Alright! But... you know. I snuck into the studio the other day. And I saw her... the one inside the Pink Princess suit! Ugh! What a dog! It was kind of a shock for a boy of my tender age.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, I remember Wright! That lawyer guy! Huh, me? I'm in training to become a paranormal photographer! You know that picture I took of everyone? Well, just behind them there's a ghost! For real! Now that's talent! I'm gonna be famous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very convinced, Mr. Wright. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are that evidence and the statement just now related...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I must be on the wrong track?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court find the defendant, Mr. Miles Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. The court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>