<xml>
<title>Turnabout Big Top</title>
<line speaker="Max">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning Max.</line>
<line speaker="Max">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Mil... Milk...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Max">If I don't have a glass of milk before I go on stage... I just can't function sweetie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">St-Stage? Don't worry... There won't be a stage. All you have to do is sit down.</line>
<line speaker="Max">I guess...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick. Max is really nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's understandable.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Hey! My sweeties!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You don't think I should fly, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Max">You know... You've got to make a good first impression! When I enter the room, maybe I should fly in and warm up the crowd a little...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no no no... We can't be having you flying around the courtroom... It just wouldn't be right. Imagine if you hit someone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry Max... Just do what Nick says and everything will be OK.</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh sweetie!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it this time, Max?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Why don't you try flying into the courtroom?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Max">I can see it now... The dashing young lawyer flying fabulously in from above! One glimpse of that, and everyone in the room will be on your side!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Max... Really... No one needs to fly today. ... Nick? What's with that look in your eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I like the sound of that... "Dashing young lawyer flying fabulously..."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And now the case of one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Sorry... I just realized that the defendant's name is Billy Bob Johns.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, isn't the defendant also known as Maximillion Galactica?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor, he does often go by that name.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You know, my grandchild is a huge fan of his. I think everyone here wouldn't mind if we call the defendant Maximillion Galactica... It sounds more... Friendly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I wonder if that is to our advantage?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma. Your opening statement if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must still be upset about what happened last time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess being born with the name Von Karma is a free pass to be arrogant and annoying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-M-M-Me!? ... Guilty!? What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her dad is gone you know...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may call your first witness Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't mention it! It's no trouble at all! I've been looking forward to this.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">At your service, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Detective. You may proceed with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The night of the crime, snow was falling until 9:40 PM, making it extremely cold out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... He was beaten to death.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here is the autopsy report for the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accept* <thought>[sic]</thought> this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A blunt object... Hmm... Very well... Mr. Wright, you may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The night of the crime, snow was falling until 9:40 PM, making it extremely cold out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me ask you about the snow...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was nearly a blizzard up until the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did it pile up?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It wasn't such a big deal... Maybe about an inch and a half was on the ground. The snow froze in place and stayed on the ground until the next day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... The snow... Let me see... There's got to be more to this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh? What's the matter? Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need to take a look at the Court Record...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Gumshoe, what were the members of the circus doing on the night of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me ask you about the snow...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was nearly a blizzard up until the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did it pile up?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It wasn't such a big deal... Maybe about an inch and a half was on the ground. The snow froze in place and stayed on the ground until the next day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... The snow... Let me see... There's got to be more to this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eh? What's the matter? Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I need to take a look at the Court Record...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All of the circus performers gathered in the Big Top to practice their routines.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When you say "all of the circus performers"... Who do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Everyone but the dancers and staff were there. Regina the animal tamer, Moe the clown, Ben the Ventriloquist... And of course, the defendant, Maximillion Galactica, and his victim, the Ringmaster. Oh, I almost forgot... Regent the tiger was there as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of curiosity, what about the circus monkey?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When I was investigating yesterday, he happened to snatch my wristwatch.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective, you are welcome to file a police report AFTER these proceedings!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The practice session broke up around 10 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After the practice was over, where did everyone head off to...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Regina was playing with Regent, while Moe went back to his room tired from work... Ben the ventriloquist went to the front gate absorbed in his own world... The Ringmaster and Max went off to the Ringmaster's room to talk privately.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Talk privately, huh? That's awfully suspicious... You wouldn't happen to know what they were talking about would you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It seems they were negotiating Max's salary...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Actually, Max was asking for Regina's hand in marriage!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The murder itself took place in the plaza in front of the lodging house at 10:15 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd like you to be a bit more specific about the events at 10:15 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh... Umm... OK... Not a problem, pal. We've got a witness that told us how the whole thing went down. OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Alright... We'll just have to revisit that testimony later. Detective Gumshoe, would you mind telling us how the victim met his end?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The victim was found bent over a wooden box dead as a doornail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A "wooden box"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right. The victim must have been carrying the wooden box when he was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Carrying the box, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It was a rather strange wooden box, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... It was much heavier than it looked... Not to mention it was locked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Locked, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This may be my only chance, so I might as well ask some questions...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This wooden box... You figure it weighs about 20 pounds, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sounds about right. The whole thing is lined with iron.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Iron plating? Why do you think it's lined with iron?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I figure they just did it to make the box heavier... Yeowch!!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S-S-Sorry... Suffice it to say, the box is really heavy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You said the box was locked. How exactly was it locked?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well... It had quite a sturdy lock on it. It took quite a bit to open that bad boy up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, when you found the box, it was locked, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, it was. Some of the forensics team took it back to the precinct to crack it open.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... Continue Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you mind telling us what was inside that box?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, when we found the box, it was locked tighter than Fort Knox. So we took it back to the station and cracked it open. All that was inside was this little bottle...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bottle? What is that, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Exactly what it looks like Your Honor. It's a condiment bottle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's inside the bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's filled with... Pepper.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pepper...? Why in the world was it locked in that big box?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There was only one little bottle in that huge box...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if that has some sort of special meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The cause of death was blunt force trauma that snapped a vertebrae in his neck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the Autopsy Report, the murder weapon was a blunt object, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You've done your homework, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And you haven't found this murder weapon, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My theory is that it is something the perpetrator ran off with.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You would think so... Especially since you didn't find it on the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No no no... I bet he made it disappear with magic... Ho ho ho!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There wasn't much that we could go after Gumshoe with this time...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He gave us the facts, as he saw them. But there's gotta be more to this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I didn't see anything... But that's why you're the lawyer and I'm the medium.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that's all we're gonna get out of Gumshoe in this case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean all we're gonna get out of him is that little bottle of pepper?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eh? I'm not even off the stand yet!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I dunno, but "wrapped up" has such a mean sound to it... I'm a sensitive guy...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you very much, Detective Gumshoe. You may step down. Ms. von Karma. Call your next witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She must be talking about Ben the ventriloquist...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if Trilo will show up on the stand as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">My full name is Trilo Quist. I am employed as an opera tenor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ex-Excuse me! The witness called to the stand was one Mr. Benjamin Woodman, Ventriloquist.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That robe must be cutting off your circulation. I said that I was a singer!! Maybe you don't believe me. Fine. I'll grace you with a song. *Ahem*... Mi mi mi mi mi! The world of the law... Exciting and daring... Guilt or innocence... Decided by a judge dressed up like a woman!! ...Well, what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It had a good rhythm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's just the lyrics... They leave something to be desired, so to speak.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">T-Trilo! You know better than to insult a judge!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Shuddup! Just look at your nose. You would think you'd have the sense to fix it!! It's so ugly I want to punch you in the face on the off change swelling would help. You know that your nose is the reason you'll never be an A-List star.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Celebrities must really enjoy saying everything that flashes into their minds.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's going on here!? Order! Order! I demand to know who the witness is!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Don't... Don't worry about me, sir. I'll let Trilo handle this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not worried about you one bit... I'm worried about getting testimony in my court! OUCH!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Once practice was over, I left the tent with the stooge... I mean clown.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Without a doubt. He had on his silk hat, cloak, and the dumb white roses on his chest. How can you mistake someone with that crazy get-up and his nose stuck up so high...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's enough... I think we all get the picture. Just one thing... You said you "ditched" the clown.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's right, dress-boy.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, since you weren't with him, couldn't that mean the clown committed the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... He's got a point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A... silk hat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well done, Ms. von Karma. Your prosecutorial skills are unrivaled. Well done.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-OK... <thought>I guess she's the boss again today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Once practice was over, I left the tent with the stooge... I mean clown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The clown... You're talking about Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course I'm talking about that old fart. He's so pathetic, I can't stand him! Just a little bit of exercise and his makeup is running all over the place... Once practice was over, he was 9/10ths of the way to keeling over for good...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Poor guy...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">We didn't have any choice, so Ben took him back to his room. When it comes to being a first place loser, that guy's ahead of the pack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Once we got to the lodging house, I ditched him and went over to the plaza.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you do then?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I went over to the Plaza to do some thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was awfully cold out that night... Especially with all the snow around... Wouldn't thinking in your nice warm lodging house have been a better idea?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I'm a good thunker* ([sic]</thought>! At least my teachers always said I was...)</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's when I saw Max heading towards the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure it was really Max Galactica?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course I'm sure. How could you mistake someone wearing such a snobby 3 piece get-up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Snobby 3 piece get-up?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Get the wax out of your ears! Lawyers nowadays... You're like talking to a brick wall! Max's 3 piece get-up! Jeez! Could you be any more dense! All together now!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I think you should put a little bit more effort into preparing your questions...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">He was the only one heading that way... How could that punk not be the killer!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw Max and only Max, right Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's right. And that makes him the killer! There was only one person headed that way that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That makes quite a bit of sense and makes Max one suspicious character...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's more to this story than meets the eye... Is there something amiss in this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't really see anything wrong with what Ben... I mean Trilo said.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe you should take a step back and look things over again, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second! There's no proof that the witness saw Maximillion Galactica...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hey! Hey! You still don't get it, do ya? I saw what I saw... It was Max's 3 piece joke of a costume! Alright! Lets* <thought>[sic]</thought> say it all together now!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think you should study up on your celebrities, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, I'm getting shut down by a toy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a bit strange, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What's strange!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That you only saw Max... Doesn't it seem like you should have seen someone else as well?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? Where are you going with this, Mr. Wright? Who else do you suppose this witness could have seen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the... victim...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's correct. If Trilo was at the entrance to the plaza... He should have seen the Ringmaster as well! Ah-hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about!? The Ringmaster and Max went together to the Ringmaster's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... It seems that at this stage I have no reason to doubt this witness' testimony. And there are clearly no conclusive contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's the... victim...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's correct. If Trilo was at the entrance to the plaza... He should have seen the Ringmaster as well! Ah-hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about!? The Ringmaster and Max went together to the Ringmaster's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't hold your tongue Ben! It's your job to answer all the stupid questions.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I'm sorry Trilo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've gotta find a way to get more information out of this witness...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Think about it some more Nick! I'm sure you'll come up with something!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You saw Max and only Max that night?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Jeez, you're persistent. You can ask all you want, my answer won't change! The only person I saw that night was Maximillion Galactica!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He really needs to improve his manners...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Then the police showed up, and took magic boy away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Around what time did the police arrive at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hmm... I suppose that would have been around... Hey, what time was it!?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Huh!? Umm... I think it was around... I'd say a bit after 10:30 PM... I think...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Practice ended at 10 PM so you hung around the lodging house the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I... I... I... I guess that sounds about right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wasn't it awfully cold? I can't believe you'd just stand outside in that weather!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... Uh... The truth is...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Will you shut up, you big nosed dope! Why are you telling him anything extra!? Why can't you believe that we'd just stand outside in that weather?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe you were waiting for someone?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">W-W-W-W-WHAT!? WHO SAID WE WERE WAITING FOR SOMEONE!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But! This witness! He's cracking under the pressure already! I'm on to something!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright! Who do you suppose the witness was waiting for out in the cold that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if he was waiting outside in the cold, it was for one person... And one person only! He was waiting for the animal tamer, Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">WAAAAHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were waiting outside for Regina to come back to the lodging house. Am I mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... I... Umm... You can't really ask me that question...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Who cares who I was waiting for that night! What's important is what I saw! Don't you forget it!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well well well... The puppet may be a bit stiff, but he's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that at this stage I have no reason to doubt this witness' testimony. And there are clearly no conclusive contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if he was waiting outside in the cold, it was for one person... And one person only! He was waiting for the animal tamer, Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">WAAAAHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were waiting outside for Regina to come back to the lodging house. Am I mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... I... Umm... You can't really ask me that question...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Who cares who I was waiting for that night! What's important is what I saw! Don't you forget it!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well well well... The puppet may be a bit stiff, but he's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Eh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't hold your tongue Ben! It's your job to answer all the stupid questions.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I'm sorry Trilo...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've gotta find a way to get more information out of this witness...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Think about it some more Nick! I'm sure you'll come up with something!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Trilo wouldn't happen to have an ulterior motive for incriminating Max, would he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Max is part of that bitter love triangle with Regina. Which is probably why Max conked him over the head.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm Nick... Wasn't Ben the one who got knocked over the head?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Yeah... I think so... I dunno anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Alright! There is obviously a reason why this witness was there that night! He spent all that time waiting for Regina to arrive! Moreover... Even if someone else would've walked right in front of him, I doubt he would have paid them a second thought!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">AHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That makes perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, he did not see the victim on the way to his eventual demise! If you accept that, then you must accept that there is a high likelihood that... He could have missed someone else other than Max heading to the scene! OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Umm... Umm... I guess you got me... Alright! Alright! I'll spill the beans for real this time! It's true. I was waiting for Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Ben">PAIN!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Quist, tell us the truth this time... And I mean the whole truth! Were you or were you not waiting for Regina at the entrance to the lodging house?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I was! I was waiting to propose to her!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were what!? Waiting to... Propose!?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What's the matter!? You think that humans have a monopoly on marriage!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That... The matter of puppet marriage is not under review in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You're the judge! I mean, look at your horrible outfit!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">MORE PAIN!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't be so surprised that I was going to propose to Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You were going to propose... You... A puppet...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't be so obtuse! Just because I'm a puppet doesn't mean I can't love!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I guess you're right... Just because I'm old doesn't mean I couldn't propose to her too!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Exactly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>His Honor is looking a little less than honorable right now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">OK Mr. Wright... Please continue with your examination... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... Did you hear that? His sigh seemed a little wistful.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Don't be so surprised that I was going to propose to Regina!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By proposal, you mean proposing marriage, correct? To Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course that's what I meant! What kinda stupid question is that!? I wasn't going to propose that we become sort of outlaw biker gang together!! Right, Ben!?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Ye-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Got it!? That's the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I even had something to give to her...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was it exactly that you planned on giving her?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You know exactly what I was going to give her, numbskull! The only thing I could find that could match Regina's beauty!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You're gonna die when you hear this... It's an engagement ring!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Engagement Ring!?!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow... Those two nearly fell out of their chairs!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Franziska's whip looks like it's about to lash out at almost anything... One hit from that thing will probably shut someone up for a long time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'm gonna live to fight another day and shut up now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Don't be such a coward!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It may be something of a joke, but this is a historic moment! The first time that a puppet has ever proposed to a human being... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm going to have to agree with the defense here. Will the witness please revise their testimony... Specifically about the engagement ring... I'd like to stick to facts, not sociology.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You sure do enjoy sweating the details, especially for a man in a black bath robe...</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"I even had something to give to her..." to "I planned on giving an engagement ring to Regina..."</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I planned on giving an engagement ring to Regina...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An engagement ring...?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Uh huh! It's actually a diamond shaped stone cut from glass! Even more brilliant than the real thing! I think Regina is going to love it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's just a ring...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... There's got to be something I can catch him on...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I kept it in my pocket, waiting for the change to propose and give it to her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who's pocket was the ring in?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Mine of course! What a stupid question!! You've got to be kidding me! You think Ben could pull that off!?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I-I'm s-s-sorry... R-R-Really...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You don't have to apologize for that!! He's the one who should be apologizing!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course, I also had it in my pocket that night. It was a present for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you went to the lodging house to give it to her?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's right! I tried to give it to her during practice so many times that I lost count, but... That uppity snob kept getting in the way!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Uppity snob!? He couldn't possibly be talking about me... Maximillion Galactica! When I get a hold of him, I'm gonna saw his wood block in half... And not with magic!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... They always say that love creates rivalries.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So what about this present?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">In the end, I wasn't able to give it to her, so I've still got it in my pocket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you are still thinking of trying to give it to Regina...?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course I am! I spent three months salary on this thing! I'm not gonna give up that easily!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm, I wonder how much he receives for appearing in the circus?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Probably way more than he deserves.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">How about it Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's time to unwrap this toy's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's the spirit Nick! Give him heck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, the judge has that dazed look again. Maybe he should get out more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo, do you mind if I show you something?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... Looks like they're going to double team me now...</thought> Do you recognize this ring?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Ah! That's... That's... That's mine!! Give it back! Thief! Thief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Didn't you just testify about this very object? I believe you said... "In the end, I wasn't able to give it to her, so I've still got it in my pocket!" Why then, do I have it right here...?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">AAAAAAAAAARRRRRGHHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is going on here!?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's... That's... Ben! Say something!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Eh? Don't put me on the spot like that Trilo!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this in Money's room...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Money's room? You mean a room they put money, like a bank vault?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hah! That filthy monkey is gonna get what's coming to him!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Quist, I would prefer if you avoided slandering innocent fiats in my court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Your Honor... Money really is a monkey... In every sense of the word.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah. I see... Well then...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Money likes to go after the shiniest things that he can find and gather them up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Shiny... Things?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo! When was this ring stolen from you?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... I suppose it was... That time... You know... That night... The night of the crime...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Details... I need more details...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... It was stolen right after Max showed up in the plaza...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right about when you saw the defendant walk past, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Well... Umm... I guess you... Might... Umm... Be able to say that... The ring might have... Well... It could have been... Taken around that time...</line>
<line speaker="???">Oooo-Ooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Ahhhhh... Yeowwwwwwwww... Ohhhhhhhhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Ben! What's with you!? ... Oh, whatever... It has nothing to do with anything! Especially not who committed the murder!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not for you to decide what has to do with what! Now Trilo! Back to the topic at hand!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I haven't admitted a thing! Not I... Mr. Trilo Quist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you do when the ring was taken Trilo?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You know exactly what I did! I chased after that ring snatching monkey Money!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you weren't able to catch up with him were you?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">It's all this slow loafy fool called Ben's fault! While he was fumbling his way through the snow, that dumb monkey was able to get away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is indeed an incredible shame.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... This does indeed prove one very important point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Obviously that one Mr. Benjamin Woodman is lacking in the area of exercise!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is clear from the testimony we have just listened to!! He was too slow and awkward to catch a monkey fleeing through the snow!!! <thought>This revelation doesn't seem to be registering too well around the courtroom...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe you should leave the courtroom drama for video games and rethink that one...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... OK.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is a huge contradiction in this witness' testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness just testified to the following effect-- Up until the police arrived, he didn't move from the entrance to the plaza. HOWEVER! The witness just stated that he chased after Money the monkey. When the witness was off chasing Money, there was no one watching the plaza!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm saying that there is no possible way that this witness saw the plaza the entire time! That's where I'm going with this little theory! Which leads me to my next point. It is entirely possible that someone other than the defendant was at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Interesting Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he obviously didn't see the victim, the Ringmaster, arrive on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness is lying! He is blinded by his rivalry with Max!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... The defense's argument does hold water. This witness does have a history of animosity towards the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What!? How dare you!? I wouldn't lie just to get that dorkface in trouble! He's not even worth it!! I saw him! No doubt about it! I saw that worthless liar!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... Just for clarity's sake, let's flesh out exactly who you saw on that night.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Hah! I've told you so many times, you'd think you'd know my story's not changing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You've already changed your story stick boy! And I'm sure it will change some more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Where there is one lie, there are usually many more behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Maya. That's why we have to keep after him!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I'll give you that I was waiting that night for Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">That's right. Money ran up less than a minute after I saw Max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then Money snatched the ring, and you went chasing after him?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How long was it until you came back to where you were waiting?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Well. Let's see... I'd say about...</line>
<line speaker="Ben">I suppose five minutes. I think...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I'll give you that I was waiting that night for Regina.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you were only concerned with waiting for Regina that night?  That means you probably wouldn't have noticed if someone else showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You should think about how many eyes I actually have. I've got four, you know! Four. F-O-U-R. Counting Ben of course... With that many eyes, do you really think something would have slipped by me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Four eyes is an awful lot of attention directed at one area, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes! The judge is even more dangerous to our case than Trilo!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">But that doesn't change the fact that I saw Max in the plaza that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you saw Max coming out of the Big Top that night?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Of course that's where I saw him coming from! I was staring at the entrance to the tent the entire time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that makes sense, especially since he was waiting for Regina.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">He showed up after I had been waiting there for about five minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About what time would you say these events took place?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You're one of the dumbest people on the planet if you can't figure it out yourself! You already know that practice finished promptly at 10 PM! And you already know that I went to the lodging house right after practice! You don't need to be a brain surgeon to know around what time it was when I saw him... Just add ten more minutes! I'm sure you can do that! Now what time was it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, what time was it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... What time was it? Lemme think about that for a second......... ...YEOW!! I'm no good at math!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahhh, yes. That sounds about right!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">It sounds about right because that's the time that I saw Max on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I said "good evening" to him, but he didn't even acknowledge my presence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you testified that you said "good evening" to Max that night.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">You must enjoy asking incredibly obvious questions! You say "good morning" in the morning, and "good afternoon" during the day, right? And it's obvious that I'd say "good night" to someone at night!!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What Ben!? You've got something to add!? Lemme guess... "That's not it Trilo! You say 'good evening' at night!"</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Ah... I'm sorry Trilo...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Quist, I would prefer if you kept your ventriloquist's act outside of the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Impossible! A performer lives and breathes his performances! You should know better!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's got to be something wrong with this bit of testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it's kinda petty to bad mouth someone's performances...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think so too... I guess you really are "Wright all the time!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Glad to see you finally coming around to that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Continue with the cross-examination please!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't that a bit strange to you?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you hate Max so much, why would you bother being nice to him? It strikes me as somewhat strange.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Why would it strike you as strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... If it was simply just being cordial to a coworker I would understand... OWW!! That hurt!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no reason that Trilo would ever say something nice to Max... But how do I go about proving that with the evidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Bluffing is everything in this world! ...But I'm sure you already learned that one!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I can give it a shot...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will resume his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hate to say it, but Ben's part of your little act is coming off a bit stale! I'm sure that if a pro was to review your work, he would say... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OW! OWWW! AWWWWWW! THAT HURTS!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I'm absolutely sure it was him! I saw Maximillion Galactica at the scene!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are 100% absolutely sure of what you just said?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I told you already! Jeez!! I am 100% absolutely sure!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">There's no way I could mistake someone wearing those three ridiculous symbols!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those three ridiculous symbols, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Out of curiosity, exactly how many times have you asked that question by now? If you're gonna ask again, I'll answer with a chorus... Everyone together now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"SILK HAT!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">CLOAK!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... You didn't have to join in did you!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... It's fun shouting out with everyone else!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There has to be a hole in his testimony somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. But do we have the proof to make something stick?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All we can do is try, right Nick!? We've gotta have something that will prove useful.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, time to go to work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo, is it not true that you had a fight with Max on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A fight over Regina to be exact.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">It wasn't that big of a deal! It was just an argument... A disagreement at most!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A disagreement usually doesn't end with someone getting clonked over the head...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">AHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That morning, Ben got clobbered over the head by Max, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What? Is that an admission of assault and battery? OUCH!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth is that on the day of the crime, the defendant and witness had a huge fight! There is absolutely no way they would have suddenly become cordial that evening! Moreover, just consider the personality of the witness on stand! There is no way a puppet this lewd would just up and say "good evening" to his rival!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">GWWAAAAHHHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">I-I-I... I didn't tell a single lie! Honestly! I just...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough from you Mr. Quist! Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's clarify this testimony for the court... Could you explain your theory about who the witness actually saw that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course, the witness did not see a soul that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Who... Who do you think you are to just up and decide what it is I saw that night!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, I just thought of something... If Ben and Trilo really didn't see anyone that night, they wouldn't have testified that they greeted someone that night, would they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think that Trilo really did say "good evening" to someone that night.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... Trilo and Max... They were in the middle of a huge fight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe you should think this over some more on your own time, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course he saw the defendant! How could he miss Maximillion Galactica!? OWWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I'm afraid that "Ahh" has just landed the defense a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Foiled again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, you've got to think about things a bit more and give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I know... <thought>And by the looks of things I've gotta hurry up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It is my belief that the witness did indeed see someone that night... It was just someone else! That's who he said "good evening" to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The correct one. Furthermore, I don't believe the person the witness saw was Max at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he had truly met Max that night, there would have been no greeting at all. Which means there is only one proper answer. The person the witness saw that night was not Maximillion Galactica. That is why Trilo made the effort to greet whoever it was that he saw that evening. Or "good evening" as he put it.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Uhh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defense kindly explain who it was Trilo saw that evening then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the person that this witness felt the need to greet that night!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... How about it, Mr. Quist?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">How about you stop asking me these ridiculous questions! You can show me all the crappy pictures you'd like, there's not one I wouldn't greet!</line>
<line speaker="Ben">...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">What the oak are you doing, Woodman? You better not say, "Trilo watch your mouth!"</line>
<line speaker="Ben">Ahh... Well... OK. Sorry about that, Trilo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! ORDER! There will be order in my courtroom! Mr. Wright!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh, now I've done it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You better rethink this line of questioning before I lose my patience with you!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Considering the ill temper of this witness, there is only one person he would greet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It must be Regina! It's Regina right!? She's so cute!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor, it is not Regina. If it was Regina, Trilo would have given her the engagement ring as a present.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... Yeah... I suppose you've got a point there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You are correct. It was indeed Russell Berry.</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person you saw that evening was the victim, the Ringmaster, Russell Berry. That's why you greeted him Trilo. Isn't that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">... *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Answer the question, Mr. Quist!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">WAAAAHHHH!! AH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">ORDER! ORDER! How do you respond to this!?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Wa-Wait a second!! Well, at first I thought it was the old man! But! But! Once I got a better look at him, it was obviously Maximillion Galactica!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think it is high time that we clear the air about this question! Mr. Quist obviously witnessed a single person in the area of the plaza that evening. The problem is identifying exactly who that person was... Was it Maximillion Galactica? Or was it the Ringmaster, one Mr. Russell Berry?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Three symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">Alright... This is getting old. C'mon man! You've gotta remember them by now!! Here we go again! Everyone... All together now!! OWWWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A silk hat and a cloak! Anyone could wear them! They'd even look good on me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the witness has endlessly repeated that he saw Max's three symbols... However, how do we really know it was Maximillion Galactica? It could have been someone else, dressed up as him. Possibly even Russell Berry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have clear evidence that the person the witness saw was the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's the case, then it is impossible for me to make a judgment at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yes! I think we've finally won a point in this one!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">HUH!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will take a 10 minute recess. During that time, I request the prosecution prepare their next witness. Court is now in recess!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Sw-Sweetie! You have to believe me! I didn't go anywhere near that crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So then where were you when the murder took place?</line>
<line speaker="Max">We talked about it yesterday remember? I was in the Ringmaster's room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And while you were there, it was the Ringmaster who left the room, right?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Exactly. He told me to wait in the room because he would "be right back".</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's when the Ringmaster headed to the scene of the crime... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what it seems like.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... The Ringmaster must've been wearing Max's costume. Right?</line>
<line speaker="Max">Oh! Sweetie! I just remembered! I went straight to the Ringmaster's room still dressed in my stage clothes. But when I got there, I went ahead and took the costume off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Which means?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that the Ringmaster could have taken his costume, and went out looking like Max!</line>
<line speaker="Max">FABULOUS! That's a fabulously possible possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh Heh... Well done Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Max">However, sweetie... Why would the Ringmaster want to dress up like me? Isn't that a bit strange?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Max">If you think about it, all they found at the crime scene was my silk hat. What about my cloak? Where did that go?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Double hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow Max. I never thought of that. You should be a detective or something!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Well, I was never quite sure what to be when I grew up... Magician or President? You have no idea how hard it was to make a decision!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's really cool...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fabulous... This mystery just keeps getting deeper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that everyone is back, let's get started. The court is now back in session. Ms. von Karma, please proceed with the prosecution's case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why did she just call him a "pitiful" clown?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... In West Clownadelphia, born and raised, on the playground is where I spent my clowin...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the witness please inform the court why he is speaking autobiographical gibberish?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">O-Oh... I-I'm sorry... I'm just not used to being in court. I've never been in a courtroom in my life. I wasn't quite sure what joke is best suited to this sort of occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What in the world are you talking about!? You're in a grand hall of justice, not some comedy club! Since it's easy to see your occupation, please state your name for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... Oh... Yeah... Maybe this joke is OK... "Mom, do I have to wear pants?" "The sign only says no shirt, no shoes, no service." Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">OK! OK! How about this? "Have you met my proctologist? Dr. Seymour Butts!!" How was that one!? Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! ...But a couple of clowns, they were up to no good... Started makin' trouble in...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Lawrence Curls. Professional funnyman, also known as Moe the clown.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes... Yes it is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Curls. Will you please testify to what you saw that evening?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">A rabbi, a priest, and a Rastafarian walked into this plaza...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Without the humor please.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">OK...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... Poor Moe can't be his normal stoogey self in court.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I know... I know... I'm not the greatest comedian in the world...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Aren't we the ones supposed to be asking the questions here?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Really!? You'll really hear me out!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Thank you!! Thank you!! I can't wait!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that that's settled, shall we begin once again with the testimony!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Of course we can! I'll talk for as long as you want!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The night of the murder, after practice was over, I went straight back to my room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's very interesting... If this eyewitness account is to be believed, I have enough to pass judgment right now...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However... The witness is a bit, how do you say, "off-kilter"... Almost like he has some sort of atmosphere of guilt surrounding him.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Aha! Aha! Aha! That must be because of my insincere smile...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, please begin the defense's cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You've gotta find some kind of contradiction in his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that if you push this witness too far, it would bring disaster upon the court. Thus, I sincerely hope you are not going to engage in pointless saber-rattling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why am I responsible!? I'm not the one with the corny jokes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">The night of the murder, after practice was over, I went straight back to my room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd say that practice wrapped up around 10 PM correct?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">See, that's the thing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">How exactly am I supposed to make a joke about 10:00 PM? Now eight o'clock... That's something a clown can riff off of... Let's just pretend it was eight o'clock... That way I can make a great joke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's not make it 8:00 PM, alright Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">What do you mean let's not! Don't take the clown out of the clowning around!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">C'mon Nick, just listen to his joke!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are three reasons why I don't want to... One, I probably won't laugh. Two, I'll get hit with a penalty. Three, I'll get whipped. Will the witness just proceed with his factual testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You are sooo boring.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You know you want to hear the joke... A man goes to his doctor and the doctor asks, "How is number 1?" The man says "Everyday at six." The doctor asks, "And 2?" The man says "Everyday at seven." "Then what's the matter?" "I slept til eight."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you're hereby penalized! This will not become a kangaroo court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't funny at all... In more ways that* ([sic]</thought> one...)</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You have no idea how tired I was that night. I was pooped.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were "pooped" that night?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes. I was very very tired... Not to mention I had some bad Mexican food.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">The double cheese double bean enchilada is a dangerous menu item... What happened after that, as they say, "happens"... Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! That one was cool, huh? I hear the kids really love toilet humor these days...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That joke was so hip, I don't want to ruin it with a reply.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've got a good reply though. That joke was so funny it just earned you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I thought I'd go straight to sleep, but before I did, I glanced out the window.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just happened to glance out of the window?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You could say that. You could also say I peeked, stared, glimpsed, peeped, eyeballed...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Curls!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh... I guess synonyms aren't allowed either...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What should I do? I wonder if I should press him further on this issue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Very well, Moe. How about we get back to your testimony now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is definitely one of your more straightforward cross-examinations, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Of course! You threatened me with a penalty if I don't keep this stooge in check!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly why did you look out of your window that night?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Why!? Why!? Clowns don't need a reason to look out their windows, do they!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not what I meant. I meant that... Well... When we spoke yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Once I had tucked myself into bed, I heard this amazing noise. It was incredibly loud. It sounded like a giant "THUMP"!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... Oh yeah! I forgot about that!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, the witness looked out of his window upon hearing a loud sound. He did not just simply "glance" out of his window that night.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Oh yeah! That's right! I forgot to mention that "THUMP" didn't I? Owwy Oww Oww...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Yeah... What she said... I believe it would be best if Moe were to revise his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Mr. Curls. Please revise your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This should start turning the tables in our favor!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">I heard a huge noise outside the window, and that's what made me take a look outside...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What was the sound like?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... I guess it kinda sounded like... Hmm... I guess you could say...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Curls. May the court remind you that humor is unnecessary.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Doh! How'd you know that I was gonna make a joke! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! I guess that the sound sounded like a... I suppose it sounded like someone getting hit with something very hard... Yep. That's what it sounded like. Honestly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Someone getting hit..." huh?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's when I saw two silhouettes! They were a bit far away though!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Far away you say... If you had to say exactly, how far away were they?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Let me think about that for a second... If my room is here... And they looked about yay-big... I'd say they were about 30 feet from my window.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It was snowing that night, and it cut down on visibility.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Please continue with your testimony regarding the two shadows that you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It was the Ringmaster, and he was with Max, who was wearing his cloak!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd say you clearly saw this? Even though you were, by your own admission, far away?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's right. I had been thinking about it over and over since that night, but things didn't really make sense until I spoke with the prosecutor, Ms. von Karma. But now I am 100% certain that it was Max and the Ringmaster that I saw that night. Just think about it? How could I be wrong if Max is always wearing his uppity symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uppity symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Lawyers nowadays!! Do you even have to go to school anymore to be one? Alright! Everyone knows what to do!! Altogether now!! Say it with Uncle Moe!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... See what I mean!! It's always like this! The crown never wants to go along with me! I must really be utterly and completely worthless as a clown... Yeowza!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Will the witness please testify as to what he saw... And only what he saw!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I kept watching them, and all of a sudden, Max clonked the Ringmaster over the head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you saw the Ringmaster get "clonked" over the head!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes I did!! It's the climax of my story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He really does enjoy the completely random non sequitur...</thought> What would you say the victim was struck with?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You mean weapon? I have no idea. A weapon wasn't found at the murder scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No no no... You did say you saw the entire thing, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... I, umm... Yeah, I suppose I did. Wait... No I didn't. I didn't see a weapon... Heh heh heh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe! Did you or did you not see the crime of murder committed that night!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*gulp* <thought>Wasn't that a bit melodramatic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... See... Right now, I don't have a clear basis to be thinking that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now wait a second Ms. von Karma! This time, I do not feel the need to treat Mr. Wright so harshly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! What he said! <thought>Bailed out by the judge! What an honor indeed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If we must penalize Mr. Wright for his display, I think a verbal censure would be best.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You know the rules Mr. Wright. There is no room for baseless hounding in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess he didn't really bail me out after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I have grounds to make this claim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's something I can't share with you at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-W-What did you just say!? Mr. Wright!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know there's something wrong with this testimony... But I can't put why I feel this way into words for the Judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we should get a bit more information... Once we find something more solid, we can give it another shot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, before we resume testimony, you know that you must be penalized.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. That's harsh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know... Moe's testimony and what he told us yesterday are kinda different...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah I noticed. We've just got to pinpoint what's changed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You can do it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got a great reason to make my claim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I will... The reason is... The witness' very own testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is the meaning of that Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe said that he heard a sound like a "thump" of someone getting hit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... He did say that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, Moe just stated the following under oath.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I kept watching them, and all of a sudden, Max clonked the Ringmaster over the head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Moe is to be believed when he says he looked out the window upon hearing a sound, there is no way that he could have seen Max "clonk" anyone!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">In 1972, a crack clown unit was sent to prison by a circus court for a crime...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Curls! How do you respond to Mr. Wright's assessment!!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">...they didn't commit. These clowns promptly escaped from a maximum security clown car...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Curls, are you reciting the C-Team theme to anger this court?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">No no no... I'm just stalling for time while I jog my memory...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great job, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">These types of witnesses always seem to have a selective memory... You just have to peel back the layers of the clown make-up to find the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahh, you're back from your jog?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Well... It pretty much happened the way I said.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Pretty much"...?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">When I looked out my window that night, the Ringmaster was already face down in the snow. The prosecution helped me fill in the gaps of my statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Von... Von Karma!! Tampering with witnesses again!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">So now you are saying that you did not see the defendant "clonk" the Ringmaster?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Y-Yes... When I looked out my window, the Ringmaster had already checked out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Checked out?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yep. He was on permanent vacation as they say. Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha! Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Curls!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You did not witness the actual crime; however, you still say you saw the criminal, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Y-Y-YES!! Exactly! The Ringmaster was slumped over and I saw someone's silhouette next to him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Then please testify to this silhouette you saw... I expect the truth! And if I even catch a hint of a joke from you... I will put you in a holding cell until you learn court etiquette, got it!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Got it.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I was a bit far away, but that shadow could only have belonged to Max.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It does seem as if the defendant was at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is decisive testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Was Max really at the crime scene that night...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He said he wasn't there. We have to keep believing that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright, Mr. Wright. Commence your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I was a bit far away, but that shadow could only have belonged to Max.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you think that you are going a little overboard with how explicit you're being? 'That shadow belonged to Max' is an awfully firm statement, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">What are you getting at...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm just saying that one of your fellow performer's life is on the line here. Are you truly, 100% absolutely certain that it was Max?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... I'm not the kind of person who would lie about something as serious as this! The silhouette I saw was Max. I'm convinced of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It doesn't seem like he is jumping to any conclusions this time...</thought> Let's go over this again then. What makes you so sure that you saw Max that night?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">There's no doubting it. Especially since I saw his uppity symbols.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo said the same thing. But if it was just the symbols, then even I could have been wearing them. What if someone had just taken Max's symbols and worn them?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I thought of that myself. But just looking at the shape of the face I saw, it must have been Max.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You're sure of that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Moe">His silk hat. That black cloak. They were all there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're sure that is what you saw that night?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly what I said I saw is exactly what I saw. I've got eyes like a hawk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... Don't birds have terrible night vision?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Moe">But that's not all I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Moe">His face was silhouetted, but there was no doubt that it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were able to see that kind of detail from your window?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of curiosity Moe, what is your eyesight like?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I can see like a hawk out of my left eye, and an eagle out of my right eye...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That must mean he could have seen the crime scene clearly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... The more we look into this matter, the more suspicious it becomes.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hey! You asked me what my eyesight was like, not what it actually was!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">His cloak was fluttering in the wind, so I couldn't really see what he was carrying.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, you didn't actually see what the criminal was holding?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That's correct. I've been curious to know what caused that loud noise... It must have been something incredibly hard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Too bad they haven't found the murder weapon to know for sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">They claim it was a blunt object... At least it says so in the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>With Trilo's testimony, and now Moe's... It really seems like Max is the killer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick... You've gotta find a contradiction in this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's not going to be enough...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to prove that Moe saw someone other than Max that night! That's the only thing that will help! I've gotta do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you saw all of Max's "uppity" symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I suppose so... The silk hat and the cloak, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe... Everyone knows that Maximillion Galactica has three uppity symbols!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Three symbols?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yay! Everyone get ready!! All... Together... Now...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">What the!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">... Do you like Pi? I love Pi! 3.141592653589793238462643383279! Tasty!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe! You didn't see the roses, did you!?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">To be honest... There wasn't any roses on the person I saw...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the witness said he was able to see the silhouette of the criminal's face. Not to mention that the roses are white! There's no way he could have missed them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that was the case, then the police would have found them near the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Are these white roses truly material to the facts of this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... <thought>I got her on the ropes now... Whenever there's a nugget of truth, it always seems to peek out at me... Then run away.</thought> Someone is toying with the court, but it's not me! Your Honor! Do you recall Trilo's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">There's no way I could mistake someone wearing those three ridiculous symbols!</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">How can you mistake someone with that crazy get-up and his nose stuck up so high...</line>
<line speaker="Trilo">How could you mistake someone wearing such a snobby 3 piece get-up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trilo saw them all! Trilo saw all three of Max's symbols! However, this witness claims there were no white roses on the person he saw! There is absolutely no doubt that this is a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Now what am I supposed to think? One is supposed to disregard the pointless, but this...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! It may be trivial, but there should still be doubt lingering in your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Frankly, I have my doubts about this witness. It seems that, unlike wine, the witness has not grown more mature with age.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I'm not... Mature...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've come to a conclusion... I'm 99% certain that this witness saw the defendant. However! My remaining one percent of doubt is quite reasonable! Which means that for my peace of mind, I'm going to request a bit more testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If there are no contradictions in his next statement, I am prepared to issue a ruling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A ruling...!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! This is your last chance!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">There's no doubt in my mind! There were no white roses that night!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright... You've got one last chance at this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just one chance?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will not allow even the slightest hint of badgering against this witness. If you are going to prove to me there's a contradiction with Mr. Curls' statement, you'd better have at least a shred of evidence to back up your accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've only got a single shot as* ([sic]</thought> this... I've got to be careful.) I understand, Your Honor. One chance is all I will need!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">There's no doubt in my mind! There were no white roses that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe... Be honest... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh... I'm finished...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Excuse me. I'm the one handing out the pen-- OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're not going to whip me too, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But isn't it kinda pointless if you only whip me after court?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">However, all of the other symbols were there... I'm equally sure of that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe... Be honest... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh... I'm finished...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Excuse me. I'm the one handing out the pen-- OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're not going to whip me too, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But isn't it kinda pointless if you only whip me after court?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Especially the silk hat! There is no way I could forget seeing the decorations on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe... Be honest... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh... I'm finished...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Excuse me. I'm the one handing out the pen-- OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're not going to whip me too, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But isn't it kinda pointless if you only whip me after court?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He was wearing it the entire time that he was on the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moe... Be honest... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungh... I'm finished...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Excuse me. I'm the one handing out the pen-- OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're not going to whip me too, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">But isn't it kinda pointless if you only whip me after court?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaddya think, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no way I'm going to lose after coming this far. There's gotta be an answer. And it's probably in the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This wouldn't happen to be the silk hat you saw that night, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yep! That's it! That's the hat he was wearing that night!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No question in your mind?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Exactly how would one mistake a thing like that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there some sort of problem, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. von Karma. Where exactly was the silk hat found?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The silk hat fell off at the crime scene! However the witness clearly testified to the contrary!! The witness stated that "He was wearing it the entire time that he was on the scene!"</line>
<line speaker="Moe">NoooooOOOOOooooo!! That's not trrrrrruuuuueeee!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">ORDER! ORDER!! OOORRRDER!! MR. CURLS!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT IS THE MEANING OF ALL OF THIS!? You are old enough to know better than to behave like this in court!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hey! That's just not right!! That's so harsh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's not right here is your eyesight and your memory, amongst other things!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">............... Wh... Why are you being so mean to me!! What did I do!? Lemme guess... You just didn't like my jokes or something, right? You didn't have to go and insult my eyesight or my memory!? They're both great! Seriously!! Why!? Just because you are sitting above me doesn't mean you belong there! And no matter how old I get, I'll always be younger you!!* <thought>[sic]</thought> WAAAAAHHHHHHHH!! *sobs*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Enough of these childish outbursts, Mr. Curls! Who do you think you are?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">I saw him! I swear I saw him!! It was Max!! Even if he didn't have his roses, he was still wearing his dumb silk hat!! I'm telling the truth!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's turned into a bratty little kid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's pitiful, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">He left the scene wearing that dumb silk hat! He was there!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He... Left the scene?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's the matter, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's something I've been mulling over for a while now. Moe?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Whaddya want!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just said that he left the scene... Exactly how did the murderer leave the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">WHAT!? He... Umm... He... Went... Whaddya mean "how did he leave the scene"? You can't ask me that!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This witness' testimony is so full of holes, Ms. von Karma's protest is useless!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You've got a point. Let's hear what the witness has to say on this matter. Is that alright with you, little guy?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Don't talk to me like I'm a little baby!! Besides, what kind of stupid question is "how did he leave the crime scene!?" The answer's obvious! He just turned around and walked away!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I expected you'd say... You sure that's how it happened?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hmph!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? I'm not sure I know exactly where you're going with this... Lawyers nowadays sure do love to harp on the smallest things. Do you have any proof to counter his story as to how the criminal left the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This isn't your idea of a joke is it, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">You're not going to get paid for that one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't look like it worked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What happened? It's like I turned into Moe or something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You'll have to excuse me, but I don't understand what you're getting at.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look at this picture. The problem is the footprints in the snow...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Footprints?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In this photo, we can clearly see the footprints of the victim! However, where are the criminal's footprints? They aren't there!!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Ai-yai-yai-yai-yai!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So Moe, exactly how did the criminal escape the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Umm... He... Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! This witness has already proven that his testimony is completely unreliable! I move to strike all of this witness' testimony from the court record!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree... This clown's testimony is as rickety as the clown car he came to court in.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">WAIT JUST A SECOND!! You guys can't just ignore everything I've said!! Fine fine! I'll tell you the truth this time...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">That didn't hurt!! I'm sick and tired of listening to you anyways!! I'll give you the real deal this time... I swear!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I dunno why, but I get the feeling things are gonna get worse before they get better.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Lawrence Curls.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The testimony you've provided up until now has been false?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It hasn't been false! I haven't lied! It's just...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's just what?</line>
<line speaker="Moe">It's just I was a bit confused on the bit about the criminal leaving the scene. Especially since Von Karma and her whip told me not to talk about what I really saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">ORDER!! ORDER!! I WILL HAVE ORDER!! Franziska von Karma!! How could you!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What opinion is that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough out of you! I'm going to listen to what he has to say. Now then, let's hear the truth about what you say you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Hah! You're not gonna believe this but it's all true I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Now it's time for our next segment, "Moe Knows..."!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... That was... Umm... How do you put this into words...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Why is she right!? You believed the other witnesses! Why won't you believe me!? Especially since it's the best part of the story!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... To be honest, this is the first time I've heard of a flying criminal. What do you think about this witness' testimony, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's obvious that the witness' eyes are playing tricks on him...</line>
<line speaker="Moe">Don't be such a fool! Who in the world do you think I would mistake that jerk for!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Jeez... I didn't say you were lying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, he looks really serious right now. More serious than he's looked all day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What he just said was so strange, I don't think he would have made it up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which means that he is telling the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I think...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, wait! That means that Max actually used magic!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! You're right! OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right now, I can't believe any of this! I'm not even sure if this day hasn't been some kind of Kafkaesque dream... OWWW!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose I will let you all in on my thinking regarding this matter... "The criminal disappeared into the sky." I'd love to believe that... But I just can't wrap my head around how that could actually happen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you disregard a need for proof, Ms. von Karma's case is sound. However... I've got the feeling that this case is in dire need of more investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thus I will conclude today's proceedings at this point! It's an undisputed fact that the criminal left no footprints at the scene. Tomorrow, I want us to find out the reason behind this mystery of mysteries.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, uhh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe that's enough for today. Court is now in recess!</line>
<line speaker="Max">Hey! Sweeties! What in the world is going on!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They say the criminal flew off into the air and disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Max, I can't believe I'm asking this, but you didn't fly that night, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Max">I know you didn't mean to ask me such a fabulously stupid question! I can't fly whenever I please. It's not that easy!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But it looks so effortless for you on stage...</line>
<line speaker="Max">It's not that simple!! I'm not actually flying on stage! I use invisible wires and have them hoist me through the air!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... You just told me the secret to your magic!!</line>
<line speaker="Max">NO!! I broke the first rule... The cardinal rule... The ONLY RULE!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Max. I'm sorry you had to break a magician's creed to keep the magic tricks secret...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What do we do now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All we can do now is hope we find the flying criminal in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Great idea! Let's do our best and catch this sucker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't sound very sure, Mr. Wright. Objection denied.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection denied. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence clearly reveals the contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They aren't, are they...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Wright, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The witness's statement is clearly faulty, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I'm sorry, but I can see nothing faulty. Unfortunately, I will have to penalize you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh, I must be on the wrong track...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong this trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court find the defendant, Mr. Billy Bob Johns...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately, to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>