
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Memories</title>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Whew, it's finally time... I'm kind of nervous...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">*Ah-HHHHEM!*</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh! Mr. Grossberg! Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, Mia. Please calm yourself down! You're going to get yourself arrested for suspicious behavior, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What are you talking about!! I am relaxed, Mr. Grossberg!! Look at me, I'm relaxed!!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">*Grrrmmphh* L-Let go of my lapels! Hmph... You obviously haven't got the temperament to be a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I, err... I'm so sorry! It's just that I'm so nervous today...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh, that's right. This is your first time in the big leagues, isn't it? Well, never you fear my dear. I, Marvin Grossberg, am at your service!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, actually this is my second time in court...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Still, you surprised me... What, with your earnest request last night... "Let me handle this case!" you suddenly said. And quite forcefully, too!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I just found out yesterday. About the case, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What? And you've already learned all the relevant facts?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well about that... You see... I mean, of course I have! I think.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh dear... In any case, don't let our client see you're so nervous. You see the poor young man in the pink sweater over there? That's our client.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*cough* *sniffle* Good morning there everybody!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Good morning... <thought>Try to keep smiling, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, err, I just want to say... I'll give it all I've got! Yup, it'll be fine! No prob! *cough* *achoo* *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh, what's wrong? Do you have a cold or something... Mr. Wry?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, it's Wright... Like the flying brothers... People screw it up all the time. And yes I have a cold. That's what this mask is for. My doc says this way, I won't give it to anyone else... Be kind to others, he says...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Right, Mr. Wright! You have nothing to fear in court today! If you are truly innocent... I promise I will save you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnnnggghh... P-Please l-let go of my shirt... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That's right, he's the one on trial, not you! He's the one who should be nervous! You need to stay strong for your client, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">My name is Mia Fey. I'm still pretty new at this lawyer thing... The first time I appeared in court was a year ago. But that trial traumatized me so badly, I thought I'd never set foot in another courtroom. It's been one year since then, and well, here I am again. But this time... This time I'll win. For my client... And for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The defense is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense today is... Ms... Ms... Mia Fey, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor. Is there a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I was under the impression that Marvin Grossberg was to be leading the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! Well, you see... Mr. Grossberg had... A-A bit of an emergency...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Emergency? But isn't that him standing there right next to you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... You're just a rookie. Are you sure you can really handle this?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Don't let him scare you, Mia! Give him your toughest look!</thought> Of course, Your Honor! ... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Payne. Your opening statement, please.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, well, well... I can't believe a veteran like me has to spend his time baby-sitting a new defense lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Don't worry little girl. It will all be over soon.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What was that all about? Was he trying to trash-talk me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now then, I'd like to proceed with a summary of events on the day in question. The incident occurred on the campus of Ivy University. The murder victim was a student named Doug Swallow. He was a fourth year student studying Pharmacology.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It sounds like he was a very bright young man.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, well, next we have a photo taken at the scene of the crime. Students discovered the scene shortly after the murder. They found the victim's body... ...and the defendant, who had obviously bungled his getaway. They then called the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That certainly makes the defendant look very suspicious indeed. Very well. The court accepts this photo into the record as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way... I can't quite tell the cause of death from this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee... Your reputation for sagacity is well-earned, Your Honor. The truth is that this victim died a rather unusual death.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">An unusual death...!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean, Mr. Payne!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well... Perhaps the defense would like to take this question.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">A simple question. I thought I might loosen you up a bit. I am a genteel-man, if you will.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Um, a what? <thought>Stand up to him, Mia! Show him what you're made of!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, a perfect opportunity! Well, what was it? The cause! Go on! ... ...Please say you know at least this much.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'm so sorry... I-I didn't get a chance to read through the whole file.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">*groan* My hemorrhoids are beginning to act up... Now see here! The details of the case are filed under the Court Record. But you knew that already, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ah! The Court Record! I think I can see that by touching the Court Record Button...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">All of the weapons we need can be found in the Court Record. Take a good, hard look at the data there and think carefully before you answer, m'dear!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, sir! I'll do just that! <thought>I've got to stay calm! I can't let that prosecutor get the better of me! The Court Record... OK, let's take a look! I just touch the Court Record Button here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, would the attorney for the defense please answer the question? What was the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well... I think you'll find it was a case of asphyxiation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Asphyxiation, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">M-Mia! What are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well it's stuffy in here! I can hardly breathe.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">No one's asking how you feel! Please, make sure to properly read the Court Record!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'm so sorry! I'll take a better look! <thought>Hang in there, Mia! Open the Court Record with the Court Record Button...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'll ask you once again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Err... Hypothermia, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, Mr. Grossberg? Does it suddenly feel very cold in here to you?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That's because your absurd reply has brought a chill to the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'm so sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Look at the Court Record more carefully, would you! How can you expect to win a case this way!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hang in there, Mia! Open the Court Record with the Court Record Button...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'll ask you once again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">According to the Court Record, it was a fatal electric shock. In other words, electrocution.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Electrocution? Hmm... But how could such a thing happen? Did the murderer use some type of new, super-powerful stun-gun, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The answer to that will become crystal clear as this trial proceeds, Your Honor. But before that, there is one more vital issue.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Why, motive of course. Apparently there was some bad blood between the victim and the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bad blood...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oopsie! I'm terribly sorry. You're the defense attorney, so you must know all about it. I shouldn't be stealing your spotlight like this.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I really don't like this guy's smug attitude...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That's Winston Payne for you. He is one smooth operator, if you catch my drift. They don't call him the "Rookie Killer" for nothing, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's hear from the defense. What was the source of the bad blood between the victim and the defendant? And this time, I would like to see some supporting evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ev-Evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, no need to get all worked up over this. As I said, all our weapons can be found in the Court Record. Find the evidence you need and then shove it into Ol' Graybeard's face!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, sir! Into Ol' Graybeard's face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Err, Mr. Grossberg. Try to set a better example for the young lady!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia, evidence isn't the only thing in the Court Record. People's profiles are as well. You can toggle between Profiles and Evidence, so be sure to go over it all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, let's see what you've got. What was the cause of the bad blood between Phoenix Wright and the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Grossberg... I honestly think it would be best for the defense if you were in charge. I'm afraid Ms. Fey might stir up some bad blood with this court if she were to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Or simply put, you are quite mistaken, m'dear.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh no... I'm so sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even if you are new, your lack of preparation is inexcusable. Now take a moment and think it over again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor! <thought>It's OK! You've got another chance, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The reason for the bad blood between the two of them was... this woman here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dahlia Hawthorne, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Very good, Ms. Fey. You seem to have picked up on at least this much. This woman is the girlfriend of the defendant, Phoenix Wright. But up until about eight months ago, she was with the victim, Mr. Swallow. Clearly she has some part to play in this story.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, he's done it again. Before the cross-examination starts, he's already got the judge thinking like he wants.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Payne. Please call your first witness!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">If it pleases the court, the prosecution would like to call Mr. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What? The defendant himself? Well, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It's fine! After all, Mr. Wright is innocent, right?</thought> The defense has no objection.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court calls Mr. Phoenix Wright to the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, ah, yes... My name is Phoenix Wright. My job is, um... Well, right now, I guess I'm a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no. He means what did you do before you were arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... *achoo* *achoo* *achoo* I was a university student.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright. You understand that you are suspected in the death of your fellow student, Doug Swa--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But! But I didn't do it! I'm innocent I tell you! I'm telling you I was... *achoo* *achoo* *cough* *cough* *achoo* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defendant please refrain from passing on his cold to the rest of us!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">It seems the witness has something he wants to say.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well then, Mr. Wright. Please tell us about your relation to the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right away, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I... I admit I was there...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. So you hardly knew the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! Like I said, I'm not a killer!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Whew... It looks like the judge understands.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mmfph... You're being naïve, you know. Too naïve.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee. It seems that you've forgotten one small thing, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This witness still has to undergo something called cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Cross-examination...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He's right. And it's the defense's duty to carry out the cross-examination. The purpose is to determine if a witness's testimony contains any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Contradictions...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">If a witness is lying, their statements will conflict with the Court Record.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But... Mr. Wright is my client!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Even if he is your client, in court, all lies must be struck down. As a lawyer, that is your duty, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What does he mean by that? Is he saying that testimony just now... That there was a lie -- a contradiction?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, your cross-examination, if you please, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Please, Mr. Wright... Tell me you haven't been lying! You wouldn't do that to me... would you...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I... I admit I was there...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">When you say "there", you mean the place where the victim was murdered?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, sort of. The place where SOMETHING happened anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">"Something"? You can't hide what happened. We have photographic evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*achoo* *achoo* *achoo* *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A-Anyway, Mr. Wright... What were you doing at the scene of the crime? I thought you said you didn't know the victim, Mr. Swallow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was just a coincidence! We bumped into each other by accident.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A coincidence, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm not a killer! All I did was find his body!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You say you found the body? So who called the police?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Um... *achoo* *cough* *achoo* *cough* *achoo* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Unfortunately it was some other students that notified the police.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Other students"...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's correct. They were witnesses. Witnesses who saw the defendant standing there, next to the body, in shock!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-What! Is this true, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*achoo* *achoo* *achoo* *achoo* *achoo* *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Could you stop sneezing every time you're in a bind...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, it's true that I was pretty shocked when I found the body. But, but I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I hardly knew the guy to begin with...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, you didn't know his face, or even his name, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! Um, well, no... That is... I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So... Which is it? Did you know him or not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*achoo* *achoo* *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, see here! You can't avoid answering the question by sneezing all day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... Umm, well... I guess I did know his name.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>N-News to me! Why didn't he tell me that before...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... I heard he used to date Dollie.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this "Dollie" person?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah yes, that would be the defendant's lover, Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I see. Ah, young love... So bittersweet...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But that's all I knew about him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I never even talked to that stuck-up British wannabe!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright, you stated the following in your testimony: "I hardly knew the guy to begin with..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's right! I mean why would I even--</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But that doesn't sound right. If you hardly knew him... ...then why would you say that the victim was a "stuck-up British wannabe"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah! No! It wasn't me! I'm not a killer, I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. I will give you an opportunity to revise your testimony. How is it that you knew the victim was, as you put it, a "British wannabe"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright, you stated the following in your testimony: "I hardly knew the guy to begin with..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's right! I mean why would I even--</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But that doesn't sound right. If you hardly knew him... ...then why would you say that the victim was a "stuck-up British wannabe"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was always walking around with a huge Union Jack on the back of his shirt.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Did you see it at the crime scene? The Union Jack, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, that's right! I saw it at the crime scene! That's why... That's why I figured he must love British stuff, see? It's true! Cross my heart! I swear I didn't do it...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>He's acting fishier than the salmon I ate last night...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">May I ask you something, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>What is it now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who is this person anyway? This "Union Jack" fellow...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The Union Jack is the name of the flag of England.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I see... So you mean like the "Stars and Stripes", right?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">As usual, Your Honor, your insight astounds me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hey, something just occurred to me... Isn't there something strange about this bit just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia... There is a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Grossberg!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Quickly now! Show that boy you mean business! With evidence, I mean!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>OK, Mia, check the Court Record carefully!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well m'dear, do you think you can manage on your own from this point?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>One year ago... I was in a courtroom just like this. I can do it. I can handle this myself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mmrgh... You mustn't try to bite off more than you can chew, Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'll be fine! I know what I have to do!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Remember, you can always press him to get more information. Oh, and one more thing. When you're going to state a contradiction, make sure you present some definitive proof.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, Mr. Grossberg... I could use a little help...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, please don't look so sad. It brings a tear to my eye when you do. Alright, listen carefully. By comparing the testimony to the Court Record... ...you should be able to discover any contradictions, if there are any. And when you've found one...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I present the piece of evidence that contradicts the witness's testimony...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes. That's the ticket!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But still... I don't see any contradictions in Mr. Wright's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... Maybe you don't have enough information yet.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Information...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You can press for more information by leaning on a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Even if they're my own client?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It doesn't matter who it is, if you think they're lying, press them like a cheap suit! That is the obligation of an attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>OK, Mia. One more time, from the very beginning of his testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Are you certain you saw the "Union Jack"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I'm sure. It was right there on his back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, is there some point to this line of questioning?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor, please take another look at the crime scene photo. As you can see, there's absolutely nothing written on the victim's back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Wait a minute! He's wearing a leather jacket! The Union Jack was on the back of the t-shirt he was wearing...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I was under the impression that you accidentally came across the body. But, if that was really the case, then you wouldn't know that, would you? You'd have no idea at all what he was wearing underneath that jacket! Mr. Wright... You've been lying to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... P-P-P-Please forgive me! Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia! You've made our client cry!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Let him! That "P" on his chest doesn't stand for Phoenix anyways! I can't believe I trusted him! Mr. Wright was all wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee. That was an impressive bit of cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Thank you for uncovering the defendant's lies for me. It's quite clear that this man did not simply "stumble upon" the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uggghhh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Uh oh... Did I go too far?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">By the way, Mr. Wright. You seem to have a rather bad cold. Have you taken any medicine for it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, err, umm... Yeah, I took some but...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Was the medicine that you took an over-the-counter brand called "Coldkiller X"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's right! It kills colds good! Hey, wait a second... How did you know I'm a big fan of Coldkiller X...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... Would you happen to have that medicine with you right now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... Actually, I seem to have lost it somewhere...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>He lost it? Does this even have anything to do with the case...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Wright... Shall I tell you where your cold medicine is right now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor! I'd like you to take a look at another photo from the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this! In the victim's hand, it's... It's Coldkiller X...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, but even I've got a bottle of Coldkiller X in my apartment!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sorry, but I'm afraid that argument won't work. There's no doubt as to who this bottle of Coldkiller X belonged to. Especially since Mr. Wright's fingerprints were all over it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Sensing his murderous intent, Mr. Swallow must have picked up the bottle of medicine... ...dropped by Mr. Wright and hid it in his hand. His purpose in doing so can only have been to identify his killer as Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Your Honor! I'd like to present this photo and bottle as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will accept them into the record.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Also, the victim's wristwatch was broken.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Broken...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, it ceased functioning when a large wave of electricity passed through it. Well, Mr. Wright! Do you have some kind of explanation for all of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uggghhh...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is really bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oh, my buttocks... My poor, poor hemorrhoids...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth is... I went because he called me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! That's completely different than the testimony you gave previously!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*achoo* *achoo* *achoo* I-I'm sorry, Your Honor! I was afraid you wouldn't believe the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You'll forgive me if I say I hardly find your current testimony any more credible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ms. Fey, please begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh please, Mr. Wright... Don't tell any more lies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The truth is... I went because he called me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Had you ever met the victim before then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No! Never! ... But... That day, he called me up and told me he wanted to talk about Dollie.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And this "Dollie" person is...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My um... It's kind of embarrassing. She's my, umm, sweetheart...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oomph...! Wh-What... What was that for, Mia!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh! I'm so sorry! I just felt like slapping something all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Dahlia Hawthorne was also the lover of the murder victim, Doug Swallow. ...Before she met Mr. Wright, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So it was one of those nasty love triangles, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was in the Pharmacology Dept., so we agreed to meet at 2:45 behind that building...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Was it Mr. Swallow who indicated you should meet at 2:45?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. And we were both there right on time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... You said the victim was in the Pharmacology Dept., correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, he was studying how to manufacture and improve pharmaceuticals. Everyone called him the "Alchemist of Ivy U".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An "alchemist"... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I gotta admit it was a little suspicious. He had a whole laboratory and everything! It was filled with chemicals and strange machines that run on high-voltage electricity.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho. How fascinating. He sounds like he was quite an ambitious young man.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What do I do!? Maybe I should ask him for some more details?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So you are absolutely certain that you met at 2:45?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, pretty sure. That's the time class ends. But they're always doing experiments, so it doesn't matter much.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Experiments...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. Those pharmacology guys are always in the lab whipping up something.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, it looks like he's right about the time anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, let's go on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I was wondering if you could tell us a bit more about the Pharmacology Department.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well OK, sure. I don't know all that much though.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A little bit earlier in your testimony, you said something interesting. You said the department uses strange machines that run on high-voltage electricity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. And they sure look dangerous. They use non-standard voltages, so there are high-voltage cables everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"High-voltage cables"...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, there were electrical poles set up all around the building. The high-voltage cables run overhead around the roof.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Finally I think we're getting somewhere...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've gotten everything I need from this statement. It's time to move on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">In any case, let's continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We talked for a bit, and then at around 3:00, we split up.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So what was it you were talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know... *achoo* *cough* That maybe we should hang out again sometime.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>"Hang out again sometime"? I wish that were true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then later when I went back, I found him lying there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So you say you went back...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, yeah. That's when I found the body.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, but why did you go back in the first place? Weren't you angry with him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, th-that's right, I was. ...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Then why, Mr. Wright? Why did you go back there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Umm... I thought maybe we could make up.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *achoo* *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Judging by the atmosphere... I'm pretty sure no one is buying this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd been taking Coldkiller X for the last 2 or 3 days...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's rather unusual to catch a cold this time of the year, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I always get a little careless when the weather starts to warm up. I guess I shouldn't sleep with the window open this early in spring, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I suppose common sense is not always common...</thought> So... Did anyone else know that you were taking cold medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I always took one after meals... So I'm pretty sure all my friends knew about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I lost my bottle of it around lunchtime on the day of the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">On the day of the incident, what did you do for lunch...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? What does that have to do with anything?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You can never be too sure...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I always eat with Dollie... Just the two of us. Dollie's homemade lunches are just the greatest! Mmm! Her mini-omelettes are magically delicious! Eheh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yeowch!! Wh-Why did you punch me in the jaw!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh! I-I'm so sorry...! I just felt like hurting someone all of a sudden!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, Mia?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I don't know... I can't seem to find any contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">The boy isn't exactly what I'd call a natural-born liar, you know. But still, we can't have him continue to spout nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I know... But what can I do!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well, I'm certain he must still be hiding something. Information! Right now it's information we need more than anything else!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm not entirely convinced by his explanation about the medicine bottle either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let me be frank here, Mr. Wright. Your testimony cannot be trusted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... I knew it was too much work for a little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmph...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, there is one mystery that still remains.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There is, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How the murder was carried out, of course. Just how was the victim electrocuted? I don't believe the murder weapon has been produced yet, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, that is... I... You are correct, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So how exactly was Mr. Swallow killed...? If I could somehow establish how it was done... Maybe I could still come out of this mess smelling like a rose!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hmm, I do have one idea, but it would be impossible to prove it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia, m'dear. If you have any ideas, now is the time to present them.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Grossberg!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Remember, silence is NOT golden. ...In court, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Silence is not golden, huh? Well in that case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I believe that if we were to piece together everything we've heard up until now... ...we should be able to solve the mystery of how Mr. Swallow died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That would be most impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... Quite the brash statement coming from a rookie! But even a beginner like you must understand the basic rules of the court, yes? An attorney must be able to substantiate their arguments with evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmph! Of course I know that! <thought>Actually, I had totally forgotten about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Ms. Fey. Let me see what you've got. Show me how you believe the victim was electrocuted!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, I'm deeply disappointed in you.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm disappointed as well, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">To be honest, I'm a bit disappointed too, Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Argh! I need to use my brain on this! Come on, Mia! You can't strike out here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">As for the cause of death... ...I'd say this picture captures it quite well!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!? But there is nothing that even remotely resembles a murder weapon here... Hmm, I'm afraid the defense is going to have to explain this in a bit more detail. Ms. Fey, where exactly in this photo is the murder weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well naturally... it's right around here! ...I think.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, I'm deeply disappointed in you.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm disappointed as well, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">To be honest, I'm a bit disappointed too, Mia.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Argh! I need to use my brain on this! Come on, Mia! You can't strike out here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, naturally... it's right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's... That's... What is that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">A severed electrical cable, I believe... Your Honor. Remember the testimony we've heard. The machines the pharmacology students use in their experiments require high voltage... ...and because of that, there are special high-voltage cables strung up everywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So then, the high-voltage cable...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, the high-voltage cable is the cause of death. That is the most likely explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That certainly sounds plausible. Well, Mr. Payne? What do you have to say about this?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well... I believe some praise is in order.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Don't toy with me, old man!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now, now. The victim's cause of death may indeed have been a high-voltage cable. However! I want you to think about what that really implies! The only one who had the opportunity to use the cable as a murder weapon was... The defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That much is certainly true.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, and that's not all. We have proof. Irrefutable proof that will establish that Mr. Wright was the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You do!? Well, what is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">His fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fingerprints...? You mean that the defendant's fingerprints were on something besides the medicine bottle?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Let's take another look at the crime scene photo. As you can see, the victim is wearing a leather jacket. And as you may know, leather holds fingerprints quite well.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ah! Y-You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes. It was quite clearly imprinted on the chest area of the victim's jacket. The palm print of the defendant's very own hand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I can only think of one way Mr. Wright could have left a print like that. Intent on murder, he squarely pushed the victim towards the severed electrical cable!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! That's enough! I think we can conclude that there is no reason to continue with this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Stick a fork in us, we're done.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">M-Mr. Grossberg!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">My hemorrhoids never lie. The show is over, Mia. I knew that boy was guilty the first time I saw him.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">N-No! You're wrong! Mr. Wright is innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No further evidence is required to convince me of this man's guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Your Honor...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At this time, I am prepared to render a verdict in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have something further to add, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Is this what you want, Mr. Wright!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You still haven't told us the truth... the whole truth. If you don't say something now, the judge is going to hand down his verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But I... I can't! I-I just can't say it! If I told you what really happened, then I'd b-be...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's OK, Mr. Wright. I'm your attorney. You can trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Miss Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No matter what it is you have to say... I believe in you and I'll represent you to the very end.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">We've already established the defendant's guilt. There's no further need for him to say anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*cough* *cough* W-Wait a minute!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I'll tell you what really happened!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">But I've already told you, Mr. Wright. There's no need for further...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*cough* I-I-I... I did it... I admit it! I pushed him! It's my fault... My f-fault that D-Doug Swallow is dead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... What you just said... Was that the truth!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I... I was afraid... Afraid that if I told the truth... ...everyone would think I was the murderer for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, as things currently stand, we're all absolutely convinced you are!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please...! Please give me one more chance to explain! This time I swear... I swear I'll tell the whole truth! It'll be OK, won't it, Miss Fey? I... I believe in you!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh! Um, th-thank you. <thought>I still can't believe it... He really did push the victim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Unnngh... It feels like my hemorrhoids are doing the Harlem Shake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That guy... He was talking bad about Dollie...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, the explanation is really quite simple. When you pushed him, Mr. Swallow flew back and touched the electrical cable. He died from the shock. And that, as they say, is that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A simple explanation indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">At the time of the incident, a light rain had been falling. Wet from the rain, the victim was more easily electrocuted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But! When I pushed him, there weren't any electrical cables nearby! If there had been something like that, even I would've noticed it!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That's true... Even a dufus like him couldn't miss that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ms. Fey. Let me warn you right now that if your cross-examination doesn't yield any new facts... ...I intend to deliver my verdict without further delay. Are we clear on that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Don't give up, Mia! If he is innocent, there must be some kind of evidence somewhere that will prove it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That guy... He was talking bad about Dollie...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So what kinds of things did Mr. Swallow say to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He said all sorts of terrible things about Dollie! He said that she was a bad girl!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Umm... Is that all?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yup!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Fey, you heard him yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh boy! You're not doing yourself any favors here, Mr. Wright! Please don't make this harder for me than it already is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway... After he said that, I just, I just...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I lost my temper and gave him a shove!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Can you tell me about what happened in a little more detail?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That guy... He just said what he wanted to say to me... And then he put on the jacket he was holding and started to leave. That's when... That's when I lost my temper and flew into a furious frenzy! I just gave him a... light, gentle shove to the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And when you did that, there was no severed cable anywhere to be seen?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right! There was nothing like that at all!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But is it possible that you merely overlooked it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Well, I guess it's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What are you doing!? Don't let that guy steamroll over you like cheap asphalt!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe what's important here is the moment the push occurred. Let's continue on with the testimony, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At that moment, I heard some kind of loud noise...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">A "loud noise"? And what would you say that loud noise was, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure... But it was really loud! It was like, "SNAP!"... You know, come to think of it, I wonder what that was...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... Clearly, Your Honor, it was the sound of the victim being electrocuted.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-You're not qualified to decide that! <thought>What should I do? I'm treading on some dangerous ground here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright, that "loud noise" you heard may be extremely important. So try to remember what it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, how do I put it... It was like a sharp crack. Aha! Could it... Could it have been...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes? Could it have been? Hurry up and tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When I pushed him, he dropped the umbrella he was holding. He fell right on top of it, and it broke. That was probably the noise I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An umbrella, huh? And did that umbrella belong to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, it was a plastic umbrella. Cheap and frail, kind of like the owner! Then again, I wish I had any kind of umbrella. I was totally soaked to the bone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Ms. Fey. What do you think? Is there something important in that testimony just now?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, well...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is it, Mia! The new information you've been waiting for!</thought> Of course it's important! No! This cheap umbrella is more than important; it's vital! I want to officially have it entered into the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ha! How perfectly fitting. Flimsy information for a flimsy lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court agrees to the defense's request. Witness, please add the bit about the cheap umbrella to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course it's not important!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Fey! How can you state that so proudly!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, it just isn't! It's not important one bit! Not even one iota. OK?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia! That's enough! You're making a fool of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Is it OK if I go on?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I've got other, more pressing things to ask about.</thought> Very well, Mr. Wright, let's move on, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After I shoved him, he... He fell down on top of his cheap umbrella.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So Mr. Swallow fell on top of his umbrella? And you are certain of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It was right there under him. Actually, if it hadn't been under him, I was planning on borrowing it for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The umbrella, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well yeah, you see I was wearing this sweater here... Dollie stayed up late for nights at a time knitting it for me... I didn't want the rain to dampen the handmade symbol of her love...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Oomph! My stomach is not to be used as your personal soccer ball, Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ah! I-I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Continue on with your testimony, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little while after I left, I started to get worried.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">After you shoved the victim, did you leave the scene right away?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I did! I admit it! I-I was furious!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You left without even checking Mr. Swallow's condition?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, um, yeah... But like I said, I got worried about him later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So I went back. But h-he was just laying there, d-dead!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">At that time, did you see anyone else at the scene of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*cough* *cough*... *cough* *cough* *cough* Um, nope. Nobody...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Geez. Could that stupid cough possibly sound any phonier?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... In that case, it's very hard to believe someone else could have been the murderer...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Unless we can find something that shows his innocence from that testimony, m'dear... I'm afraid the judge will make his final decision with no remorse whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, sir! <thought>Right now I need more info; info that will help me turn up some contradictions!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why didn't you testify about the umbrella from the very beginning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on... If I had mentioned that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I would've been able to counter the prosecution's arguments earlier!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Take another look at the crime scene photo! According to Mr. Wright, the victim fell on top of his umbrella. However, if you look closely... ...the umbrella is nowhere near the victim. Actually, it's by the electrical pole!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You're absolutely right!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The conclusion here is obvious. After the defendant left, the victim moved from where he fell. In other words... After he was pushed by the defendant, Mr. Swallow was still alive!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nnnnooooo!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! The victim... He moved...!? Mr. Payne! The umbrella in this photo... Where is it now?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well, it was collected by the police at the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I want it presented as evidence immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">B-But the umbrella could have simply been blown there by the wind!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">According to the testimony, the victim fell on top of the umbrella. There's simply no way it could have been blown there by the wind!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Nnn... Gggg... Hrrmph! B-B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know this matter of the umbrella seems relatively trivial... But as long as the smallest doubt remains, I cannot render final judgment!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">N-N-N... Noooooooooooooooooooooo!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, I still find it hard to believe that a huge hole has been blown in the... ...prosecution's case by the defendant's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well done, Mia!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">......Hee hee. Hee hee hee hee hee...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Payne! What are you chuckling about?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Pardon me, Your Honor. It seems I was expecting too much of a free ride. It was foolish to think I could establish guilt through cross-examination alone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't follow what you're saying!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Let me guess. You have another witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly! And this witness's testimony will be incontrovertible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well!? Who is this witness!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dahlia Hawthorne? You don't mean... "Dollie"?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I do, Your Honor. The defendant's very own lover is a witness to the whole thing! That's right. She was at the scene of the crime when the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm sorry to break the bad news to you, my dear.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... "Bad news"? You couldn't be more wrong. Actually... I've been waiting for this.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You can't be serious...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia! What do you mean by that...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I think this is a good point for us to stop at. Court will now enter a 20 minute recess. Afterwards, we will listen to the testimony of Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miss Fey... I-I'm sorry about what happened back there... I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's alright. At least you told us the truth in the end, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... So I guess I can start to relax then, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Relax, my boy? You can't be serious! After hiding such important facts...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But...! But the next witness is my Dollie, right? She'll save me! I just know she will!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why do you think that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? What do you mean!? She... She's the love of my life, that's why!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The love of your life, huh... Would you mind telling me more about you and... Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure! No problem! Dollie and I... We first met about eight months ago right here in this very courthouse. Actually, I'm studying to be a lawyer, on the side... Anyway! One day, she and I just bumped into each other in the reading room downstairs. That's why I really think it was fate that brought us together. As soon as I first set eyes on her, I knew she was the one for me. Oh, here! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She gave this to me the day we met as a symbol of our love! She had been wearing it around her neck that day, but then... ...she took it off, but before she gave it to me she said, "I want you to carry this."</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So she gave it to you as a present, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This darling little bottle is filled with memories of my darling little Dollie!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It certainly is a little bottle alright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It makes me so happy, I show it to everyone I meet! I want to share my happiness with the whole world!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Um, anyway... So after that, you and Ms. Hawthorne started dating?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but she's so shy. Every time I see her, she always says the same thing to me. "Please give it back now."</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What a strange girl, asking for a present back like that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">By the way, Mr. Wright. The day you first met Dahlia Hawthorne, eight months ago... It wouldn't happen to have been on August 27th, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Y-Yeah, it was... But how did you...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">This happened on August 27th, right here in this courthouse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? A newspaper clipping? Let's see... "Murder in the Courthouse?" M-Murder?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What are you reading there!? Let me see that! .........! Oh, I see. Mia... I think I understand what you're trying to say. And I think I understand why you suddenly took such a keen interest in this case. You believe there is some relationship between these two cases. Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I hope you don't mind, Mr. Grossberg... I... I need to finish this myself.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, yes, but... I'm afraid what you have will not be enough, m'dear. I'll go and have a look at the downstairs reading room and see what else I can find.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Th-Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I want to do whatever I can to be of help to you, Mia! Well, it looks like recess is about over. We'd better all get moving!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I guess so... That recess sure seemed longer than 20 minutes though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court will now reconvene. Mr. Payne, please call your witness.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This next person is someone who witnessed the crime as it happened. The prosecution calls Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Wh-What's with this stiff silence...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">In my long career as a judge, I have been deceived by many witnesses. It's my job to doubt; to take no one at their word... But in your case, I must admit that you radiate a glow of complete sincerity.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I can't believe he actually said that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Oh! Um, now then, witness. Could you please state your full name?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... I, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't worry, sweetie. There's no need to be nervous!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">If anyone says anything rude, you can be sure, I'll cut them right down to size!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I will bash them with my gavel!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I love how they look straight at me when they say that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Um, thank you... for calming my nerves. You are all so nice... I almost feel right at home.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Not at all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If we may move on now... What is your full name and occupation?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">My name is Dahlia Hawthorne. I'm a junior in Literature at Ivy University. I just want to say... It's an honor for me to be here in your noble presence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The honor is all mine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No... The honor is all mine.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, we know whose milkshake brings all the boys to the yard...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...Umm. Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Is there something I can help you with?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just go on and say whatever is on your mind!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I'm sure that there must be some kind of mistake. Feenie wouldn't kill anyone. I just know it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, yes... I can see why you'd say that.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>She's going to be a tough witness, alright... It only took her 12 seconds to wrap them all around her little finger.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, please proceed with your testimony. Let's hear about what you witnessed on the day of the incident, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I had been planning to go back to Feenie's place after class was over.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I don't know what to say! According to you, Ms. Hawthorne... ...the defendant didn't do anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Young lady. As old as I am, even I recall how hot the flames of young passion can burn. Nevertheless... It is my job to discover the truth. Please, tell us the truth...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">But... But, I... I would never...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's more than enough, witness. I won't allow this to continue.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please, just let me proceed with my cross-examination, Your Honor. I, for one, don't plan to win my case on a bunch of paper-thin lies!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...Tee hee. You haven't changed a bit... Mia Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What's this? So, you two are... acquainted?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes. We've met before... Once.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case, Ms. Fey, the floor is all yours.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">It's good to see you again, Madame Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"Madame"!? <thought>I'm no one's grandma yet, girlie!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I had been planning to go back to Feenie's place after class was over.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now, unless I'm mistaken, Feenie -- I mean, Mr. Wright is in the Art Department. If that's the case, then what were you doing by the Pharmacology building?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well... I'm in the Literature Department. I'm studying Japanese Senryu poetry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oho hoh! How wonderful! It's that humorous, yet satirical style of haiku, yes?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">"Nothing left to do... When a man reaches this age, sleep is his best friend."</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That's supposed to be poetry? Sounds more like a mid-life crisis!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">For me to get to the Art Department, I have to walk through that back area.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes I see. That makes sense. When I want to enter the courthouse, I always walk through the front doors.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>How else would you enter? Teleportation!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Feenie and Dougie...They were talking behind the building.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So who is this "Dougie" person?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh, I'm sorry. Doug Swallow. We were dating until about eight months ago...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So what were Dougie-- *ahem* Mr. Swallow and Mr. Wright talking about anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... H-How can you be so mean? I would never... I would never eavesdrop... I wasn't raised to be so rude and unrefined!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's right, Ms. Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't drag the witness down to your level!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Why am I being demonized here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please, go on. What did you see next?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Then suddenly... Dougie got all wobbly and just collapsed.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Are you saying that the victim just collapsed on his own?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In other words, the defendant never touched the victim. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I was watching the whole time. Feenie never did a thing to Dougie!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>If I press her for no good reason, I just know the judge will get angry with me... Hmm, so what should I do about her testimony just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hmm... I suppose her statement works in our favor, for now. I'll hold off on looking into it any deeper until it's necessary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, young lady, please go on with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Feeble lies are not very becoming, Ms. Hawthorne, so let's drop them, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Wh-What...! I...! I would never...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Fey! I will not allow you to badger this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I-I believe the defense is engaged in a-a... fishing expedition.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That is... Err... She has no supporting...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">P-Please don't glare at me like that...! I-I'm just doing my job!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Now then, Ms. Hawthorne. The defendant's palmprint was found on Mr. Swallow's leather jacket. It has already been shown that Mr. Wright did, in fact, push the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's no need to try to cover for the defendant. It would be much better if you came out and told us the whole truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There's nothing to worry about, young lady. Just tell us everything that you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes, Your Honor... I-I will. If you don't mind, I-I'd like to revise my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Looks like we're finally getting somewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's when Feenie noticed that I was there.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">And what did Mr. Wright say when he saw you?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I-I'm sorry. I-I was so flustered that I... I really don't remember. P-Please forgive me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You don't remember...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that's common enough. Sometimes I can't recall a sentence I passed only minutes prior!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Please... Someone, anyone... Stop him before he gets hurt... by me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Um, actually, I didn't see the moment he pushed Dougie.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You didn't see it!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well, I saw the moment when Dougie fell to the ground...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And at that time, there was only the two of them at the scene? The defendant, Phoenix Wright, and the victim, Doug Swallow?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes... that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">It didn't look like they were fighting, and I didn't hear any noise either.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So then, what did it look like they were doing to you?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I thought they were having a nice, friendly afternoon conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh, give me a break!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's why I really wasn't watching them all that closely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you notice anything out of the ordinary at all?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">No, nothing at all... Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I like the sound of that! "Mr. Judge"... Now then, please proceed with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I went to go and find some other students and they called the authorities.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">When you say "students" do you mean students from the Pharmacology Department?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes. They're all very fond of their drugs...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please try to stay on topic! So to find some Pharmacology students, you went to the labs, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's what I was planning to do... But in the end, I wound up not going. A group of about 10 research students came running out of the building entrance. Somehow they all seemed to know what was going on...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The students knew what was going on...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The Pharmacology students... They have nothing to do with the incident. I think what I need is more information about Dahlia herself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But how could the students have known what was going on?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well... I don't know for sure that they knew what had happened. It's just, they all seemed kind of excited about something.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Hmm... It doesn't look like I'm going to get any more info about the students.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">So did the students call the police?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes. I-I was just so... I was so panicked...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. Yes, well anyone would have been, my dear.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>That girl... She's telling a super obvious lie, and she knows it. She's just pretending to protect Mr. Wright... Yes, that's got to be it! Way to go, Mia! OK, that means I'm going to have to dig deep to find the contradiction on this one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You say you didn't hear any noise. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes. That's why I was very relaxed, looking at the scenery around me.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's nice, but I find that just a little odd. I have here, the testimony of your boyfriend, Mr. Phoenix Wright. And he clearly testified to the effect... ...that when he pushed the victim, he heard a sharp, loud noise.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">H-He said that?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If you were really that close to the two of them, why didn't you hear this noise as well?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well, maybe the noise just wasn't all that memorable.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">But according to Mr. Wright's testimony, it was a sharp noise like a "SNAP"! There's no way a noise like that could fail to make an impression!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ack!!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Umm... May I have a moment to answer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-By all means!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I know the reason why I didn't hear the noise. You see, the truth is... I had my headphones on, and I was listening to music at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">H-H-Headphones...? You mean that both of your ears were covered?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The rain was just beginning to let up... But it seemed as though Thor wasn't ready for his fun to come to an end yet. So the sky continued to flash and rumble.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thunder and lightning, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Yes, I'm afraid of the sound of thunder. So I put my headphones on to block it out...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... Well, Your Honor? As you can see, there weren't any contradictions in her testimony after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Wait a sec, Mia! That testimony just now... She said something that could totally change this whole case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! There is a problem with the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What is this "problem"!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's obvious. The problem is that the witness claims to have not heard the "SNAP!"</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">A-Are you deaf!? Did you pay attention to the testimony!? She said she didn't hear it because she was listening to music with her headphones!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! I'm surprised you're going senile before me!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I'm not THAT bad! ...I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, the testimony we've just heard seems to be very decisive. The only one that could have killed the victim was the defendant, Mr. Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">N-No! Please...! I-I never meant to incriminate him!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is bad, Mia! If you don't do something, we're going to lose this!! Think again! What is it about this testimony that doesn't make sense...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! There is a problem with the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What is this "problem"!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's obvious. The problem is that she claims to have been listening to music!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">A-Are you deaf!? Did you pay attention to the testimony!? She explained she was listening to music to cover up the sound of thunder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! I must warn you that I can be even more frightening than Zeus when I'm angry!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Yikes! I'm in trouble now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, the testimony we've just heard seems to be very decisive. The only one that could have killed the victim was the defendant, Mr. Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">N-No! Please...! I-I never meant to incriminate him!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is bad, Mia! If you don't do something, we're going to lose this!! Think again! What is it about this testimony that doesn't make sense...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! There is a problem with the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Didn't you notice? She said there was lightning, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, lightning is actually a large discharge of electricity in the atmosphere, am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now's not the time for a science lesson, Ms. Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, Your Honor. Anyway, since the cause of death was electrocution... ...isn't it possible that the victim died from being hit by a bolt of lightning!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I must admit that the thought had not occurred to me!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Just what kind of thoughts DO occur to this guy anyway?</thought> This entire case is built on the premise that Mr. Doug Swallow was "murdered"... ...but that very premise itself is mistaken! The defense believes that Mr. Swallow was, in fact, the victim of a stray bolt!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It appears the defense may be on to something! Could it be that the death was actually accidental?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Alright, you did it, Mia! I'll be taking that "Not Guilty" now if you don't--</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee... I'm hurt that you have such a low opinion of me, Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm not a fool, you know. The prosecution has done its research, Your Honor. We found that there were no lightning strikes on that day at that location!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Whaaa!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What's more... We have evidence that the electrical cable is definitely linked to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">E-Evidence, Mr. Payne!? Well, what is this evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This affidavit.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who is this affidavit from?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The Pharmacology students who were conducting experiments in their labs that day. Allow me to read out to the court the testimony of the Pharmacology students. "All equipment in the labs lost power all of a sudden at around 3:00 PM that day."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was it a blackout?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">All of the labs' equipment runs of high-voltage, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So you're saying the equipment lost power because...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Precisely. They lost power because of the severed electrical cable. The power outage occurred at approximately 3:00 PM...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Which fits with the time of death listed in the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly! In other words... The victim died as a result of touching the severed electrical cable. According to the students, the cables were very old. They were planning on having them replaced in the near future.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Apparently the cables had become so brittle... ...that even the smallest bump would've caused them to break.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However... There is one thing that troubles me. If the cable could have been broken by any small bump... ...then it wouldn't have snapped if it hadn't been bumped into, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well... I suppose you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, Ms. Fey. Do you have any thoughts regarding the cause of the severed cable?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Your Honor... <thought>I don't like how this is looking one bit! I have to come up with something to try to regain some momentum!</thought> If it pleases the court, the defense would like to state its opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, let's hear it. Who or what was it that caused the cable to break?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia">This is it! This is why the cable snapped.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe that the only thing that has snapped is the mind of the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, that was one of your best lines yet, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Nnnfff...! <thought>Ouch, that was harsh...</thought> Please, Your Honor! Give me one more chance!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor. Please think back to Mr. Wright's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">He said that after he pushed the victim, he heard a loud, sharp noise. Now, this happened at around 3:00 PM, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that sounds right. Wait! Are you saying that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The lab equipment lost power at 2:55 PM... which fits right in Mr. Wright's timeline. In other words, it was Mr. Wright's shove that caused the power outage.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes! The prosecution also came to that same conclusion. And it was that very shove that caused Mr. Swallow to be electrocuted!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm afraid I can't agree with you there, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Take a good look at where the victim landed after being shoved. See the umbrella? It's by the electrical pole. That's right. The victim banged into that pole as a result of being pushed. It was that impact that caused the cable to break.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, that makes sense. And then the victim was electrocuted.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm sorry Your Honor, but no. It doesn't make sense at all. If the victim was shoved into the far pole... ...then he couldn't have been electrocuted by this severed cable in the foreground here!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">AAAAAAAAAAHH!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In other words... Someone other than my client must have electrocuted the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ah, the lamentations of my enemy. How I've longed to hear them!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It-It's true... The defense is absolutely correct! There doesn't seem to be any way the defendant could have done it--</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Umm... Mr. Judge, sir? May I say something? The madame attorney's explanation... She said some things that are a little different than I remember them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-Wh-</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What the...!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Please, just once more. May I please testify one last time? Please... Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Of course it's alright! Just go right ahead and give your new testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This is it... She's finally starting to show her true colors!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The truth is... Feenie pushed him twice.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So after being shoved... ...the victim got up and tried to run away.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And that is when the defendant pushed him for the second time.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I'm so sorry, Feenie... But I... I just have to tell the truth. Am I doing the right thing? Am I, Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Of course you are, my dear! As painful as it may seem, you are.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Ms. Fey. You may proceed with your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The truth is... Feenie pushed him twice.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ms. Hawthorne... Previously in your testimony you said the following... "Actually, I didn't see the moment he pushed Dougie."</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I know... I-I'm sorry. I wanted to protect Feenie.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So that's why you basically lied to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I was a bad girl... I know... Um, Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Would you please, please forgive little old me?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course he won't! What you did is called "perjury"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, come now! It was just a little old white lie! We'll forget it this time! But please be more careful from now on, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh, thank you so much, Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all! Ho ho ho...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The judge had better be more careful himself! A dark alley is friendlier than that girl!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The first time was into the electrical pole. That's when the cable broke.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You're saying you actually saw the victim get pushed into the electrical pole?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I know he doesn't look it, but Feenie can be a bit of an imp when he wants to be.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Oh, really...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">But I never imagined that he would cause an electrical cable to break... Feenie really is scary when he gets mad...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, he sounds like a very dangerous individual indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">then Dougie tried his best to run away from him...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So let me get this straight. You were happily listening to music on your headphones while you watched this scene unfold?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Waaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Fey! I'll have to ask you to stop badgering the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Umm... I wasn't happy... I was so scared that I couldn't even move. All I could do was stand there and cheer them on...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ch-Cheer them on? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well, I wished the best for them both, and that they would each give the fight their all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's very sweet of you to be so supportive.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">And what happened after that?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">But Feenie caught up and crashed into him from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That doesn't sound quite right... There were handprints found on the chest of the victim's leather jacket. Mr. Payne, were there also prints found on the back of his leather jacket?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well, um... N-No, there weren't...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Madame Fey, may I suggest that you listen a little more carefully?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I said that he "crashed" into him from behind, right? My Feenie wouldn't leave any prints behind in that case, would he?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Unngghh...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The cable snapping, and Dougie being electrocuted -- it all occured [sic] in less than a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Did you actually witness the moment the victim was electrocuted?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I-I'm sorry. I didn't actually see it. I... I turned my eyes away...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">That's understandable.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes indeed. It would have been a horrific sight for anyone to behold.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>If I don't figure out the contradiction here... ...it's all over! She didn't have much time to come up with her lie, so this is my best chance. There must be a hole in her testimony somewhere! Think, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's enough, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I'm afraid I don't understand...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You will in a minute. Could you please take a look at this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh. That medicine... That's the one Feenie likes to take for his cold.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's not the medicine I want you to look at... It's the wristwatch. It stopped at the precise time the victim was electrocuted. In other words... 3:05 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, and your point is, Ms. Fey...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">My point is this! What time was it when the lab suffered that power outage due to the cable snapping?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, according to the students' testimony, the answer is clear. It was 2:55 PM... Yeeaaaaaaarrrgghhh!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Would you care to explain to the court, Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne... ...what exactly happened during this 10 minute interval!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The defense proposes that... ...it was during this interval that the real murderer killed Mr. Doug Swallow!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or-Order! Order in the court! What is this all ab--</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-This is nonsense! The "real murderer"...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Even you can't deny that the time between the cable breaking and the electrocution... ...are completely unaccounted for!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-Then who was it!? Who else are you saying could've done it!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">There's only one person who could have murdered Mr. Swallow. Only after my client had left the scene... ...was there a window of opportunity for the real killer!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey. Is the defense ready to indict someone as this "real killer"?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>It's finally time. This is the moment I've been waiting for.</thought> Yes, Your Honor. We are ready.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But remember! If you accuse the wrong person, you will be penalized. Think very carefully before you speak, Ms. Fey. Now then, Ms. Fey. Let's have it. Who is the "real killer"!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">......</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that supposed to be!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Err... Umm... A bout of youthful indiscretion! ...Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe so, but I still have to penalize you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Unngggh... No way! I won't let it end like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now this time, I expect you to think a bit more carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It could only have been you, Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Waaaaah! H-How... H-How can you...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-The defense is grasping at straws!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ten minutes passed between the time the cable broke and the time of the electrocution! What exactly were you doing that whole time, Ms. Hawthorne? Were you really listening to some music while "cheering them both on" as they fought? I find it hard to believe that you didn't lift a finger to stop the men "dearest" to you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Ms. Fey! Wh-What... I mean, why... That is to say...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ms. Hawthorne! I believe you did witness the two men fighting on that day. However! After Mr. Wright pushed the victim, and subsequently left the scene... ...it was YOU who pushed Mr. Swallow to his death by your very own hands!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">AAAAAAAAHHH!!! H-How can you say something so mean, Madame Fey...! I... I didn't do anything...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey! This is a very serious charge you are--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! P-Please, I have something I want to say! *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Y-You! Wh-What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please... Please strike everything the defense said just now from the record!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What the...!? Are you daft!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're totally wrong, Miss Fey! Dollie... She... She couldn't do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!! Get back in your seat! Bailiff! Grab that man!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaarrgghh... *achoo* *achoo* Leave my Dollie alone! *achoo* *cough*</line>
<line speaker="???">... *sigh* That boy...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He's gotten himself in way over his head.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh...! Mr. Grossberg! You're back!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It seems I've arrived just in the nick of time. I found the police report on that incident in your newspaper clipping!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thank you so much! This is exactly what I was hoping for!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You'd better take a good look at it... It... err... details how you came to lose your boyfriend.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, the defense has made a very serious accusation. Mr. Payne, what do you have to say about this?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">W-Well really, Your Honor... I... I... That is I...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ah, don't you worry, my dear. I have this situation well in hand.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... ... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Err, that is I... Um... G-G-Go right ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Madame Fey, are you seriously accusing me of killing my sweet Dougie?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes. I am. Not only am I saying you murdered Doug Swallow... ...but you also tried to pin the whole thing on your current lover, Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I told you that you should let me handle this...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... ... *weep*</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk. Sorry. P-Please go ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">How can you say that!? I'm absolutely devoted to my dear Feenie. The notion that I would try to frame him is ludicrous! This is all just too much for poor little me to bear!!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, I believe the girl is trying to ask what on Earth her motive would be.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The answer to that lies somewhere in this police report. It must!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eight months ago, an incident occurred in the basement cafeteria of this building. And then... that same day the two of them "accidentally" meet...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor. The defense requests further testimony from Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">F-Further testimony...? What about?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">About the events of the day when she first met the defendant, Mr. Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">What could that possibly have to do with this case!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The witness claims that she has no reason to frame the defendant, am I correct? Well I have evidence that suggests that she, in fact, had a very good reason!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, the court grants the defense's request. Young lady. Would you mind staying on for just a bit longer?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Of course not, Mr. Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Get ready for the battle of your life, Dahlia Hawthorne!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I first met my darling Feenie eight months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're so lovey-wuvey we literally make people sick! It's just jealousy, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Do that again and you will be held in contempt of court!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>And now we enter the final act of our little drama!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">As we used to say in the days of my youth, "Go get her!"</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I first met my darling Feenie eight months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So until that time, you had been dating Doug Swallow?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Y-Yes. I'm a real fool, I know. Letting my emotions change so quickly... I'm ashamed of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no. Not at all! Look at me! I'm infamous for changing my mind! My critics have even taken to calling me "Judge Fickle"! Ho! Ho! Ho!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Maybe you should look for a different line of work...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Despite that, however, he always, always hands down the correct verdict. That's why some people also call him "The Great Judgini".</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">It's like we were destined to meet in this very courthouse's basement reading room.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The courthouse reading room? That's a strange place to meet the love of your life.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's not true, Madame Fey. After all, Feenie was... Feenie was not only an art student, but he was also planning on becoming a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm not talking about him. I'm talking about you, Ms. Hawthorne. What was a literature student like you doing in a courthouse reading room?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">This line of questioning is a waste of time! It has nothing to do with our murder case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey, I'm warning you. If this has nothing to do with Mr. Swallow's case...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I have to remember the judge is on Dahlia's side. I'd better tread carefully...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Mia, if the judge gets any angrier, you'll lose the whole case! I'll just have to hold my tongue for the time being.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, young lady, please go on with your testimony. Tell us about the time you first met Phoenix Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor, if you'll allow me some latitude, I think I can establish relevance. Please ask her to continue on with her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Young lady, I've got a simple question for you. What were you doing downstairs in the courthouse reading room?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">If it pleases Your Honor, the answer is simply this.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The courthouse reading room? That's a strange place to meet the love of your life.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's not true, Madame Fey. After all, Feenie was... Feenie was not only an art student, but he was also planning on becoming a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm not talking about him. I'm talking about you, Ms. Hawthorne. What was a literature student like you doing in a courthouse reading room?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Tee hee. There's nothing strange about that. ma'am.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I had come to this courthouse to do some research for a paper I was writing.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were writing a paper? On what?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">On the relationship between modern Senryu poetry and the criminal underworld.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. That sounds like a fascinating research idea.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">"Am I getting old? Now I've even forgotten what I've forgotten..."</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Again with the mid-life crisis stuff!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia, why did that girl really come to this courthouse? Isn't that what you wanted to know? And speaking of forgetting things, you haven't forgotten the police report, have you? I went through a lot of trouble to get it, m'dear, so be sure to read it carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The moment our eyes met, my heart skipped a beat!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmm... So what was it about Mr. Wright that made your heart malfunction like that? In my personal opinion, he just looks like a typical snotty-nosed college brat.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Perhaps to a woman your age. But to me, Feenie is handsome!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Perhaps to you, Ms. Hawthorne. But to the rest of the planet, he's a dime a dozen.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Love is a mysterious thing, and I object to this line of questioning! If you were to look at my wife for example, you might all be shocked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He's telling the truth. It was truly, truly shocking.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">"Beautiful mushroom, growing tall in the darkness. It comes from cow dung." That's the poem that best describes how I feel about my Feenie.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">We've been going out ever since that fateful day.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Were there any bad feelings between you and Mr. Swallow?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">No, none at all. We parted on very good terms.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But that can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Our investigation also shows that it was a clean breakup.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Huh... Are you... Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Yes, it seems that they both wanted it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So the victim wanted to break up with her...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">So you're saying that Mr. Swallow also wanted to break up with you?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">W-Well, y-you see...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">What a cruel thing to ask a lovely young lady like this! ... By the way, I have never ONCE considered leaving MY wife!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No one cares, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>She didn't deny it... That must mean... Doug Swallow must have seen through her little act. He must have gotten a glimpse of her true nature.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>What did the victim think of Dahlia Hawthorne...? Well, I guess I don't have to think about that now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Listen to me, Mia. That woman has the judge in the palm of her hand, you see. So the only way to discredit her is to find a contradiction in her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Ms. Hawthorne, you weren't here because of your research paper, were you? Didn't you actually come here for a much more important reason?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wh-What is the meaning of that cocky smile on your face, Ms. Fey!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eight months ago, right here in this very courthouse, there was another tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Another tragedy...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean the incident in which an attorney was poisoned?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The name of the suspect in that incident is listed here in this report. And that name is... Dahlia Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Dahlia H-Hawthorne!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes! The sweetie-pie of everyone's eye, Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne! She was the prime suspect in a criminal case just eight months ago!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! ... Th-This is unbelievable! It's true then... The loveliest rose can hide the cruelest thorn...</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ms. Fey! Th-That's not fair! You can't slander my witness with an unrelated case!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I, Winston Payne, will not allow it!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Mr. Prosecutor... I believe I was speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Urk. P-Pardon me... G-Go right ahead...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">It's true that about eight months ago... ...the police expressed some interest in me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Expressed some interest, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Mr. Judge, sir... I know I'm under oath, so I'll tell you the absolute truth. I did not commit the crime that occurred during that incident eight months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>OK... I've tied the two crimes together! Now I've just got to stay on the offensive!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Well done, Mia! Ooohhh... You've really lit a fire in my heart... And my buttocks! I can hardly tell which is more inflamed, my spirit... or my hemorrhoids!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I met the lawyer who was poisoned to discuss something in the cafeteria that day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So that's what happened here eight months ago.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">However, as you've heard from the witness's testimony, she had nothing to do with it. I think the defense is just about out of tricks...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Payne. But I'm afraid the defense has many more tricks up its sleeve today. And I'll be sure to show them to you before the end of this cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Unnggh! What the...!? Why does the defense suddenly feel stronger...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Aha! Mia! You're glowing with a true lawyer's aura, m'dear! That proud posture and self-confidence! Absolutely smashing!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I met the lawyer who was poisoned to discuss something in the cafeteria that day.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">What were you talking about with the defense attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well I... I'm sorry, but that's confidential.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to the report, you were being interviewed regarding another case.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The lawyer that was killed... He said he wanted to talk about an incident I was caught up in when I was younger.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Why don't you tell us all what that incident was?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">That has absolutely nothing at all to do with this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection sustained. The defense's question is stricken from the record.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You get involved in a lot of "incidents", don't you, Ms. Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well, I guess I was just born under a bad sign.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry, Dollie! I'll protect you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You heard the man. Now THAT is true love, young lady!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh, Feenie... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>*gag* Those two really are making me ill. Albeit for decidedly different reasons.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I left my seat for just a moment, and that's when it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">How long were you gone?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I've already answered all these questions for the police... But if you must know, maybe 10 or 20 minutes...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">And where were you during that stretch of time? Using the toilet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you SAYING, Miss Fey!? Toilet!? My perfect little Dollie doesn't poop!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You heard the defendant, Ms. Fey. Better luck next time.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh, Feenie... Please...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The police have already looked into this whole matter. This line of questioning is nothing but a waste of the court's time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection sustained. Ms. Hawthorne, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">From what I heard, it was a liquid poison that is lethal at just 2 teaspoons.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">About how much liquid is 2 teaspoons?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, well let me see... My bottle of eyedrops says it's 1/2 fluid ounce... Which is equal to 3 teaspoons...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So it's about two-thirds of that amount, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The poison was found in the lawyer's mug of coffee. It must have been after I left the table... Someone must have quietly slipped it in there.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Not only that, I heard it was a very special kind of poison.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">A "special kind of poison"? How so?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well, I heard that it's almost impossible to detect.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And where would something like that come from...?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I'm sorry... All I know is what I overheard the policemen saying. They said something about using advanced chemical processes to purify it...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Chemical processes"...? Well, well... That's quite... ...impressive. Most impressive...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The better question is, how did the criminal get something like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">So you see, I'm innocent! I wouldn't even know where to get a poison like that!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">And that's the reason they didn't arrest you? Because no one could show how you could've gotten the poison?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I think that's a good enough reason, Madame Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">She's right. And I think we've all had enough of Ms. Fey's questions!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So in essence, the main reason Ms. Hawthorne was never arrested for this crime... ...was because no one could show how she could have obtained the poison.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Then all we have to do is find a way to establish how she could've gotten some, right? <thought>Great... Now just how did a lit. student get a hold of poison, of all things...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">You wouldn't know how to get that kind of poison? I don't believe you.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">What...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">In fact, you had easy access to that kind of poison, didn't you? At your boyfriend's lab!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Boyfriend!? You mean the victim, Doug Swallow!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's right. Up until eight months ago, Ms. Hawthorne was dating Mr. Swallow. And if you'll recall, Mr. Swallow was a Pharmacology student at Ivy University.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ph-Ph-Pharmacology...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">His laboratory contained highly advanced chemistry equipment. In fact, without such equipment... ...the culprit could never have obtained such a rare and special poison!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Ms. Hawthorne? It seems you had access to such a poison after all. And then, it was a matter of slipping it into the victim's coffee when he wasn't looking. The only person who could've done that was the one sitting at his very table -- you!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">NOOOOOOOOOOOO!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order! C-C-Could it be...!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That's nothing but a baseless accus--</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">May I say something, Madame Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What is it, Ms. Hawthorne?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">The amount of poison in the coffee was 2 teaspoons, correct? In order to carry that much liquid... you would need some kind of container.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, yes... That's true.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I was searched immediately after the incident took place.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Quite true. In fact the entire courthouse was turned upside down.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">But... they didn't find a suspicious container anywhere, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>She's right... They even mentioned that in the report!</thought> W-Well, you could've easily gotten rid of something that small!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Excuse me, Madame, but this is a court of law! If you're saying I threw the poison container away... ...I think you need to show some kind of proof!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">P-Proof...!? <thought>She got me good with that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Provide some evidence or I'll have to disallow this line of questioning, Ms. Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Unless we can come up with some evidence, we're going to lose this lead!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>The police conducted a full body search of Dahlia and of the entire courthouse. And yet the container holding the poison disappeared right after the crime occurred...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're going to accuse the young lady of committing the murder... ...then where is the container the poison was carried in? What happened to it?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">... ......</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... ...... .........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey... I'm sure even you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In a narrative, this is what they call the "moment of truth"! And you've ruined it!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">That's correct, Mr. Judge... But you play your part so well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Leave it to me, young lady! It's my job, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Ohhh...! Don't do it, Mia! Don't cry!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You're so close, Mia! Don't give up! Think!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You were forced to get rid of the container in a hurry, weren't you? And that's why you passed it on to someone that had nothing to do with the case! Someone that you knew wouldn't be searched!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Who is this person!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Phoenix Wright, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">So the defendant was this witness's accomplice?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Of course not. She gave the poison to him disguised as... a present.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Wh-What...!? B-But... But that's...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's a charming little necklace. Is this... a little bottle? It's really quite cute. So what about it? What does it mean, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The day that the witness met and fell for Mr. Phoenix Wright was eight months ago... August 27th. The very same day as the poisoning incident. Under the pretense of love, the witness gave my client a present. All for the purpose of hiding the one piece of evidence that would give her away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaat!? Are you saying there's a deadly poison in here!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">No, there's no longer any poison in that bottle. However! I'm certain if the crime lab were to analyze it, they would find a trace amount!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">......... NOOOOOOOOOO!! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or-Order! Order in the court! Ahh, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On behalf of Dollie, I object!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">M-Mr. Wright! Control yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I won't let you bully her like this...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I thought I told you to stay in your seat!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright... Why? Why are you going through so much trouble to protect her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why? B-Because...! Because I'm madly in love with her!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm, hmmmm... "Madly in love"... I haven't heard anyone say that in a long time...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright... Have you ever thought about this... Why exactly would a woman like Dahlia Hawthorne want to date you anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well... I guess she must be madly in love with me too...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Mr. Wright... Please! Open your eyes...!</thought> At this point in the trial, I think it should be obvious to everyone. The real reason that Dahlia Hawthorne is dating you is...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally it's because she has fallen madly in love with you too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See? Just like I told you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">M-M-Mia! Are you thinking clearly!? Th-That flies in the face of everything we've learned up to this point!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I-I'm sorry! I don't know why I even said that... *sigh* I guess it's because I just like the sound of that phrase, "madly in love"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey. You can't remain a starry-eyed maiden for the rest of your life, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please let me think it over one more time, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally, it's to keep you quiet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What...!? To k-keep me quiet!? ... Um... Keep me quiet about what...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well... uh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems that the rest of us don't quite understand you, Ms. Fey. Nor do we understand what this vile secret that Ms. Hawthorne holds is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because there is no secret, I tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>ARGH!! How dense can you be!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey... Please think it over and try again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Dahlia Hawthorne was not and is not madly in love with you. The only thing she's after is that bottle necklace you love to wear around your neck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My n-necklace...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Back there in the waiting room, you said it yourself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, but she's so shy. Every time I see her, she always says the same thing to me. "Please give it back now."</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What a strange girl, asking for a present back like that...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">For Dahlia Hawthorne, that necklace is irrefutable evidence of her crime. That's why she absolutely had to get it back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You're lying!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">But you never gave it back to her. And to make things worse for her, you insisted on showing it to everyone you met. That's why she......</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I don't...... I don't believe you... NOOO!! Th-That's a LIE!! Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eeeeeek!!</line>
<line speaker="???">M-Mia! Are you alright!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Bailiff! Hurry! After him!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia! Mia! Are you alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, I-I think so...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That boy...! He went completely insane!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Where... Where's Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It looks like the bailiff caught him, so he should be brought back here soon.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thank goodness... ... Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The bottle necklace...! Ms. Hawthorne's "present"...! It's gone...!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Whaaaaat...! That's terrible!!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright must have grabbed it when he slammed into me!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Foolish boy...! That's the only thing that could have saved him... What in blazes are we supposed to do noooow!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright!! This sort of behavior is unprecedented in the history of this court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I'm afraid that your apology is not enough!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright! What did you do with the bottle necklace?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Forgive me... I... I... I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It's OK. Just give back the necklace.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I ate it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... You what?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You... You... You ate it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was too big to swallow, so I had to chew it into little bits first, but yeah... ...Ugh. Aaaaaaaaahhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What the...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Wha--...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is he doing now!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Your Honor!! You've got to stop the trial!! Mr. Wright! Mr. Wright! Are you feeling OK!? Does your stomach hurt!? That bottle you swallowed may have had some poison left in it!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Ehee hee... Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee... It seems the defendant has proven the prosecution's case for us. Clearly that bottle did not contain a deadly poison!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">H-How can you be so sure!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee... I think that's obvious... As you can see, the defendant is still very much alive. As for the poison? More like a fledgling defense attorney's overactive imagination!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">No! There must be some mistake! The bottle must not have had any poison left in it! Either that or the poison must have lost its potency...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There, there... It's alright, rookie. Trusting your client is the most noble thing a defense attorney can do. And it's heartwarming to see that you placed this much faith in Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">But that's how it is for us on the prosecution side, too! For example, I would trust the witness, Ms. Hawthorne, with my very life! Which is why I can state that your assessment of her is completely wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! Unfortunately, Ms. Fey, I cannot accept your explanation of the events.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">B-But why!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This may be impossible for a beginner like you to understand... ...but in a court of law, evidence is everything.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Unngggh! <thought>Even though I've proven so much, is she going to get away with everything...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, now that the suspicion surrounding Ms. Hawthorne has been cleared up... I would like to proceed with the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">M... Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Miss Fey. It totally slipped my mind. I'm really, really sorry... I know you believed in me, and I feel like I really let you down.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright... What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... There's something I forgot to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That day... The day I met Doug Swallow...</line>
<line speaker="Swallow">Last night, someone stole some poison from our lab.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Poison...?</line>
<line speaker="Swallow">The same thing happened eight months ago. A drug sample was stolen. She came to the lab that time, too. It could only have been her! That girl is a thief!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop it! D-Don't talk about her like that!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Is it true? Did he really say that?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That's ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's one more thing... After I pushed him that day... I got worried and came back to have a look. And she was there... Dollie was right there. She was crouched down next to him...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She told me not to ever tell anyone about it, but... I'm sorry, Dollie!</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Your Honor! This is... The defendant is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miss Fey! You tell them! D-Dollie didn't do it... Sh-She's innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>So Dahlia stole poison eight months ago too, huh... If you put that together with Mr. Wright's testimony... ...then there's only one possible conclusion!</thought> The defense believes that Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne... ...stole some poison on the night before she killed Doug Swallow.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The night before...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Naturally, her motive for stealing it was to kill someone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miss Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're so certain of your theory, then let me ask you this.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Mia, this is your last chance. Think carefully now... There's something that she desperately wanted to get back... Therefore...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Exactly who was Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne planning to kill?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">W-Wait a minute, Mia! Why would she want to kill Doug Swallow?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Because Doug Swallow had figured out what kind of a person she was! And so...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">No, no! Well, that may be true, but Ms. Hawthorne had no way of knowing that. From her point of view, who was it that was really in her way? THAT is the question you have to ask yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey. I'm beginning to run out of patience with you. What is your answer?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor! <thought>I can't mess up again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Are you trying to mock this court, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Wh-What are you doing!? You sounded so sure of yourself at first... Now it turns out you have no idea what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">W-Well it's been a long time since I've been in court...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will cost you, Ms. Fey! Now think more carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I apologize, Your Honor... <thought>No more mistakes, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia">There was one person that was standing squarely in Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne's way... And that person was... Mr. Phoenix Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... M-M-M-M-M-M-Meeee!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Th-That's preposterous!! After all, it was Doug Swallow that was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, it's true that that's how things worked out... But, let's remember that Mr. Swallow died of electrocution, not poison. The person that Ms. Hawthorne was planning to poison was in fact... You, Phoenix Wright. There's no one else that it could be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But how can that be!? I-I thought Mr. Wright and Ms. Hawthorne were in love!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Poor Mr. Wright... This must be killing him... Hang in there... I'll bring her to justice... I swear it!</thought> As I said before, the only thing Ms. Hawthorne truly cared about was... ...the one piece of evidence linking her to that incident eight months ago. That's right. The bottle necklace. That's all she cared about.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But even so... Why... Why would she go so far as to murder him!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eight months ago, just after the fall of that attorney in the basement cafeteria... Dahlia Hawthorne could think of only one thing. How to get rid of the bottle necklace as quickly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... It-It can't be...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It was a pretty good move she made, too. The evidence was missing for a long time. But there was just one big problem. Although she got him to hide the evidence, Mr. Wright refused to return it to her. To him, the tiny little bottle was a cherished treasure. He even showed it to everyone he met!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-You mean... TH-THAT'S why she tried to kill Mr. Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Correct, Your Honor. It was to retrieve that piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Th-Th-Th... That can't be trueeeeeeeee!!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">"Feenie"... What a joke you are. Honestly, how can any woman ever count on you for anything? I even told you time and time again to keep your trap shut about me and that necklace. ...You disgust me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. Hawthorne...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It appears that this trial will be coming to an end soon...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Fine. I can tell you plan on making me into a criminal no matter what I say!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">You ARE a criminal, Ms. Hawthorne!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">We'll see about that. But first, where's your evidence? It seems your sniveling little crybaby of a client has eaten the bottle as a snack.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Urk...! W-Well, umm...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Hey! Old man! Are you senile or something!? Why don't you say something instead of sitting there with that dumb look on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-M-Ms. Hawthorne! What's happened to you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Hmph! Are you really that shocked? ... Or do you prefer me... this way, Mr. Judge?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nnnnggghh...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">With absolutely no proof, you treat a voluntary witness like she's a mass-murderer... Well, I have nothing more to say. I'll be heading home now, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But y-you're not finished...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Fine! Then ask this nasty old hag to finish up already!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>I can't let her get away this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Stop, Mia! If you keep on pushing without any evidence... ...you could pay the ultimate price as a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">The ultimate price...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You'd be forced to take off your attorney's badge forever, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">N-No...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">You'd better think it over carefully, Ms. Fey... Or should I say, Ms. Gray.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Fey? Can you provide evidence that would establish her guilt once and for all?</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>If I mess up here, my career as a lawyer is over! But to be honest... at this point I don't have any evidence that's well-founded. Even so... I'd rather lose my attorney's badge than let her get away with murder!</thought> Your Honor! The defense would like to present proof!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Im-Impossible! You can't possibly...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Stupid woman!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is the opinion of the court that there has already been enough discussion. Therefore, I will allow only one piece of evidence to be presented.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">J-Just one!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you are unable to establish her guilt... ...then I'm afraid that a very harsh verdict will immediately be handed down on Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I understand, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I can just imagine the headlines for tomorrow's newspaper. Up-and-coming lawyer plummets to Earth before she gets the chance to soar...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>She was planning to poison Mr. Wright... If that's the case, then the poison was probably in there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, Ms. Fey. Please present your evidence. Show to this court irrefutable proof that Ms. Hawthorne was planning to poison Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Fey...! After all that thinking, THIS is your best answer!?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">C-Couldn't you have tried a little bit harder...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Please wait, Your Honor! I just... made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But even I have my limits!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Here it is, Your Honor! The evidence that will prove her guilt once and for all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Coldkiller X... Phoenix Wright's beloved cold medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hee, hee, hee, hee... Does our rookie defense attorney have a bit of a cold?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If I did, I still wouldn't take this cold medicine. After all... It's been poisoned.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Remember what the defendant said in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I lost my bottle of it around lunchtime on the day of the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I always eat with Dollie... Just the two of us.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She was the one who took his bottle of Coldkiller X. Then she poisoned it, knowing that Mr. Wright was going to take some.</line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now you're really grasping at straws! After all, it was the victim, Doug Swallow, that was holding the medicine.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I would like the court to recall the crime that happened here eight months ago. Where did Ms. Hawthorne hide the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Eight months ago, the poison was hidden in her bottle necklace... ...which she then gave to someone else for safekeeping. Someone she had accidentally run into in the reading room. My client, Mr. Phoenix Wright! Yes, that's right... She did the same thing this time as well. After shoving the victim, Mr. Phoenix Wright left the scene of the crime. That is when the murderer, Dahlia Hawthorne, appeared. With her, she was carrying the poisoned bottle of Coldkiller X. This, of course, was so she could carry out her plan to murder Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I believe she did testify that she was going to meet with the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, and she heard and saw everything that happened at the scene of the crime. Including what the defendant and victim were arguing about, and the cut electrical cable.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">She used the severed electrical cable to silence him forever. Unfortunately for her, this is when the problem occurred. Mr. Wright, who she thought had left the scene, came back to check on the victim. And on top of that, because of the power outage, some students showed up as well. It's hardly any wonder that she was, as she put it, in a state of panic. Recall that she was carrying that bottle of poisoned cold medicine. She must have thought, "What if they search me like they did eight months ago?"</line>
<line speaker="Payne">E-Eight months ago...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Yes, she disposed of the evidence exactly the same way as she did back then! She had someone else hold it! In this case... Doug Swallow!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Oh come on now, everyone. Surely you aren't fooled, are you? This stupid woman! She's nothing but a filthy, stinking liar! Right, Mr. Prosecutor...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Huh...!? Y-Yes... Th-That's exactly right. It's just pure desperation!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Hmm... I wonder which one of us is the desperate one? So, Ms. Hawthorne. This cold medicine... I wonder if you wouldn't mind taking some?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well, Mr. Wright ate that necklace of yours, right? Now it's your turn to prove your innocence. What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">If I'm just a filthy, stinking liar, then there's no need to worry. So come on! Show us! I dare you to take some of this medicine right now!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">... ...Grr... Nngghh... Hnnn... MIA FEY...! MIA... FEYYYY...!! Do. You. Think. You've. Won? Well!? Do you, Mia Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...!</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Heh... Heh... Heh... Heheh... That's. Just. Fine! For the time being... For the time being, victory is yours.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">"For the time being"?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well... I have a very long memory, you know. You and I will meet again... I'm certain of it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">...?</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">Well then, Mr. Judge... I'll see you later too, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Huh...!? Err, why, um... Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Dahlia">I'm going to go spend a little quality time with the men in blue now. I wish you all the best.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Whew... It's finally all over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Payne">I... I refuse to accept this! The defense hasn't shown a scrap of evidence to support their outrageous claim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But even so, your witness seems to have accepted it...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">I don't care!! I'm Winston Payne! And I don't believe one word that this rookie lawyer has said!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Well then, Mr. Payne, let me ask you this.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Would you care to try this cold medicine?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Just a little earlier, I could've sworn you said...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">There, there... It's alright, rookie.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">For example, I would trust the witness, Ms. Hawthorne, with my very life!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">So, if she's so trustworthy... ...then I'm sure there couldn't possibly be any poison in here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Err... Well... Ummm... You see... Umm... Y-Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">...And here comes the backpedal! Come on now, "Rookie Killer"! Show this rookie how it's done! How much trust do you really have for this woman? Are you willing to bet your life!?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Gggg... Nnngh... Unnngggggh... NNNNNNYYYYAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA M-M-My HAAAAAAAAAAIIIIRRR!! IT-IT-IT'S FLYYYYYIIIIIIIING OOOOOFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFF!! MY BEAUUUUUUUTIFUL HAIR!! NOOOOOOO!!! NOOOOOOOOOOO!! WAAAAAHAAAAWAAAAHAAAA NO-NO-NO-NO-No-No-no-no noooooooooooooooooooooo...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm, Mr. Payne? About Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne...?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Y-Y-Yes, Your Honor! I'll file papers for her immediate arrest...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Tragic... but not surprising. I knew there was something suspicious about her from the very beginning!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Don't lie! Just admit you were wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way, Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Y-Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You said earlier that you and Ms. Dahlia Hawthorne knew each other...?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Your Honor... How we knew each other had nothing to do with this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Very well... Err, Mr. Payne.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This can't be happening! It's a nightmare! It's like losing to my daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It appears Mr. Payne has lost his spirit along with his hair. Does the defendant have anything further to say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It-It can't be true... My... Dear... Dollie... *achoo*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well then... I believe I am ready to pass judgment and bring this trial to an end. The court finds the defendant, Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Mia! You were wonderful in there!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Thank you for everything, Mr. Grossberg.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">During the verdict, I thought my hemorrhoids were going to explode like Mt. Vesuvius!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Umm, Mr. Grossberg... Do you, um, maybe think you could stop talking about them?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmph! That's rather rude. Anyway, this case really made me think. What does it really mean to have a relationship of mutual trust with the client? Perhaps it is we veteran lawyers who have lost sight of this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oh! Mr. Wright...! Congratulations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks... Um, you know... I was thinking...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Go on...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Dollie that I saw up there on the witness stand... I don't think that was really her.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Um, what?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... The Dollie I know could NEVER have said those kinds of terrible things... Maybe... Maybe she was like... I don't know... A fake or something.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Boy... This poor kid still hasn't got a clue...</thought> You need to forget about her, Mr. Wright. For your own sake...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right... That's probably for the best.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Also... You need to relax a bit more. Try to grow up a little.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But... Out of all my friends, everyone says I'm the most grown up!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Eek! What kind of company must this guy keep!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Right now I... I'm studying to become a lawyer myself.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">That's what you keep saying... But I thought you were in the Art Department?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, yeah... I guess I am... But there's a friend that I desperately want to help! And if I hurry, then I should still be able to save him in time!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say, Miss Fey? A lawyer is someone who can help people when they're in trouble, right?</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Mr. Wright, I'm still new at this myself. But... I think that's exactly what a lawyer is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">OK... I'm going to do it. I'll study my butt off. I'll become a lawyer for sure! I hope... I hope we see each other again some day, maybe even in court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's been five years since I was acquitted of all charges. I became a lawyer like I planned, and managed to save my friend. But Mia has passed on to a better place. For me, this trial brings up a lot of painful memories. But... it also brings up some very precious ones. And memories that I thought would never rise to the surface again... Mia is gone now. But even so... I can hear her in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Phoenix, no matter what, always believe in your client. In a court of law, your greatest weapon is your belief.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Five long years... Something has happened that's made me think back to her words of wisdom... But that is a story for another day...</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! What do you think of the witness's statement!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't really see any problem with it.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">... Actually... I don't either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then what are you making a fuss for!? Think before you speak, young lady!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Your Honor! That statement contradicts this evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In what way...? I'm not sure I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Actually... I don't quite get it either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, make sure you do before you speak out again!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Aghh... He's mad at me now. But you can't give up yet, Mia!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">Does this evidence establish that the defendant is lying?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Don't ask me! You're the one who's supposed to know!</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Oops, sorry. This is all still kind of new to me...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I've got something new for you, too -- a new penalty! Objection overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>This isn't going as smoothly as I had hoped...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mia"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Mia">The witness's testimony just now is clearly contradictory, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It could be...</line>
<line speaker="Mia">It has to be, right!? I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, your evidence doesn't show whatever contradiction you think you see.</line>
<line speaker="Mia">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think it over again.</line>
<line speaker="Mia"><thought>Well, there goes a few points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! This court sees no reason to further prolong the trial. Nor is there any need for more time to decide the case against the defendant. This case is extremely clear. I see no room for misinterpretation of the facts. This court finds the defendant, Phoenix Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The accused will surrender to the court immediately... ...to be held pending trial at a higher court within a month from today's date. That is all. This court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>