<xml>
<title>Turnabout Countdown <thought>demo</thought></title>
<line speaker="???">Heh heh heh! The best thing about bombs is how they erase and destroy... without discretion. Now all I have to do is pin everything on that little girl!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... These good ol' pre-trial jitters... It's all coming back to me. They never seem to go away no matter how many times I do this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright! What's the matter? You've been pretty quiet there, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I-I have? I was... just thinking about t-today's trial. <thought>And about how I could do with a glass of water right about now. I feel like a newbie again.</thought> My name is Phoenix Wright. I run what could be called a law office, I guess. Although, I was forced to take a break from practicing until only recently. <thought>This is Athena Cykes. She's a rookie defense attorney that just joined our team.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What I lack in experience, I make up for with heart! I love orange juice after a workout, and I love to win!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's a force to be reckoned with, no doubt, and she's got the temperament to match...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Setting up a positive mental image before the trial, huh? That's my boss for you! That must be one of the secrets to your success, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Um... yeah. I guess? <thought>Project confidence... like a boss...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Mr. Wright, Thena... Thank you again for agreeing to help me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is Juniper Woods. She's our client for this case. She and Athena have been friends since childhood.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't you worry, Junie! Mr. Wright here will definitely get you acquitted!</line>
<line speaker="???">Do it for me too, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Apollo! <thought>Shouldn't you still be in the hospital?! This is Apollo Justice. He's another young defense attorney at my law office.</thought> How are your injuries? Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm fine! Ngaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(That's... not the sound of someone who's feeling "fine." A dying cat, maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I couldn't laze around in a hospital bed. Not when I'm one of the victims in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's true... He was the one at the bench when the bomb went off that day.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I actually wanted to serve on the defense myself today.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Rest assured, Apollo! Mr. Wright here will make short work of anyone who doubts Junie's innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, r-right. Yeah... Yes, of course! <thought>Urk! She sure knows how to ramp up the pressure on a guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it looks like it's just about that time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you ready, Athena? <thought>I sure hope so, because I don't think I am...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! I'm always ready for a good fight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I can't do much except cheer you on from the gallery... But you just have to win this one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And we will! Los geht's!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come what may, it's show time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Juniper Woods.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution is also ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. Now that I'm actually standing here, the butterflies in my stomach are going nuts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, Mr. Wright. It's been quite a while, but it's good to have you back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. It's good to be back!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite frankly, I didn't think I'd ever see you at the defense's bench again. But now that you've been reborn, so to speak, let's see how you do here today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I-I think you'll see I've learned quite a bit during my time away, Your Honor! <thought>Gulp... Throat drying... Voice... cracking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hope you're ready over there, because it's a whole new Phoenix Wright on our side!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">You mean "Phoenix Van Winkle"? I doubt I have much to worry about then, in that case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh--! Why you--! Whatever! Believe what you want! But mark my words: my boss will wipe that smug look off your face in ten minutes or less!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoa there, Athena! Let's not make any wild claims, and especially not impossible ones!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. A quick verdict might not be such a bad thing. There isn't much time in a demo, after all! Now then, Mr. Payne. Please tell us about the incident, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The incident happened in this very courthouse, in Courtroom No. 4. A time bomb that was being presented as evidence suddenly went off during the trial. I have here the bomb's specifications and the police report on the incident for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... If memory serves, I touch the Court Record Button (R</thought> to check the evidence.)</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait, so this impish stuffed animal was the bomb?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Well, yes and no. The actual bomb was stuffed inside that to hide its wires and timer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And it's your claim that it was the defendant who activated this bomb?</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Exactly. The defense may boast that they can finish faster than a bag of boil-in-bag rice... but the prosecution has decisive evidence of the defendant's crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what, pray tell, is this? It appears to be a little singed.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This, Your Honor, is the tail of the stuffed animal the bomb was in. It's apparently called "Phony Phanty," or some such nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And what does that tail have to do with anything?!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">This tail is made of vinyl cloth. And we found something very interesting on its surface... the defendant's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>WH-WHAAAAAT?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">Now do you see? This evidence clearly proves that the accused had handled the bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. That does appear to be pretty irrefutable evidence... The court accepts this item into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. It looks like this trial may very well end in under ten minutes... But I'll be the one wiping the smug look off of YOUR face with a guilty verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What are we going to do, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't know...! This is all thanks to you making that "ten minutes" comment!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? THAT'S what got us into this mess?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, I'll overlook your private quarrel, but just this once. Now then, let's move on. Mr. Payne, please call your first witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Witness, your name and occupation, please.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">NAME: TED TONATE OCCUPATION: BOMB DISPOSAL SPECIALIST</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! What a strange, robotic voice you have!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">SPEECH SYNTHESIS VIA TYPING. IT IS THE SAME AS ME TALKING.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. What an odd witnss.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Mr. Tonate was in charge of the bomb for that trial and was there when it went off. He is here to testify about the circumstances surrounding the moment of the explosion.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE BOMB WAS ORIGINALLY DISARMED BY ME, THEN TRANSPORTED HERE AS EVIDENCE. BOMB NAME: HH-3000 OPERATED BY TIMER OR WITH A REMOTE. I WAS WATCHING FROM THE GALLERY WHEN I SUDDENLY BECAME ALARMED. I SAW THAT THE BOMB'S TIMER WAS COUNTING DOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm. The HH-3000... So that's the name of the bomb in this thing, huh? I honestly wouldn't have known such a thing was hiding inside if you hadn't told me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So even though the bomb was supposed to be disarmed, it somehow got switched on?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">PRECISELY. ACTIVATING THE TIMER IS VERY SIMPLE. EVEN A MONKEY COULD DO IT. I AM SURE THE DEFENDANT WOULD BE ABLE TO.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Well, Mr. Wright, you may now begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Cross-examination time! This is where the real battle begins!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Go get him, Boss! Give him that famous Phoenix Wright treatment! Unleash the wild accusations and unabashed bluffing we all know and love on him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just you watch! I'll get him! <thought>Though it's been years since I've done this... Ugh, I hate to admit it, but maybe I should ask Athena for a refresher course...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Athena, you remember how to conduct a cross-examination, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Of course I do! What kind of lawyer would I be if I didn't?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now! Don't get upset! But why don't you humor me with a little review...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it! Basically, we examine a witness's testimony... and compare it against the Court Record, searching carefully for any inconsistencies. This green text represents a witness's testimony. Touch the right arrow to advance to the next statement of the testimony. Touch the left arrow to go back to the previous statement. Pay close attention to the testimony, and when you've found an inconsistency... touch "Present" <thought>R</thought> to open the Court Record! The Court Record contains information on all the evidence we have at our disposal. You can use it to look for facts that conflict with what the witness has said. When you find something, "Present" <thought>X</thought> that evidence to refute the witness's statement!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if nothing conflicts with the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's when you "Press" <thought>L</thought> the witness for more information. Find any inconsistencies or lies in the testimony and reveal them to the court. That's what cross-examination is all about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you remember it just as I taught it. <thought>And, thanks to you, I remember it now, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't ask my subordinate for help on how to cross-examine! I'll just have to wing it. I hope it's like riding a bicycle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I'm ready to cross-examine the witness now!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THE BOMB WAS ORIGINALLY DISARMED BY ME, THEN TRANSPORTED HERE AS EVIDENCE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">ABSOLUTELY. I CAN DISARM ANYTHING. IN A FLASH.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That looks more like "dismantle" than "disarm" to me...</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">Oh. Pardon me.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Heh heh heh. If you must know, Mr. Wright, according to the court's own records... the fact that the bomb had indeed been disarmed was officially confirmed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I guess I can rule out the possibility that he forgot to disarm it...</thought> Could you talk about the bomb in a little more detail for the court, Mr. Tonate?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">CERTAINLY.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">BOMB NAME: HH-3000 OPERATED BY TIMER OR WITH A REMOTE</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">DIMENSIONS: 9.5" H x 9" W x 10" D WEIGHT: 12 LBS</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet if I dropped that thing on your foot, you'd be hoppin'!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you dropped that thing anywhere, I'd be "hopping" for the nearest exit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Tonate, you were keeping an eye on the bomb? Where were you watching from?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WAS WATCHING FROM THE GALLERY WHEN I SUDDENLY BECAME ALARMED.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I WAS ON STANDBY DURING THE TRIAL, BUT I WANTED TO KEEP WATCH JUST IN CASE. EVEN WHEN A BOMB HAS BEEN DISARMED, YOU CAN NEVER BE TOO CAREFUL. EXPLOSIVE DEVICES ARE VERY DANGEROUS THINGS.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, how admirably responsible of you. A model to be emulated. Now, then. What did you witness from the gallery?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SAW THAT THE BOMB'S TIMER WAS COUNTING DOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">THESE GOGGLES HELP ME SEE VERY SMALL THINGS CLEARLY FROM VERY FAR AWAY. I CAN EVEN SEE WHAT YOU HAD FOR BREAKFAST BY LOOKING AT YOUR TIE.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I suddenly feel like a bug under a magnifying glass?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I guess it's possible he saw the timer if he was wearing those goggles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure. There's something that just doesn't sit right with me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? You mean there's something wrong with this part of the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The bomb was completely hidden inside the stuffed animal. So well concealed, in fact, that it didn't even look like a bomb at all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you're trying to find testimony that conflicts with the evidence, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. So the first step is listening carefully to Mr. Tonate's testimony. Then, it's a matter of taking a look at any evidence that seems relevant.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Remember that you can touch "Present" <thought>R</thought> to check the evidence in the Court Record! If you find evidence that conflicts with the testimony, "Present" <thought>X</thought> it! Let's see... This testimony is about when the bomb went off... So the state of the bomb at that time must be pretty important!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... A bomb that didn't look like a bomb because it was inside a stuffed animal...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you could see the bomb's timer counting down, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">OF COURSE. I CLEARLY SAW IT COUNTING DOWN TO ZERO.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And I say... that you are CLEARLY lying!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no way you could have seen the bomb's timer. After all, the bomb was concealed inside a stuffed animal.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Tonate! How can you claim to know the bomb was about to go off... when you couldn't even see the timer?!</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL... I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh! That was great, Mr. Wright! You found a contradiction right off the bat!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aw, it was nothing. <thought>Nothing short of amazing, that is! All right, I'm starting to feel like I'm in the zone here. I can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very impressive, Mr. Wright. I see the great "Turnabout Terror" is back! Ah, this brings back memories...! Now those days were the stuff of legends! Oh, how you would tear through trials with wild accusations and unabashed bluffing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... that actually doesn't sound like such a flattering legend, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! How do you explain the contradiction in your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">WELL, LET ME SEE... I... UH... OH, YES! YES, OF COURSE! I REMEMBER NOW! THE SOUND! I KNEW BECAUSE OF THE SOUND! WHEN THE TIMER OF THIS TYPE OF BOMB IS SWITCHED ON, IT MAKES A BEEPING SOUND. BEEP... BEEP... BEEP... IT IS THE SOUND OF THE COUNTDOWN.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose it would be possible to notice that, even with the bomb inside the stuffed animal.</line>
<line speaker="Tonate">I SIMPLY MADE A MISTAKE. MY BAD.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? No way! <thought>Why am I not surprised...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">The prosecution believes it's time to hear from the defendant herself, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please show the defendant to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">............ I... I don't really remember much... about when the bomb went off... I... think it's probably... the shock of it all...</line>
<line speaker="Payne">Hmph! What a convenient excuse!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright... Can I go and give that prosecutor a smack?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What?! Of course not! Do we have to review Courtroom Manners 101 again?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But this is so painful for Junie! She's so scared... so very scared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Athena's picking something up with her heightened sense of hearing... And it sounds like this time, it's the pain in Ms. Woods's voice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Payne">If you would, Ms. Woods, please testify to this court about when the bomb went off.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, that day... *cough* I was watching from the gallery... *cough, cough* The bomb went off... *cough* *cough* And rubble started falling... It fell on top of me... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Junie looks like she's in pain, being forced to recall the bombing like this... Why can't the prosecution see that she can't even get her words out?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This isn't working... Hey, wait a minute! If she can't tell us what she wants to say, there's only one thing to do! Yes, now's the perfect time to use Athena's power! Athena has a unique ability, you see. With her special sense of hearing, she can discover a witness's true feelings. In essence, she can discern emotions from the tone of a person's voice. At a time like this, all I can do is leave it to Athena and her special ability.</thought> Athena, I need you to do something for me. I want you to use the analytical psychology you studied... and listen to Ms. Woods's TRUE testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Okay, Mr. Wright! I'll give it a try!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So your holographic thingamabob can show us how Ms. Woods is feeling, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In a nutshell, yes. The emotions and images that I picked up on just now while listening to her testimony... I can enter them into my computer and use its Mood Matrix program to analyze them. These mood markers here reflect fluctuations in Junie's emotions. When she feels happy or is enjoying the memory, the "Happy" marker will light up. When she feels angry or frustrated, the "Angry" marker will react. When she feels sadness or is frightened by a memory, the "Sad" marker will blink. And when she feels surprised or confused, the "Surprised" marker will let us know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, basically, with your special ability and that computer's Mood Matrix program... you can let me know the emotions Ms. Woods is feeling during her testimony. Is that how it works?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You've got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay! It's time to listen to Ms. Woods's true testimony!)</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Well, that day... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was watching from the gallery... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">The bomb went off... *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Woods">*cough* And rubble started falling...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It fell on top of me... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think I have a good grasp on Junie's emotional state now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This power of Athena's is incredible...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'm seeing an unexpected emotion that's inconsistent with her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Already?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at this! When she says, "It fell on top of me," the "Happy" marker is reacting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, look at that. That IS odd!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There must be a reason for this contradictory emotion! We just need to do some digging! When you find an unexpected emotion... touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>... and then select the unexpected emotion or reaction from the four mood markers.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">It fell on top of me... *cough, cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods! As the rubble was falling, was there something that made you feel happy?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">What?! *cough*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Take your time and see if you can remember what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Um... Let's see... Just as I was about to escape the courtroom... rubble started falling! I thought I was done for...! And then... Oh, I remember! Just then... Apollo came and rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's when Apollo got hurt...</thought> It looks like we were able to make Ms. Woods recall something after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll just input this new information and make an update. Now, let's continue with Junie's true testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So when I find an unexpected emotion, I should touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! And then you select the unexpected emotion from the mood markers. If we can find the reason for the discord in her voice... Then we should be able to draw new testimony out!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I tried to run, but I was too slow.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Before I could get away, the bomb went off.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I was so startled I tripped! Then rubble started falling on me.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">I thought I was done for...</line>
<line speaker="Woods">But then Apollo came and rescued me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can sense some discord in Junie's voice when I listen to her testimony. There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere! When you find an unexpected emotion... touch "Pinpoint" <thought>L</thought>... and then select the unexpected emotion from the four mood markers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were happy when Mr. Justice rescued you, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Yes... I was happy and relieved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But was there also something you felt sad about at the same time?</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Sad?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The reason I ask is... when you were describing how you were rescued, we sense a little sadness, too.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">......Oh! I think it was probably because of Bum Rap Rhiny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Bum Rap Rhiny? <thought>Well, what do you know? Something new!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">That's right. I... I brought my stuffed animal, Bum Rap Rhiny, to watch the trial with me. Bum Rap Rhiny and Phony Phanty are brothers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't tell me those things are part of some kind of "collectible" craze...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woods">I had Bum Rap Rhiny with me while I was watching the trial... But it wasn't until Apollo saved me that I realized I'd lost him as I was running away... My poor Rhiny! A victim of that terrible bomb!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I don't sense any discord in Junie's voice anymore! I think we managed to draw out all of her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Oh, I know! You can see what he looks like in this poster! This little guy is Bum Rap Rhiny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Say, that tail looks mighty familiar... Aha! It's all starting to make sense now!</thought> Your Honor! The defendant has just made a very important new statement! I assert that the existence of this "Bump Rap Rhiny" negates the prosecution's evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, it might've taken a little longer than ten minutes... but it looks like I'm taking you out after all, Payne.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't follow, Mr. Wright. Perhaps you could clarify your assertion for us. Which of the prosecution's pieces of evidence does the existence of Bum Rap Rhiny negate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm having a look, but I fail to understand what I'm supposed to be seeing.</line>
<line speaker="Payne">The defendant's testimony negates the prosecution's claims about this evidence! ...Um, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you asking me for?! If your next question is "Am I going to get a penalty?" the answer is "Yes."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk... But I actually wasn't going to ask that question... Guess I'd better rethink this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods, I know this trial has been very hard for you. But you can relax now. You are, without a doubt, innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! What wild assertion are you making now?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My "wild assertion" is simply this: the two stuffed animals were mixed up. The tail the defendant's fingerprints were found on wasn't that of Phony Phanty. It was the tail of her gallery companion, Bum Rap Rhiny!</line>
<line speaker="Payne">WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it! You did it, Mr. Wright! You turned it right around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too early to celebrate, Athena. We still have a long road of refuting ahead of us!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh. *ahem* Right, Mr. Wright. But I just know we'll win this thing for Junie! We'll crush anyone who even doubts her innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's get Ms. Woods that not guilty verdict together, you and me! <thought>And reclaim the legendary title of "Ace Attorney"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it clearly contradicts the statement... er, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't see any particular contradictions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whoops! I got it wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's a penalty for you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think you'd better start over from scratch, Mr. Wright. I just get the feeling that's the wrong evidence AND the wrong statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you're right. I think the last statement is the one we'd better concentrate on.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I think the Stuffed Animal Bomb is the evidence we need to look at!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. The last statement and the Stuffed Animal Bomb, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... And what exactly about the testimony is inconsistent with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ I apologize, Your Honor. May I please try again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, by all means! But I'm afraid I will have to penalize you first, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ouch. <thought>Guess I should've seen that one coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I agree there's definitely something off about this statement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Wonder if I presented the wrong piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet that's it! Why don't you take another look through the Court Record? There must be something in there that contradicts the statement: "I saw that the bomb's timer was counting down."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... I'm sorry, Mr. Wright... but the only thing I find "odd" here is your objection.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't go so well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just don't understand it. I was sure that the correct evidence to present was this Stuffed Animal Bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. I guess I presented it at the wrong statement.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet that's it! Why don't we take a good look at the other statements? There must be a statement in the testimony that contradicts the Stuffed Animal Bomb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Woods, you probably aren't aware of this yourself... but there is a contradiction between your testimony and your emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Woods">Huh? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we view your emotions alongside your testimony, we find the unexpected emotion-- <thought>Wait a minute... there really isn't anything strange here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but I think maybe we made a mistake, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I think maybe you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's take another look! There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I still have so much more to get out of him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I declare this cross-examination over!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to hear further argument in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>B-But... Your Honor...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This concludes the trial of Ms. Juniper Woods!</line>
</xml>