
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reminiscence</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is this incredibly overpowering sweet scent...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It smells like flowers.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uncle Badd! Is this it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Isn't that Detective Badd and Kay over there?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like she managed to escape the bailiff.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">No... That's not quite it...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Aww, too bad. But it's so pretty!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I think... you're still a bit too young to be wearing that. But since you found it... I guess I can let you keep it.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Thanks! I'll treasure it, always!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Those two seem to get along rather well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">Oh, here... I've got something else for you...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yay! Thank you, Uncle Badd! ...Earlier, I ate one of these with Gummy.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Gummy...? Oh, you mean Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy is... *sniffle* He was trying to be nice to me because I was gonna get in trouble... ...and then he got in trouble because he lied to protect me... Gummy... *hiccup*... I know he didn't kill Daddy...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Don't cry... Faraday would be sad if he saw you crying...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I-I'm not crying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! it's the mister from before and the lady, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you think it would be a good idea to go home for the time being?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're not involved in the investigation, so it's for the best if you do.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... Actually, I'm Uncle Badd's assistant! So I'm related to the investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that so, Detective Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What!? You were just scolding us like kids to not mess up the crime scene... ...and now you let this child run free!? Why!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...People are free to investigate things outside of the actual crime scene. Yew also had a few things she wanted to look into... Got a problem with that...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Rrrrnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't have a problem with that, but I am curious as to what Ms. Yew is looking into.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Uncle Badd! I'm gonna go look somewhere else now, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Alright... I'm counting on you...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, that's right! Hey, mister!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I know Gummy really isn't the bad guy... I mean it... So please... find the real bad guy, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............ <thought>I won't forgive whoever did this. But in the absence of the perfect piece of testimony and evidence... ...there is no one else who could be the true culprit other than Detective Gumshoe.</thought> ...Hm? She wandered off while I was pondering...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is this... smell that has permeated the air!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It's sweet and flowery. Although, at this strength, I'm likely to suffocate from it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I can't conduct an investigation under these circumstances! We need to open a window and air this room out! I demand that you open a window right now! Hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, one of the windows is already open.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........I can see that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I wonder... Is it just a coincidence that one of the windows in this room is already open, too...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That expensive painting is ill-suited to be hanging on the wall of this room.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder if a guard detail should be placed on it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, a desperate, low-paid detective might make off with it someday. You never know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She may be thinking about hiring a guard... ...but it's obvious she isn't factoring in that guard's salary whatsoever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>One of the windows in this lobby is open as well... The air-conditioner is working just fine in this room, so why did they open it, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This decorative plant's leaves are shinier than the ones on the plant in Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's probably because it's next to the windows where it's easier to photosynthesize.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You may right. Plus, the curtains are always drawn in Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The caretakers of this courthouse don't think enough about the plants, do they?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's because they're the courthouse's caretakers, not a bunch of botanists.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What an incredibly strong-scented herbal tea.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I fear that more than being relaxing, this scent may make one a bit heady instead.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yew put in a special request for that.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No wonder she's so violent, if she's been drinking this stuff the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Neither woman should be allowed to comment on this particular topic. Ever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can see down into the courthouse courtyard from here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is that mess supposed to be!? It's like an optical illusion...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it's supposed to be postmodern in design.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">More like "thoughtlessness in design".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't disagree there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It may not look like much, but I find that ordinary tables like this one are very useful.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I think it's time they bought a new one. I wonder if they will replace this table if I hit it enough with my whip?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A much too heavy-handed method if I ever saw one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This television is the same model as the one in Defendant Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Looks like the two rooms are basically the same in terms of layout and supplies.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. <thought>Hmm... The two rooms are basically the same, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">All that's left to investigate is Defendant Lobby No. 1. If there is anything left to be found, we'll find it there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Perhaps I should head over to Lobby No. 1 and see what I turn up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This bench is covered with ants. The janitor is going to have a tough time with this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that they're coming in through the open window up there. <thought>Ants are unusual creatures. We can learn so much from their diligence and zeal.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This vending machine is stocked with a variety of base food products. Yet, despite their banality, they're priced extraordinarily high.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have no interest in anything that is unrelated to the case, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hold on, I wouldn't dismiss it yet. Clues are often found in the most surprising of places. No matter how insignificant it may seem, we should give all things due consideration.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose... In that case, Miles Edgeworth... ...you will buy me one of those ham sandwiches! For evidence's sake, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I believe that preserving the crime scene takes precedence, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth, prepare me some change.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what if I refuse?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, aren't we stingy? I'm shocked that you're unwilling to part with a few coins!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Think what you will. Besides, we cam't go around changing the state of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph, you don't have to treat me like a child! I already knew that, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Oh? Then why did you bother asking for change in the first place?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't believe it! This judge has it all wrong. The star of the courtroom isn't him; it's me, Franziska von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As long as she doesn't turn evil, I suppose I can live with "just another megalomaniac".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That extinguisher looks like it would be good at extinguishing any bad memories... With a solid smack across the back of a person's head.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you saying you have memories you'd like erased at your tender age?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I am perfect. Therefore, I don't have anything I want to erase from my mind. I was talking about you, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................I have no intention of revisiting the past.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? That's too bad. Well, if you ever want my help erasing memories...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'll be sure to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You must be tired, Franziska. Care to take a short break on that sofa?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Surely you jest! Me? Sit on that tiny, dirty, disgusting thing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>But that detective said he could sleep "all 25 hours of the day" on this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if the killer used these plastic bags in a flash of inspiration?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">With THAT detective? I somehow doubt he's that quick-witted.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that this crime was thought out in advance...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">With THAT detective? I somehow doubt he's capable of making such a complex plan.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... When will you learn to take responsibility for your statements?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It seems that detective has more brains than he looks in some regards.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think so? Because, to me, in order to pull off a crime of this magnitude... Let's just say that I doubt he has enough mental prowess to be successful at such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah, don't think that kind of subjective commentary is going to prove anything. If you have a theory, then prove it to me with evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. That has been my intention all along.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Was this table here all along?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, clearly, it's out of place. When you take the sofa into consideration, that table is much too tall!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I get the impression the two are not meant to be used as a set, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! I-I knew that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* It seems she's lost her calm sense of judgement in her eagerness to defeat me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose it's impossible to enter or exit through these windows thanks to these bars.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Actually, that's not true. I bet a person of small stature could slip in. Franziska, would you care to help me test my theory?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unnnrgh! <thought>Drat. I must remember to be more tactful around the vertically challenged!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this was the bag I was to receive with the evidence for today's trial in it...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Aha! I have it! The killer hid himself inside this bag and that's how he snuck into this courthouse!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspect that was arrested is hardly the type of man to carry a bag of this kind. Besides which, I doubt there is enough space inside this bag for him to hide in.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ooh... Just shut up!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">What is it, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... Nothing in particular, however...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...! "Nngh," he says!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahaha! You did it again! What IS that supposed to be? Your mating call!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is everything I do humorous to this woman?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Look, Edgeworth, I'm incredibly busy right now. I've got a mountain of things to figure out and check up on. If you want to talk, you're just going to have to wait until later, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph. I'll just continue with my investigation, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That is one tiny TV.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe was rather shocked at this, and said it is "huge" compared to his own.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah, anything you compare with something he owns will always seem grandiose.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Speaking of grandiose, I'd say that ego of yours could use a little deflating.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Lab Technician! I want to know what you found!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Oh! I've found some fingerprints that I can't show to any kids.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Whose fingerprints are they?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I think they're the victim's!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what kind of prints are they?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">The kind that Detective Badd told me not to show you kids!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>Argh! That only makes me all the more curious!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, sorry, mister. I'm a little busy right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Doing what...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Um... Well, I'm looking for something. Uncle Badd told me to, so that's what I'm going to do.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Let's go. I don't want to interfere with the girl, lest Detective Badd get angry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, agreed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears I won't be drinking out of this until it's been repaired.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you want a drink of water, just find a tap. It's all the same.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, actually, the water from this is apparently something special. There was a man here who was practically bathing in it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............ I know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, then obviously we are both thinking the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose we'll just have to wait then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have no interest in that perfume, or in that woman. Here we are, trying to be serious, and all she does is break out into laughter. It's borderline rude!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Franziska seems to hold some ill-will towards Ms. Yew. Although... ...between whipping people all the time, and laughing when people are being serious... ...I'm not sure which one I find more annoying.</thought> Aaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You were thinking something bad about me just now, weren't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I take that back. Ms. Yew is slightly less annoying due to the lack of physical pain.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, what exactly was Kay searching for?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Nothing that concerns you, boy...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? And I suppose it has something to do with Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It does, because she's Faraday's daughter... Anyway... Hurry up and get to the point... I don't have time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It sounds like he'd rather be left alone...</thought> I have something I'd like to confirm with you once again.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I... don't have anything to say to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. be that as it may, we still have questions that we need answers to. Now then, first of all, what is the overpowering smell that is permeating this room? Upon entering this room... I thought I was going to suffocate!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It's that ultra-strong perfume Yew wears... She spilled some of it... I was... having a bad time of it myself. I didn't think twice and opened the window... but that smell's still here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Perfume, huh... <thought>So the sweet scent in the air... is perfume.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, it's giving off quite a stench. I bet it's some cheap, no-name brand.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...She said... it's a famous brand from overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............ It's a knock-off. Yes, definitely a knock-off.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...No disrespect, but... she forced one of those bottles on me. ...Here, little girl. You can have it...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. I was born for a much more expensive and refined perfume! However, seeing as how you just happen to have a spare, I suppose I'll take it. Miles Edgeworth! You will hold on to this bottle without fail!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Arnngh. <thought>Why can't she ever be honest about her wants...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So now we have the perfume Ms. Yew wears... Just fantastic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Is that all you wanted to talk about? If so, I'm going back to investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I still have a few other things I wish to inquire about.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Tch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you were in this room the entire recess?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Like I said... ...I made a call to the precinct to get that big lug down here. But other than that... I was waiting for the recess to end in here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">At least your story is consistent.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Earlier, you started that you were in this lobby with Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah, I ran into her in the hallway... She said she wanted to talk to me about something, so we came in here...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, what you're saying is that until Detective Gumshoe's arrival... ...you and Ms. Yew were in two different locations?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Hmm... Guess I am...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Speaking of that lawyer... She seems to have a great dislike for you.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Oof...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Let's see... Ms. Yew is the sister of the victim of the KG-8 Incident. And, as I recall, Detective Badd was the lead detective on the case.</thought> I wonder if the reason for her distain isn't simply because you failed to guard Cece... ...but because you were the lead detective on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">! ...You knew...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I also know that today's trial involving the Cohdopian Embassy staff member... ...is being referred to as the second KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Detective. I believe it's time you were honest with me... ...and tole me the truth behind your relationship with Ms. Yew and Mr. Faraday... ...and the KG-8 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................If you already know that much... I guess it'd be alright to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, I'd like to ask you a few questions about the KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It's not exactly a happy story... Other than the people who were directly involved... ...you two will be the first to hear what I'm about to tell... The honest truth behind the KG-8 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Faraday, Yew, and I... As you already know, we three were involved with the KG-8 Incident. Faraday and I, we were originally on the trail of a smuggling ring.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean the smuggling case involving one of the Amano Group's secretaries...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph, that trial was just a front!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A façade...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... But the case became tainted! All because the witness who was going to testify... ...about the Amano Group's ties to the smuggling ring, Cece Yew, was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, what became of the secretary who was arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...His name... was Colin Devorae... To be honest... the guy didn't know a thing about the smuggling ring... But... he confessed to knowing about it anyway... Devorae was probably being intimidated by the big boss man... Just another scapegoat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The "boss man", of the Amano Group...? He can't seriously mean Mr. Ernest Amano... ...That can't be right. It's probably just Detective Badd's personal hypothesis. What is he trying to do, suspecting Mr. Amano of being involved with smuggling...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose it would've been quite difficult to secure an acquittal after he confessed. But the man who killed Cece Yew, Manny Coachen, was a completely different person. But since he's already been acquitted once of her murder... Mr. Faraday, how could you have let him go!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If I remember correctly... ...I heard that Mr. Faraday had an important piece of evidence stolen from him.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........That wasn't Faraday's fault. It was mine... I wasn't vigilant enough. Faraday, Cece... I was supposed to protect them both...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ms. Yew did mention that as well... About how Detective Badd was supposed to guard her sister...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">But... even I, who was supposed to protect them... ...I fell into their trap...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What kind of a trap...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph... The holes in this jacket are a testament to that trap.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Y-You mean... you were fired upon!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Y-You were shot at that many times in one gunfight...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........No. Only about half of these... are from that case... But... the reason I continue to wear this jacket is to remind myself... ...of the lessons I learned... from the KG-8 Incident...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I couldn't protect Cece Yew... and the suspect was found not guilty. We had hit a brick wall... as far as the law was concerned... And that's when she came to the courtroom... the victim's sister... ...That's when I first met Calisto Yew...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About when you first met Ms. Yew... It was on the day the verdict of the KG-8 Incident was handed down, was it not?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yes... Faraday and I... We apologized to her from the bottom of our hearts... It was all we could do... But... "Just saying you're sorry won't bring my sister back!" she said... ...and then she gave me a hard slap across the face...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well... She certainly had a lot of self-control to stop at just a slap. If it was me... not even a hundred lashes would've been punishment enough!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I suppose not... Yew said it herself... that she never wanted to see either of us ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But after that, you've seen her many times over, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah. Faraday and I... Even after the KG-8 Incident had come to a close... ...we continued to hunt down the smuggling ring, and got involved in a variety of cases. But... it was no use... We cracked so many different cases... ...but the result was always the same. We couldn't find the real mastermind behind the ring.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is the ring... really that big...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">It was in the pursuit of the ring... that we met Yew once again... ...It was during another trial... related to the smuggling ring... Faraday was the prosecutor... and I, as the lead detective... ...took to the witness stand. Yew... She appeared out of the blue as the defense attorney...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Her client was related to the smuggling ring, and she was defending them...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... Yew... was pursuing the ring as best she could as a lawyer. I think she defended Rell this time... for the same reason...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Come to think of it, Ms. Yew did say something to the same effect...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">I... phwwh... have my own agenda. Phwwwh... I'm still on the hunt for leads regarding the KG-8 Incident, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And for that, you have not a single qualm about defending a known killer...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Don't put words in my mouth. I said no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The only was I had to get close to Mr. Rell was to be his lawyer. I had no intention of covering for him, ever. So don't you dare suggest I was going to.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. It doesn't matter what her reason is... helping a criminal is just despicable!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You're so naïve... little girl. I could've stolen this lollypop from you, that's how naïve you are!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">H-How dare you insult the daughter of a Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Just like us, Yew felt that she had hit the limit of what the law could do. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...The law is merely a tool. There is no limit to it, only the skill of the craftsman.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You two... are still too young... But one day, you'll know what I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But enough sidetracking... What matters... is that we met Yew again... in pursuit of the smuggling ring. ...That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim to know much about the Yatagarasu... Would you care to share what you know with me?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... What you two should be looking for right now... ...is proof... of murderous intent towards Faraday and Rell...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I agree, which is exactly why I am asking you about the Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The KG-8 Incident and this "second" KG-8 Incident... Both of these cases are tied to the smuggling ring... ...and in both of these cases, the witness who was to testify about the ring was murdered. However, there is one point in which they differ. And that is the presence or absence of the Great Thief Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Rell claimed to be the Yatagarasu, however, in the middle of the trial... ...he suddenly declared Mr. Faraday to be the real Yatagarasu. Then, during the recess, they were both killed. Don't you find that to be the least bit odd?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Stop beating around the bush and just spit it out already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that there must be some reason that... ...the two men suspected of being the Yatagarasu were both killed at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...A reason... huh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And so, in order to catch Mr. Faraday's and Mr. Rell's cold-blooded killer... ...I feel that I need to learn as much as I can about the Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........If it will help you solve this case... Then I'll tell you! I'll tell you the reason why we've never caught the Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What was that sudden outburst for!? You almost made me whip you by accident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghooh! <thought>It still "accidentally" whipped me anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">There are three main reasons why the Yatagarasu will always be one step ahead! First! The Yatagarasu always knows the exact location of the target object. Second! The Yatagarasu always knows exactly how to disarm the security system. Third! The Yatagarasu doesn't leave a single shred of evidence behind, ever!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. So those are the Yatagarasu's special traits.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Sounds like an incredibly elusive thief.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The Yatagarasu... ...has never been caught on tape... never tries to draw anyone's attention... ...and would never do something... as low-brow as commit murder...! That's how I knew... that Rell wasn't the real Yatagarasu right away.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But you can't use that sort of logic on its own to prove that he wasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... Listen, little girl. I'm not done talking yet...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Gnrrk!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What's different about this time... was that evidence related to the smuggling ring... ...was sent to the police... And the sender was none other than the one who infiltrated the Cohdopian Embassy... ...the Yatagarasu...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Yatagarasu sent the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Until now, the Yatagarasu... ...would always publicize any corrupt dealings through the mass media... ...but not this time... The evidence this time... ...was something only Faraday and I... and a select few others knew about...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, how can you be so sure that it was the Yatagarasu who sent it?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">That's easy... A special card that only the Yatagarasu uses was attached... That's how I can be so sure...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And just what sort of card is it?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Here, take a look at this article... Whenever the Yatagarasu wants to publicize something... ...a white card is sent along with the stolen information... But... when we questioned Rell about what was sent along with the white card... ...Rell had no idea what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ahh, and that's how Detective Badd knew that Mr. Rell was a phony...</thought> Thank you very much. I have a much better understanding of the Yatagarasu now.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So what was your relation to Mr. Faraday? You even seem to know Kay fairly well.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I met him... when he was a rookie prosecutor... Known him ever since. And Kay... I've known her... since the day she was born. ...Faraday and I... we cracked quite a few cases together...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, but you two seem to have made no progress at all in the Yatagarasu case.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Did we touch a nerve?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. I only have one thing... to say to you. ...No one knew more about the Yatagarasu... ...than me and Faraday... That's why... I was called upon to testify in today's trial... ...To prove... that Rell was not the real Yatagarasu... Which I would've done... if he hadn't turned around and accused Faraday... After the accusation, I was asked to testify, but this time... ...to prove or disprove the accusation... But I guess I won't be doing that either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense that there's more to that statement than meets the eye. Perhaps a bit more digging into the Yatagarasu is what's necessary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">That snack has quite a history attached to it for me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Our recently departed Faraday loved the Courthouse Special Swiss Rolls... ...and his daughter, Kay, also seems to have taken a liking to them. The three of us used to sit around eating them together...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I guess that's why we wanted to get Detective Gumshoe into them, too. But look at the sticky situation that came out of that.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Actually, the biggest reasons for the sticky situation we find ourselves in are... ...the absolute poverty of that scruff-face, and his unnecessary soft-heartedness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Unforgiving as always, I see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">I'm not a big fan... of perfume...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, exactly what kind of relationship do you have with Ms. Yew?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Like I told you... ...we're connected through the victim of KG-8 Incident, her younger sister. I was supposed to protect her... ...but I failed in my duties; just another pathetic detective... After that... Coachen's not guilty verdict... ...sparked our pursuit of the case. Me as detective, and she as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In other words, they're still working together...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Excuse me, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">His Honor would like to transfer the evidence from today's trial over to you. So if you could please head over to the courtroom, it'd be much appreciated, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood. I'll be there shortly. Detective Badd... What does the law mean to you?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.............................. Finding the answer to that question is the only reason I'm still alive...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I became a prosecutor to find the answer to that question myself... ...and to play a part in ensuring that all criminals everywhere are found guilty!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh, it's you, Mr. Edgeworth. ...*sigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears that His Honor is still a bit dispirited...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">For the first time today, I experienced what it's like to stand at the witness stand... *sigh* I now have a greater appreciation... for just how hard it is to give testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, there's no reason for you to be all depressed about it, Your Honor. As a judge, no one expects you to think about anything other than the verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, there is no need to further depress His Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But I'm not trying to, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ehh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, I've come to collect the evidence that was to be transferred to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. The evidence...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Y-You! Yes, can I help you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'd like to collect the evidence now, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Your Honor... Do you think you can stay focused long enough to at least do your job!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, I'm sorry! And I would, except that the defense attorney has yet to arrive.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">She is busy with the investigation, so let's keep this brief, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. In that case, please confirm that all the pieces of evidence are present. Furthermore, the evidence that was used in the murders of Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell... ...are also included, so please go ahead and use them in your investigation into their case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood, Your Honor. <thought>The pieces of evidence that were used in the murder of those two men... This could be a very good chance for me to find new leads regarding their case. And maybe even something that will finally lead me to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I've placed all of the evidence over at the Prosecutor's Bench for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Thank you very much. I will go and confirm that they are all accounted for.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like your debut trial fizzled out thanks to it being declared a mistrial. Too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But now you can take your time bidding the evidence they transferred to you goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... It's much too early to shelve the pieces that were given to me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? How do you figure?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two of the pieces were used to kill Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell. Naturally, having all of them makes it easier for me to examine them more thoroughly.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Argh! Y-Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me... Your forgot about that fact, didn't you, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't have to answer the characteristically foolish question of a foolish fool! Now, hurry up and check the evidence already!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Trust me, I will. In due time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*siiiiiigh*... *siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that the Judge is still a bit dispirited.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......... Stop that! You're being so depressing!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Muhwooooohh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You should listen to her, Your Honor, before things go from bad to worse. <thought>...Although, it can't really get much worse for him, other than to be whipped by her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Evidence that Ms. Yew prepared is just sitting here on this table.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You know you can't just walk off with it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I do. <thought>Ms. Yew must've been caught off-guard by her client's sudden accusation... I wonder how she would've defended Mr. Rell in that case if he was still alive?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">You're in the way, boy. Move.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You look terribly busy, however, I was wondering what you're busy with.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Just looking for something. It's got nothing to do with you...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is with your terrible attitude...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I guess I'm out of luck. I really should get back to what I need to do, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The curtains are shut tight.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The color of those curtains is rather gloomy. For a place where people's lives are in the balance... ...they could've chosen to hang something a little more cheery, you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know, however, I think the designer had more things to think about than the lobbies.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Well, as a Von Karma... ...I would afford any location related to the law extra attention to detail.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A bit obsessive, aren't we...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So the knife that was used to kill turns out to be the Yatagarasu's Key... It must've taken great skill to combine both aspects into one object so well... Make no mistake, I think this is the key to the whole case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying... ...that this key is the golden key to unlocking the secrets behind this case!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No lame puns in my presence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Perhaps that was just a bit too corny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So this is the evidence related to today's Cohdopian Embassy trial from Mr. Faraday's bag.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You mean the evidence bag that was on the table in Lobby No. 2, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Finally, we can now take a look at the evidence itself, and not just data about them. Let's be sure to thoroughly examine them while we have the time.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Agreed. I want to take a good look at all of the evidence from the Embassy murder, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Because! I still don't fully understand what today's trial was about!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnwaaah! Don't point your crop at me just because you don't know something!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And don't you try to order me around just because Papa chose you today!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I see someone is still sore about not being picked by Mr. von Karma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...It's all so... real too see the knife up close.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, we have the knife, the gun, an envelope... and what's this organizer doing here...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! That's right! I completely forgot to tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About what, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They found Mr. Faraday's personal organizer inside that evidence bag of this. Detective Badd requested it be passed along to you. He said it would help the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd said that...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...What a strange stroke of luck.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, never look a gift horse in the mouth. We might as well flip through it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This gun... It was originally used to kill the Cohdopian Embassy staff member. When the crime was reported... ...the responding police found Mr. Rell still holding it, which led to his immediate arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And then... this gun took the original shooter's life. How ironic.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. <thought>There doesn't seem to be anything else we can learn from this piece of evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the knife that was used to kill Mr. Faraday...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Who would've thought that such a beautiful piece of art... ...could be used for such a cruel act!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And it's never crossed your mind that you use your riding crop for the wrong purpose?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday's organizer... It appears he was in the habit of using it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like he wrote his strategy for getting Mr. Rell convicted down in here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that Mr. Faraday honestly believed that Mr. Rell was the killer in the case. And it would also appear that he had proof that Mr. Rell was not the Yatagarasu. Hmm... And he apparently also had a very definitive piece of evidence. Yes, I believe that Mr. Faraday was well prepared... ...to discredit any claim Mr. Rell may have made about being the real Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And he had a way to prove that Mr. Rell was the guilty party in the Embassy murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This organizer is a clue straight from Mr. Faraday. I'll have to take my time and give it a thorough read later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Look, there's a picture stuck between these pages here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears to be... a key.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And a rather ornate one at that. Just look at the design on the handle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The craftsmanship is superb... Could this be the "Yatagarasu's Key" Mr. Faraday mentioned in his organizer?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The Yatagarasu's... Key?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd said something earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What's different about this time... was that evidence related to the smuggling ring... ...was sent to the police... And the sender was none other than the one who infiltrated the Cohdopian Embassy... ...the Yatagarasu...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Yatagarasu sent the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Until now, the Yatagarasu... ...would always publicize any corrupt dealings through the mass media... ...but not this time... The evidence this time... ...was something only Faraday and I... and a select few others knew about...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Faraday must've been trying to keep this secret key safe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As the prosecutor on both the Yatagarasu and smuggling ring cases, that's to be expected.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday's organizer... It appears he was in the habit of using it. <thought>This organizer is a clue straight from Mr. Faraday. I'll have to take my time and give it a thorough read later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I took a quick look through these documents before the trial started.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, I wasn't even afforded the opportunity to skim it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...I suppose I should explain it to you then.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, you should. Perfectly and in its entirely, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On the night of September 8th, an Embassy staff member was killed in front of the Embassy. The staff member died of shock due to being shot in the heart. Mack Rell was brought in that night as a suspect and thoroughly questioned... ...because the murder weapon was found on him, for which he was arrested on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A simpleton of a man, that's what he was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Perhaps he was, for the weapon wasn't the only incriminating evidence we had. Mr. Rell was caught in the act on film by a security camera.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He was an even bigger simpleton than I'd thought. I can't believe he didn't notice a security camera!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Cohdopian Embassy's security system is supposedly very well designed. He may have simply not been aware that there was a camera in the area.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So... have you seen the contents of the video for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the surveillance video the security camera took... ...was played during the trial by Mr. Faraday. You can clearly identify Mr. Rell on it. Even the sound of the gunshot was crystal clear.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So the footage included sound, huh? I don't think I'd ever want to see the moment of someone's death in real life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Me neither.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, that's odd...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday didn't mention anything about a knife in his organizer.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...That certainly is odd.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The weapon that was used to kill the Cohdopian Embassy staff member was the gun. But if that's the case... ...then where did the knife that was used to murder Mr. Faraday come from!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Isn't it obvious? It was brought into the courthouse by Mr. Rell! That's the only logical conclusion, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, because it's not that easy to smuggle a weapon like that in here. Every person who enters the courthouse doors is checked thoroughly for contraband. Furthermore, the suspect was handcuffed... ...making it possible for him to bring a knife as large as this inside.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In that case... how do YOU suppose this knife ended up inside the courthouse!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>I need to think carefully here... There is nothing related to the knife written anywhere in Mr. Faraday's organizer... However... it is a fact that this knife... ...came from Mr. Faraday's evidence bag. ...Conversely, there is one item listed in Mr. Faraday's organizer... ...that no one has claimed to have seen today! So in order to solve this mystery... ...I believe I will need to take another good look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... Can I take the fact that you have yet to answer me... ...to mean that you don't have an answer for me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, I do know the answer, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What!? Then what is it!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">One of the pieces of evidence we've been holding has been hiding a secret of its own. And it was through this piece of evidence that the knife was brought into the courthouse!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't see how that answers my question at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Every piece of evidence has some secretive aspect about it...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? Then I demand to know what the secret is to this one!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnrk! <thought>Alright, maybe there is no secret to this one... I need to think carefully here... There is nothing related to the knife written anywhere in Mr. Faraday's organizer... However... it is a fact that this knife... ...came from Mr. Faraday's evidence bag. ...Conversely, there is one item listed in Mr. Faraday's organizer... ...that no one has claimed to have seen today! So in order to solve this mystery... ...I believe I will need to take another good look at the evidence.</thought> The knife was definitely brought in somehow...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This "Yatagarasu's Key" Mr. Faraday mentions in his organizer... This is how the knife was brought into the courthouse.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're not making any sense, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You just need to look a bit closer, Franziska, to see what I mean. Don't the color and ornamentation of the key's handle remind you of anything?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................They do remind me of the knife...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good. Both the Yatagarasu's Key in this photo and the murderous knife... ...have this very unique design on their handles. Furthermore, even though Mr. Faraday mentions the Yatagarasu's Key... ...the only object we found at the crime scene was the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Y-You don't seriously mean to say...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that you've finally caught up. And yes, I DO mean to say that these two pieces are, in fact, one and the same!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But that's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if that is what you believe, we should still investigate this possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Nnrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, let us examine this knife in a little more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the weapon that was used to kill Mr. Faraday... The handle and the blade itself both have beautiful designs worked into them.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Look! There's even a flower-shaped design in this gold section here. If this hadn't been used as a tool for murder, I'd want it for myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...She seems to be drawn to the embellishments. Too bad this isn't mine to give.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I can't believe it turned into a key! To think there was such a trick to this thing...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the weapon used to kill Mr. Faraday is actually the key the Yatagarasu stole... <thought>This piece of information is more critical than anything we've learned up until now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Frankly, I'm shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday only mentioned the key aspect of this piece of evidence in his organizer. It's possible that even he had no idea the key was hiding a knife blade inside.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But if that's true... ...then only someone who knew about the key to knife trick... ...could have killed Mr. Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even among law enforcement, this key was top secret... We're looking for someone who knew even more about the key than even Mr. Faraday... Meaning that the only person it could be is the one who sent the key in the first place... The Great Thief Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! .........Then maybe Mr. Rell really was the Yatagarasu... ...and he was the one who killed Mr. Faraday. Isn't that one possible scenario?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, not really... Especially since Mr. Faraday... ...was absolutely convinced that Mr. Rell was not the Yatagarasu. Besides, as Detective Badd said earlier...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">But... when we questioned Rell about what was sent along with the white card... ...Rell had no idea what it was.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see... Alright then, I guess the person who knows the trick behind this key... ...is someone else, and that person is the real Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems that this key is truly the key to solving this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The trigger -- such a small piece of metal, and yet, it can take a whole life away... I wished that I never had to lay eyes on another gun again...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What's this? Are you afraid of guns, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's not that at all! It's just...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well! I am not afraid of these things in the least!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Where does she find the gall to say things like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe and Kay pooled their money and bought the Swiss rolls together.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose they both just wanted a snack that much.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay was probably saving this one for her father to cheer him up. Not that I blame her. I know the feeling myself.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................Hmph. Well, so long as we're here, once we solve this case, let's buy some and bring them home.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sure, why not? <thought>Ah, and I mustn't forget to give this to Detective Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's odd. We're short one piece of evidence. And the piece that's missing is the surveillance video that was played in court!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The surveillance video...? How could a piece of evidence just disappear? Where did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The video showing the moment in which Mr. Rell committed the murder... Where could it have gone indeed!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you done with your inspection of the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'm finished. However, Your Honor, I am missing a single piece of prosecutorial evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Your Honor... Were you derelict in your duties?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!? No! I dare not lick my duties! What do you take me for!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, Your Honor. The most important piece of evidence in today's trial... ...the surveillance video, is not amongst the evidence you laid out for me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But I brought Mr. Faraday's whole bag with me from the crime scene. Maybe the tape is still somewhere at the crime scene...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>There's something wrong here... Something about this missing piece of evidence... It would appear that for me to find the answers I seek... ...I will have to pay another visit to the scene of the crime, Defendant Lobby No. 2!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? That's Detective Badd... but who is he with...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I've never seen that officer before.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">So, did you find it...?</line>
<line speaker="???">No, not yet, and I've looked everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I see... Well, then... please continue with the search...</line>
<line speaker="???">Understood. I'll continue the search. Heh. So you're the one running this show. Prosecutors like you shouldn't even be allowed at crime scenes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How dare you!? Just who do you think you are...!? What was that all about, and who was that man just now!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Whoever he was, I've never seen a more impudent officer in my life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does he even know that we're standing right here behind him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........I know you're standing right behind me. What do you want... kids?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like you were paying attention after all.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Of course I was. ...I have eyes... in the back of my head...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, so that mirror isn't for vanity's sake... It's for him to keep an eye out on who or what is behind him at all times.</thought> So tell me, Detective Badd, who was that rude man just now?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The guy came here... from the Republic of Zheng Fa to study... He's Agent Lang. He's trying everything he can... to revive the lost honor of his family... He's traveling the world... to study different philosophies of detainment... from scratch...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By visiting various police departments around the world? He has a lot of dedication.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">He's still just a rookie cop... but I sense a strong grudge of some sort from him. The guy's... more useful than Gumshoe. .........Even if he is rude.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, he sure has a lot of guts to come to this country and give prosecutors a hard time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I agree, however, I can think of one young lady that statement also applies to.</thought> Anyway, what was that agent looking for, Detective Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Earlier, that little girl was poking around in Lobby No. 1 as well.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Like I said before, it's got nothing to do with the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I highly doubt that it has nothing to do with me.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Fine, if this is the game I must play, then I will take this opportunity... ...to draw out what he's been hiding and what happened in this room straight from him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like Detective Badd is searching for something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. I'm curious as to what it could be myself. <thought>Maybe I should just ask him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Earlier, you were in Lobby No. 1, and now you're here in Lobby No. 2... You are quite the busy man, Detective Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">"Multiple returns to a crime scene brings about success"... That's what we detectives say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... In that case, you wouldn't mind if I asked about what happened again, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I don't have anything left to say to you, boy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! "Boy"!? You'll see. I WILL draw my answer from you, one way or another!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Would it kill you to help us even a tiny bit in our investigation!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I gave Faraday's notebook... ...to the Judge earlier... ...That's help enough... don't you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please, we are asking you for just a bit more of your cooperation.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Don't push me, kid...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to ask once again about what happened around here at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I refuse to answer. ...Any more investigating you do... would be a waste of time. Besides... how am I supposed to answer questions about things I don't know about?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Things you don't know about? But aren't you supposed to know everything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He should... <thought>Wait, is it possible...? Maybe he doesn't know about the trick behind that piece of evidence! I should try showing it to him. It may prove to be the key to getting some answers from Detective Badd!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd. Did you know of the existence of the item in this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Hmph. Of course I did. It's my job to know everything related to the Yatagarasu case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, let me ask you something. Did you know that the knife that killed Mr. Faraday and this Yatagarasu's Key... ...are one and the same?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What!? ...That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like he didn't know after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The piece of evidence which we call the Yatagarasu's Key... ...is actually a well-camouflaged knife.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday was planning to use this Yatagarasu's Key... ...to prove that Mr. Rell was not the real Yatagarasu. Isn't that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, Mr. Faraday had no idea that it was, in fact, a knife.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah, I have to admit, neither one of us knew that fact. And if neither of us knew, then no one in law enforcement knew either. How did we miss something as big as this!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I noticed that since a little while ago, you appear to be searching for something. I presume that this key is what you were searching for.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...! ...Yeah, that's right...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why were you searching for it?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Because... I promised Faraday... I promised that I'd protect that key with my life... But after he was killed, the key disappeared from Faraday's evidence bag... Who would've thought... that the key... is what took Faraday's life...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd. So that we may find the truth, please, testify for me once more.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Alright. But it doesn't matter how many times I tell you about what happened... Nothing'll change...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd. I ask that you please testify once more... ...about what happened in Lobby No. 2 and what you experienced in Lobby No. 1.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...My answer is still the same. And this... is the last time I'm going to do this...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's fine, because I only need this one last time to clear everything up. <thought>And find the truth behind this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I was in Lobby No. 1... talking with Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It sounds like the exact same story he told us before...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. However, I feel that we have yet to draw out all the information that we can.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I was in Lobby No. 1... talking with Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did Ms. Yew choose Lobby No. 1?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Answer me!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Who knows. She just said that she had something she wanted to talk me about... ...and we walked into Lobby No. 1 together... That's all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So his answer remains the same as before, I see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...We were talking about... some trivial things.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was hoping you could expand on what exactly you were discussing with Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......... Trivial stuff... It was nothing important.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's for me to decide.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Alright, I suppose that's for him to decide. Moving on then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I heard the gunshot... right before the trial was about to reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Until you heard the gunshot, did you notice anything else that was out of the ordinary?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I didn't hear any other strange sounds... until that gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If the gunshot Detective Badd heard was really the one from the murder... ...that would give that other piece of evidence an entirely different meaning...!</thought> I ask that you please amend your testimony with that statement just now!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Sure...</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"...I didn't hear any other strange sounds... until that gunshot..."</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I didn't hear any other strange sounds... until that gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd... You honestly don't remember hearing anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is it possible you were so involved in your conversation that you missed something?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I've been a detective for a long time, and even if I were involved in something... ...I've got quite the habit of keeping tabs on everything that goes around me... If there had been some other strange sound, you can be sure I would've heard it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I suppose with this detective, that's probably very likely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">So, the gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Badd">When we heard it, Yew and I immediately dashed out into the hallway together!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why did the two of you dash out into the hallway straight away?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Because we clearly heard the sound of a gunshot... And we knew it came from somewhere nearby...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And how did you know that it was a gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... In my line of work, you hear enough of them to know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose it's only natural for a detective to know what a real gunshot sounds like...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">But given the circumstances... ...the only person I could think of whose life would've been in danger was Faraday. That's why I ran out into the hallway right away and headed for where he was...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I saw Gumshoe goofing around there... and then we all ran in to Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe was there in the hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why didn't you attest to that earlier!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">When I saw Gumshoe, it was after I had heard the gunshot. Having seen him then didn't change the fact that he still could've done the deed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It sounds exactly like what Detective Badd told us before, however...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Is there something in particular we should be asking the detective about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There just might be... <thought>No one knew that the knife is actually the Yatagarasu's Key... Reflecting on that... ...perhaps there are other things that we know now, but Detective Badd doesn't yet. Yes, that should be my angle of attack!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd... Does this balloon fragment remind you of anything?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It's the same color... as the one Kay was holding...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? So you knew about that girl's balloon?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah... I was sitting with her up in the gallery... During the recess... just before we split up, I filled that balloon up for her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, as you may have already surmised, this piece did indeed come from Kay's balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">So? What about the balloon...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if you might remember hearing this balloon pop at some point?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What are you getting at?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... This fragment was found in the hallway, right in front of Lobby No. 2. Furthermore... ...it was the sound of this balloon popping that the judge mistook as a gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Oh? So the sound that the judge heard... was not actually a gunshot, huh...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">On top of that, His Honor said that he heard the balloon pop... ...about 20 minutes before the trial was to reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, which means that His Honor heard the balloon pop in the hallway... ...when you were in Lobby No. 1, Detective Badd! And if you were in Lobby No. 1 at that time... ...you were close enough that you should have heard the balloon popping as well!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...So?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? Don't give me a "So?"!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We just proved that there is a flaw in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The cracking of the truth... is louder than the sound of your sweet naïveté cracking... And since you kids don't seem to know, let me fill you in on something! Did you ever stop to think why the doors and walls of this place seem so rugged? That's because they were designed to keep secrets from being leaked!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What... is that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The doors and walls are super thick... the windowpanes are double-layered... To top it all off... even the curtains are made of a special sound-absorbing material.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Then, you mean...!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Since I was shut up inside Lobby No. 1, there was no way I could've heard that sound!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">N-No!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>I knew that's what he was going to say!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then that means that scruff-face's testimony is completely useless! If the rooms are soundproof, then of course he wouldn't hear any sign of a struggle!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That's also why it's only natural... ...that I didn't hear the balloon popping... ...Now do you get it... kids?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles! I thought WE were supposed to be the ones finding flaws in his logic... ...not the other way around!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The... other way around...? <thought>It's not possible to hear the sound of a balloon popping if one were in Lobby No. 1. However, if we examine this situation in reverse... ...a person standing in the hallway should not be able to hear the real gunshot either. And yet, Detective Gumshoe claims to have heard it while he was standing in the hallway.</thought> Detective Badd... If that is the case, how exactly did you hear the gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What do you mean, "how"...? I just did...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... It would appear... ...that you have yet to realize the contradiction in your own words.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Oh? How so...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the rooms are as soundproof as you say they are... ...then how did the sound of the gunshot enter your ears?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...! I see what you mean... I guess I'm more out of it... from Faraday's murder than I had thought...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Which means what, exactly, Miles!? In the end, what does it all boil down to!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It boils down to this: There must be a reason... ...as to how detectives Badd and Gumshoe heard a gunshot they theoretically couldn't have.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looked like we need to examine the state of the crime scene again, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! <thought>The state of the crime scene...? Wait! Can it be...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It's that ultra-strong perfume Yew wears... She spilled <thought>Dissipating the smell - A window in Lobby No. 1 was opened to allow the perfume Ms. Yew spilled to dissipate.</thought> some of it...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uwaah! And way too noisy <thought>Very loud television - Lobby No. 2's television. It looks like it was set to an incredibly high volume.</thought>!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The surveillance video...? How could a piece of evidence just disappear <thought>Missing evidence - Where did the surveillance tape from Mr. Faraday's bag disappear off to?</thought>? Where did it go?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's simply not possible for the killer to have escaped through barred windows... ...and yet, the fragrance of the perfume managed to escape from Defendant Lobby No. 1. Of course! Incorporeal things ccan move freely through these open, barred windows (Open windows - The criminal couldn't have made it through, but what about incorporeal things?</thought>!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now then, what else besides a smell can go both in and out of an open, barred window...? The answer... is sound! So, no matter how careful the killer was, if the windows were open, the jig would be up. And since the windows in both Defendant Lobby No. 1 and the hallway were open... ...that explains how the sound of a gunshot could be heard (Gunshot could be heard - Windows were open, so the gunshot could be heard, but where did it originate from?</thought> in both locations!)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The missing piece of evidence is a video... ...that shows the moment in which Mr. Rell killed the Embassy staff member. The sound of the gunshot left quite an impression on me when it was played during the trial. The video should have been returned to Mr. Faraday's evidence bag for the recess... ...and brought back here. If it disappeared after that time... ...then it's possible that the tape is still here in this room. Eureka! The evidence that the missing evidence created for me... ...is the gunshot sound that no one should've been able to hear in the first place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles... What have you been thinking about? Stop wasting time thinking, and let's start looking again!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not a waste of time to think, for I have figured out where we should look.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And where would that be!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe we should examine... the television!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">The TV...? ...Well, you kids have fun... Go ahead and examine whatever you like...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We've already checked everything in Lobby No. 2, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not quite. There is still one more thing we have yet to thoroughly inspect. Because Detective Badd gave Detective Gumshoe an angry lecture for touching it... ...no one has examined it since.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you talking about the television?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Precisely. And that is where I believe the last piece of evidence awaits us!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So the evidence that we thought to be missing was actually at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This surveillance video was placed into the video player by someone.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Perhaps it was Mr. Faraday. Maybe he wanted to check something on it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That is very plausible. However, if that were the case, it raises an interesting question.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure you remember what happened. When that detective went to turn the television on, it made an incredibly loud sound. If you had simply wanted to check something, would you have set the volume so high?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you can understand that much, the rest is easy.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, don't keep me waiting... Explain this crime scene's biggest contradiction to me, now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. With pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Go ahead and do your investigating. Just don't mess up the crime scene... ...You hear me, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The window is wide open.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The scent of flowers is being blown in from the outside. I think it softens the heavy air in here somewhat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Windows in both Lobby No. 1 and No. 2 were opened.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Maybe they were trying to air out the room, just like in Lobby No. 1. Or maybe they sought to ease some of the tension through some fresh air.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">With Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell in the same room, I imagine the latter to be the case. <thought>But was there really a need to open the window just for that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just as with the spilled perfume in Lobby No. 1... ...If the windows were open, that piece of evidence's sound would also dissipate out...! Now, to show what the gunshot detectives Badd and Gumshoe heard was... ...and through where they heard it from!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Earlier, when Detective Gumshoe touched this... ...it made a most terrible racket.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You mean when Scruffy turned the television on, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, come to think of it... ...I don't think Detective Gumshoe actually touched the television at all. Furthermore... ...it seemed more like when a video feed suddenly stops. ...At least, it did to me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder why that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a video player... And there seems to be a video tape inside.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like it. The tape must have stopped on its own when it reached the end.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This tape... Could it not be the missing surveillance tape?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...! I suppose, but...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, would it be alright with you if I verified the contents of this video?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Sure... Knock yourself out...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Alright, then let's rewind this and see what we have.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">If I remember correctly... the footage of Rell killing the Embassy staff member... ...should be at about... the 30 minute mark... from the start of the tape...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood. This should be about right. Now then, let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Nngh... This is...! This is the footage of Mr. Rell shooting the Embassy staff member...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I knew it... The missing piece of evidence, the surveillance video, was here all along!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...This sound... What's the meaning of this...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears that Detective Badd has figured out the true source of the gunshot he heard!</thought> With this, I think we can figure out the trick behind this double murder!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! Do you mean that you've figured it all out, then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. All I have to do now... ...is show what the gunshot detectives Badd and Gumshoe heard was... ...and through where they heard it from!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Nngh! Fine! In that case, show me what you've deduced!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now, to show what the gunshot detectives Badd and Gumshoe heard was... ...and through where they heard it from! I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So someone left this video on play the whole time, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose so... Other than the killing, there's hardly a sound on the rest of tape.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then why did the television make that loud noise when Scruffy got near it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's probably because the tape had run out and stopped its playback.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...It's not just bad luck, that detective has the worst timing in the world, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone purposefully left this video on play... The question is "why"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence... will clear away the last remaining contradiction in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles... I believe that piece... ...may actually be proof of a different last of sorts. It proves that today... will be your last day as a prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>It appears that I've made a mistake... However, I know that the last riddle and its answer lies somewhere within this room! I need to calm down and think it through once more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I think there should be one.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do not anger me with a foolish game of semantics, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnuurk! <thought>Nngh... I'd better look a bit more carefully through my evidence once again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the door and windows to the crime scene, namely, this room that we're in, were closed... ...the killer could've used the gun and no one would've been the wiser.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's true. This courthouse does seem to be well-designed for such a thing, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, what happened in reality was... ...Detective Gumshoe, Detective Badd, and Ms. Yew... All three of them heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, the windows in Lobby No. 1, No. 2, and the hallway were open... ...so naturally the people in those locations could hear it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but then, why would the criminal open the window in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...To allow the gunshot to be heard... I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct. That's the only logical conclusion we can draw from this.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But why was that necessary in the first place? I want a real answer, Miles! I demand satisfaction!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. I believe that the killer wanted to manipulate our perception of a certain fact. <thought>What was it that the killer wanted to manipulate our perception of?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer wanted to manipulate our thoughts regarding the real crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So you're suggesting... that the killing really took place in a different location?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In that case, would you care to explain to me how someone... ...was able to carry two adult, male bodies all the way here without anyone noticing? Furthermore, given that the scruff-face was in the hallway the entire time... ...I believe you've just created your own contradiction, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, well... <thought>I suppose a mistake is a mistake... However, the whole reason why the killer left the window open... Was it not to mislead us on that particular fact...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer wanted to manipulate our thoughts regarding the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles... We already know that the murder weapons... ...are genuine! The forensic scientists have already proven that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>It would appear that I've made a miscalculation... However, the whole reason why the killer left the window open... Was it not to mislead us on that particular fact...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The killer wanted to fabricate the time of death to their precise wishes! And they used the gunshot in the surveillance video to do so!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! So that's why the tape was left running!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You mean... the gunshoe I heard... was from this video!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. Which means that the murders really occurred at an earlier time than we thought!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It must have been during the recess, but before Detective Gumshoe was on guard duty. Someone who has no alibi for that time period... ...and planned this crime out in advance... That person is the real killer...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Ms. Yew is asking for you. She's in the courtroom. She says that she's identified the murderer, but that she wants to clarify something...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like Ms. Yew is still investigating something.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood. Please tell her that I will be right over.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I'll come along. I want to hear what she has to say...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that the time has come... to uncover the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay... What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, hello, mister! I'm still investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the object you're looking for has already...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Kay... don't mind him... Please continue with your investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">OK! You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective Badd, haven't we already found what you were looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">If it means I can keep her in the dark just a little longer... any little task will do.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? You're more sympathetic than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I've been waiting for you, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've also been waiting... for the moment in which we can finally lay this case to rest.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh! Ahahahahaha! "The moment in which we can finally lay this case to rest"? Wasn't that when we placed Detective Gumshoe under arrest...? Phwwwwwh. I think we've more than solved this case already... Phwwwwhhkkk... Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We'll see. It all depends on whether or not your logic holds.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, I see we even have a viewer in the gallery! And... why, even Mr. Badd is here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A... A viewer in the gallery!? I'm hardly just a by-stander!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I have a duty... to see this case through to the end... No matter how it turns out...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Oh? Is that right? Anyway... I thought you might like to hear what I've slaved away to find out. I've taken statements on every single person's movements... ...during the time when our suspect was in the hallway. I also confirmed that there is no possible route of escape from Lobby No. 2. Therefore, the killer must without a doubt be... Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that's all you have?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yeah, that's all there is to my conclusion, and this case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but I beg to differ. In a trial, there is always time for a rebuttal, and we ARE standing in a court of law. It'd be more than appropriate to follow the rules of court, in this case, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Ahahahahahaha! How absolutely like a rookie to think such a thing. But alright... I'll play along and give you a proper testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>If my logic is correct, then I've already won. All I have to do now is to prove it... by showing who the real killer is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Everyone, sans the suspect, has an alibi for when the gun went off.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwh... Now that you have your testimony. I expect a good rebuttal, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph, but of course. <thought>There is no need to confront her logic head on right now. I should instead focus on drawing out any trump cards she has up her sleeve.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Everyone, sans the suspect, has an alibi for when the gun went off.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspect...? But I thought that Detective Gumshoe's alibi has already been proven.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahaha! Are you joking, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I assure you, this is no joke.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Look, I know you heard from the judge earlier... ...that the detective was in the hallway with Mr. Faraday's daughter eating a Swiss roll.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">But see, that was 20 minutes before the real gunshot went off, right? And the problem is, there's no one else who can corroborate what he did since the snacking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>I see she's done her research well. Which means that I should focus on drawing whatever trump cards she's withholding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Furthermore, the areas around the crime scene have all been thoroughly investigated, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether they have been thoroughly investigated or not is for me to decide.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwh... Ahahahahaha! The scrunched eyebrows and lines on your forehead are back! Anyway, even if you believe it hasn't been exhaustive, the crime scene, Lobby No. 2... ...has no way out other than the hallway Detective Gumshoe was standing in. And because he claimed to be there, that makes him the only possible suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But isn't it also possible that someone escaped through a window and into the garden?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwwwwwwwh! Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! That's the first place everyone looked, silly! The police aren't a bunch of lazy bums! They looked into every possibility, you know. Isn't it right, Mr. Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Yeah. There wasn't a scrap of evidence... to suggest someone used... one of the windows... There also weren't... any footprints or anything... in the courtyard garden...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose they really did check everything that could be relevant to the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">I also confirmed that there is no possible escape route from Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you absolutely positive that there are no possible routes of escape?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Of course I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why are you so certain?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">This is a courthouse, the place where criminals are brought to be judged. If there were an escape route, I'm sure every criminal would be using it to escape. It's just common sense! Phwwh,,, Ahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I suggest you use a bit more of it in the future!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Which leaves us with one unshakable conclusion, that Detective Gumshoe is the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You may think it's unshakable, but to me, there are still too many unanswered questions. For example, who was it that placed the gun in Mr. Faraday's hand?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahaha! But you're the only one still wondering that! Detective Gumshoe probably had no idea which hand Mr. Faraday used to write with. Even if you know someone, it doesn't mean you'll know which hand they write with, right? I mean... I certainly don't care about that sort of thing. Ahahahah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... <thought>I'm not about to let her get a rise out of me with such a flippant statement. Besides with, my first order of business is to press more information out of her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There is no need to confront her logic head on right now. I should instead focus on drawing out any trump cards she has up her sleeve.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I suppose we've really reached the end now. I already have my trump card ready. All that remains is to play it! But before I do... ...I think I should inquire into a little something about her argument.</thought> You said earlier that you confirmed the alibis of every person other than the suspect. However, I don't recall either Franziska or myself speaking with you about the subject.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ah, but there were witnesses. For you, there is your mentor who gave you an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">As for the little missy... Phwwwwh... She came to the courthouse during the recess... ...phwwh... and was stopped by a security guard... at the door to the hallway... She gave him quite a whipping for that, or so I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...! I'm the daughter of Manfred von Karma. And I will not be forcibly stopped by a guard, or a bailiff, or anyone else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wait, so basically, the only reason Franziska bothered to show up today... ...was because she found out that I was to be the replacement prosecutor...?</thought> By the way, Ms. Yew... ...what about everyone's alibis before Detective Gumshoe was assigned to guard duty?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">What about them?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you looked into what people were doing during that span of time?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwh... What kind of idiot do you take me for? It doesn't matter when the killer went into Lobby No. 2. From the time we heard the gunshot... ...to the time Mr. Badd and I arrived on the scene as we dashed from Lobby No. 1... ...the only person who could've committed the crime was Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, let's talk about when you and Detective Badd heard that gunshot, shall we? I suppose that if we go by your logic, then Detective Gumshoe is the only one. However, what if the crime had occurred... ...at an entirely different time than when that gunshot you heard went off? What then?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That gunshot was a trap meant to manipulate our perception of when the crime took place</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Sadly, your explanation is very lacking, Edgeworth. The gunshot we heard in Lobby No. 1... Care to explain how that could've been fabricated?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was fabricared through this, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwh! Ahahahahaha! It's a joke, I get it! Your deadpan delivery is great! Of course, if you're actually serious... well, that's less of a laughing matter.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argh! <thought>Alright, so I was mistaken! The gunshot they heard in Lobby No. 1... What was it that they mixed it up with...? All I have to do is present that piece of evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">That tape...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it's exactly what you think it is. This is the surveillance tape of Mr. Rell the prosecution presented in today's trial. This was found loaded in the video player in Lobby No. 2... ...that was connected to the large television that had its volume turned all the way up.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You can't honestly mean that the sound we heard was the gunshot in the video...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but I do. Which leads me to my next point. The murders occurred much earlier than when anyone heard the "gunshot"!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That's the only thing I can think of, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">After committing double homicide... ...the killer took the surveillance video out from Mr. Faraday's evidence bag... ...turned the television's volume all the way up, and left the video to play. If played from the beginning, it would take 30 minutes for the gunshot sound to come on. And since we now know that this method of time manipulation is possible... ...it opens up the possibility that the killer is someone other than Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Sounds from a television doesn't amount to much here. But of course, Mr. Prosecutor Edgeworth, and Little Miss von Karma... ...already knew that much from the very beginning, right?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">O-Of course we knew! Didn't we, Miles!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, of course. We know about the soundproof quality of this courthouse's rooms. <thought>Of course, I'm not about to admit we had no idea until only a little while ago...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">That's right, and if the rooms are soundproof, then we should not have been able to hear it. And yet, we heard the gunshot clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........And?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">A-And!? Th-That's it, end of story!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... But it's not.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How should I explain why she was able to hear a gunshot from a soundproof room?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The door to Lobby No. 1 was open!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Phww......... Ahahahahahahahaha! You... You really... phwwwh... love to make me laugh, don't you? Sorry, but the door to Lobby No. 1 were Mr. Badd and I were was closed tight. Isn't that right, Mr. Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? <thought>I was mistaken...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... you have sullied the name of Von Karma. That logic just now... ...was unforgively bad!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>I need to carefully think this through once more... There is a reason as to why they were able to hear it so clearly. Now then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There was a hole in the wall!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, I don't think that such a hole exists. Because if it did, I think the two of them would've noticed the crime going on next door!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahaha! That's exactly right! Besides, if there's a hole to be found, it's probably in your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... I was just thinking the exact same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>Whose side are you on, Franziska!? I need to carefully think this through once more... There is a reason as to why they were able to hear it so clearly. Now then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is, actually, one common point between Lobby No. 1 and Lobby No. 2. And it is that despite the fact that both rooms have air conditioners installed... ...a window was open in each!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, we know that the window in Lobby No. 2 was opened by the killer... ...however, a window in Lobby No. 1 was also opened.</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahaha! It's probably just coincidence that they were both open at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. It was no mere coincidence, I assure you. <thought>Why was the window opened in Lobby No. 1? The answer is that a certain person did something to cause the window to be opened. And the person who triggered that action... that person is the real guilty party! The real killer in this double murder is...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This person... is the real culprit behind this case!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What sort of nonsense...!? Be serious here, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>That must not be the correct person... I must carefully think this through once more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Calisto Yew! I hereby formally indict you of the murder of Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Y... You indict... me!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you serious, Miles!? Why do you think she is the killer...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't understand her motive just yet... ...but of course I'm serious. Because she is the only one who could've done it. Well, Ms. Yew. Do you still feel like laughing now?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha, hahaha... Of course I do, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! <thought>My argument must not be tight enough yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Although, I never thought things would spiral into this. But I'll have you know I'm enjoying this dance... quite a bit! I guess this means it's time for my own rebuttal now, right?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You argue that the window was opened, however, do you have any proof it was I who did that?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It sounds like the exact same story he told us before...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is were it really starts. I mustn't let my guard down for even a second, or the truth will blow away. Now is the time to put the patented Von Karma "perfect proof" to the test!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">You argue that the window was opened, however, do you have any proof it was I who did that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Evidence? All I'd need to do is have some prints analyzed and we'd know straight way!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Hmph... Be my guest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She sounds as though she has the room to maneuver... which means... even if we were able to lift prints, they'd only show that it was someone else, but... ...why that someone else was forced to open the window... hmph, that's simple logic. Why don't I try presenting that piece of evidence? I have nothing to lose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwh, what's wrong? The scrunched eyebrows, lines on your forehead, they're all back! More importantly, are you going to be OK not running a fingerprint analysis?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'll be fine.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh! Well, in that case, I'll just continue with my testimony, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Furthermore, do you have proof that the tape was used in committing the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I thought I just proved that it was.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Sure you proved that the tape was there at scene of the crime... ...however, that doesn't prove that it was actually used in said crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Unfortunately for you, Ms. Yew... ...the fact that the tape was there at the crime scene is in itself very important.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">How so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... By the very existence of that tape at the crime scene... ...it proves the possibility that the "when" of the crime could have been fabricated. And that possibility alone renders all alibis and witness reports irrelevant. Basically, it means that we will need to re-examine every person's movements again!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether the tape was used in the crime or not, that we can re-evaluate afterwards.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Knnrh...! So in conclusion, you're admitting that you can't prove that it was at this point!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Frankly, I'm shocked at you for going around accusing people of murder like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even is you're shocked, that is of no concern to me. I do things my own way.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see that you're not laughing, for a change.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Because I'm shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Again, you being shocked is of no concern to me. Let us continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! Alright, but let me say just one thing. You shouldn't go around accusing people.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Especially with logic as full of holes as yours!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Full of holes...? Hmph... Well, I suppose it might be.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh? Admitting to your faults now, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"At this point in time", is what I meant to say.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Should I take that to mean that you're just a sore loser? Ahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No matter how full of holes my logic may be right now, if I plug them one at a time... ...I will ultimately make my way to the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">What a paradox! Take care to not fall into one of those holes before you fill it up. Ahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, you remember, don't you? About why a window in Lobby No. 1 was opened?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, of course I do. <thought>And that's how I'll attack! I'll present the reason why the window had to be opened!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure you've seen this before, haven't you, Ms. Yew?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! Edgeworth! I never knew you were into wearing that kind of perfume! It's not exactly what I'D recommend for boys, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? Th-This isn't mine!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's right, it's mine. And I received it from Detective Badd, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, you can pretend all you like, but we know at least this much for sure! That this bottle of perfume was given to Detective Badd by you!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Kphwwh... Ahahahahahaha! Because it gets really strong, really fast! So? What about the perfume?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">While you were in Lobby No. 1, you made a big show of spilling some of this perfume. That's according to Detective Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwwwh. Oh, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You also knew that if you spilled it, he would naturally move to open a window!</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Come now, I've already told you that's all just a big coincidence. After we opened the window in Lobby No. 1, I just left it open, you know? So maybe it was just dumb luck that we heard the gunshot through the window!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The timing of when you were going to spill the perfume is something you could control. And the most important fact about this case is when people were made to hear the shot. Furthermore, it would've been pointless if you didn't have an alibi for yourself at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, you were the one who called Detective Badd into Lobby No. 1... ...when you saw him bring Detective Gumshoe into the hallway. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All of today's premeditated events could only have been thought up by you, Ms. Yew!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Grr! ...Ha, hahaha. You accuse me of murder on the fact that I spilled a little perfume. Well, allow me to say this much. I couldn't have killed Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you care to testify as to why?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Hahahahaha... Look, I've had a lot of fun today, really. ...But I grow weary of this game of cat and mouse. Let's make this the last testimony, and wrap up this absurd case once and for all!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Accusing someone of murder over a spilled bottle of perfume is a bit over the top.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, her testimony... is flawless.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, but no matter what sort of trick she may try to pull, she won't escape me! <thought>And if I'm lacking in information, I'll just draw it out of her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Accusing someone of murder over a spilled bottle of perfume is a bit over the top.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think I already explained the significance of that earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You only confirmed that I did spilled some perfume. But that's all. That you would accuse me of murder based on a simple spill... Don't you dare complain when I sue you for defamation of character! Ahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do as you like... but as for me, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You "believe"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe... that you are the true culprit in this case!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwwwwh... My, you're enthusiastic! Of course, I should've guessed...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">But I suppose forgery of evidence is to be expected of a disciple of Von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I formally request that you desist in your attack against my mentor!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes! Or we'll sue you for defamation!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! All I'm doing is telling the truth. Well, maybe more like spreading gossip. Although, your adamant denials are, shall we say, just adding fuel to the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How dare you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Say such a thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Calm down, little girl...! Don't let her... get to you...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Nnrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Aww, wy did you have to ruin my fun...? Phwwwwwwwh... Well, shall I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">In any case, it simply could not have been me who killed Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why exactly could you not have killed him?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! I was just about to testify to that. ...You're such an impatient man... Phwwwh... I'm not really into that, you know, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! Your preferences have no bearing on what is at hand!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahaha! Feeling a little uncomfortable, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrrrrrnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ms. Yew! You will desist in this tomfoolery and return to your testimony! And Miles! If you're going to lose your coolm then I won't show you any mercy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ahem... Sorry. Ms. Yew, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................Sure. As I was saying, I couldn't have possibly killed Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">After all, I don't even know where the knife that was used to kill him came from.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At this rate, she will inevitable escape! But if she really was the one who killed Mr. Faraday... ...then she must have known about the existence of the knife!</thought> I'm sorry, Ms. Yew. Maybe you weren't aware... ...however, the knife that was used to kill Mr. Faraday was taken from his evidence bag.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! Miles... What do you think you're doing...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I'm drawing the truth out of her, that's what I'm doing.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Huh? But I don't recall a knife being presented at the trial earlier today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I suppose that's because the evidence was something Mr. Faraday had yet to use.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Ahahahahahahahaha! Ah! So that's what you're trying to do! Look, why don't you cut it out with the lies. I've already figured you out. There was no knife inside Mr. Faraday's evidence bag. The only evidence he had yet to present was the key to the Yatagarasu had sent. And unless a key can magically turn into a knife, you really don't have a leg to stand on.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwwwh... Did you really think you could trap me? Come now, be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh, I never intended to do such a thing. It was all a misunderstanding on my part. In any case, I wonder if you might append what you just said to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Sure... Why not? II'll even say it as many times as you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"There was a key in his evidence bag, but you can't kill anyone with a simple key!"</line>
<line speaker="Yew">There was a key in his evidence bag, but you can't kill anyone with a simple key!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, I would just like to confirm something with you one more time.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh? About what's going to happen to Detective Gumshoe after this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I don't need to ask you about that... because he isn't the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Looks like the number of wrinkles on your forehead have increased yet again! Ahahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........That issue aside, Ms. Yew, I'd like to ask you about what was inside the bag. You are sure it was the Yatagarasu's Key, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwh... Yes, I'm sure. Which is why I'm completely baffled as to where that knife could've come from.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I think I've just spotted the road to a perfect victory.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, her testimony... is flawless.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, but no matter what sort of trick she may try to pull, she won't escape me! <thought>And if I'm lacking in information, I'll just draw it out of her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Finally, it would appear that you have revealed your true identity, Ms. Yew...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles... her final statement...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I know. All I have to do now is to present the evidence! <thought>But what is this... ominous feeling that I can't shake...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, I wonder if you might take a look at this photo for me? This is a picture of the key the Yatagarasu sent to the police. However, while it may look like a key at first glance... ...it, in fact, has the secret ability to transform into a knife. Which means that what was inside Mr. Faraday's bag... ...was both the Yatagarasu's Key and the murderous knife! You knew that the key was inside Mr. Faraday's bag, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, with the Yatagarasu's Key alone, it's more than possible to kill Mr. Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Gnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you understand now? Just knowing of the existence of the Yatagarasu's Key...</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">I still haven't had a good look at it. Showing it to me from that far away -- you could be lying for all I know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You would, even now, still feign ignorance!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! I'm not feigning anything! Buy we can't have you accusing me of a crime with false evidence, now can we? I mean, Mr. von Karma... I've heard some very... interesting rumors about him.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arngh! Are you mocking my papa!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you dare sully the good name of my mentor! Now take a good look! This piece of evidence is more than real.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Wow, who knew there was such a trick to this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you satisfied now? But, of course, you knew from the very beginning, didn't you? You knew that the knife and the Yatagarasu's Key are one and the same! Otherwise, someone like you, who isn't a member of law enforcement, and who... ...would never have been privy to this trick, would have never known about it to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Furthermore, the something that the Yatagarasu sent to the police... How did you have knowledge as to what it was?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Phwwwwwh... Actually, I heard it from Mr. Faraday. Just before he dragged Mr. Rell off, he told me. Oh, that's right! I almost forgot! He also told me about the key turning into a knife at that time. But he didn't tell me about how the key actually transforms...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What you are saying is simply not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">! Oh? And why not?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because Mr. Faraday himself didn't know about the hidden knife within the key! For within these pages, he mentions nothing about a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwh... I'm not sure he would've written everything in his organizer, you know? Wouldn't something of this importance be better left to oral communication?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, that is also impossible. Because Detective Badd didn't know about the knife aspect either!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Tchhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What would've been highly classified information, even with the police force... ...and is something that even the lead detective on the case didn't know... Why would Mr. Faraday have felt the need to share such information with the opposition?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Kphwwwh... Ahahahahaha! Yeah, I guess he wouldn't have much of a reason to... Phwwwwh. Looks like I gave a pretty lame excuse, huh... Phwwwwh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How can you laugh at a time like this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">She probably just realized the flaw in her logic, and is actually in a panic over it. But that's not something we need to concern ourselves with.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm......... I suppose you're right. Ms. Yew. I'd like to state that I also know how you know the real nature of the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Heh heh heh... Ahahahahahahahahahahahaha! Do you know? Well why don't you put your money where your mouth is and show me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, I will, and I'll wipe that smile off your face by the time we're through! <thought>This is it, the moment of truth. The secret behind the Yatagarasu's Key... Only one person would have had knowledge of it from the get-go!</thought> Who would know from the start that the Yatagarasu's Key could change into a knife?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would be this person!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh. Phwwwwwwwwwwwh. Ahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha ...Ahem. Thanks for the best laugh I've had all day. Now are we ready to call it a day yet?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait a second! <thought>I was mistaken...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is only one person who would've known about the dual nature of the key.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Ahah. And that is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And that is, the person who sent the Yatagarasu's Key to the police...! That is to say, the Yatagarasu herself!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Are you saying that this lawyer is the Great Thief Yatagarasu...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew. You used Mr. Rell to lure Mr. Faraday into a trap, didn't you? You, who profess to bear a grudge against criminals, why!? Why do something like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">........................Phwwh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Hee... Hee hee hee... hee hee... hee hee....... hee hee hee hee hee! ...Ahah! Ahahaha! Ahahahahaha! Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha......... .........Who would've thought... that you.................. ...a stupid rookie prosecutor... would see through me...? You're sending the biggest chill down my spine right now, Edgeworth! This feeling of thrill... it's even greater than when I sneak into someplace...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yew! ...You...! You killed Faraday...!? Why...? Answer me! Calisto Yew!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Ahah! Calisto Yew... huh... That's not my real name. Becuase my real identity is, yes... the Great Thief Yatagarasu!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Let me tell you something, Edgeworth. Mr. Faraday... was one difficult man to deal with. For you see... he had discovered my true identity. Which is why I had to erase him from the world of law. I made Rell an offer: an acquittal for a little favoe in return. All he had to do was accuse Mr. Faraday of being the Yatagarasu in court. But once we entered the recess, Rell was dragged off by Mr. Faraday... ...which threw my plan into a complete mess. I chased after them, and eavesdropped on them through a crack in the door. That Rell caves to only two things, money and authority, just as all thugs do. I feared my plan was going to be ruined if Mr. Faraday held onto Rell any longer. Plus, if I had let them continue on the way they were, I would've been found out. That's why I had no choice... I had to kill them both!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But didn't you say that you despised criminals!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh. But do I really...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You...! Have you forgotten... about the KG-8 Incident, too...!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What sort of woman would--!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So then, was it your plan to kill Mr. Faraday with the very "evidence" that you sent!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha ha... Well, I had a good idea of what Mr. Faraday was going to do. I anticipated that Mr. Faraday was going to prove that Rell wasn't Yatagarasu... ...by using this Yatagarasu's Key as evidence, and that he would bring it with him. Which is why I thought to use the knife portion. With a weapon as well-disguised as this, no one would be the wiser... Because who in their right mind would think something like this could be a weapon? I casually entered Lobby No. 2 on the pretext that I had to talk with Mr. Faraday. And in order to get in with him, I pretended to be worried about something. He then let me hold the Yatagarasu's Key, just like that. He never noticed that I had changed the key into a knife inside that plastic bag... ...and he didn't have the chance to take note of the knife that took his life.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...! How could you kill him......!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I knew him for a long time, you know? At the very least, I thought to give him a quick and painless death.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But if you killed Mr. Faraday first, there was no need for you to kill Mr. Rell as well!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I believe I mentioned why when we were placing Detective Gumshoe under arrest. Something about "having accidentally created an eye-witness"...? And how that led the killer to think about setting them up as though they'd killed each other.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Then the trick with the surveillance tape...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yes... I hadn't actually planned to use a gun. The risk was too high that I'd be caught. However, that's when I remembered the existence of that surveillance tape. Which is why I had Rell help me set up the crime scene... ...and after all was said and done, I rewarded him for all his hard work with a bullet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You! You're a defense attorney, aren't you!? How could you... How could you betray a client!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahaha! Client? If you want to talk about who was a client of whose first, it was me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I was the client in the murder of the Cohdopian Embassy staff member, Deid Mann!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Y.........! You... ordered a hit job!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha ha ha... You still haven't figured it out, Mr. Badd? I had Deid Mann killed because he was about to give away info about the smuggling ring. Now , who exactly do you think would benefit from such an assassination?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I-It can't be.........! Yew... You're...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">That's right... I'm a member of the smuggling ring.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How could this...!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You don't mean... you're working with Manny Coachen, too, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahahahahaha! Ahah! Maybe, maybe not. Guess you'll never know.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The Yatagarasu claims to be noble, but you're just another cold-blooded murderer!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah! Ahahahahahahaha! That's right, little girl. The Yatagarasu is just another killer!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Be quiet! Yew...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yatagarasu! You can run from the law, but you'll never escape it.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So just humbly accept the judgement of this court!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.................. Ha ha ha... Hey, Edgeworth. Did you know? The Yatagarasu has three legs. Do you know why that is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha ha! No? Well, let me tell you. It means that the Yatagarasu has more than one razor-sharp way to do her work.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You really are too naïve, Edgeworth. You even handed the Yatagarasu's Key right to me without a second thought. Everything may not have gone according to plan, but I'll still gladly take it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! You mean...!? The key was your real target!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">*sigh* ...And even after I gave you such great advice... Didn't I tell you to "always keep a good eye on a criminal"......... ...or you may regret what comes of your negligence!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You two! Get down!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Eek...! Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>My body... I can't move...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Hey mister! To your right!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeeeeeew!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you alright, Franziska!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........! I-I'm perfectly fine, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Her voice is shaking... But it looks like she's unharmed.</thought> Hm...? Where did Kay go?&#160;! That's a gunshot...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Sorry, but it looks like she got away. I called the precinct... They should have a perimeter set up soon...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd! Are you alright!? I heard a gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I'm OK... Just got... another hole in my jacket...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He may say he's fine, but he looks quite shaken...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">But more importantly, boy... I mean, Mr. Edgeworth, Ms. von Karma... ...are you two hurt?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! I... I'm absolutely fine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm also alright... thanks to Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">! Speaking of Kay... where is she?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I don't know. She just sort of... disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmm... I'll go look for her... Oh, and... hey, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yes, sir! Detective Badd, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I'm sorry I doubted you...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry, sir! It's not your fault! I... Well, I lied to you guys too, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I heard about what happened... from Kay... Lying while giving testimony is still unforgivable... ...but in this case... you were protecting Kay and her feelings. Looks like you just might have what it takes to be a real detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Now, don't you ever lose that detective's spirit, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You got it, pops!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"Pops"...? Watched one too many detective dramas recently, have we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Way to single-handedly destroy the cheery atmosphere with one snarky comment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I should get back to the investigation. I swear... I'll catch Yew if it's the last thing I do...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Be careful, Detective Badd, and take care.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Thanks. Well, I'm off... Maybe we'll run into each other again someday.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... So, uh... Thanks a bunch, pal! You're the best! You really did find out the truth behind everything!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... I'm glad we solved everything before you were taken to prison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't believe how much trouble I caused you with my testimony, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah, it was no problem, really! Ha ha ha! I mean, I lied, too, so I didn't help anything! It's really not your fault, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, even if we didn't have His Honor's testimony... ...I think that lawyer would've found another way to get you convicted on her behalf.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... I can't believe I was about to get fired during my first week as a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Well, so long as you're not fired... ...you should work hard, give all that you have, and perform your duties well. ...Oh, and one more thing. Kay left a present for you with me.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She did? Ooh! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What was it that Kay left for me -- the proof of their friendship...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's...! It's a Courthouse Special Swiss Roll! C-Can I really have it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it's a present meant for you, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Thanks a bunch! You have no idea how happy this makes me, pal! I'm gonna eat this right now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sure, go ahead. <thought>The Swiss rolls Detective Gumshoe and Kay bought together... While the one Kay saved never reached her father... ...it would appear that her sentiments have touched the heart of this detective.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He's so happy, it's as though he's having a welcome back celebration of his own.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I was asked by Kay to give it to him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoooop! That was good, pal! I can't believe I got to eat two of these delicious things in one day! It's like I'm in Swiss roll paradise or something! I've gotta thank Kay myself... Hey, wait... Where is she?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">? I'm not sure what this is supposed to be, but are you sure it's OK for me to take it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait, that's not what I meant to give you! Please return it at once!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles... You're really not that bright, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk! <thought>Argh, I made a simple mistake, Franziska...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aww, it's OK. It's the thought that counts, anyway! Hey, speaking of Kay, where'd he go, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He only noticed just now...? Was his mind not present when we discussed her earlier...!?</thought> Detective Badd left to go search for her earlier. Maybe you should go join him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah! You betcha, pal! I'm gonna go help him! Oh! But first...! You know what, pal...? Actually, I guess I shouldn't be so rude to you anymore, huh? I'm gonna stick right by your side from now on, Mr. Edgeworth, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>I sense nothing but a most troublesome relationship from that ominous statement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We should go home too, Miles. We have to hurry and report what has happened to Papa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agreed. Well, I'm afraid we must be going now, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Roger, sir! And don't you worry! I'll investigate the next case we're on real well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll, um... be counting on you. <thought>The scent of trouble is definitely in the air...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus, like a bad dream, my first outing at court came to a disturbing end. A few months later... ...I was finally able to properly stand in court as a prosecutor... ...but the detective in charge of the investigation was, as I dreaded, Detective Gumshoe. After that, he became my direct subordinate... I have tried, but words fail to describe the immeasurable suffering he has caused me. But I suppose that's just how things are. As for the little girl who suddenly disappeared... She's now..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So? Do you remember now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... I remember everything. Kay... It's been a while.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay! You sure grew up a lot!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Of course! But thank goodness! I thought you two had totally forgotten about me!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know, I was really worried about you after all that! Where have you been all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh! Gummy, I didn't know you cared! After my father died, I went to go live with my mother's relatives. They lived really far away, so I wasn't really able to come back here all that much.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, is that what happened...? Well, I'm just glad you're alright!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh! So, does it all make sense now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You betcha it does!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, you know what? I was going through my father's bookshelves recently, and...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, there are still a number of things that don't make sense, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First of all, why did you come all this way to see me? And second... Why are you calling yourself the Yatagarasu? The Yatagarasu is Calisto Yew... the woman who killed your father.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">No, you're wrong. The real Yatagarasu... was my father!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">M-Mr. Faraday was the Yatagarasu...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Like I said, I was going through my father's bookshelf recently... ...and I found a secret diary hidden among his books. "I have no regrets in choosing to walk the path of the Yatagarasu." That was written in his diary, and that's how I know for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........But that's... That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">What's with that look? You don't believe me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It wasn't just the expression on my face, I clearly said it was impossible just now.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Alright, then. How do you explain this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's a way of disarming any security system of the user's choosing...!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup! That's Little Thief! Truth be told, this is the Yatagarasu's greatest secret. And this little gizmo was used by my father!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wooooow! Mr. Faraday wasn't just a great prosecutor, he was really a great thief, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, my father worked really hard to steal the truth! But he was killed... and the Yatagarasu was no more. ...But despite that, the Yatagarasu has been spotted again recently!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone other than you!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Here, Mr. Edgeworth... Take a look at this article.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! The Yatagarasu sent the Embassy... a calling card?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, meaning this person's a fake! I'm almost certain... that Calisto Yew lady is behind this. Because the real Yatagarasu would never send something like a gaudy card out!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But the Yatagarasu did send a white card along with anything to be publicized. <thought>...That's what Detective Badd told me seven years ago, if memory serves.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, as soon as I heard the news, I got all wound up, and I knew I couldn't just let it go. So I searched you out... so that I could obtain the truth behind the Yatagarasu. Because if anyone can help me find it, I figured it's you, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that I have your father's and Ms. Yew's identities backwards?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yes, because the real Yatagarasu is noble to the end! And I want to revive the real, noble Yatagarasu! If I don't... my father will never be able to rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay... you're so honorable! I don't care what anyone else thinks, I'll always be here to cheer you on, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Even if you are honorable, a thief is a thief. And if you are plotting to commit a crime, then I'm afraid I can't be complicit.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Edgeworth... Oonngh... You guys are not making it easy for me! Who am I supposed to support now!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth... What I want from you is not to steal something. What I want is the arrest of that evil woman.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That evil woman... You mean Calisto Yew?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I think it's too hard for me to catch her all by myself. But I thought that since you were able to expose her for who she is, then maybe... Please, Mr. Edgeworth! Won't you help me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. Come to think of it, I do believe I owe you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh...? Owe me for what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">When Ms. Yew made her escape, it was you who saved my life. Furthermore, you helped me with the investigation today. I am not so rude as to leave favors un-repaid.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Th-Then you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... That case has been weighing down my soul ever since that fateful day. Perhaps the time has come to settle things once and for all. If you don't intend to sully your hands in a crime... then I believe I can help you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Mr. Edgeworth! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yay, Mr. Edgeworth, siiiiiiir! Isn't that great, Kay!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah, it sure is, Gummy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Even though he had completely forgotten about her until just now... Arngh... What is with their chummy relationship...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Great Thief Yatagarasu... After all that time, the true identity of the thief sank back into the darkness. Byrne Faraday, Calisto Yew... and Kay Faraday. The phantasmagorically changing identity of the Great Thief Yatagarasu... ...and the Yatagarasu's real goal... It would all come to light the day after I made that promise to Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence stands in contradiction to what you just said, Detective Badd!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...No, it doesn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I can't find a contradiction either, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>Curses! Then I must be mistaken.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Go wash the sleep out of your tired eyes and try again.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I need to look carefully at all the evidence again, and find a contradiction, now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to show the contradiction in your statement... with this.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...And how will you do that? Because I can't see how you can.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Would you care to explain how you plan to do so in a way that I can comprehend?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...If what you're doing right now is thinking up a way to explain it... ...then that means it was simply a guess all along, wasn't it, Miles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argnk! <thought>Sh-She saw right through me! I can't keep this up. I will wind up losing the truth if I continue this tactic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd! That statement... is in clear contradiction with this!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Boy, I don't see a contradiction anywhere. ...Now, if you disrupt the investigation any more... You get the picture?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Yes, sir! <thought>It would appear that I was wrong... Nngh! I must think things through again, but this time, calmly and rationally!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence stands in contradiction to your statement just now!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">There's no contradiction here. Too bad, huh, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arnnnnnnnnnnnngh...! <thought>She took the wind out of my sails with a single sentence! But I must keep my composure. I can't allow her to gain the upper hand...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your statement... ...is nothing before this perfect piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I don't think I'd call that "perfect".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... If you don't try to verify it, how will you know?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... I guess so! Ahahaha! Oh, I just love the way you say that with such confidence! But just as you said, you can only say something is perfect after you've verified it! Now try presenting evidence to me again, but this time, in the correct way, rookie!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Gnrk! <thought>I was a fool to claim that it was perfect!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence reveals the hole in your logic!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh... Phwwwwwwwwh! Ahah! Ahahahahahahahaha! Before you try to prove there are holes in my logic, you should prove something else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........? And that would be?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Whether or not you really are a diciple of Manfred von Karma. With such weak logic, I'm not sure you're cut out to be a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnwooooooohh!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Your investigation has dragged on for long enough.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Go on, get out of here. I've got work to do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! No, I can't be tossed off the case now...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahaha! Looks like you're at the end of your rope. We already have a suspect, so you can spare me the rest of your long-winded speech. Mr. Badd... I leave the rest in your capable hands.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm not done with you yet!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Ahahahahahaha! Maybe not, but I'm done with you. See you around, Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! I can't let her get away, not now...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>