<xml>
<title>Turnabout Samurai</title>
<line speaker="Maya">That rocked! "See you in Hell, Evil Magistrate!!!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! Stop waving that broom around!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, Nick! I didn't know you were here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I'm here! What was that surreal show you were watching?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Nick, you mean, you don't know the Steel Samurai!? He's only the most popular TV hero for young people!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Young...? Like, how young?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... 10 years old?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then what the heck are YOU doing getting all excited!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! I'm only 17! That's seven-"teen." See? I'm a teen! Not like you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Don't talk to me like I'm your grandpa or something. I'm only 24 myself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then watch it with me!  He's really cool! And... it's really popular! When they asked grade school kids what they wanted to be, "Steel Samurai" was no.1!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I really worry about kids these days.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gramps! Well, the Steel Samurai's over. I guess it's time to close up the office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess... Wish we had some clients!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A month has passed since my trial. Mia's murder was the talk of the town for some time... But no one paid any attention to the Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices... How am I going to pay the rent this month?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It'll be okay. I'm sure some big client is just around the corner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">Brrrrring... Brrrrring...</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hello? This is Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-N-Nick!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya? What? It's still early...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-it's the Steel Samurai! The Steel Samurai got arrested!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean the guy on that show?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! They're saying that the Steel Samurai killed a villain!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Umm... Isn't that what he's supposed to do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, on TV!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! I mean, he actually did it! In real life! He skewered a villain with his Samurai Spear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have absolutely no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just come to the office, quick! Please, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's here... watching television.</thought></line>
<line speaker="TV">Now for the morning news. The actor Will Powers was arrested yesterday. Powers plays the lead role in the popular kid's show "The Steel Samurai: Warrior of Neo Olde Tokyo." He was arrested on suspicion of murder. The victim was Jack Hammer, who plays the villain known as the "Evil Magistrate." His body was found still inside the Evil Magistrate costume. The "Samurai Spear" was also found stuck through the body. Police believe this was the murder weapon, and are investigating further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... This has to be a joke.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, no, no! It's a nightmare! The Steel Samurai is over! The world is over!</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">Brrrrring... Brrrrring...</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes... Wright &amp; Co. Law Offices. ... What!? Nick! I-it's the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes... yes, of course! We'll be right there!</line>
<line speaker="Cellular">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go? Go where?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They have the Steel Samurai down in detention!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, I've decided this will be our first case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a horrendous amount of legal books here. Scarier still is the thought that I have to read all of these now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's favorite potted plant. Maya has been watering it so much lately it looks a little... swollen. She's either trying to make it grow... or she's perfecting her water torture technique.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A poster of an old movie that Mia liked. I was thinking I should go see it myself. Then I realized that the poster doesn't actually say the title of the movie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mia's desk. Actually... it's my desk now. Sitting here always makes me feel like a professional.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a nice day outside. The hotel across the way is always full these days. There's the bellboy, happily cleaning the room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What should we do!? How can you just sit there like that!? We have to get down to the detention center and meet the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does she want to investigate this case or just do some sightseeing, I wonder? My money's on sightseeing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">We don't have enough information to make a case yet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just admit it: you don't have a clue what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! We just don't have enough information!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You like showing that off, don't you, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>My poor, poor ego...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, but I don't see how that will help us figure this out...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's wrong, Maya? It's him! In the flesh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Is that guy really him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaddya mean "that guy"? Of course it's him! Will Powers, our client! That's him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, maybe I shouldn't be saying this... But he definitely did it. Murder. At least once. Maybe twice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa whoa whoa! What are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Something wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no! No!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is getting off to a great start.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">I know, I know. You're disappointed, aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">D-disappointed!? Oh, no. Oh no.</line>
<line speaker="Will">No, it's okay. This is the real me. When I got the part of the Steel Samurai, with that mask... I decided I would never show my face in public until the job was over. It's the kids, you know. I didn't want to wreck their dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Will">I guess it didn't matter. So much for dreams. I wonder what they think of the Steel Samurai now. *sniff* Uwaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's a good guy! I mean, he's good!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He didn't do it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Smile for the camera...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He seems frozen in awe of Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you could start by telling us what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes. Of course. It seems like it was only yesterday. Actually, it was only yesterday. The cast had come down to Global Studios for a run-through. We went through a few action sequences at 10:00 that morning. There was a rehearsal scheduled for 5:00 in the afternoon. But when 5:00 came around, and the staff gathered at the studio... The Evil Magistrate was found lying in a crumpled heap near the set. They took off his mask... And discovered that it was Jack Hammer... dead! He had been expertly skewered with the Samurai Spear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "Samurai Spear"...?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes, it's a long spear that I... that the Steel Samurai uses as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe you could explain to me just what "the Steel Samurai" is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! How could you say such a thing? I-I'm sorry, sir, I apologize for my partner! He's new to this, and a bit OUT OF TOUCH with the world.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Who's "new to this"!?</line>
<line speaker="Will">No, it's alright, really. The Steel Samurai is the lead character in a popular kid's show. He walks the streets of Neo Olde Tokyo... Fighting battle after battle against the Evil Magistrate and his minions. Of course, he never really defeats the Evil Magistrate. Although... I guess he did defeat him this time... *sniff* Uwaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see. <thought>Neo Olde Tokyo...? Who comes up with these names!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, where were you on the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Well, that morning I came to studios at 9:00. We worked through some action scenes until noon. Rehearsal was to begin at 5:00, but I was a little tired. So after lunch, I took a nap in my dressing room. When I woke up, it was after 5:00! I was late for the rehearsal! I hurried to the studio... and found everyone looking shocked. They arrested me on the spot, and brought me here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he was sleeping the entire afternoon of the murder? Some action hero!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">What will the kids think? *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, here.</line>
<line speaker="Will">I... I see. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Let me guess... this guy wasn't the top student in improv class.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Will">I-I'm sorry. I'm sure that's very important and all. I just don't see what it has to do with my problem.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think I should probably check out the scene of the murder...</line>
<line speaker="Will">Right... Global Studios. I'll draw you a map.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! Nick! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm willing to bet 10 bucks she asks for autographs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sitting around here won't get us anywhere, that's for sure. The studio! We should go to the studio! I'm sure we could find some clues there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Does she want to investigate this case or just do some sightseeing, I wonder? My money's on sightseeing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! So this is where they make the Steel Samurai show! Awesome! Aren't you excited!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! You there! You want in, you gotta go through me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O-oh... s-sorry! W-we're, um, lawyers.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh yeah? Well that's great. I'm security! And it's my job to make sure that gawkers like you stay OUT.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">G-gawkers?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Gawkers! Sightseers! Tourists!!! I know the type. You heard about the incident and came to snoop around. Youths today! Something horrible happens and all you can think of is sightseeing. Wasting your time at a place like this. Don't you have jobs you should be doing? Or do lawyers not work like the rest of us? Maybe I should become a lawyer too. Sounds like a life of ease to me no work just loafing around all day as you please. Well when I was young things were a mite different, mind you we didn't prance around in strange hippie clothes. What are the youths coming to these days my own son hasn't called in...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... Nick? Will I grow up to be like her? Please say "no."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno! It's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! Listen when you're being spoken to! Youths today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The computer that runs the studio security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey! No touching!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The security guard station. That security lady must like junk food. There's a mountain of it on the desk in there. I can see the computer that runs the security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The main entrance to the studio. There was a big scene here yesterday with onlookers pressing up against the gate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An overhead map of the studios. Right from here is the Employee Area. To the left are the actual film studios.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like a studio van. They probably use it to carry around film equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you do here at the studios?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">At Global Studios, we make children's dreams come true! In fact, in my younger days...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No! You were a star!?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Only a little twinkle between the stars here, I'm afraid, dearie.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wo... wow.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">This place has really gone downhill, you know? But 10 years ago, now that was a studio of dreams! Hammer was a big star back then too, he was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hammer...?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">The victim, dummy! The Evil Magistrate! He's been reduced to playing villains now. Not exactly the best material to work with...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can you tell me about Mr. Will Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">He's not a bad kid, but don't be fooled by his mask! You wouldn't want him on the silver screen without it, believe me. Little old ladies watching would lose their lunch! That's probably why he thought that the Steel Samurai was his "big chance." No one thought he was capable of doing what he did to poor Jack Hammer...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We don't know for certain that Will Powers is guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Powers? Of course he's guilty! How do I know? I know everything! That's my job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of person was Jack Hammer?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What "kind of person"? Oh... if you only knew! Jack Hammer will live on in many hearts as the ultimate action hero! He was simply dashing in the Dynamite Samurai series!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Should I have heard of that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">But... there was an accident during filming five years ago. He got an unlucky break after that. Reduced to playing the villain on a children's program! What's more, I heard they were paying him peanuts. It's enough to make you cry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why are you so certain Mr. Powers is the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">I was standing right here yesterday, I was. I was here from 1:00 in the afternoon, to 5:00, when they found the body! Now the studio where the murder took place is to the left here. So if you want to go to the studio, you have to pass by me! Only one person went by here between 1:00 and 2:30, when the murder took place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... that person was Mr. Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Yes. I saw him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Powers says he was sleeping in his dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, I'm sure he would say that. He's no fool! But he was the only one that walked by. He's the killer, you can bet your biscuits on it.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What's that? You giving that to me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Absolutely not!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Isn't it about time for you to be heading home? There's nothing to see here. Move along.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, actually, we're here at Mr. Powers's request.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmph! I thought you were suspicious lookin'! Show me a "letter of request." And maybe I'll just let you in.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This lady here thinks she owns this place, obviously.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Hello! How was the studio? They all think I did it, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-no, not at all! Isn't that right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, not at all. At worst, you're a suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Will">*sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers, you aren't hiding anything from me, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Will">W-what? No! I'd never do that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just now you said that you were sleeping in your dressing room after lunch.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Yes. Like a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the security lady said she saw you that day. She says she saw you heading towards the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Will">W-what!? That's not possible! I... I really don't know what to say! I was sleeping, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Powers, if you want me to help you, you have to tell me the truth. I'm new to this lawyer business, and I need every advantage I can get.</line>
<line speaker="Will">I know... I-I'm sorry. *sniff* But, I swear to you on my momma's grave, I was sleeping. Maybe the security lady only thought she saw me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did she see...? He doesn't seem to be lying.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... about the security guard at the main gate to the studio...</line>
<line speaker="Will">Oh, the security lady?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">She's terrible! She called me "suspicious lookin'"!</line>
<line speaker="Will">Y-yes... actually, she's said the same thing to me before. "Take off that mask!" were her words, I believe. She sucks up to all the bigwigs at the studio... But let her see you stumble once and she'll never let up on you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Grr! She's got some nerve!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you for the letter of request.</line>
<line speaker="Will">Show that to the security lady and she should let you in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could write up a letter formally requesting my representation?</line>
<line speaker="Will">Of c-course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I just hope this will get me past that security lady.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, look what I have!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! The Steel Samurai said we'd need that to get into the studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean Will Powers said we'd need it...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes, the Steel Samurai.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ma'am, have a look at this. It's a letter of request from Mr. Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmm...? Yes, yes. I recognize the bold, childish scrawl.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">To think he would entrust his fate to youths of such unreliable appearance... Really!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Anyway, you may pass. But only left from here, toward the studios! No going to the right. That's the Employee Area. "No one allowed inside, pal" were my instructions. The good detective told me himself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There were maps in the security guard station.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Not bad!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Those are 50 cents a piece,</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, time to go, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">50 cents!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Aren't you that murderer from the other day!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah! It's that confused detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey pal, you know Prosecutor Edgeworth is all upset, and it's your fault! I saw him sipping tea and staring gloomily out the window!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... so?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! If he's depressed, it's all your fault for doing sloppy detective work!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">!!! ... ... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think you hurt his feelings.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no! I... I'm sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I think his feelings are easily hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You're right, pal. It's all my fault. I can blame other people all I want, but I know the truth in my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey! Don't take it so hard! There's always the next case!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I suppose you're right. Hey! What exactly are you two doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, well... We're on this case too, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Hey! You can't just go saying "pal" like that! That's MY endearing character trait!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'd say he's a character alright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm a little bushed. Maybe I'll take a short rest here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, good idea, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Detective! Aren't you on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-well, yeah, but... Hey, us detectives get tired of standing around too, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, what's down the path to the left? It looks like a tree fell down over the path...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah. That way's kind of dangerous. You should stay out, pal. There's nothing down there, anyway. That's where Studio Two used to be, they tell me. They don't use it now, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The studio mascot. I guess it's a monkey of some kind. But what kind of monkey has a nose like that? He's holding a sign in his hand. [Right: To Studio One; Left: To Studio Two]</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's up with that thing!? It looks kind of... busted.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, the wind was pretty strong yesterday, and the head broke off. It took that tree down with it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, there's a camera here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the security camera. It takes photos of people going to the studio. All you have to do is look at the data and you can see who went where!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a number plate on the camera... [ST1-307]. That must be the camera ID number.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The entrance to Studio One. This is the studio where they found Jack Hammer's body.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go in and check it out, Nick! ... Hey! It's locked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like you need a cardkey to get in. It makes sense that they would want to keep the non-employees out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a big welcome sign above the path.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, apparently the studio's fallen on tough times. They've started letting people in on days they aren't filming. They make a bit of extra money by charging for admission.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh. You sure know a lot about this place, Detective. You know, you could always quit being a detective and work here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! And what perfect timing, with the monkey's neck broken and all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? Just what's that supposed to mean, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how is your investigation going, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, it's... Hey! I can't tell you that, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Maybe you need to be a little more indirect with your questions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. So, Detective, mind if I take a look at what you got?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What I got?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The autopsy report! The latest version, if you please...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... right, right. Sorry about what happened last time, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how is your investigation going, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not at liberty to give you any more information, pal. You'll hear all you need to know in court!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh well, it was worth a try.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why was Mr. Powers arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Simple, pal! The murder took place right over there in Studio One. Now, the victim entered Studio One at approximately 1:00 PM. At that time, there was no one other than the victim in the studio. According to the autopsy report, the time of death was 2:30 PM. Only one person went to the studio between 1:00 and 2:30! And that person was none other than Will Powers! No one else, pal! If you think I'm lying, ask the security lady at the main gate.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! If that's true...! Anyone would think that Powers did it with that kind of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for cheering me up...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the security lady...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, that sweet old lady. What a charmer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? A-are we talking about the same person?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">When I showed her my badge she gave me a donut and some coffee!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Remember what Powers said. She's a sucker for authority.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She even gave me a piece of valuable evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, that, er, photo. The photo of the Steel Samurai heading toward the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What! Who took that!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">See the camera up on that gate, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The gate? You mean the one with the welcome sign?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah. Whenever someone walks by, that camera automatically snaps a photo of them!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh no! Nick, he has evidence! We're finished!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Funny, for someone with hard proof he doesn't look too happy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective, see this? This is my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh huh? Don'tcha think it's a little sad when you have to explain what your badge means, pal? Real men show their P.D. badge and that's that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll admit the design of my badge leaves a lot to be desired...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe it should just be a big "L" for "Lawyer"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I'm not so sure about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Detective. Any ideas about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, I don't got time to look at every little trinket you got, okay pal?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's wrong, pal? You seem down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't look so happy when you say that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh hoh hoh hoh hoh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... We'd like to ask the employees here some questions...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal. Go wherever you like. Of course, you're not going to find any clues I haven't already found! Hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm glad someone around here seems to be enjoying themselves.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's go! We've got a free pass to the place. Now's our chance to check things out!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look! That security lady is in the guard station stuffing her face with donuts! I guess all cops like their donuts!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, and they're soft enough she doesn't need teeth to chew them...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hey, you! Well? Are you satisfied Powers is guilty yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Urk! She had to make my life harder by giving that photo to Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why didn't you tell us about the security photo, ma'am?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Hmm? Oh, that? I just thought it would be more thrilling to talk with the detective himself! These things are important, you know. Oh, just to the left from here is the gate with the camera that took that photo. It's my job to check the photos every day, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">This guard station is in a central position. No matter where you go here, you pass by my station first! Now poor Hammer, he went to the studio just before 1:00. The murder happened right around 2:30, see? The only one I seen go through here between 1:00 and 2:30 was Powers himself! The security camera got a good look at him too. If he's not the one what did it, I don't know who is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe... it was you?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Gyah hah ha hah! Good one, sonny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She thinks I was joking.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was the victim, Mr. Hammer, a popular actor?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh, he was the biggest star in the studio!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Was"? Past tense?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh yes! He was great as the "Bearded Samurai"!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">That too, yes. He shone the brightest! Back in the day. Making a star like him play the "Evil Magistrate"... It's a disgrace, I tell you! Hammer took it pretty hard, and who can blame him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About the security camera...</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh yes, the camera. It's automatic. It can tell when someone walks through that gate, see? Then it snaps a photo! Apparently, it records the time when it takes a picture too. But I don't bother myself with those details. I just view all the photos on the computer over in the security guard station. I check 'em every day before going home, I do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's going on, Nick!? Powers said he was sleeping in his dressing room! But now there's a photo of him going to the studio!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't look at me! How should I know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That photo the detective was talking about is the problem here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, that's hard to say, without seeing the actual photo ourselves. But if it is Powers in that photo, his alibi is shot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Only one person went to the scene of the crime before the murder took place. And there's a photograph to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess it makes sense that that person is the killer then. What do we do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe there was someone else who could have gone to the scene other than Powers? Let's take a look. Maybe that security lady missed someone?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">On thing's for sure, if there are any clues, they'll be in that studio.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Apparently they have Mr. Powers in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... right.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look pal, that camera takes a picture automatically whenever someone walks by. And it took a picture of Will Powers!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I have to ask him about that photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh well. Let's try again later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This guard monitors the visitor's room. He must get pretty bored. I bet he's making funny faces at that camera.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! This is where they do all the behind-the-scenes stuff! Hey! Look! There's Powers's dressing room! No one's here this soon after the murder I guess. Let's take a look around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like one of those electric-powered bicycles. I dunno about these. I mean, what's the point?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It makes it a lot easier to go up hills!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't people cycle to get exercise!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The metal grate on the drain here has been taken off. That's a pretty big drain. A kid could fit through there, I bet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, if you snuck in that way you wouldn't have to pay at the gate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you want to leave that way, be my guest.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right! Huh? Hey! I'm not a kid!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The remains of yesterday's lunch are scattered around. Everyone was probably too shocked to clean up. There's a t-bone on one of the plates, minus the steak.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm! T-bone steak! That would have hit the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just had a burger!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I have a second stomach just for steaks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a half-finished backdrop for a stage here. Looks like a castle. Probably "Neo Olde Tokyo Castle."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The door to the dressing room. It's not locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Let's take a look inside! Maybe we can find something as a souvenir...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean "find"!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You never know! There might be something like... the Samurai Spear!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We don't need a spear! <thought>And that's the murder weapon for crying out loud!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a sign on the dressing room door. "Mr. Will Powers"... it must be neat to be the star and have your own room like this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A window into the dressing room. The glass is frosted, so I can't see inside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be the storage room. That's where they keep all the film equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, Nick! You know a lot about the industry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm, what else would they keep in a film studio?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... cola, candy, chips, gum... Huh. It's so... normal. I was expecting some cool theme snacks or something. Popcorn, at least!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-wait! Look! "Samurai Soda"! Nick! Try this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ladies first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Powers's dressing room... So this is where he was sleeping? Or at least, this is where he claims he was sleeping.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">No one actually saw him taking a nap here, did they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, and there's a picture of him near the crime scene. <thought>I hope he's telling the truth... for his sake!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a vast array of cosmetics here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! This is the wig he used in "Samurai Boogey-Woogey"! Nick! Try this on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. And how can you tell the name of a show just by looking at a wig!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I, um, kinda like samurai movies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Kinda"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's some regular suits in among the costumes here. Those must be his own clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It'd be fun to wear one of the costumes...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd say you were already wearing one, myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like someone was sleeping here. Maybe Powers did take a nap here yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They always have mirrors like this in dressing rooms. I see my hair is still nice and spiky, just how I like it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm? This must be Powers's bag.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, don't open that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An employee cardkey. That must be Powers's. It says "Studio One."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's take it, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Borrow it. You mean borrow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what else is inside Powers's bag...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Stop that! <thought>My partner, the thief in training.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a bunch of snacks on the table. They must give these to the employees. Some tea and cookies...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... I'm hungry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You just had a burger!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, but I have a separate stomach for sweets!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How many stomachs does this girl have!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's locked. Looks like he doesn't open his window much. I guess it is kind of dusty outside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, hey! That's the cardkey to get into Studio One where the murder took place! Let's go check it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me about this, ma'am?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Oh that! Isn't that a studio cardkey? You better watch it! The scene of a murder is no place for sightseeing! I'll be taking that! Hand it over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait! No, that's mine!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Look, I don't have a cardkey to the studio, see? I want to go pay my respects to Jack Hammer where he died.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W... well you'll just have to wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The entrance to Studio One. This is the studio where they found Jack Hammer's body.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's go in and check it out, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder if this cardkey we borrowed from the dressing room will work...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It opened!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright! We're in!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's way too happy for someone visiting a crime scene.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Detective! Take a look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whazzat?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa whoa whoa! Don't show him that! He'll confiscate it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... I just wanted to show it off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're real quiet all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Doesn't it give you the shivers, Nick? That white tape! It's so... so real!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, the Evil Magistrate did die here. And the Steel Samurai killed him. The murder weapon was the Samurai Spear. Sounds pretty real to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Look! That's the chair the director sits in! I've always wanted to sit in one of these. Hey Nick, take a look at that. One of those black-and-white boards they clap at the start of filming! And look! A megaphone! A real live megaphone!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ready, Nick? Action!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This girl is more troubled than I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's for reflecting light. They call it a reflecting screen or something like that. The assistant holds it during filming.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Where's your enthusiasm for all things entertainment?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, lighting is fine, but I'd want to be the director. Or maybe the Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think she's being serious...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like a backdrop for a stage. This must be used in the Steel Samurai show.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course! That's the mountain, Neo Fujiyama!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't the Steel Samurai take place in Olde Tokyo? Can you even see Mt. Fuji from there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not Olde Tokyo, Nick! "Neo" Olde Tokyo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, a ladder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's a "step"-ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So? What's the difference? You need to stop judging things based on narrow-minded cultural assumptions, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right... sorry. <thought>This girl is OUT there!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They outlined where Jack Hammer's body lay with tape. His body was found still inside the Evil Magistrate costume. I guess that's why the head part looks like a helmet. Funny, I expected a spear stabbing would leave at least a few bloodstains. I guess the costume must have absorbed most of it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, look at that camera! That must cost a ton!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah! So don't touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! It's heavier than I thought...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey! You! No touching that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, um, sorry, my partner is kind of, y'know...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Y'know"!? No I don't know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Who me? I'm an assistant here. I help with props and stuff. Moving them around, ordering new ones, et cetera.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're lawyers representing Mr. Will Powers.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Oh, you're WP's people.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"WP"...? Oh, Will Powers. W.P., I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I don't envy you guys one bit! But... do what you can for WP, okay? He'd never hurt a fly! He has to be innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't worry, leave it to us!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me anything about the day of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes. I was in the studio the whole day. I was the only assistant on staff that day, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Only one assistant!?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, well, the studios aren't doing so well right now. And yesterday was only rehearsal for our action sequences.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see. Neat!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">In the morning we went through the action sequences in the employee area. WP and Hammer were there, along with everyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The employee area--that's where Powers's dressing room is, right?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, that's the place. After eating lunch there, Mr. Hammer went to Studio One. Then I saw WP go into his dressing room. But I didn't see either of them after that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you know that Mr. Powers was sleeping in his room?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">No! I wouldn't go in there unless I had some urgent message for him... I mean, it's his private... What kind of a girl do you think I am!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what kind...? No, no, I'm sure you're a fine girl. Um, sorry. <thought>So much for getting a confirmation of Powers's alibi.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you sensed that someone other than the regular film crew was in the studio?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes... I think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"I think" doesn't cut it in a witness testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! What about that security lady! If someone else came into the studio, she must have seen them!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, any thoughts about this?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Sorry... I... don't really want to think too much about what happened just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do we do, Nick? We haven't found anything. If WP was the only one who came to the studio... Then he has to be the killer! They even have a photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Umm... Sorry... I know you're busy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not really.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Actually, there's been something bothering me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ah hah! That's what I'm talking about! A clue! A lead!</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Well, I don't know about that, but that day, just after noon, I sensed someone was here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You "sensed"?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">Yes, several times.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Some other studio employees, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Penny">No, I don't think so. The only thing we had scheduled was an action scene run-through. I was the only assistant here that day. I have a feeling it was someone from... outside.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-really!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But wait, if someone had come in here... Wouldn't that security lady have noticed them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Penny">I'm sorry I don't have any better information than that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No, thanks! That helps us a lot. Anything helps. Let's go put that security lady on the spot!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? You're still here? Really! You look as though you've seen a ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What? I saw that suspicious look on your face!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to ask you again about yesterday... You came here at 1:00 PM, correct? And the estimated time of Hammer's death was 2:30. Are you sure that Powers was the only one to go through here between those times?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Sure as can be!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But we have a witness who thinks there was "someone from outside" here that day.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you absolutely sure you were here watching the whole time?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ma'am?</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Who was it? Who told you that? Who dares question ME!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Alright you better tell me and tell me quick, you spiky-haired cretin! Someone's been complaining about the work I do, eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh... um, we were just talking to the assistant in Studio One.</line>
<line speaker="Oldbag">Her! She's not even a full-time employee! All you young'uns are like that nowadays, running your mouths like there was no tomorrow saying this that and the other thing. Well when I was young let me tell you we knew a thing or two about respecting our elders. Back then we did and it's a crying shame that you youths today just say what you please about poor old ladies Graaaaaaaaaaaawr!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She left...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick? This is our chance to do what we can without her looking over our shoulders!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No one's here. I wonder if the security lady got mad at that assistant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. That's definitely a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The computer that runs the studio security cameras.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Maybe we can see that photo of Powers with this computer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, maybe. <thought>Should I try the computer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I'd better not fool around with this, or that security lady will get me. Maybe next time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? You're not going to look at it? Bo-ring!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. Let's give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know how to work these things, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like I just have to enter in a few numbers. Let's see... first, I need the date of the murder. <thought>It looks like the camera turned on at 1:00 PM that day... 1:00... That was when the security lady arrived at the guard station.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There! Entered!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ... Nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Maybe I got the number wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sigh* Maybe we should go look at that camera again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There! Entered!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... ... Nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Maybe I got the number wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*sigh* Maybe we should go look at that camera again?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There! Entered! ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! It printed out the data for that day!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see what we got... ... Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How is this a picture of Will Powers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he is the one who always wears that suit... I guess that's why the security lady thought it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't imagine the detective was very happy with this photo as evidence. Hmm? Something's printed on the back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? [Oct 15, 2:00 PM, Photo #2]</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe there's more photo data from that day?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nope--that's the only one in the computer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, hey, Nick! Can't we use this photo as evidence for the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We'll put that security lady in her place with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right, we'll put her in her place...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, that's what I said! Anyway... Let's show her this photo and see what she says!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait. Let's not.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's never a good idea to reveal your hand to the enemy too soon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! You're craftier than I gave you credit for. Why, you could be the next... Evil Magistrate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! Why do I have to be the villain.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Relax, it was just a joke! So, are we done for today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think this photo is what we needed for the trial. Still, it'd be better if we had some idea who the real killer was! Maybe it really is that security lady...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>