<xml>
<title>Turnabout Goodbyes</title>
<line speaker="Maya">What was Mr. Edgeworth talking about...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A memory of a crime... that I committed. A memory... of a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you really think Mr. Edgeworth killed...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... I don't believe it. Not Edgeworth. Some painful memory has been troubling him recently... But he'd never take someone's life! Never!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo! How's everyone doing? Whaddya think of my performance today? I had 'em swooning in the aisles! Huh, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">S-swooning? Me? Oh... Oh, yes. I do remember feeling faint.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Right on! Tell me the truth, it was like love at first sight, right? Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-huh? Me!? I... uh, well, maybe my heart skipped a beat or two...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... I think you can do better than that! C'mon! I saved Edgeworth in there, dude! Edgey! You guys should be bowing before me! Yeah! Bow before your hero!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Woo hoo, I was hot in there. Hot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm glad someone's happy about how this case is going... He seems too happy to care about anything I show him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Looks like Edgeworth is back in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We have our own questions for him! Let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't forget, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Looks like Detective Gumshoe hasn't gotten back yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Police">Gumshoe? He won't be coming back today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... really?</line>
<line speaker="Police">He said there was some guy he had to arrest by tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The boat shop caretaker...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Police">He shouted something about "catching him if it's the last thing I do, pal!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good luck, Gumshoe!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"Please! Think about what you're doing, Jolinda! Don't take my Tommy away from me! No!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for a nasty divorce argument.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Wha...!? Th-that's not possible! The world ended... yesterday!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be reading predictions for the future on someone's homepage.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's out... again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">When does he work, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, now. Don't be harsh. <thought>Guess we'll have to come back later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... You really helped out in the trial today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You did! If you weren't there, Larry, I'm sure Mr. Edgeworth would have been found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah hah! But, seriously, Nick. That boat shop caretaker guy is pretty suspicious... But Edgey ain't off the hook yet!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Way to spoil the mood, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I'm just a guy sitting in the audience, you know? But from where I was sitting, Edgey seemed pretty... edgy. I mean, can you really know he's telling the truth about that night?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. But... what I do know is... I'm going to believe in you two until the end.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Us two?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Edgeworth and... who else? You mean me right?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nah! He means me! Right, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, you, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not... me? ... B-but why you, Larry!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Um, actually, yeah. Why me, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph. Enough with the silent treatment!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... Why do you trust Mr. Edgeworth so much? I mean, he's changed recently, true. But when we first met him, he was kind of jerk, don't ya think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You didn't know him back then. Back when he wanted to become a defense attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait... Was that when you two were classmates?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. In grade school... They saved me... Miles... And Larry. They saved me and I'll never forget it. That's why I became a defense attorney, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? Hey, hey, Larry. What's he talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Uh... umm... Er, sorry. I kinda forgot.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph. Okay, Nick. Out with it! I'm going to hear this story today, and that's final!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, okay. It's kind of a long story, so hang in there. ... It was the beginning of Spring, 4th grade. I was on trial. A class trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A c-class trial!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You remember, Larry? Spring, 4th grade? A kid in my class got his lunch money stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lunch money?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Our school was really small. Every month, kids would bring in an envelope with money for lunch from home.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, this kid's envelope disappeared. With $38.00 still inside.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh... Yeah, now that you mention it, I do remember that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can see why you'd forget, though. You were out of school that day. Anyway, the envelope had been stolen during PE class. I was coming down with a cold, so I'd skipped PE that day. I was the only one not in class.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... they thought you did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. The kids in class said I should be put on trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Trial...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the next day we held a classroom trial, with me as the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"I... I didn't do it!"</line>
<line speaker="Teacher">"Now, Phoenix, you know you shouldn't steal people's money! It's not right."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the end, even the teacher thought I'd done it.</line>
<line speaker="Teacher">"Apologize to the class, Phoenix."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I didn't know what was happening. I was so sad... I couldn't stop crying. Everyone was staring at me like I'd done it... I tried to apologize. I went over to where the boy was sitting... ... That's when it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Teacher">"M-Miles?"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"It wasn't you who stole my money, was it?"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"No..."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Then you shouldn't apologize! Everyone's been shouting you did it, but no one has any proof! That is why, Your Honor, this boy is innocent!"</line>
<line speaker="Teacher">"B-but Miles, it was your money that was stolen!"</line>
<line speaker="Butz">"This is always how it is, everybody ganging up and picking on one person. Just think how he feels! He said he didn't do it, so he didn't do it!"</line>
<line speaker="Teacher">"Very well. I will replace the money myself. This class trial is over."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's how it happened. After that, the three of us were always friends.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... I had no idea!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah... I had no idea, either! I mean, I forgot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I learned what it meant to be alone. Totally alone, without a friend in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You did a good thing, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Um, yeah, well... I was just lucky that I took the day off from school. If I'd been there they would have thought I'd done it! So, I took it kind of personally, see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"When something smells, it's usually the Butz."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, Edgeworth and I talked after that class trial. That's when I heard his father was a defense attorney. I remember, his eyes would shine when he talked about his father.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"I'm going to become a defense attorney, just like my Dad! A famous defense attorney!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then, a few months later, he suddenly transferred to another school.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The DL-6 Incident...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. I'm not sure, but the transfer probably had to do with his father's death.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's so sad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... It was several years later when I heard Edgeworth's name again. There was an article about him in the newspaper. The headline was something like "Dark Suspicions of a Demon Attorney." Fabricating evidence, manipulating testimonies, covering up facts... The article said he'd do anything to get a guilty verdict. Anything.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">But why? What happened!? I mean, that's not the Edgey I used to know at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's what I thought too. I tried to get in touch with him I don't know how many times... He never replied.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess he didn't want to see his old friends...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I couldn't just drop it, though. I wanted to meet him, to know why he had become who he became. That's when I decided.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Wait... You don't mean...? That's why!? That's why you became a defense attorney!? To meet Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I was a defense attorney, I knew he's have to meet me whether he wanted to or not. In court. ... Edgeworth believed in me, and I believe in him.  He's in pain... And no one's on his side. I'm the only one who knows the real Edgeworth. I'm the only one who can help him.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Whoa... Nick. S-so, is that why you helped me out for free?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... yes. I helped you because I believed in you. <thought>Except I don't remember saying I'd do it for free...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Aw, Nick! Nick!!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! We have to save Mr. Edgeworth if it's the last thing we do, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. <thought>It very well may be...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">First, there's that rental boat shop caretaker. We need to find out who or what he is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd settle for who. <thought>I guess I can clean out some of this evidence I no longer need... ...</thought> Okay, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You look grim as always.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um, Mr. Edgeworth? I heard the story about the class trial...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Class trial? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You... don't remember?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your lunch money was stolen, wasn't it? In 4th grade...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Lunch money...? ... Oh... Oh, right. Yes, I seem to remember something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick. I think you're the only one who really remembers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it probably only really mattered to me anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Edgeworth, didn't you know? That trial was the reason Nick became a defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Gee... thanks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That said... It does sound like that kind of thing you'd do. You haven't changed a bit, have you, Wright? So...simple. To a fault, even.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, maybe yeah, but... I think you changed too much, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Edgeworth. Why did you become a prosecutor, anyway? You used to look up to your dad... You said you wanted to be a defense attorney, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... I couldn't let myself deny reality like you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My father was taken from me, and you want me to defend criminals? I'm sorry, Wright, but I'm not that good of a person!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">One suspect was apprehended in your father's murder, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. The man trapped in the elevator with my father. His name... was Yanni Yogi. He had to be the shooter, any way you look at it! Yet... he was found innocent. That defense attorney got him off the hook!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That would be Robert Hammond...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">On that day, 15 years ago... The three of us were trapped in that elevator for five hours. When we were rescued, we all suffered oxygen deprivation. I had lost all memory of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lost your memory?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even now, I can't recall what happened in that elevator. That was the crux of Yogi's argument in court. He claimed Yanni Yogi had been "not of sound mind" due to the oxygen deprivation. Yogi was released due to a lack of evidence... innocent. That's when I changed my mind. I started to hate defense attorneys.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's your relationship with von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He's my teacher, and a man who deserves respect. I learned everything I know of courtroom techniques from him.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, he's like my sister was to you, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He is a perfectionist in all things. In court... In his personal life... He is obsessed with doing everything perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Perfectly, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In all the cases he has taken on, none were left unsolved. And not one suspect was declared innocent. Ever.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But... but that's...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know. It's possible some of the suspects were indeed innocent. However, it is impossible for us to accurately determine that in every case. All von Karma does is his job, to find the suspect guilty, perfectly. In any case... It's nigh well impossible to find a weakness in him. Should a weakness appear, he would do everything in his power to make it go away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Edgeworth? If what you're saying is true, you're headed for a guilty sentence tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-he's right! Now's no time to be praising the enemy, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmph... It's a strange situation in which I find myself, I'll admit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No kidding.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you showing me this picture for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, uh, no reason.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... You know, I was impressed by your deduction in the trial today. Granted, you were at the end of your rope, but still.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, he noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hah hah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... It was that case that changed my life. And tomorrow, on December 28, its statute of limitations runs out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Tomorrow... Could that be a coincidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But... even if the case is finally closed on paper... It will never be erased from my memory. Never...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! No! Th-that's a photo of his father! Don't show him that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're right... Now probably isn't a good time to dredge up those old memories...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, um, n-nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry. I'm not sure I can help you with that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Long time no see!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh! Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Close one today, eh! I got so worked up, I snapped my tie in half!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No prob, pal! Thanks to you, we now know who really did it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean, the boat shop caretaker?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, I'll make you a promise. I'll have that scoundrel in my custody by trial time tomorrow! Come what may! It's my duty to you as a police officer! Now, I'm off to catch me a criminal!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Detective Gumshoe sure is... active today.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, one other thing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No one can go into the woods today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The woods?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Where Lotta was camping?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The woods are off-limits to camping, and apparently the park ranger found out. He got pretty mad. No one can go in for a while.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess Lotta's in a 'lotta' trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Anyway, I'll be seeing you tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? The Steel Eyesore is missing...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Eyesore"!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like the hotdog stand is closed, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess Larry's been too busy with the trial to show up for work...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This lake sure likes to cause problems, doesn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I mean, everything that happened here turned out to be a lie! Gourdy was a lie, and the charges against Mr. Edgeworth were all lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I mean, I'm glad the charges were all lies, but still.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A trashcan with no trash. At least the place is well maintained.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No one's going to sit here on a cold day like today. Well, unless they were eating a Samurai Dog!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How would that change the temperature, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? You seem troubled, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, who? Me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess Larry has today off.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He was pretty happy about saving Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">True. We owe him big.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That old caretaker got away...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I never imagined he might be the real murderer! ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>I'd know that clearing-of-the-throat anywhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah hah, hello! What might you be doing here? Out for a walk, hmm? "Ahh... the days of my youth... like the scent of fresh lemon..." you see.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Grossberg! This is no time for idle reminiscing! Mr. Edgeworth's trial ends tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Er... that is true, yes. But, from what I saw of today's trial, Edgeworth should be fine, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I'm not so sure about that.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ho ho! What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... I'm not sure.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... If you find anything out, come by my office at once. I may be able to offer you some assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks... <thought>Bye...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think Mr. Grossberg was doing here anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a forest here beyond these bushes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! The forest! There's someone in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... You're right. There's a few policemen in there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">They must be looking for the caretaker!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good luck...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The boat rental shop. Doesn't look like anyone is around.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The caretaker must have run for the hills, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, looks like it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He didn't seem like a bad person...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nobody's home.</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! It's Polly! I wonder where your owner's gone, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe he'd run off and leave his poor parrot to fend for herself!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't look like he used this kitchen much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess the whole pasta restaurant thing was a lie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, you thought he was telling the truth!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Nick. Don't people usually put pictures of fish up on the wall to boast about them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, yeah, I guess so. You mean picture of the fish they caught, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right... but don't all the fish on the wall here look really puny to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you know what they say... "You shoulda seen the one that got away!"</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Except the one that got away from us was the caretaker! And we did see him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I feel like we're having two different conversations here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This fishing pole looks expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe we should bring it to Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you think the caretaker would mind?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we can just leave him the metal detector in exchange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... maybe we'd better not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm. Everything's cold. Looks like he didn't turn his heater on. I guess he hasn't been back here since the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-what's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Oh... N-never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Tell me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just, when I saw the TV, I remembered... They're showing a Pink Princess special this week...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See? That's why I didn't want to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That reminds me, Nick! Polly here knows the number to this safe, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly, what's the number to the safe?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"1228"! *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's open it, Nick! C'mon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure there isn't any money in there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... But, hey! He keeps it locked, right? So there must be something of value in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not so sure...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick, let's see what's in there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there might be a clue or two...</thought> ... The only thing in here is a letter.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A letter? Aww... boring!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... There's no name or signature on this thing. It's handwritten in very precise, clear letters...</thought> ... "Get your revenge on Miles Edgeworth..." Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-N-Nick! Why would Mr. Edgeworth's name be on here...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How should I know!? I'm going to read the whole thing...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The rest of the letter goes on to describe the murder plot in detail! How to kill Robert Hammond, and frame Edgeworth... ...Calling Edgeworth out to the lake, getting on the boat... firing twice! This is exactly what I figured out today in court! It's all here... in perfect detail!</thought> ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think it means, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... but it looks like these are instructions for that caretaker. When he killed Robert Hammond and called out Edgeworth, he was following instructions!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But who could have written that letter? And... what does it mean, to "get revenge on Miles Edgeworth"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look, I don't know, okay? But one thing's for certain. This letter is an amazing clue!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing left in the safe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder why the caretaker didn't take the letter with him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He left in a hurry, right? I don't think he even came back here after the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe I should take care of Polly, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You probably shouldn't just kidnap her. The police know about her anyway. I'm sure they'll do something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... okay... Sorry, Polly. He says I can't take you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, now the bird's going to hate me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">One day left, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, no time to waste! Let's get going!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think we should do now, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You would know best, Nick! Just do what you do! That should work.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? Had any good ideas?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is all tied to the DL-6 Incident... We'd better find out as much as we can about that murder before tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Something that happened back then has a hold on Edgeworth and it won't let go.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Stop showing me stuff and let's get cracking! We only have today to get to the bottom of this!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yanni Yogi was a court bailiff at the time. We just happened to be in that elevator together 15 years ago. The quake was incredibly strong... Before I knew it, everything was dark. We were there for so long, it felt like forever. The air thinned... and the darkness closed in on us in that little box. We became... unsettled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's all I remember... When I came to, I was in a hospital bed, staring up at the ceiling.In court, Yanni Yogi's mental condition was called into question. They claimed the oxygen deprivation and stress had caused temporary insanity. In the end, the claim passed the court, and Yogi was found innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh... But, isn't that strange? This letter tells him to "get revenge on Edgeworth"... Why would he want to take revenge on you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's something that's been troubling me these last few days. I... didn't know whether or not I should tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You mean the nightmare?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's... a nightmare I've had. A memory of a crime... that I committed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A crime you committed?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...A memory... of a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think... I think the time has come to tell all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">For the last 15 years, I've had the same dream almost every night. I wake up in a fearful sweat, every time.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What kind of dream?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a dream about my father's killing... in the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then I see the pistol lying by my feet. I don't know if it was evidence from that day in court, or the bailiff's... In a daze, I pick up the pistol...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Get away...! Get away from my father!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And with that scream... I wake. It's a bone-chilling scream. A scream that has rung in my ears for the past 15 years.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... B-but... That's just a dream, right? Right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... That thought is the only thing that has kept me sane for the last 15 years. But what if I'm wrong? What if it's real? They say that sometimes people shut out memories in self-defense. Maybe it was I who killed my father!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you think about it that way, this letter makes sense. "Get your revenge on Miles Edgeworth." Think about it. Yogi was really innocent. That's why he wanted revenge against me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, Edgeworth! You... you mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was me. I was the true criminal of DL-6. I shot my father!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth... See this letter?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This came out of the safe in the shack where that boat rental caretaker lives.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... ...! Revenge... on me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who is that old guy, anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could he be an innocent defendant you got declared guilty or something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nice, Wright. But I don't remember that old man. Not at all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, he was following this letter, then?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means there was someone else behind it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Two men... meaning myself and Robert Hammond?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It also says: "This is your last chance!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Last chance...? Wait, maybe... Maybe he's talking about the statute of limitations on the DL-6 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">... Wait... Wait, that old man...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what is it!? Do you know who he is!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yogi... Could he be Yogi!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yogi?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The suspect in the DL-6 Incident. The one who was found innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is bad...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are we doing to do, Nick? What can we do!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... I don't think there is anything we can do. Like it or not. If there's someone else who knows a lot about the DL-6 Incident, maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! There is, Nick! There is someone else who knows about DL-6!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Grossberg!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, hello there. What's wrong? You look troubled.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No kidding! I can't believe you're not!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">M-my my my... Just calm down and tell me what's happened, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's M-Mr. Edgeworth! He... He... *sob*</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I see... So, Edgeworth dreamt he shot his own father?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's o-only a dream! Only a dream!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-what...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">If that's the case, then why do you two look so troubled, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-well...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Also, consider this. Yogi quite certainly holds a deep grudge against Miles Edgeworth. So deep, he'd want to frame him for murder. This leads me to surmise... That Mr. Edgeworth's dream was NOT a dream. It was real. As you imagined. Miles Edgeworth threw the pistol to save his father... the pistol fired... and the deed was done. ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N... No! I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yogi was suspected of murder, and his career as bailiff was irrevocably wrecked. Thus, he sought revenge on Miles Edgeworth. This was his last chance, of course, with the statute of limitations so close.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you know about Edgeworth's father?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... He was a defense attorney without peer. It sounds trite, but it's true. Well, he may have had one peer now that I think about it. Your mentor, Mia Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My sister...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Gregory Edgeworth was very disapproving of Mr. von Karma's techniques.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's no surprise...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">von Karma is an extreme man. Forged testimonies and evidence are nothing to him. The result: he has a perfect win record in court. To beat him, Gregory Edgeworth tried to call attention to his methods.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He lost. And died in despair, as it were.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">When Gregory Edgeworth was killed, the police called on a spirit medium. That was your mother, Misty Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yet Yogi was found innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's when my mother left us. Everyone called her a fraud.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">That's right. Everyone thought she was, you see. Yet... now that I think about it. It seem the one who lied was Gregory Edgeworth's ghost... Gregory Edgeworth must have known who shot him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe it... So you're saying he falsified his "testimony"? That Edgeworth's dad lied to protect his son...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It's only a possibility, mind you. But... a possibility nonetheless.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">If it truly was von Karma who wrote this letter, then he would know the truth. He would know that Miles Edgeworth had accidentally killed his own father.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He'll say as much tomorrow in court, I should think. He'll press the point until the court finds Miles Edgeworth "guilty."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but how could von Karma know about Mr. Edgeworth's past like that? Even Mr. Edgeworth thought it was just a nightmare!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... That, I do not know. Yet I do know that von Karma is both persistent... and a perfectionist. He may be seeking to satisfy a grudge against Gregory Edgeworth by hurting his son.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It was fifteen years ago... von Karma met Gregory Edgeworth in court, and von Karma did win... But he didn't make it through the trial unscarred.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What happened in the trial between Edgeworth's dad and von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">von Karma got the "guilty" verdict he wanted. He won the trial. But Gregory Edgeworth accused von Karma of faulty evidence. And though he lost the trial, Mr. Edgeworth's accusation stood.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Faulty evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It was the only penalty von Karma has ever received in his career as a prosecutor. Gregory Edgeworth dealt a blow to his perfect trial record.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">It must have been quite a shock for von Karma. He took a vacation for several months after that, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A vacation...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, an unusual event for the man. That was the first, and the last vacation he's taken in his many years of prosecuting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!? He doesn't take vacations!? Like... go to the sea, or, uh, to the mountains? Don't tell me he's never been to Europe!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You have strange ideas about vacations, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">In any case... That was the only time he took a vacation from work. I believe the penalty upset him quite a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Odd... If he wanted to keep a perfect record so badly... why would he take such a long vacation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">In any case, it's good that the one shooting isn't Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You bet it's good! <thought>I can't believe the fiendish planning that went into this murder... And we almost fell right into his trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a creep!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Ah, she was a beautiful woman... I'm truly sorry about what I did...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? Sorry about what?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'll stay out of this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">This incident took place 15 years ago tomorrow. So tomorrow will see the completion of not one, but two trials. All thanks to the statute of limitations. However... I'm afraid the damage the DL-6 Incident has done will never be eased...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Gregory Edgeworth...? He was a gifted man. His death was truly a loss. I wonder what would have become of von Karma were he alive...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">So this is the letter? It does seem that Yogi was following this letter... when he killed Hammond.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, why kill Robert Hammond?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hammond was a skilled defense attorney. But... he defended clients not for their sake, but for his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? His own sake?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He never trusted his clients, that one. The only thing he trusted was his own ability.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, he got his client found innocent. So why should it matter?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Actually, my dear, it's quite different. He won that innocent verdict for no one but himself. Yogi was a free man, but socially, he was ruined.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You'll understand soon enough. ... Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">This letter... I've seen this handwriting somewhere before... a long time ago! Whose handwriting was this...? Do you have any idea who wrote this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miles Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Wh-wh-whaaat!? Why in heavens would he write something like this!? Why, this letter is an attempt to destroy Miles! Think before you speak, greenhorn!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh. He's angry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Think again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it was Yanni Yogi?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yanni Yogi!? You claim he wrote himself this letter... then followed his own instructions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Yeah, I guess that would be what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Harumph! Perhaps you think Mr. Yogi has a split-personality, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that's definitely a possibility, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hmm... No, I think not. I do not know this Yogi, in any case. There's no way I would recognize his handwriting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Yes, Wright. I'll ask you again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... could it be Manfred von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">von Karma? Why would he have something to do with this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, well, I'm not sure...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Hmm? von Karma... von Karma... W-wait! You're right, my boy! This is von Karma's handwriting, I'm sure of it! I used to see it all the time on court reports...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaaaat!? But... but that means...! Th-the one who told Mr. Yogi to kill was...</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Correct. Manfred von Karma, himself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What does this mean, then? Why would von Karma want to frame Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">No doubt about it, this is von Karma's handwriting. Yogi was following von Karma's instructions when he killed Hammond.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, why kill Robert Hammond?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Hammond was a skilled defense attorney. But... he defended clients not for their sake, but for his own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? His own sake?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">He never trusted his clients, that one. The only thing he trusted was his own ability.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, he got his client found innocent. So why should it matter?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Actually, my dear, it's quite different. He won that innocent verdict for no one but himself. Yogi was a free man, but socially, he was ruined.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">You'll understand soon enough. ... Now, there's only one question left. Why did von Karma write this? And why now?</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Er... quite sorry. I have nothing to say to that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do we do, Nick? von Karma is going to bring up DL-6, you can bet on it! What if Mr. Edgeworth pleads guilty to DL-6!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I won't let him!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">Erm, yes, Mr. Wright... I hate to say this... But even accidental murder is murder, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know that! ... I... I just believe in Edgeworth's innocence! I can't believe he'd kill someone!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">B-but, Nick! Mr. Edgeworth admits it himself! His father must have lied to protect him, beyond the grave...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't care! I know he's not guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">... Mr. Wright... If you say so, I suppose I could go check again. The police files might hold something of interest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Grossberg... thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Grossberg">I can't promise anything. In fact, I think the chances of finding something are slim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I understand. <thought>The police materials... hmm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's hardly anyone here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Everyone must be out looking for the old guy... Yogi.</line>
<line speaker="Police">Ah, it's you. I don't think Gumshoe'll be coming back today. He's staying out late looking for someone.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sounds like Detective Gumshoe is pounding the pavement for real! Um, we were wondering if we could check out the Records Room again...</line>
<line speaker="Police">Well, now, I can't have just anyone wandering around in there. But... I guess Mr. von Karma is in there now, anyway. You can go in as long as he's there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">von Karma...?</line>
<line speaker="Police">Yes. He just arrived actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>von Karma's in the Records Room!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Let's hurry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"So, um, what are your hobbies?" "Well... I like to do stake-outs now and then..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for a first date.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Dusty as always!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We were only here just yesterday. I'm sure they just haven't had time to clean... ...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's wrong, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing. I was just noticing that he isn't here. von Karma...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This cabinet is where they keep evidence for current cases. Some of the things are obviously murder weapons others... are question marks. Most of it just looks like random junk.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... what do you think this clothespin is for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't touch that. It's evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? One of the drawers here is open.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Someone must have been looking in it recently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The label says, "Unsolved Cases: Evidence"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... "Unsolved cases"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! The file for DL-6... it's completely empty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">What are you doing in here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeek! v-v-von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">You...! ... How do you know my name?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Have we met?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">W-w-what are you saying!? We see each other every day, don't we? We're Miles Edgeworth's defense team!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Defense team...?  Ahem. I beg your pardon, you see, I rarely remember defense attorneys. They are like bugs to me. Needless things, to be crushed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can see how this guy was Edgeworth's mentor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This large drawer is half-open. The label on the drawer reads: "Unsolved Cases: Evidence." All the stuff in here looks like random junk. Only the evidence for the DL-6 Incident is missing. I can guess who took it, too. von Karma.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh, umm... Mr. Edgeworth was your student, right?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... A romanticist who could never shed that veneer of amateurism. Just like his father. Always second rate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. von Karma... You had an axe to grind with Mr. Gregory Edgeworth, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Me? A grudge against a mere defense attorney? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he dealt a blow to your otherwise perfect trial record?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you did... but what I don't get is... Why did you take his son under your wing afterwards? The son of your most bitter rival?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... That, my dear attorney, is none of your business.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Tomorrow will be the last day of this trial. It's been a while since I've had a defense attorney last this long. Still, you will lose in the end. Miles Edgeworth will admit his own guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His guilt of 15 years ago, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... You're quite the researcher. If you've done your homework so well, then certainly, you must understand. You know what Miles Edgeworth will tell the court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We were right... So von Karma is going to bring up DL-6 in court tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Karma">Fool. You think I, a prosecutor, would you, a defense attorney, information? Bah!</line>
<line speaker="Maya"><thought>Creep!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. von Karma, have a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This was you, wasn't it? You instructed Yanni Yogi to commit murder.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">... Yanni Yogi... How many years has it been since I've heard him called by that name. He's a fool. I told him to burn it after he read it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! S-so you admit it! You... you wrote Mr. Yogi this letter!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Yes, my dear defense attorney. Thank you for taking the trouble to bring it to me. You've saved me from a lot of needless hassle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! What is that thing!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A stun gun. For self defense... usually.</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Indeed. 600,000 volts will course through your body like a dog touching an electric fence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Six hundred thous...!?</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Oh, don't worry. People don't die from it, usually. Now, give me the letter.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No!!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Whoa! What are you--!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Run!!! Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Karma">Out of my way!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Waaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... he got us. The letter's... gone, of course. And he took the DL-6 evidence... all of it. Back to having no clues. Wait... Maya jumped first. Maya...! Is she okay? ...</thought> Ma...Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! Open your eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... The letter! Did he take it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh!? Oh... yeah. A-are you okay!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I... I couldn't stop him. I jumped as fast as I could, but one shot from that thing knocked me out cold. I'm useless. I'm not good as a lawyer, or a medium! I can't even call my sister. Not even now, when we need her the most. I wish I hadn't woken up at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya! <thought>Grr! There has to be some way I can help her! I'd better do something about her self-confidence, first.</thought> ...? <thought>Maya... She's holding something! What is that? A bullet?</thought> "DL-6 Incident, Evidence No. 7 Taken from the heart of Gregory Edgeworth." I remember... von Karma was holding this when Maya jumped him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll prove it to you, Maya. You're most definitely not useless! I'll prove it to you in court tomorrow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>