
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reminiscence</title>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay Faraday... the young lady who calls herself the second Yatagarasu... The piece of cloth that she conjured up has taken me back to many years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Defendant">Yeah, that's right. I did it. I killed the guy. But it was the Great Thief Yatagarasu that told me to do it!</line>
<line speaker="Lawyer">I ask the defendant... Just what exactly are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Defendant">Don't you get it? I know the true identity of the Yatagarasu! ...The Yatagarasu is the man standing over there at the prosecutor's bench!</line>
<line speaker="Prosecutor">Are you saying... that I'm the Yatagarasu?</line>
<line speaker="Defendant">Don't you dare deny it! You told me to kill him when you snuck into the embassy!</line>
<line speaker="Lawyer">Are you claiming that Mr. Faraday is the Yatagarasu?</line>
<line speaker="Defendant">That's exactly what I'm saying!</line>
<line speaker="Prosecutor">Mr. Rell! I think we've heard just about enough out of you...!</line>
<line speaker="Defendant">Your Honor! Please listen to me! I'm telling the truth... You've gotta believe meeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph... In accordance with the defendant's accusation... ...a new prosecutor shall be called to replace Mr. Faraday. This court will be in recess until the new prosecutor is ready.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This badge's design is said to reflect the relentlessness and discipline of law enforcement. It comes from the authority vested in us as strict protectors of the law... ...and executors of sentences, much like harsh winter frosts and blazing summer days. To wear it is to identify oneself as a prosecutor... ...but my mentor has taught me that it's more fashionable to keep it in my pocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...It's almost time for me to enter the courtroom. And so, it is that my first assignment as a prosecutor will be... ...as a replacement for a prosecutor who has been accused by the defendant.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! ...Sir.</line>
<line speaker="???">Have you read over all of the documents regarding this trial?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, sir. I've memorized everything there is to know.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Very good. The paperwork for the prosecutor substitution is just about complete. Edgeworth... always bear in mind that as your mentor, I, Manfred von Karma... ...will accept nothing short of perfection.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand, sir. To have the chance to stand in court at such an early stage in my career... ...I am honored and proud.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">As I have watched over your studies, I am giving you this very rare chance. Prove yourself. Crush the defendant's pathetic lies into oblivion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Yes, sir! <thought>That such a legendary prosecutor is watching over and judging my performance... ...I have to perfect in every way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This should lead to the defendant lobbies.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Edgeworth! Where is your composure!? If you wish to take a look at your enemy, do so in the courtroom... as you crush him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed, thank you. You are a man of wisdom and experience, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A bulletin board... There are trial schedules posted on it. Trials scheduled for this week... Huh? There's only today's trial listed... This must be a mistake, or this country's judicial system is not working as it should!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Man">Th-This is so good! *gulp, gulp, gulp* I could drink a whole gallon!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've never heard of water that tastes THAT good...</thought> .................. <thought>Maybe I'll give him a minute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Man">*gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp* *gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp* *gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp* *gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp* *gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp* *gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does he plan on gulping an entire reservoir dry!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, madam, but is something the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">I just thought someone would have brought hors d'oeuvres by now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">B-But this is a courthouse! It would be quite atypical to provide hors d'oeuvres here!</line>
<line speaker="Old Lady">Are you sure? Someone poured me a fresh cup of coffee last night I was here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What the heck does she think a courthouse is for!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This trial is about to resume. I should stay on the premises.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Mr. Prosecutor, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've got a good eye if you can tell that I'm a prosecutor with just one glance.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">As there are always only prosecutors and defense attorneys in this lobby... I usually hit the mark if I guess one or the other while there is a recess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You were only guessing!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Father">Aren't these great? Daddy made all of these.</line>
<line speaker="Boy">Awesome! But didn't you get fired right after you made them?</line>
<line speaker="Father">Ah, yeah I did... I spent the same amount of money on this model as it cost to build the real thing. And my boss wasn't very happy with me. Haha.</line>
<line speaker="Boy">Hey, Daddy. Didn't you say you built a secret mechanism inside of it?</line>
<line speaker="Father">Hahaha. I'll tell you about it someday when you're older.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A secret mechanism...? Maybe he installed it as payback for getting fired? It could be trouble... ......Now I'm curious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A model of the courthouse. It's pretty well constructed. Hm...? Hands and a face...? Don't tell me this thing transforms... Yet, I wonder for what other purpose could they have been made...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Today's trial should have ended in just one minute.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because the defendant was picked up by the security camera, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Exactly. The killer had the gall to say that he only killed because he was instructed to do so. Even more outrageous is his claim that the case prosecutor. Byrne Faraday, gave the order. Hah! Faraday is such a fool! He's been cornered by his very own prey.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sir... Are you an acquaintance of Mr. Byrne Faraday?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmph. He is a pathetic man who speaks nothing but nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nonsense...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">He once tried to explain to me a way of punishing "those who cannot be brought to court".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Those who cannot be brought to court"...? That IS nonsense, for no man is above the law.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Well... there are always a few exceptions. However, there is no reason to even deal with such individuals. A prosecutor is a guardian of the court, one with no obligation to outside matters.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Thus, there is no reason to deal with such individuals, I see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Edgeworth... Disgracing yourself as Faraday has will not be forgiven.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hace no fear. I will not let you down, sir. In place of the accused Prosecutor Byrne Faraday, I'll prove the defendant's guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Very good. I've secured an hour of recess for you to prepare to do just that. Show them all... the power of Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">So, have you achieved a firm understanding of the case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, sir. I have memorized everything that is written down in the case files.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Well then, explain the case to me. ...I want to see if you really know what you are talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood. A murder was committed on September 8th in front of the Cohdopian Embassy. The victim, Mr. Deid Mann, was a staff member at the embassy. The defendant in this case, Mr. Mack Rell... ...was held for questioning the night of the incident as he was deemed suspicious. He was quickly placed under arrested for possession of the murder weapon, a gun. Furthermore, at the time of the murder... ...the Great Thief "Yatagarasu" had successfully infiltrated the Cohdopian Embassy as well. At first, Rell claimed that he himself was the Yatagarasu... ...but that he did not kill Deid Mann. I wonder what he expected to gain from such a desperate lie?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">It's possible that he wants to go down while in the spotlight, if he is found guilty. There truly is no limit to people's inanity... But I digress. Continue, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, sir. During the trial, the prosecution presented the security footage that captured the murder... The footage clearly showed Mr. Rell as the murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">The act of Mr. Rell firing the gun could be clearly seen from the visitor's gallery.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Upon seeing that, the defendant retracted his statement and admitted to the murder. "I did it because I was told to... ...by the real Yatagarasu, Byrne Faraday."</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Hmm. That sounds about right. However, you've forgotten one thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">While this may appear to simply be the murder of a Cohdopian Embassy staff member... ...people are actually referring to it as the second KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The second KG-8 Incident...? I'm very sorry, sir. I fear I've failed to study hard enough.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Hmph. Well, even among the police, it's information that only a select few are privy to.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please enlighten me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sir... What do you mean by "the second KG-8 Incident"?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">In order for me to tell you that, you must first learn about the original case. Take a look at these documents.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is a... three-year-old newspaper.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">You have heard of the Amano Group scandal before, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I have. The secretary of Ernest Amano, the Amano Group's director, was arrested... ...under suspicion of smuggling.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Correct. Cece Yew was an employee of the Amano Group... ...and the sole witness to the smuggling operation. It was she who brought the crime to light. However, Ms. Yew was silenced before she could testify in court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wasn't a Cohdopian Embassy staff member arrested for the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Yes... A Cohdopian by the name of Manny Coachen was the suspect. However, due to lack of evidence, the case went unresolved.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Lack of evidence!?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hah! If only I was in charge of the case. I would have done everything in my power to prove his guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>To make sure that all criminals are found guilty... My mentor really is dedicated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Faraday was the prosecutor on the case then, and he was as pathetic as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Mr. Faraday was in charge of the KG-8 Incident as well?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">That's right. And now, once again, the victim of the case you are currently assigned to... ...was someone who was scheduled to testify against that smuggling organization.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And just like last tome, the victim was murdered right before he was to testify.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">You're catching on. The victim was murdered just before his day in court against the smuggling organization. Events are occurring almost exactly the same way as they did in the KG-8 incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So that's why it is being called the second KG-8 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Yes... Yet, there is one difference between the two incidents.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What would that be...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">The so-called noble thief that is sending everyone into an uproar... The Great Thief "Yatagarasu".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yatagarasu...? I'd better find out more.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is thanks to you that i have finally become a prosecutor, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">It's amusing that you wanted to become a defense attorney, yet became my student. Hmph... It is a strange path you have traveled.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's true that I had once wanted to become a defense attorney... But now, I am honored and proud to be a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I see. Then as a student of mine, I suggest you remember this well: The Prosecutor's Badge... is not to be flaunted! The dignity of a prosecutor lies in the man himself, not in the badge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand... I will keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Besides, why put holes in your fine garments? It's simply preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Prosecutors must also take pride in their appearance... I will keep this in mind as well.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I'm constantly having to remind the others at the Prosecutor's Office of this... "It's more fashionable to keep your Prosecutor's Badge in your pocket!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, always treat a Prosecutor's Badge with care and honor? I understand, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About the KG-8 Incident... The trial came to a proper conclusion, did it not?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hah! I'd hardly call the defendant being found innocent! a "proper" conclusion! If I had been on the case, no one would have a single doubt about his guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But, wasn't there a lack of evidence to prove that Mr. Coachen was guilty...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...A lack of evidence? Hah! There is no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's just like him to be able to prove a man guilty, even when the evidence is lacking!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm. A luxurious and beautiful leather sofa. I must say, every part of this courthouse is meticulously well kept. Although, the positioning of this sofa puts one under the direct gaze of the judges. Every judge in this courthouse's history has had a quite the beard... ...and has gallantly parted with their beloved head of hair, I see. Being a judge must be a very stressful career.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Egad...! What a cold stare he's giving me! However, as a disciple of Von Karma, there is no option but to win!</thought> ..................!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh...... He's good! The power of his cold stare rivals my own!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">..................zzz.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............! <thought>He's sleeping while standing up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This trial is about to resume. I should stay on the premises.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial will resume shortly. Please wait a moment, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I was already well aware of that. <thought>Shortly, or in a moment... Which one is it? Be specific!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bookshelf, huh...? <thought>"Compendium of Laws for Beginners"... I don't have the time to read this and second-guess myself now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's true that the Yatagarasu showed up at the Cohdopian Embassy... ...what could he or she have been better?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmph... No doubt to steal any suspicious accounting records and release them publicly. Or, more likely, to steal secrets from the Cohdopian Embassy itself... ...since the item that the Yatagarasu stole from there was sent to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What was it that the Yatagarasu sent to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...I don't know the details. Anything related to the Yatagarasu is getting the top-secret treatment. Still, I find it very ironic. By returning the stolen item to the police, it was proof positive that the Yatagarasu... ...had infiltrated the embassy on the same day the staff member was killed. Criminals have a way of incriminating themselves, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would have to be the first time the Yatagarasu has left evidence behind, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Yes, indeed. If you wish to learn more about the Yatagarasu, then I suggest you ask Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">He happens to be the prosecutor in charge of the Yatagarasu case, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's the prosecutor in charge of both the KG-8 Incident and the Yatagarasu case? Mr. Faraday really has a lot on his plate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...What is it, little girl?</line>
<line speaker="???">......... ...You're scary, mister.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you need something?</line>
<line speaker="???">Umm... I want to trade these coins with you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A fistful of dimes, quarters, and pennies... but it looks like you've exactly a dollar. Is this what you want?</line>
<line speaker="???">Thanks! That's exactly what I needed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could that child be here to watch the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">How disrespectful for a child like that to be running around inside the courthouse! Does no one have respect for this country's judicial system anymore!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The paperwork for the prosecutor substitution is complete!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Why you! Do you even know how much time there is left before the trial resumes!?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">I... I-I'm so sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I can have you mopping up this courthouse instead of protecting it in an instant!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">! *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's no bother, sir. Not being completely prepared could prove to be a prefect handicap for me.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmph. A proud one you are. You had better collect the evidence from Faraday and prepare yourself. It's time for your debut, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Just what is going on!? Why isn't Faraday here yet!? How is it possible that the defense is not prepared yet, either!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Bailiff... Where is Mr. Faraday?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">I-I'm not sure... I wasn't really paying attention...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you must be the one Mr. von Karma recommended... I hear this will be your first trial. I look forward to seeing how you perform. Oh, by the way, was there someone celebrating a birthday during the recess? I could have sworn that I heard a popper going off... Come to think of it... The other day with my grandson...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sir, it looks like the trial is about to resume, however...</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Yes, it will be all but impossible to prove the witness a liar... ...without the evidence from Faraday! What is that balsted buffon up to!?</line>
<line speaker="???">I-I-It's an emergency, siiiiiirs!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">There shall be no yelling in this sacred hall of law! Bailiff! Remove that man from this courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="???">P-Please... wait! You have to listen to me! There's an emergency! Defendant Lobby No. 2...! M-Mr. Faraday and the defendant... Th-The two of them... They're... They're both dead, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Stay back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ungh...!</line>
<line speaker="???">...No one's allowed on the crime scene... Period.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just who does this... oddball think he is...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">This is becoming quite the hotspot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Isn't she Mr. Rell's defense attorney...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">H-Hey, you! No running in the hallway, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And who are you to tell me what to do? <thought>I'll never find out what's going on like this. It's time for some civil discourse.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This soda looks like it's seen its fair share of use. And it looks like another part of the courthouse is visible from the window... Ack! My eyes have locked with my reflection's eyes in the barred window! As a student of Von Karma, I refuse to back down!</thought> ..................I won.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Excuse me, but... who are you?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Detective Tyrell Badd. ...Homicide.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was informed of the situation and came as quickly as possible... ...so how did you arrive and inspect the body before me?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Faraday requested for me to testify in the trial... Plain and simple.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday requested that you be here...?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I've already contacted HQ about the situation. I've... got nothing to say to you... kid.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>K-Kid!?</thought> I'm Mr. Faraday's substitute in today's trial. Therefore, I insist that you update me on the situation!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't back down here. I have a right ot know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Do I need to teach you a thing or two about how to talk to adults, kid!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! <thought>Is he threatening me? I-Is he going for his gun!? I-It's just a mirror... How dare he trick me like that!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Faraday was stabbed to death with some kind of blade. And he had a gun in his hand. The other man, a Mr. Mack Rell, was shot and killed. He was found holding a bloody knife in this hand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Was there anyone else who went into Defendant Lobby No. 2?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah, that big lug over there. His name's Gumshoe. He was in charge of guarding the place... He's claiming that no one else entered the room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, then... they must have killed each other, correct!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Such impudence! This guy is really testing my patience!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why was I not informed that you were going to testify in court?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Homicides aren't my only gig; the Yatagarasu case is also one of my assignments.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So you were called upon to comment on the Yatagarasu's characteristics... ...in order to assess if Mr. Faraday really was the Yatagarasu or not?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Well, well... Looks like you just might have a brain after all in that head of yours, son.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>S-Son...!? I'm not your son, "pops"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Does showing that off make you feel like a big, strong prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">O-Of course not! I was simply proving my title of prosecutor to you.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I see. But most prosecutors don't go around flaunting those tings... It's like a detective walking around outside with his badge flashing in the sunlight. ...Show that off too much, and before you know it, you'll be elbow-deep in angry criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That would... definitely be a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd... I'd like to ask you about this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please pay attention?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Heh... I'm listening. But I've got nothing to say... End of story.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Very well. <thought>Why didn't you say that in the first place?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have a minute?</line>
<line speaker="???">...You know, I'm not really into talking to people I don't know. Especially at a time like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah. I apologize for not introducing myself before bothering you. My name is Miles Edgeworth. I was to take Mr. Faraday's place in court.</line>
<line speaker="???">Edgeworth, huh...? Never heard of you. So Faraday's substitute is a newbie, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll have you know, madam, that I studied under Manfred von Karma. Do not take me for some naïve novice.</line>
<line speaker="???">..................Phwwh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Mu...Phwwh. "Do not take me for some naïve novice"...!? Ahahahahahahahahahahahaha! So, you're a student of Von Karma! I should have... Phwwh...! Those clothes are a dead giveaway!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">S-Stop right there! These are the garments of one who gallantly presents the facts...</line>
<line speaker="???">Phwwh... Ah, thanks for the great laugh, but try not to make me laugh so much, OK?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wasn't trying to do anything of the sort!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahaha! Just kidding! I was just goofing around! By the way, do you know who I am? My name is Calisto Yew. And if you're telling the truth... then we were about to go head-to-head in court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, but of course! I have heard much about you, Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...! "Ah, but of course! I have heard much about you"... You're a regular Shakespeare!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Did I say something funny...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to update me on the situation.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I don't really know anything. ...Why don't you try talking to those detectives over there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that's the case, then why are you here?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh............ Ahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Urgh! What's so funny!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">It's just that the way you speak is so tactless! The person I was going against in court until only a little while ago was just murdered. It's not like I could go back into the courtroom pretending as though nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! ......That's a good point. I apologize for asking such an insensitive question.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...It's fine. Don't worry about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It is a shame that we will not be able to face each other. It was to be my first trial, too.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, was that a declaration of war? How nice it is to be young and carefree. And what a nice squeaky clean badge you've got yourself there. I'm jealous!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm sure its gleam will dull over time with experience.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Are you saying your reputation will also tarnish over time with it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! That's not what I meant!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Well, you just can't avoid some things in life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'll never allow my badge or my reputation to become tarnished.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew... What do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Actually Edgeworth, I'm interested in finding out what you think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I don't really know all that much about it.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Hmm... Then, I don't really know all that much about it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh! Ahahahahahaha! Sorry! Guess I can't be of any service!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I shouldn't push her too much... She'll just start laughing again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="???">...Who, me? Hey, pal... ...it's common courtesy to tell someone your name first before asking their's!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! Point taken. My name is Miles Edgeworth. I am a district prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="???">A prosecutor? I've never seen a prosecutor as young as you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I've told you my name. Now would you mind telling me yours?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Dick Gumshoe! And just recently, I achieved my dream of becoming a detective! More than a dream... It's what I was born to do! Wait... Maybe I should check and make sure I'm not really in some crazy dream first...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This detective is entirely too excited to be at a murder scene...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So Detective Gumshoe... Would you mind telling me what you know about the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You know that I don't have to tell you anything, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that. But it would behoove you to fill me in on what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Wow, you're a proud one for such a youngster, aren't you? Well, anyway, Detective Badd is the one in charge... ...so you're just gonna have to ask him for all the details, OK? As for me, I was guarding the door to Defendant Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So you were the guard detail... Did you notice anything strange while you were on duty?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I freaked out when I heard a gunshot, and then I kinda froze.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You're a detective and a measly gunshot scared you that much? ......Then again, I can hardly claim to not know what it's like to hear one at close range...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then, Detective Badd came running to the scene. We went into Lobby No. 2 together, and both men were lying there, dead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is that everything?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm......... Yeah, that's it. I was in the hallway the whole time, but I didn't hear a single peep of a struggle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting... Other than the gunshot, he didn't hear a single sound of commotion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mentioned that you've only recently become a detective, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it! I'm a brand spankin' new detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So that means you've probably never seen a real Prosecutor's Badge, right? If you so desired to see one, I just might be able to make your day.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't have to go through the trouble, pal, because a real man has a police badge! And someday, I'm gonna become an Ace Detective, just like Detective Badd!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Did I say something wrong, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... ...Forget it, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you were guarding the door to Lobby No. 2 at the time of the crime, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's right! And I'll have you know, not even a single ant got by me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really? Are you sure that not even a single ant slipped in?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, umm... I-I guess if we're talking about "slipped in", then maybe a frog or something did!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It would appear that my point also completely slipped by you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you have any insight on this, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm, well... As a detective I'd rather see something that is actually related to the case, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And here I thought this was related enough...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Interesting. They're selling special court-themed food products here. Many of them seem sort of troublesome and suspicious. Objection...! I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, a drink vending machine. .................. Ack! <thought>Now is not the time to be pondering what kind of drink I want!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Defendant Lobby No. 1 is through here. The incident took place in Lobby No. 2 next door... I shouldn't allow myself to be sidetracked like this. I'd better get a move on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A poster of the Judge. There's a slogan of some sort on it... </thought> "Every strike of my gavel brings the truth closer to me, and my hair farther away." .................. <thought>Is this a promotional poster for the court or a hair growth product...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>A fire extinguisher... If one were to be hit in the head with this... ...I suppose the victim would lose a memory or two. But it's not as though I'D ever be so foolish as to be struck by one of these.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>First, I need to get a handle on the situation. Perhaps, I should talk to some people.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Ms. Yew! There is someone here who wishes to see you...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">......Who is it?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">A Cohdopian Embassy staff member by the name of Manny Coachen.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Wh--!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What's going on? Detective Badd and Ms. Yew's moods just changed all of a sudden. Wait a second... Wasn't Manny Coachen...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">I'll be right there.</line>
<line speaker="Coachen">It's nice to see you again... Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Why are you here? I have no desire to ever see you again.</line>
<line speaker="Coachen">Now, now... Actually, would you mind stepping outside for a brief chat?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">........Fine. Let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Von Karma...? It's been a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I knew you would show up. You usually do when the Yatagarasu is involved, and I see this case is no exception.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you know Detective Badd, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Yes. He's like an old bloodhound that never leaves the scene of a crime. If only he would get a promotion and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's the crime scene where a detective is most useful and effective.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmph! It's not like I don't know that. Moving on though, Badd. The man that I just passed by... ...was he not the suspect from the KG-8 Incident!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So I was right...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Just what is that man doing, wandering around here!? That Faraday... I can't believe he let such an easy catch get away! Imbecile! I would've proved his guilt in three minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Von Karma! ...I think you've said enough for now. It's in poor taste to speak like that about the departed.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmph...Very well. Back on topic... I'm placing Edgeworth in charge of the investigation here...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="???">Papa! How can you place him in charge!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm here for summer vacation, what else?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Franziska von Karma... So she is here on vacation from Germany... She is the daughter of Manfred von Karma and a student of his, who's also junior to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're the one who's junior to me! And don't you forget it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're not conveniently avoiding the Bar Examination, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah... If you were able to pass, then I'll have absolutely no trouble at all. I'll never allow myself to lose to you! Never!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why does she always have to be this competitive...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Anyway... Papa... Are you really assigning Miles Edgeworth to cover the case?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Yes, I am. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, you know... I'm close to becoming a prosecutor myself... And I am 100% confident that I can do a better job than him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's just like Franziska. She has no problem bad-mounting someone right in front of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yeah...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">These two will be conducting the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">What? You want me to let both of these kids loose on the crime scene?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hah. This is a perfect opportunity for them to work on their prosecutorial skills.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">A crime scene is not a place for children to be messing around in!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I'm the one with the authority over this crime scene, Badd. ...And I will not tolerate complaining.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Knngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Edgeworth! Franziska! I leave this case to the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Understood, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, Papa.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I'll go take care of the paperwork now. Remember, I'll accept nothing but a perfect report from the both of you. Do not disappoint me.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hold up, Von Karma.........! I still... haven't agreed to this!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's been quite some time, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This will be the perfect chance for us... ...to see which of us is truly worthy of the Von Karma name.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would it kill you to at least say hello?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Unngh... Umm... Long time no see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very good.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just because you became a prosecutor first doesn't mean you can act all proud!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>S-She hasn't changed a bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! As I was saying, we shall see which one of us is worthy of the Von Karma name...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">For cryin' out loud... I've been reduced to a babysitter...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like Mr. von Karma was successful in convincing the detective. That's just like him; he never fails.</thought> Now, I'd appreciate it if you could quickly run me through the facts, Detective Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You're better off checking things out on your own.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Very well. <thought>Seems like getting help from Detective Badd will be a most arduous task...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... Is the only real explanation that they killed each other simultaneously...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! You should listen to someone until they are finished talking!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'll only say it one more time... This is a competition to see who is truly worthy of the Von Karma name!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A competition...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The person that figures out the truth first wins.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... So the person who doesn't discover the truth is a dishonor to the name?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Exactly! I don't care that you became a prosecutor before me... ...I simply refuse to hear any more foolish things come from your foolishly, foolish mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Fine, whatever makes you happy.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Can I take that as you accepting my challenge?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Once again... Whatever makes you happy.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah... Well then, let's begin the investigation, shall we? I'm going to find the perfect evidence and prettily present it like the professional I am.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Competing to discover the truth behind a crime -- how delightfully... childish.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">You kids, over there! <cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Kid"!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ha! Serves you right, Miles. He just called you a kid...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I said "kids", kid.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">H-How dare you call me a kid as well!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I'll do what I please. And I won't allow you to cause a ruckus on my crime scene. Hey, big guy. You're... going to watch over these two.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Detective Badd, sir! Now, do what I say from now on kids, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You'd better not get in our way, Scruffy! You'll feel the bite of my whip if you do!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">E-Eeek! Th-Then you, p-prosecutor boy! Let's get your investigation started already, alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Great. Now, even THAT detective is treating me like a child...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Alright! It's time to get investigating! Get a move on, prosecutor boy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...My name is Miles Edgeworth. And if you were to call me "prosecutor boy" one more time... ...it will be my duty as a prosecutor to "look into" your monthly salary.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!? And what would you do with my salary after you saw how much it was!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's up to you now, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really!? Sounds good, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's so naïve...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, may I have a word with you?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that both a knife and a gun were used as murder weapons.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah, it does.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That leads us to our first question of the investigation. Where did the men acquire the weapons?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...The gun was inside of Faraday's bag. It was a piece of evidence that was presented in the trial earlier today. It was used... to kill the Cohdopian Embassy staff member. But... I never heard anything about the knife. Mr. Rell was being held by the police. There's no way he could have brought it in. Which means it's possible that Faraday had the knife on him from the start as well.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Could it have been a piece of evidence that had yet to be presented...? But then, why doesn't Detective Badd know about it? Wait! What if...!?</thought> It's possible that Mr. Faraday brought the knife in under the guise of prosecutorial evidence. He could have then brought it out and attacked Mr. Rell with it.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Huh... Maybe you've got a brain in there after all, kid.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...! <thought>Is he going to treat me like a child forever!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It looks like Mr. Faraday attacked Mr. Rell first, who then counterattacked... That's the only logical conclusion you can draw from a scene like this.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Not yet. I feel that it's much too early to be drawing conclusions already. I must first find conclusive evidence, so as to ensure the honor of the Von Karma name.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a very tidy pile of plastic bags on the table... ...and yet, a portion of them wound up scattered on the floor as well. It's not likely that the ones on the floor were knocked over during a struggle... ...in which case, might there not be another explanation as to how they got there?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Another reason...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it's possible that the blood on the outside of the bag is related somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eek! Please get that blood away from me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. Whose blood is on this bag?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ummm... Hold on, let me ask the lab guy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright. Please hurry. ..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait 'till you get a load of this, pal! It's Mr. Faraday's! Oh, and the technician said they didn't find anything else on or in the bag, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It would appear that this bag is a very important piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, if you say so! I leave it in your hands, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That splotch on Mr. Faraday's hand... I wonder if it might be the ink from his fountain pen.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, let's ask the lab guy!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Detective Gumshoe! I can confirm that the substance on Mr. Faraday' hand is the ink from his fountain pen!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I see. Good work! Ahhh... You know, I've always wanted to say that! Even if it was just one time in my life!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... <thought>If Mr. Faraday wrote with his fountain pen in his left hand... I think it's fair to assume he was left-handed.</thought> It appears that Mr. Faraday's pen is very important to our case as well.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">OK, if you say so, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I'm so excited, pal! This is my first real crime scene! Let's get investigating!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... Detective Gumshoe... I thought investigations were supposed to be conducted in a calm, collected manner.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmph! What do you know about how to run an investigation, little boy prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that at the very least, I have greater grasp than you of what happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why you! You don't know any more than me, pal! Look, you just stay behind me, boy, and out of the way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ironic coming from the guy that's been a step behind me the entire case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This is my first time setting foot inside the courthouse! Who would've thought it'd be for my first case as a detective? But you know... I get the feeling I'll be coming here a lot more in the future!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...As a suspect, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Of course not, pal! Anyway, this lobby's actually pretty luxurious. I mean, for a defendant's lobby, it's got a pretty big TV... Oh! And there's that tea set on the table over there! Bet you didn't know that I like to drink tea... Wow, this room really is decked out. If it means spending time in here, maybe being a suspect isn't such a bad thing after all!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm beginning to suspect that leaving this detective in charge of anything might be bad... But he is right; this room is rather well furnished. And somewhere in this room, the truth is slumbering. It's time to find it, and give it a wake-up call!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So... Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, what is it, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr! Of all the people to call me that, this detective is by far the least qualified!</thought> ...I wanted to ask you about how the investigation is proceeding.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......See for yourself... pal. Ho ho! Do I do a great Detective Badd or what!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Has this man not a professional bone in his body!?</thought> Nngh... Very well, then I will inspect the victims' bodies myself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, so that's a prosecutor's badge, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mentioned that you've only recently become a detective, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it! I'm a brand spankin' new detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... So that means you've probably never seen a real Prosecutor's Badge, right? If you so happened to want to take a look, I just might be able to make your day.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You don't have to go through the trouble, pal, because a real man has a police badge! And someday, I'm gonna become an Ace Detective, just like Detective Badd!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Did I say something wrong, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Let's return to the investigation, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the whole truth there, pal. I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, you were guarding the door to Lobby No. 2 at the time of the crime, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's right! And I'll have you know, not even a single ant got by me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really? Are you sure that not even a single ant slipped in?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, umm... Guess if we're talking about "slipped in", then maybe a frog or something did!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It would appear that my point also completely slipped you by, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeek! Hey, pal! I'd appreciate it if you didn't point that thing at me, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't get cheeky with me, Detective! I simply wished to show it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And? You got a point in showing it to me!? B-Because I don't even have a single penny on me, so you're out of luck, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well THAT was an unusual reaction to being shown a piece of evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That knife is one of the murder weapons, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it is the weapon that took Mr. Faraday's life.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooonnnrrrgh... There's blood stuck on the blade, and it's still fresh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're in the Homicide Division, correct? You'll be seeing a lot more blood. Even if it's not your cup of tea, you might as well get used to it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Rnnngh... But the sight of blood isn't something I want to get used to...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't think of it as seeing blood, but rather, as a representation of the killer. If viewed in that sense, you begin to see how the killer operates.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...You're right, pal! Thanks for the fresh perspective. I feel so much better now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmph... I'm glad someone does.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So that's what Mr. Faraday uses to write with. It's in a completely different league from my 10 for $9.95 ballpoint pens!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It looks to be well-used.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, he probably used it a lot at work. I heard he was really passionate about his job. I just can't believe he died like this... Poor guy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As for why he died... I suppose I'll find that out once we solve this case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This decorative plant's foliage is quite nice. It's actually soothing to be around it. Hmm... Perhaps I should purchase one for my room.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like this sofa is ready to be disposed of...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's so soft! I could sleep for all 25 hours of the day on this thing!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. <thought>If only I could dispose of him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...? Why are there plastic bags scattered all around?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Those bags are for keeping evidence safe, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that much, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You sure are good at this stuff, aren't you, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Normally, I'd be happy when someone compliments me, but when it's this guy... Anyway, could these plastic bags be evidence of a fight (Plastic bags strewn about - Plastic bags used to store evidence are strewn all over the floor.</thought> between the two men?)</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like Mr. Faraday fell on top of Mr. Rell. At first glance, it seems like they must have killed each other, however...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Using logic, the only conclusion is... Aha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What was that outburst for!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My detective's instinct just hit me real hard! It was Mr. Rell that feel first, see!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You don't need a detective's instinct for that! It's common sense!! <thought>But I suppose we won't know much more than that until after I examine the bodies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like Mr. Faraday died while holding the gun in his right hand...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So he shot Mr. Rell, and then fell on top of him while still gripping onto the gun...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...I guess that does seem kinds strange, huh? I mean, why would Mr. Faraday know how to fire a gun!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's not exactly rocket science; even I know how to pull a trigger. ...Although I doubt I'll ever need to use one.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I hope I never have to fire a gun, either, pal. But it sure look cool to hold a gun in your hands!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears that the police's screening procedures need a thorough review... Anyway, I should jot down some notes about the handgun in Mr. Faraday's hand.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">His hand is all black down here, see? ...I wonder what it could be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... If you look closely... ...this blotching pattern resembles an ink stain <thought>Ink stain - Mr. Faraday has ink on his left hand. Why is there ink on such a place anyway?</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">An... ink stain?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. I usually get ink on my own hand when I use my feather pen.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A feather pen...? I've never seen one before. Sure you aren't just making it up, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday... How ironic it is for him to lose his life in a courthouse.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, why did it to be like this? I don't know what to say... I can't believe this happened while I was on watch, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Rather than beathing yourself up, you should spend your time continuing the investigation. Didn't you become a detective in order to solve crimes?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then get back to work. Find out the cause of his murder!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">R-Right! I'm on it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">First he killed a Cohdopian Embassy staff member, then he was murdered himself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">This guy... wasn't exactly an angel, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? What makes you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, he's been hauled in to the precinct several times for theft and assault, pal. So yeah, he's definitely the type to have committed a murder or two.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, he did admit to killing Mr. Deid Mann.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Good point, pal! I knew my detective's intuition was telling me something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective's intuition...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup! Do you know about it? It's a special feeling that all detec--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We don't have time for this conversation right now. Let's return to the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Looks like Mr. Rell died with the knife in his hand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's some blood stuck on it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then, he must've used this as a weapon. Yup, no doubt about it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was Mr. Faraday carrying this on his personage...? Did he bring this as a piece of evidence for the trial? Or... did he bring it with a very different intention in mind...? I should jot some notes down about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Rell's cause of death was from being shot, correct? That's what we think, but it's hard to tell with him lying face down. Death is bad enough, but it's truly lamentable that someone would try to hide the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...Um, are you sure they were trying to hide something?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't confirm Mr. Rell's cause of death with his body positioned like that.</thought> Detective Badd, I'd like to examine the bodies in firther detail, if possible...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What's this? You're not able to form a theory with them the way they are?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe an examination of the bodies is vital to finding the perfect evidence, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmm... I suppose you do have a point. Well!? Hurry up and get on with it!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Labbie.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! We've taken enough photos of the scene, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...And there you have it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Do you not approve?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Investigation of a crime scene is the work of a detective. So don't touch a thing. Hey, big fella, turn over the bodies for me, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-OK......... Please forgive me, Mr. Faraday, sir...!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Gumshoe... do not get emotionally involved. Remember, you're a detective!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yes, sir! Understood, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It looks like Mr. Faraday was stabbed with this knife that Mr. Rell is holding.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeooooowch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's wrong, Detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My stomach started to hurt from just thinking abour being stabbed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Just keep your mind on the case, alright!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Shot in the chest...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It takes some guts to fire a gun in a courthouse... I mean, I've been a detective for a whole week and I STILL haven't fired a single round yet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There aren't any burn marks on his clothes. That must mean...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait... Burn marks...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A round grows very hot as it is discharged from a firearm. Therefore, burn marks are usually left when a shot is fired from point blank range. Ergo, Mr. Rell must have been shot from at least a yard or two away.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You sure do know a buncha neat stuff for your age, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Apparently, this detective has as much comon knowledge as your everyday marsupial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's something in his breast pocket. It's... a mirror shards <thought>Fountain pen in pocket - The fountain pen in Mr. Faraday's pocket has an especially nice nib.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you know, I always keep a pencil behind my ear! It's because Detective Badd is always telling me... "You should always write your name on everything you own!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes... Somehow, you do strike me as quite a forgetful individual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's a knife wound in his chest here, see?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wonder if the wound matches the knife Mr. Rell is holding?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Labbie.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! Verifying now, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Make it quick.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>From the look of things... ...one could deduce that the knife Mr. Rell is holding is what killed Mr. Faraday.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday is holding a gun in his right hand.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the one Mr. Rell got blown away by, right?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Labbie, your answer.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Yes, sir! We've found that the ballistic markings do match that gun.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, um... Ballistic markings are, um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are the figurative fingerprints a gun leaves on a bullet when fired. Every gun leaves its own unique ballistic markings. Therefore, by looking at the markings on a bullet, you can tel which gun it came from.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, that's it! O-Of course, I already knew all about that, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Maybe you'd be better off going back to the academy.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeek! Come on, sir! Cut me some slack, will ya!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the bullet that was fired from this gun is what felled Mr. Rell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let us now try to understand how the two men died. First, Mr. Faraday took the gun and the knife out from today's trial evidence... ...then he aimed the gun at Mr. Rell and fired. However, Mr. Rell managed to grab the knife and counter Mr. Faraday while being shot. Then, the two men fell together where they stood. ...That is my theory, in any case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What a crazy way to go...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Still... something about that explanation just doesn't seem right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I believe I now have a firmer grasp on what happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ahh... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you figure something out?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This is a competition, Miles! And as such, I'd appreciate it if you didn't talk to me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* As you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are some plastic bags stacked up on the table. There's a tea set, too... but there doesn't seem to be any sign of a disturbance.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... The table's all neat and tidy <thought>Neat and tidy table - The tea set and plastic bags on top of the table are completely undisturbed.</thought>. Maybe... they were super quiet in their scuffle!? After all, I didn't hear anything from out in the hallway, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe the plastic bags scattered on the floor are throwing us off?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The window is open, and... heh, there's a fresh, flowery scent in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ugh! The flowers in the garden down there are so gross and ghastly!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>......Do you think maybe you could try offering something useful for a change?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, at least there's no way someone escaped through this window, pal! They wouldn't wake up and smell the flowers after a fall from the third floor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are you willfully ignoring the fact that there are also iron bars on the windows <thought>Lobby No. 2 window - No human can climb through these barred windows. The scene of flowers is in the air.</thought>?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, I guess there's that, too. Either way, no one could get through these windows, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>They thought of everything when they were designing this courthouse. Very nice.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There's some stuff in the bag, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose this was Mr. Faraday's bag...</thought> It's probably the trial evidence I was supposed to collect from him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Th-This is the evidence!? Ah! I'd better not touch it! I'll leave prints on it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Do you just not pay attention to anything you do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whoooaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What is it. Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">My TV at home is so tiny compared to this one, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Then perhaps you should purchase a more normal-sized television like this one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooh, let me see here... Wow! This thing is huge! Uwaah! And way too noisy!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're the noisy one, Scruffy!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Don't touch it! You'll get your fingerprints all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But...! I didn't touch it...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Preservation of the crime scene is the foundation of detective work!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The foundation, huh...? Sounds like something the rookie here needs to shore up on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The TV has been left on...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why are you looking at me like that!? It wasn't me! I didn't touch anything!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Gumshoe... you do know what will happen to you if you touch something again... Right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I won't touch anything! I won't even go anywhere near the TV, sir! A-And you! Get back to your investigation, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was planning to do so anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, do you have any thoughts on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Faraday and Rell... It looks like they killed each other to me... Although... there are a few things that just don't seem right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... And what would they be?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph...... Why don't you try thinking on your own first before you bother me, boy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Wh--!? Now I've been downgraded to just "boy"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This blood here is from Mr. Faraday, but there are no other clues to be found. Which begs the question... ...do I need to put this bag inside another bag to preserve it as evidence?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems Mr. Faraday was in the habit of using very nice fountain pens.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's the total opposite of me! I don't get these things at all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Well, I think the pencil behind your ear suits you just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Really!? You think so, pal!? Man, I knew it was worth something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........That wasn't exactly a compliment, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What? Me? I-I'd never do something like that!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>......Is it possible that she has never wanted to steal from a jewelry store before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... This looks like a quality nib.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, let me test it out, pal! Ooh... This is really, really... Ack! I got ink all over my hand!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Detective Gumshoe. Don't EVER play with the evidence like that again!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I guess there's not much left to investigate, huh? They really did kill each other...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No... We can't conclude that quite yet. There's still something I find very peculiar here. The theory that they simply killed one another is too simplistic in this case. In fact, there is actually a contradiction that shows there is another possibility!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way, pal! Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I suppose I will just have to show you the conflict in this crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a clear contradiction with the evidence here in this spot!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Um... Really, pal? Because I don't see anything wrong there...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah... I was merely testing you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Don't make me arrest you for lying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ngh! <thought>I guess I was mistaken...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now we come face to face with the contradiction I spoke of, and it is... this! Mr. Faraday used his left hand to write with his fountain pen. Ergo, he is left-handed. And yet, the handgun is in his right hand! Don't you find it odd that the left-handed Mr. Faraday would hold the gun in his right hand? That. lady and gentlemen... is the great contradiction haunting this crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you're right, pal! That does seem kinda strange! But... How could something like that happen?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The facts add up to one conclusion, and one alone. Someone else put the gun in Mr. Faraday's hand after he died.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Someone else...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Plastic bags scattered on the floor, and a gun in the wrong hand... I sense the presence of a shadowy figure behind this case. A person of vile intent who is serious about keeping the truth from us!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Here's the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"It is probable for that Mr. Rell survived for a short time after he was shot. However, Mr. Faraday died instantaneously from his stabbing." Interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like we now know everything we need to know about this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure we know everything...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course! The incident began with Mr. Faraday attempting to get his revenge. The prosecutor went into a rage from being accused, and tried to kill the defendant... But, the defendant fought back and they ended up killing each other. It's all very clear and simple. There is absolutely no margin for doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really believe that to be the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah! Are you saying that just because I figured out the truth before you... ...that you don't want to believe it's true?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's alright. If you disagree with my argument, then prove me wrong. Well, if there are any contradictions to be found, that is...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't worry, I will.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Faraday's death was instantaneous, while Mr. Rell survived for a short time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Faraday's death was instantaneous, therefore, he must've attacked first... Proving that logic to be false is probably the fastest way to show her that she's wrong. In that case, I should first look for any holes in her theory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Faraday's death was instantaneous, while Mr. Rell survived for a short time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you truly believe that Mr. Faraday died instantaneously?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have the murder report right here... "Mr. Faraday died instantaneously of shock due to being stabbed in the chest." There, you see? It's been documented, clear as day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">From this, it is obvious that Mr. Faraday died after he shot Mr. Rell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday shot Mr. Rell before he died...? Do you have any basis for that statement?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Your foolishness has no end, does it? Now, I hate to repeat myself, however... ..."Mr. Faraday died instantaneously." That's all the basis I need.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, so if Mr. Faraday died instantaneously... ...then he must have attacked Mr. Rell before being stabbed.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're finally beginning to catch on, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And Mr. Rell, while on the brink of death, stole Mr. Faraday's knife and stabbed him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you believe that the dying Mr. Rell stole the knife from Mr. Faraday?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Rell became desperate as he did not want to die. Human beings can do amazing things when they are put to the test. So, the two men struggled... And in the end, Mr. Rell was able to grab the knife and stab Mr. Faraday. The messy condition of this room is a testament to their struggle. Hmm... Yes, my logic is perfectly sound.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Can you really say that it's "perfect"?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you insinuating?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nothing... However, I can't let what you said slide by without further inquiry. One must be clear and precise, so if you could append that statement to your testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"And Mr. Rell, while on the brink of death, stole Mr. Faraday's knife and stabbed him." to "They struggled, and Mr. Rell used the last of his strength to counterattack Mr. Faraday."</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">They struggled, and Mr. Rell used the last of his strength to counterattack Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About this statement...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Rell used all of his remaining strength to take the knife and defend himself. One can easily see that they had a violent struggle. Of course, it's nothing compared to what my riding crop can do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How does one compare the damage her crop can do with the state of this room!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Furthermore, all the plastic bags on the floor in this room... ...were scattered there due to the fight. Is there anything else that I can explain for you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, that will be fine...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Those are the facts of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Claiming speculation as fact already? Don't you feel that the evidence is a bit lacking?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You'll find all the evidence you need just by looking around this room. Mr. Faraday collapsed on top of Mr. Rell... In addition, Mr. Faraday died instantaneously, making a counterattack impossible. Furthermore, the room is a total mess from their fight... Heh, I dare say that there's more evidence here than you could whip a whip at.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It looks like she's becoming more and more confident... And... looking at this place, she might have a right to be. After all, everything here seems to support her theory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like you're starting to see my point. I've as good as won our little competition.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>There's something strange about Franziska's theory... I should compare her claim with the data I've gathered thus far. I just know there's a contradiction somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the two men were fighting, their struggle would've surely caused quite a bit of noise. However, Detective Gumshoe testified that he heard absolutely nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah. You place too much faith in that detective's testimony, you know. But for the sake of argument, let's say there wasn't a fight. How, then, did Mr. Rell get his hands on the knife?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday's bag was sitting right here in Lobby No. 2. It is not hard to imagine that perhaps Mr. Rell saw a chance and took it out at some point!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.................. So... What you're saying this: Mr. Rell took a chance when he saw the opportunity, and took the knife from the bag. And then Mr. Faraday shot Mr. Rell after being stabbed...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm......... <thought>Isn't there something... strange in Franziska's statement just now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It... does all add up.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...So then, there's no problem, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Taking random shots in the dark is unbecoming of a disciple of Von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Now, take a step back and think for a change!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-nngh... <thought>Is Franziska's explanation of things really perfect? I'm going to carefully review what she said once again in my head!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Rell took a chance when he saw the opportunity, and took the knife from the bag. And then Mr. Faraday shot Mr. Rell after being stabbed...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As I suspected... There is definitely something wrong with her theory!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah... If you have nothing to say, then I suppose that I win--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, as I suspected, something doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait, something doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's simply not possible for Mr. Faraday to have shot Mr. Rell after being stabbed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is the piece of evidence that proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah! And what is this supposed to prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........? I'm still not seeing it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... In that case, I'll just have to try and explain it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... You should know by now that you can't fool me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaarghn! <thought>I guess this evidence was unrelated after all... I have to think this over one more time... Mr .Rell grabbed the knife from Mr. Faraday's bag when he wasn't paying attention... And Mr. Faraday shot Mr. Rell after being stabbed by the knife. But it just doesn't add up, and I have the evidence that proves that it doesn't!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to the coroner's report, Mt. Faraday died instantaneously, meaning... ..that he died immediately upon being stabbed by the knife! Ergo, he could not possibly have fired the gun after that!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Ooh, you got me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But of course.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well then, if the report is correct, then there is only one correct explanation. If we suppose that Mr. Rell attacked first... ...then Mr. Faraday, who died instantaneously, would have been unable to kill Mr. Rell.  Therefore, Mr. Rell must have stabbed Mr. Faraday after he was shot. Then they both died. That is the only explanation that make logical sense!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Negating your opponent's ideas in order to prove your own theory... I see you've been studying, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I just wanted to explain it to you as simply as possible. before you foolishly propose a foolish theory that only a foolish fool like you could.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... How naïve of you to believe that only your opinions are valid... ...and still expect to discover the truth that the crime scene offers you... Franziska... You've still got a ways to go.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you talking about!? Are you saying there's a flaw in my logic!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Mr. Faraday dies instantly... And the fact that he did is what gives rise to the contradiction in this scene!</thought> The contradiction here in this crime scene is...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a contradiction in the order you say the crime took place in.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Oh? In that case, why don't you prove the contradiction already!? Miles Edgeworth! Remember that we Von Karmas must strive to be perfect in every way!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Nnghhoooh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And that kind of half-baked answer can hardly be called "perfect", now can it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe I should've given a more detailed explanation... Let's see... Mr. Faraday died instantaneously...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The evidence bag is too far away from the bodies. If the bag that held the weapons was this far from the victims... ...then neither of the two men could have taken one out without the other noticing!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Heh. Weren't you the one who just said: "...perhaps Mr. Rell saw a chance and took it out at some point"? Now take some responsibility for your own claims!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooh...! <thought>Maybe I should've given a more detailed explanation... I need to think this over one more time. Let's see... Mr. Faraday died instantaneously...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me get this straight. What you are arguing is this: Mr. Faraday took the gun from his evidence bag and shot Mr. Rell. Then, the wounded Mr. Rell found an opportunity to take the knife and strike back. Upon being stabbed, Mr. Faraday died on the spot, and Mr. Rell died thereafter. If that's the case, then how do you explain this? Take a good look at the order in which their bodies are piled.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............N-No...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday's body is lying on top of Mr. Rell's. Therefore... ...Mr. Rell must have died before Mr. Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I-Impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, I agree that it seems strange no matter what angle you approach it from... ...which means that the real mystery behind this crime scene that we must solve is--!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No...! Not so fast, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What now...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I simply think that you ought to think a bit more outside the box... And that it's even clearer now that the incident started with Mr. Faraday's murderous intent!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She sure bounced back quickly. An explanation won't be enought this time. It's going to take some very decisive evidence to prove her wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It was just chance that Mr. Faraday's body fell on top of Mr. Rell's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I just know that Franziska's explanation isn't absolutely correct. All I have to do is find a hole in her logic! Once I do, I can then present her with the evidence that proves the contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't think you could ask for a more perfect witness testimony. Wouldn't you agree, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Not really. It's hardly perfect when there's a gaping hole in it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It was just chance that Mr. Faraday's body fell on top of Mr. Rell's.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About that--</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">*sigh* Pressing someone's testimony in order to gain some time to think... You're a real one-trick pony, aren't you? It's too bad your trick only works on fools.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That wasn't my intent! I simply wish for more details as to how Mr. Faraday ended up on top of Mr. Rell...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Someone's impatient. I was just about to explain everything to you. So do you think you could hold on for a minute!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argh! ......Franziska, I'll make you a deal. I'll hold on if you hold on to that whip of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh, I'll hold on to it alright, As I whip you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, now that you've quieted down a bit, I'd like to continue, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The two bodies fell into a pile...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The two fell on top of each other...? Don't you find that to be just a bit strange?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Not at all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aarngh! <thought>I can see it in her eyes... She's dead set against me from the bottom of her heart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... Once I'm done here, you'll see that there's nothing strange at all! Now then, the two men fell into a pile...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...which indicates that they attacked each other at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What do you mean by "they attacked each other at the same time"?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I assume Mr. Faraday had the two different weapons in his hands... He made to attack Mr. Rell while holding both the knife and revolver... and then... After Mr. Faraday fired the gun... ...Mr. Rell grabbed the knife as he was falling, and stabbed Mr. Faraday. That is how Mr. Rell wound up on bottom with Mr. Faraday on top. At close range, that is more than possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, it's possible, but...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, if you have any other ideas... ...then show me what you've got!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, I will. And to that extent... I'd like for you to append what you just said to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... I don't see any point to that, but as you please.</line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"...which indicates that they attacked each other at the same time." to "That fact indicates that they attacked each other at the same time from close range."</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That fact indicates that they attacked each other at the same time from close range.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're saying that they attacked each other at the same time from close range?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Exactly. Mr. Faraday pointed the gun at Mr. Rell's chest and pulled the trigger. Mr. Rell then took the knife from Mr. Faraday and stabbed him before he fell unconscious. The dead Mr. Faraday instantly fell on top of Mr. Rell from the stabbing... ...pinning Mr. Rell under him, where he died shortly thereafter. And that's how they ended up on top of each other with no contradictions to be seen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It really doesn't matter in the slightest that they fell in the opposite order.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really believe they fell in the exact opposite order in which they attacked?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... You're not listening to a word that I'm saying!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">They both attacked each other at the same time, and Mr. Rell fell first by chance... ...leaving Mr. Faraday to just happen to fall on top of him. Then, Mr. Rell died shortly thereafter, pinned underneath Mr. Faraday. That's how it happened.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So the two men attacked each other, with Mr. Rell randomly falling down first...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The fact that the order that they attacked each other in... ...varies from the order they fell in doesn't cause a problem for me. However, there's definitely one certain aspect that I'm having trouble swallowing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you believe they killed each other at close range...? Sorry, but that's impossible. Just as it is written in the crime scene notes... ...the firing of the handgun did not leave a gunpowder burn on Mr. Rell's clothes. Therefore... Mr. Rell and the gun... ...must have been separated by a distance of at lease two or three yards!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes... This is by far the biggest contradiction! The two bodies are piled up on each other, yet the gun was fired from a distance. And with there being no chance that Mr. Rell moved that far after being shot... ...that leaves only one possible explanation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What a completely foolish line of foolish thought from a thoroughly foolish fool! If I'm not right... ...then who was it that made the first move with the intent to kill, huh!? Who!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The person that attacked first with murderous intent? That would be...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal. What you're saying now contradicts with what you said earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, um... <thought>I have to re-think this... carefully!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Rell, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You know... ...your foolishly foolish foolhardy idea is making me feel just as foolish as you! The murder weapons used in this case were taken straight from Mr. Faraday's bag. The fact that Mr. Faraday had items that could be used to kill in his possession... ...is something Mr. Rell wouldn't have known!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>She's right, of course... Mr. Rell wouldn't have known what was inside Mr. Faraday's bag... I have to re-think this... carefully!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here in this room... ...contradictions appear no matter which man we claim attacked first. Thus, there can be only one explanation. There was... a third person here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It was that third person who killed both Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell... ...and set their bodies up to make it look like a double murder... That third person is the real culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">............ Miles Edgeworth... There's just one thing you're missing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Evidence, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Exactly. Everything you've said up until now is nothing but a story played out in your head. However, this is where the real test begins. Can you prove that there was a third person involved in this crime!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course. <thought>If a third person was truly here, that fact would resolve the glaring contradiction. The proof that this has all been a set-up, made to look like they killed each other... I'll present it, and lay bare the final piece of the puzzle that's not yet in place! What is the piece of evidence that proves there is a third person involved...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is that very evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...? And exactly how is this related? Do you think you could explain it to me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... There is no need for an explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, well, I have no idea how it's related, so could you please explain it to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Let me guess, you can't explain it can you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..............................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnaaargh! <thought>I-It would appear that I was wrong... But there is definitely a contradiction here... ...and it should resolve itself if there truly was a third person here... I just need to go over the evidence and my thoughts once again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The gun in Mr. Faraday's hand and the plastic bag with his blood on it... These two items point to the presence of a third person.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">How so...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Recall Detective Gumshoe's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was in the hallway the whole time, but I didn't hear a single peep of a struggle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If there wasn't a struggle in this room... ...then there shouldn't be any plastic bags on the ground. Meaning that someone else must've deliberately scattered them around!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you not see the possibility in this? Disregarding the gun for the moment... ...there's a high probability of blood splatter when a knife is used on a person. If the culprit held the knife with a plastic bag around it... ...they could use the bag to catch any blood splatter from when they withdrew the knife. Then, by spreading a few more plastic bags around, mixing the bloody one in with them... ...and arranging the room to make it look like there was a struggle between the two... ...they were able to conceal their presence!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Aaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Looks like... we've still got a long way to go in this investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What the heck's up with you, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Mr. Badd, I advise you to place Detective Gumshoe under arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh...WHAAAAAAAAAAAT!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......What's the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Hah! Looks like you're not man enough to discipline your own subordinates.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Don't you dare...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">That detective claims he was there, standing in front of the door the entire time... ...but I have it on good authority that it was all a giant lie!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">......!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ms. Yew! I ask that you please explain that last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I'll let His Honor explain it himself.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I saw it with my own eyes, I tell you! During the recess, there was a period of time when there was no one in the hallway!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">See, Mr. Badd? So I ask you, why would a detective who was supposedly doing his job the whole time... ...want to fabricate such a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Gumshoe. Did you... Did you kill Faraday...!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-Noooooooooooooooooo! Of course not, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It would appear that the one who set this whole crime scene up is that detective. ...Which basically renders his testimony a complete lie and wholly invalid. It looks like your "perfect" logic has just come tumbling down, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I was in the hallway the whole time, but I didn't hear a single peep of a struggle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Was that statement really a lie...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Detective Gumshoe. You're now a suspect in the murder of two men. Now, spit out the truth, or so help me...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I...I haven't lied to anyone, sir! Honest! I really was really there... I was in the hallway the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, I ask that you please do not act without my permission. After all, I am the one that is heading up this investigation, am I not?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Don't talk like you know what's going on, boy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All I want is for this investigation to run perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Perfection is the only wish of a disciple of Von Karma, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Therefore, before you take Detective Gumshoe into custody... ...I'd like to set the record straight on something.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...And what's that...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, what should I ask Detective Gumshoe about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, why were you missing from the hallway for a span of time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Look, pal! Like I said, I was there the whole time, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But there is testimony against you that...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Why are you wasting our time with a completely useless question!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The only logical reason as to why he was absent is that he was busy committing the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Anyone who says otherwise... is a fool!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk...! <thought>Maybe I should ask about something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. I take it that no one else was in that hallway at any time, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? O-Oh, of course not, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're being awfully defensive... Might you be hiding something from me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">W-Watch your mouth, pal! You can't go around saying stuff like that about me without any evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...! I suppose you're right. I have no evidence at this point...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! How can you be losing a battle of wits with THIS detective!? You're a disgrace!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk...! <thought>Maybe I should ask about something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose the one thing I'd liked clarified... ...is Detective Gumshoe's motive for committing this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... Motive, huh. Gumshoe... You got a grudge against Faraday or anything...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No, sir! Not me! Not a single bad thing against Mr. Faraday, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Is that a fact...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">...You really have a problem with lying, don't you, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm telling you... I AM NOT LYING!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The more unnatural you act, the more suspicious you become, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">If you want a motive, Edgeworth, I have one for you right here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Could you please share it with us? However, be forewarned that I won't hesitate to object to flights of fancy... ...because all I'm interested in is the perfect explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Ahahahahahaha! You're serious, aren't you? ...Fine. You amuse me, so I'll humor you with a little courtroom practice.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">It was... about a week ago.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-You totally misunderstand me, pal! No matter how mad I get, I could never hold a grudge!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Quiet. We can't trust anything you say...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sir...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... There's nothing wrong with the motive she proposed, per se... ...but there are some gaps in her logic that need to be filled in. Ms. Yew's "perfect explanation"... ...may not be so "perfect" at all...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">It was... about a week ago.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A week ago...? Then, you and Detective Gumshoe are acquaintances?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwh...! No way. I only met him in-person today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then how did you know about Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, I've seen him around before.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I saw the detective get chewed out by a livid Faraday in front of the precinct.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Faraday was upset?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yeah. You know what else? Mr. Faraday isn't exactly known to get angry often... ...Phwwh! Phwwwwwh! But there he was, totally beet red in the face! ...Ahem. And the offending detective just stood there, pale as a ghost, like he was about to die!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just like the face he's making now, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Arnngh... I'm completely innocent I tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh! Phwwwwh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The poor man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! ...Ahem. I was quite the scene with the detective.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">He stood there super pale, as Mr. Faraday yelled, "That's a salary cut for you, you nitwit!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You just stood there, watching this unfold in front of you?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yeah. I have to say it was really enjoyable, too. But that's why when I saw Detective Gumshoe earlier, I knew to steer clear of him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way... I thought it was because I had something stuck on my face!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...! Ahahahahahaha! But you do!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What've I got stuck on my face?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Let's start with your eyes, nose, mouth... Oh, and those ridiculous eyebrows.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwh! AHAHAHAHAHAHA! Oh, man! Messing with your head is just too much fun!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ms. Yew. If you don't mind, I'd like to return to your testimony now.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwh... Sure, why not?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">A brand new detective suddenly getting his salary cut -- that's reason enough for a grudge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... To cut a new detective's salary right off the bat like that...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I'm not really familiar with the way you guys relate, but is that a common practice?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Nnnnnnn... Speaking of cutting my salary, didn't you threaten to do that to me earlier, too!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............I suppose I did.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's only natural to cut a worthless detective's salary down to their actual worth. My father can even fire anyone, new or old, with a snap of his fingers.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! Do you think maybe that's reason enough for detectives to hate you people?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Well, I guess... They really... shouldn't cut people's pay.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Detective Badd... Don't tell me, Mr. von Karma cut your salary earlier...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well? How's that for a "perfect explanation"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You call your explanation "perfect"?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah...! Is it not to your liking?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately for you, it's just not up to my standards.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh? Is there something you want me to clarify, in that case?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What should I do? Should I raise an objection?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Maybe I should wait and listen to what she has to say for a bit longer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Detective Gumshoe certainly had a motive to kill Mr. Faraday. However, there is just one thing I can't wrap my head around in this explanation. I'll just have to force Ms. Yew to explain herself fully!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Alright, if you could clear this one thing up for me...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You still haven't explicitly established how Mr. Faraday was killed!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Going senile already, Miles? Mr. Faraday was stabbed to death with a knife!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnghoooh! N-Not that! What I meant to ask was... ...how were the two men killed when they were in a guarded room!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...We're going to find that out very soon from Gumshoe at his interrogation, boy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aaarghn...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... "Aaarghn...!" Oh, you're a riot, Edgeworth! Poor baby... Tell you what, I'll let you another go, how's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, allow me ask the detective directly. What was your relation to Mr. Faraday?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Faraday was in charge of training rookie detective to testify in trials. I met him on the very first day I entered the Criminal Affairs Department, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? I had no idea Mr. Faraday was so involved.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Faraday... He may look like an easy-going guy... ...but he's actually... a bit of a nut for strict discipline and manners. Guys like Gumshoe... ...tended to rub him the wrong way...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">There, now you know how the detective and Mr. Faraday were related. Happy now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No...! Wait...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! ...You said you only had one thing to ask, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnnnnngh! P-Please allow me to ask about one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... "Nnnnnnngh!" Oh, you're a riot, Edgeworth! Poor baby... Tell you what, I'll let you another go, how's that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand Detective Gumshoe's potential motive for killing Mr. Faraday... ...however, what about his motive for killing Mr. Rell?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">His motive for killing Rell? Like I would know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... If there was no clear motive for both of the murders... ...then I doubt this incident would've occurred. Wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there anyone else who might have had a grudge against either of the two men? Or should we look into that ourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh... In that case... .........I have absolutely no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........! <thought>What? But that's impossible! She must knew SOMETHING!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Wait... Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! Can you please not glare at me like that? ...It makes me laugh. Phwwwwwh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Grr...! I didn't even do anything, and you're already laughing away!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, anyway... the way I see it, as long as he had a motive to kill one of the two... ...this crime would've played out the way it did anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Oh? Would you care to explain your logic? And this time, please try to provide a truly perfect explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwh...! Perfect this, perfect that... Stop being so uptight, or is that a requisite trait for being a Von Karma? Ahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I demand that you shut this rude woman up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I wish you'd BOTH be quiet for just one second...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahem... Oh well. I guess I'll just have to explain it to you kids.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">There's no one out there with a motive to kill both Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if that's really true... Is there no one out there with a grudge against both men? I should take another hard look at the evidence for this morning's case. The second KG-8 Incident, as people are calling it, involving an Embassy staff member... ...and the two men who both wound up as suspects in the case... Is there someone else I'm overlooking who is somehow related to them?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">There's no one out there with a motive to kill both Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So there is no one else who might have a grudge against both Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I suppose "no one"... is a bit of a stretch. But I'm pretty sure no one like that was here in this courthouse today.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...She's lying through her teeth. We just saw a someone "like that" here earlier!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Besides, you don't need to prove that the killer had a grudge against both men.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">All you really have to establish is that someone had a grudge against one of the two men.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Someone with a grudge against one of the men... In that case, aren't there plenty of other people who fit the bill?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Sure. After all, who doesn't garner scorn from another simply by being alive? But the only one who held a grudge and acted upon it by killing was Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Furthermore...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Mr. Rell, who happened to be there, became a witness to Mr. Faraday's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you're saying that he was basically silenced...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Aren't you glad you managed to avoid the same fate, Your Honor? Why, if you had been the one to witness the blood-covered detective... Ahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What!? Detective Gumshoe! Y-You would kill even me!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaaat!? I-I... I could never do something as terrible as that, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There's no need for even a second of deliberation! I will hand down my verdict here--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Take a look around. We are not in court right now! It would be greatly appreciated if you would stay here with us in reality.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ack! Please forgive me! I know not what I do!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And you there, Ms. Yew! Hurry up and continue with your testimony. If you fail to do so... I will whip into shape!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha ha ha... That's nice. Sounds kind of like fun, actually. Anyway, Detective Gumshoe had to erase the witness, Mr. Rell.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Therefore, he was killed out of necessity, and set up to look like they had killed each other.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I. Didn't. Do. It. Pal!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">No hard feelings, but I don't think we can take the word of a criminal seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*whimper* B-But! I can't even begin to think up ways to set up a crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I suppose you do lack the necessary tactical mind required to do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*whimper* Why do you have to kick a man when he's down, pal?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahaha! You shouldn't put yourself down, Detective! You're a big boy. I bet you thought it up all by yourself, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah! That's right! And I worked real hard as it, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think this proves one thing about the detective: he has the mental acuity of a worm.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have to admit, her explanation makes sense. However, there is also something she overlooked in her testimony. I should present that piece of evidence, and see if I can't make her see the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew. I believe there is someone you overlooked in making your statement. Or rather... is it because you'd rather not bring this person up...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We are looking for someone with a reason to kill both Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell... I can think of at least one person that fits the bill! He was the suspect in the original KG-8 Incident... ...and a member of the Cohdopian Embassy staff, Mr. Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. The very man who came to visit you earlier out in the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The man who killed a member of the Cohdopian Embassy staff, Mr. Rell... ...and the man who was the lead prosecutor of the KG-8 Incident, Mr. Faraday... Are you telling me that Mr. Coachen has no reason at all to kill both of these men?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well......... I suppose he might have a reason or two...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You! You covered for me, pal! ...Maybe you're not such a bad guy after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't get ahead of yourself. You're still a suspect, make no mistake about that! The perfect evidence, the perfect testimony... These are the only things I wish to hold.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-But I didn't do it...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... You will stay under my authority, and go investigate Mr. Manny Coachen for me. And remember, I will not be very forgiving should any of this leak out--</line>
<line speaker="Badd">You want to investigate Coachen...? You'd just be wasting your time...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why is that?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Coachen was up in the viewing gallery, watching the trial... or so I was told. Every cop in this place has been keeping an eye on the guy since he arrived...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Then the only real suspect we have is still Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No way... Come on, Detective Badd! You've gotta believe me, sir! I really was in that hallway the whole time, sir! I never took a single step into this room, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...OK, then are you saying... there was someone else who passed through the hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I... No... There was no one else, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Then why should I believe you didn't do it...!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That is one incredibly foolish detective. Standing right in front of a crime scene all by himself... It's as good as a confession of guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I have to admit it's a bit strange. Most criminals will fabricate some sort of lie to escape their crimes. And if that detective really wanted to prove that he is innocent... ...you'd think he would at the very least offer up "I spaced out while on duty" or the like.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Come on, Gumshoe. Time for your interrogation...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.........Detective Badd...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... I will go ahead and report this to Papa.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that, as they say is that! Right, everyone? Ho ho ho.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, I suppose we should both be getting back to our real jobs now, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Before we do, Ms. Yew, there is something I'd like to speak with you about.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It's just another cheap sofa. If I should buy one for my office, I'll be sure to select a much more luxurious one.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahaha! Hey, wait! Phwwwh... Edgeworth? Phwwh... Where are you off to? Aren't you the one who wanted to talk...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, yes... Sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These plastic bags look like they fell here by chance at first glance... But all of them, with the exception of the bloody one, are just camouflage. I suppose you could call this a twist on the old "to hide a tree, hide it in the woods".</line>
<line speaker="Yew">So? What did you want to ask me about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The current case of the murdered Cohdopian Embassy staff member... ...I've heard that people have begun calling it the second KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Only among you law enforcement types. And? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like for you to tell me everything you know about the original KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........I'm afraid I can't help you. I don't know anything beyond what was reported in the papers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I believe you know much more... since you are directly tied to the KG-8 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">......I'd appreciate it if you'd stop with the false accusations. Baseless outbursts are useless both inside and outside the courtroom, don't you know?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I do, but I also know that I DO have a leg to stand on here.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">............ Phwwh... Phwwwwahahaha. Think you can stop making that ultra-serious face in front of me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk! I-If you could please stop laughing for just one second! <thought>I'm not going to make any headway like this... I'm just going to have to show her... ...exactly how related to the KG-8 Incident she is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">As you guessed... the one who reported the smuggling activities of the Amano Group... ...was my sister, Cece Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As I thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">And... she was killed right before she was to testify at the impending trial... ...by Manny Coachen! But, because he was tried once... ...and was acqutted, he gets to live out the rest of his cushy life, completely carefree.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All because of a lack of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">No, I heard that the evidence to convict him did exist.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I heard it from Mr. Faraday himself after Mr. Coachen's trial was over. Apparently. a man in black made off with the most important piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...! Then, the evidence had been tampered with!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Isn't it just like a criminal to do something like that? The smuggling ring being run out of the Amano Group by one of its secretaries... They bailed Mr. Coachen out. Turns out, they were in league with each other all along.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How big was that smuggling ring? Was it a large operation?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I don't really know. Which is why I wanted to become the lead defense... ...on this case that people are calling the second KG-8 Incident. But, I haven't learned anything new at all. I was probably expecting too much, I know...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean, you think this case has nothing to do with the smuggling ring?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I... don't know what to think...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why did Mr. Coachen want to meet with you earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Actually... he came to watch the trial. Apparently, he only found out that I was the defense lawyer of this case after he'd arrived. He figured he should say, "Hi"... and one other thing: "Looks like you couldn't resolve anything this time either. Too bad."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......! What's that supposed to mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Ahahahahahahahahaha! Ooh, boy! Stop it with the scary face, already! I'm fine. Really. I gave him a good slap across the face!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The way she talks about slapping him as she laughs away is kind of creepy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahem... But, it's just as Mr. Badd said. He's not related to the double murder. I asked around, and people in the gallery claim that he was in his seat the entire time. ...Talk about "cruel fate".</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew... I believe that I have proof of your connection to the KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">That file is your proof? Very well, then... Why don't you tell me exactly how I'm related to the KG-8 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're linked to this case through the former-suspect, Manny Coachen!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yes, and that sheds light on our discussion... how?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? <thought>It looks like I jumped the gun on this one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Ahahahahahahaha! Weren't you the one who mentioned it earlier...? About how Mr. Coachen came to see me? Obviously, that makes us acquaintances, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">So, is that all you wanted to talk about? If so, I'd like to get going.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Hmph. Alright, then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're linked to this case... through Mr. Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, I guess we WERE just duking it out in the courtroom... I suppose that makes us "related" in some sense. But so what? Who cares?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I suppose... <thought>Nngh... I guess that wasn't it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">So, is that all you wanted to talk about? If so, I'd like to get going.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Hmph. Alright, then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your connection to the KG-8 Incident... ...is through the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim's name is Cece Yew. You will note that she has the same last name as you. Can you really still tell me with a straight face that you are not related to this case?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Phwwwwh. Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! ...Sorry, but we're not related.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Just kidding. You asked that question with such a serious look on your face... ...that I couldn't help but... Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmmrrrrgh...! Ms. Yew, I ask that you please tell me the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................Ahem. Alright. I'll tell you everything I know.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, I ask that you please tell me truth.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Alright. I'll tell you everything I know.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Mr. Faraday was killed with this knife, correct...? I feel bad for him -- being killed by evidence you prepared yourself is just awful.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, what do you think about this piece of evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">What do I think? Well, other than the blood, it's a very pretty and ornate knife. I'd love to use it as an ornament in my home. If it's alright with you, may I have it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What are you talking about!? This is a weapon that was used to kill someone with!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwh! Ahahahahahaha! Why so serious!? I think someone needs to loosen up!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrk! <thought>There she goes again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Looks like Mr. Rell was killed by the very gun he used to kill the Embassy staff member.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You speak of the concept of karma, I assume...? And that you take your life into your own hands when you commit a crime, correct? Hmph... I never thought I'd be dealing with a gun this soon upon becoming a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ah, well, for a veteran like me, they're pretty much par for the course. To be honest, even if it's just once, I've always wanted to try firing one. Hey! Is that thing loaded? Do you think I could give it a try right now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">D-Don't be ridiculous! This isn't some kind of toy!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! ...Phwwwwh! I was only joking! Duh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Why is it that anything I have to say is a joke to her...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To have set these two men up and make it look like they killed each other... If there's one thing I cannot forgive, it's the desecration of the dead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Everything is neat and tidy on top of the table, with not a single disturbance in sight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A pleasent breeze is blowing through this window. If only I could exchange it with the stifling atmosphere of this crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's Mr. Faraday's bag. The evidence for the trial of the Embassy staff's murder is in here. And if things had gone smoothly, they would now be mine. Including the two weapons in this double murder, the knife and gun, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The television has been left on... to preserve the crime scene, of course. And it will stay on until the police are finished with their investigation. ...Do they think nothing of saving electricity? *sigh* How bothersome.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems Mr. Faraday was in the habit of using very nice fountain pens.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... This looks like a quality nib. ...But I bet it's no match for my beloved feather pen.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, this is about all I know. Haha... Sorry. Guess I wasn't much help, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's not true. I'm sorry I made you recall such a painful time in your life.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...... Ahahahahahahaha! Edgeworth, you really are too serious for your own good. You really need to learn to relax. We wouldn't want you to die of stress, would we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Thank you for the advice, but there's no need to worry. I work in my own way, and I will catch this criminal in my own way as well. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha! Look at you with your game face on, ready to go!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I...! I'm making no such face!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Did you know? Laughter is the best medicine, Edgeworth. Don't you get tired of making such a serious face all the time?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm charged with making sure that all the criminals of this world are found guilty. I... have no need for laughter.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">There you go, making that face again. Oh well. I've got to get going. I still have a few loose ends I need to tie up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>.................. The KG-8 Incident and this murder investigation... It is my belief that these two cases are related to each other somehow. Plus, that detective... Detective Gumshoe...It's obvious he's lying, even though the lie is hurting his chances. ...Clearly, this case is far from over. But whether or not that detective is the murderer... ...can only be determined once I've completed my perfect investigation. Mr. von Karma... I swear to uphold your honorable name, or my name isn't Miles Edgeworth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sir... What is to become of the trial into the Cohdopian Embassy staff member's murder?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Indeed. Since both the suspect and the prosecutor are now dead... ...the case will be dismissed. In other words, the trial ends here prematurely.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hah... Looks like you'll have to wait just a bit longer for your big debut.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose it can't be helped.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">The evidence for this trial will be transferred to you in a little while.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... Sir, what do you think about the murder of the Cohdopian Embassy staff member... ...and the murders of Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...What an outrageous circus it has all become. That Faraday brought it all upon himself wirh his naïveté.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An outrageous circus... Right, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">I grow weary of this topic. Edgeworth, I will have you assigned to a different case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Papa! You'll come and watch my courtroom debut next, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Hmm... I'll consider it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Sir, if I may, please allow me to continue with my investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I know that there is already a suspect in the murder of Mr. Faraday and Mr. Rell... ...however, there is not enough evidence to prove that it was he who committed the crime. I'd like to continue investigating in order to find the perfect proof of his guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">The perfect proof? Don't make me laugh! A worthless person like you has no right to claim such a thing as perfection!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Umm, Papa? Who do you think is the real culprit behind these murders?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles and I, we're competing to see who can find the real killer first. Plus, being able to investigate a real crime scene is a really rare opportunity. It would give us some real-life experience, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">...Hmph! If you want to investigate this case that much, then do as you wish.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then, you're allowing us to continue...?</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">In court, your top priority is to win, and a solid investigation is one of the keys to winning. We have to make sure you become recognized as a first-rate prosecutor, don't we? .........It wouldn't be very interesting otherwise. I'm returning home now. Edgeworth, Franziska! See to it I'm not disturbed, save for the results of your competition.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course, Papa!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you thanking me for? Your logic earlier was built on that scruffy detective's lie. That means that the competition is still on!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, just as you wished.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... I couldn't let you get off so easily. Now then, let's see how well you fare on the investigation from here, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I know I don't have enough information yet. So my first order of business will be to question anyone involved with this case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It feels like there's a whole backside to this case we're not seeing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>And here we had thought that it was a case where the two men had killed each other.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We're lacking in information. And as a Von Karma, I can hardly call this a perfect investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, it is as you say.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ack...! I can't believe we agree on something...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Just what is so revolting about agreeing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Anyway! Our first move should be to speak with everyone related to this case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Even if you had not said it, I was planning to do so anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Argnk! <thought>What was that lash for!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do you think you can win this competition by simply showing that to me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not at all. In fact, I was planning to thank you. I wouldn't be a prosecutor today without you and your father.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I didn't really do much. You became a prosecutor first, that's all. But just you wait and see, Miles Edgeworth. Very soon, I'll be a prosecutor, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Good, then we can both send criminals away together as colleagues!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph... But you can be sure that I will always get more convictions than you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's almost cute that she's going this far to insist that she'll always win... Almost.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The KG-8 Incident, huh... The defendant was acquitted in that case, but I don't think we've seen the last of it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The fact that he was acquitted on a lack of evidence is just revolting. It's inexcusable!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, if it was my papa, he would've been found guilty in three minutes flat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Indeed. We would do well to watch and study more from our mentor... ...so that we may secure a conviction for all those we try. That will be our rule.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...What's all this "we" business? Don't lump me in with you, Miles. Any suspect I come across... will confess everything to me before we even reach the trial! Hmph... I'll show you exactly who is the superior prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>.........Clearly, only one of us is playing to win here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's one of the weapons in this case... I pity Mr. Faraday. It's bad enough to be killed with evidence that he prepared himself... ...but to also be killed in a courthouse of all places... ...and right in the middle of one of the trials he was running, too...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It just goes to show that nothing in life is predictable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering what you think of this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Asking people for help is breaking the rules, Miles. As I said earlier, this is a competition! A battle of wits! If you want to ask someone for an opinion, you should start with yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...In other words, you have no real opinions about this piece of evidence, do you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What is the meaning of this bulletin board!? Why are there so few trials posted!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It would appear that the entire week is devoted to Mr. Rell's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Is the crime rate really that low in this country? Or maybe... ...the police lack the proper motivation to get out there and catch the criminals?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm afraid I can't comment on that, however... ...I can say I have my doubts about the younger detectives.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Sounds to me like they're in need of a stricter hand. And I'll start my discipline regiment with that pathetic, filthy-coated detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>*sigh* I feel bad for the big guy... and yet, I can find no suitable reason to stop her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">I-I can't stop the water, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems that the man who was here earlier broke it by drinking from it too much.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Bunch of fools who pretended to not see the foolishly foolish actions of a foolish fool!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well then, why don't you lend the officer a hand?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. As if I should have anything to do with this. Besides, that water-drinking fool's mouth is the thing that officer should be covering. Let's give that officer a description of the water guzzler later.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She seems to have quite the grudge... It sounds to me like someone wanted a drink...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">This area is restricted to authorized personnel only, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If I'm not "authorized personnel", then what, may I ask, do you think I am?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">...Um, the younger sibling of a dysfunctional relationship...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm not the younger one! He is! Now get that straight in your head!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I believe there is a more objectionable part you should be upset over, Franziska.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Uuuu...nnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the matter, officer?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">I've been standing here for forever, sir, and I really need to go to the bathroom...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why don't you just make a quick trip? The nearest one isn't that far, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Officer">N-No, it's a short way down the hall beyond these doors, but... ...I don't want to be blamed for anything that might happen while I'm gone! So, I-I'm gonna hold it!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Perhaps Detective Gumshoe can be a positive influence on the force after all.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">Wow! This thing is so incredibly detailed! My inner modeling fanboy is impressed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I'm not exactly a fan of plastic models, per se... ...but even I can sense the superb quality of this model.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I simply cannot comprehend how that man can feel so much love for such a trifle.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh...? I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're a disciple of my father. So you would go well to guard yourself against an interest in such unproductive things.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Yes, perhaps I should take up whipping people like the young lady over here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's an incredibly detailed model, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I heard that it cost as much to make that as it cost to build the courthouse itself.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What was the point of making such an expensive model!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I felt the exact same way upon hearing it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ugh. It's so hard to understand such foolishness!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agreed.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Sir! Nothing to report, sir! ...ZZZzzz...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Is there no one who will make this man take responsibility for his actions on the job!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Looks like we have no choice but to report this to Papa. Then, this guard can have fun in a waking nightmare after being awakened from his dream.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Actually, let's not. I kind of feel sorry for him now.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It wasn't me, I tell ya! I didn't do anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Yes, I understand. So let's just calm down, OK buddy?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I doubt I'll get anything useful from the detective while he is this agitated...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a bookshelf... Hm? What's this...? "Judges' Trial Exchange Log"? It appears to be a journal where the various judges share their thoughts and ideas. <thought>The real daily lives of the judges are laid out here on these pages...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...There's nothing about the court in here! It's just page after page of unrelated drivel!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Judging by the content, they are very enthusiastic about the courthouse's daily menu. ...And it would appear that fried oysters are a favorite.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I have no use for such foolishly foolish words from that foolishly foolish crowd.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Someone please assure me that this is not the true state of this country's judiciary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It seems Mr. Faraday was in the habit of using very nice fountain pens.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Really? Because my papa uses fountain pens that are much, much nicer than this. The way he signs his name with those pens makes his signature look like pure art.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...I'm surprised Mr. von Karma has to sign anything. I thought he'd have a crest stamp made!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... This looks like a quality nib.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Well, my ballpoint pen is much easier to write with.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You're obviously still too young to appreciate the finer points of a fountain pen.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! Don't treat me like a child!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh...! I wouldn't have to if you would only grow up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that this bag was actively used in the murder of Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">! Wait... Isn't it possible that the killer left his fingerprints on the inside of this then!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sorry, but it looks like the killer was very careful not to leave any evidence behind.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Sounds like we have a very clever killer on our hands. Which means that, on second thought, maybe that detective didn't do it after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'll make sure that each and every person that ever stands here will be found guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are others beside the defendant that stand at this podium, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't care! Just make sure you never end up standing at one of these... ...or you'll be sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I'll keep that in mind.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's the viewing gallery. This is where the riffraff sit when they come to watch.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's situated at the same height as the Judge's bench... I wonder if that's to represent the intense scrutiny of each and every case from all sides?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Are you or are you not man enough to stand up to all those eyes!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What sort of--!? Of course I'm man enough!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Any day now, I'll be taking my rightful place behind this bench.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">By that time, I should already be standing here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It'd be downright disgraceful if I beat you to it, wouldn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If that were to happen Franziska... ...I'll eat my cravat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's the defense attorney's bench. .................. <thought>I'd probably be standing on this side of the courtroom if that incident hadn't happened.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you thinking about? Lately, the more wrinkly your face becomes, the less I'm able to read what you're thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I never--! I'll have you know, I don't have a single wrinkle upon my youthful brow!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This must be the Judge's desk. You can tell by the gavel sitting on top.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I had a dream once that I was being squashed from above by this gavel.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're such a weakling, Miles Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You have no idea how frightening it was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Judge's chair... It must be wonderful to be able to sit the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, as apposed to us prosecutors and defense attorneys who have to stand. I think it'd only be fair if the Judge had to stand the whole time, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">His Honor is an old man. He should be afforded some comforts...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph! Fine, he can enjoy his chair, but he'll share in our pain through my lashes!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I fear for the Judge if Franziska were to ever become a real prosecutor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, it's you, Edgeworth. And who... are you? Wait... you were at the crime scene just now, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...You should be disbarred for not knowing who I am. I am Franziska von Karma, and I am about to become the successor to the family name.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">About to? I guess that means that for now, you're still just another kid. In which case, it's only natural that I didn't know who you are.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh--!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-Why are you whipping ME!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwwwwwh... Anyway, it looks like they're planning to hold the evidence a bit longer. If there's one thing I can't stand, it's waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm terribly sorry, but I have but a few more questions to ask of you.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Ahahahahaha! Look at you -- eyebrows scrunched, with lines on your forehead... And that, "To ask of you"! Ahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What exactly is so funny!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Mnnpphwwwh... Sorry! I'm just bad at dealing with a super-serious atmosphere.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Apparently, they failed to teach you proper behavior at a crime scene in law school.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ah... Hoo. I feel much better now. So, what is it you want to talk about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to inquire as to where you were at the time of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">We were in Defendant Lobby No. 1 the whole time, up until we heard the gunshot. And by "we", I mean Mr. Badd. If you don't believe me, feel free to ask him yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You were with Detective Badd? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">We had a little something to discuss, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, I take it that you are acquaintances with Detective Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yes, he was the detective in charge of the KG-8 Incident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! Detective Badd is also related to that incident!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">That's right. He was the one who was supposed to protect my sister, Cece. But you know how that turned out, don't you Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! I have no idea what you two are talking about! I've heard of the KG-8 Incident from my papa... ...but how does that case relate to you, Ms. Yew?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The victim of that case, Cece Yew, was my little sister.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahaha! You're making that super-serious face again! I'm fine... Really. I just make it a point to rub some more salt in his wounded prode every time I see him!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The way she talks about doing that as she laughs away is kind of creepy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, speaking of Mr. Badd, he and Mr. Faraday... ...I'd say they met up just about every single time the Yatagarasu made a move. It was practically a given that the two would meet up at every one of the crime scenes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. He did mention that he is in charge of the Yatagarasu investigation earlier. <thought>Maybe I should ask her what she knows about the Yatagarasu in more detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim that at the time of the murder, you were with Detective Badd...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...But don't you lawyers usually discuss the trial with your clients during a recess?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">We do, and that's what I was planning to do. But Mr. Faraday was being rather threatening and he dragged Mr. Rell away. After that, Mr. Badd came into Lobby No. 1, so we just stayed there and talked.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what did you talk with Detective Badd about?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwh... Nothing interesting. I just insulted him some... ...talked about how the trial was going... and then I insulted him some more.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Bloody... When she's not laughing, her mouth seemingly spews nothing but insults.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Anyway, Mr. Badd and I were in Defendant Lobby No. 1 when the murders occurred... ...so I really can't tell you anything about the hallway or Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to ask you a few questions about your client, Mr. Mack Rell. Now, your client first claimed to be the Yatagarasu, is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yeah... Once I heard that it was the Yatagarasu that had made off with the evidence from KG-8... ...I began to ask Mr. Rell all sorts of questions, but to no avail. Turns out, Mr. Rell was not the Yatagarasu. He had just made that up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He made it up...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Mr. Rell's crime was caught on tape by the security cameras... ...but there is no footage of him sneaking into the Cohdopian Embassy itself.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hold on for just one second! Then, you mean to say that you knew that he was not the real Yatagarasu... ...and that he was just another cold-blooded killer? And you were ready to defend him!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... So a defense lawyer is actually just someone whose job is to cover for criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That's why defense lawyers are so detestable! But they are no match for us Von Karmas!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Phwwh... Ahahahaha! I don't believe it! You're serious! Why don't you save that face for something really worth being serious about? And Edgeworth, do you remember what I said earlier? I... phwwh... have my own agenda. Phwwwh... I'm still on the hunt for leads regarding the KG-8 Incident, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And for that, you have not a single qualm about defending a known killer...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">.........Don't put words in my mouth. I said no such thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The only was I had to get close to Mr. Rell was to be his lawyer. I had no intention of covering for him, ever. So don't you dare suggest I was going to.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I'm sorry. Forgive my rashness.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew. I was wondering if you could tell me about the Yatagarasu.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The Yatagarasu, huh... I don't really know much about that character myself. But I do get a lot of consultation requests from companies to defend them.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Requests from companies...?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The Yatagarasu isn't some petty thief out for money, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Alright then. Perhaps the Yatagarasu is in the business of stealing people's lives?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">............ You're not very funny, or witty, are you, little Miss. von Karma?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Grr.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska! Be careful about who you whip! Choose carefully, or we may be sued by... Nnghhoooh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">There. I chose carefully, just like you wanted.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Mnnphwwwwwwh! Ahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahah... Ahahahahahahahahaha! Th-That just now... was hilarious, little missy!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Of course it was.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>.........What is wrong with these two women!? Why does my pain give them delight?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And? So, in the end, what is the Yatagarasu? I have to say, I had never even heard of this thief when I was in Germany.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">The Yatagarasu deals in information. Namely, in digging out dirt about back-room dealings and the like of companies. The Yatagarasu is a vigilante who steals such info and then makes it public for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Vigilante or not, this person sounds like just another criminal to me.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I suppose you could put it that way, too. But either way, I get a lot more clients now, thanks to that thief.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Sounds like Ms. Yew is profiting nicely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">My sister was killed in that incident... And the defendant, Manny Coachen, got off scot-free due to a lack of evidence! It's so frustrating... The prosecution was a breath away from putting him away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She's not laughing at this particular topic... Although, it's to be expected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwwh! I can't believe what a forceful face you're making! Ahahahaha! That face is totally killing me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh... Well that moment of seriousness was short-lived...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Circumstantial evidence and a motive... It all points to that detective, doesn't it? On top of that, even his testimony turned out to be a lie. Well, that's what you get when you trust a criminal. They're all just liars in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>All criminals are liars...? Well, at least we agree on something.</thought> But that detective is telling a lie that is nothing but a disservice to himself...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">...Phwwwh. You're really too naïve, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You don't understand. If I should leave even the smallest mystery unsolved... ...I can't really claim to have conducted the perfect investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... "The perfect investigation"...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Speaking of... I fear that why she laughs when she does is a mystery I may never solve.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I suppose I've gotten all I can out of Ms. Yew. I should move on and speak with Detective Gumshoe now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Scruffy's annual bonus envelope? What a useless piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well, obvious point aside, what do you think about the low amount of money?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A pathetic amount for a pathetic detective. I think it rather suits him.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">But don't you think it's a bit too low, even for an officer like him?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">By his pay, I can tell he's a fool that I'd never trust anything to. A foolish fool like him would only blotch my record with foolishly foolish mistake. Well, not that it matters. I'll never have to work with that pathetic fool anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That was a bit harsh... even for you, Franziska...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey... It's you, pal! You're here. ...Yeeeeeooowwch!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...As am I.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I don't think you needed to whip him to let him know that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I-I didn't do it, pal! I swear on my honor as a detective! I really didn't!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your words are useless. I place my trust only in the evidence, Detective. Once the investigation is fully over, and should we find out that you are the killer... ...there will be no mercy to be had for you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-Have a heart, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. But you're not worried, right? After all, you have nothing to worry about, if you really are innocent, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right! Hey, pal! Go and do your perfect investigation and get the real killer for me, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I would've done so, even had you not requested me to, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you and Mr. Faraday had a small "meeting" last week, did you? And what exactly did you do to make him so angry?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I just asked Detective Badd the same thing myself, pal. Turns out, he was mad at me because on my very first day as a detective... ...I reported in at my usual post instead of the Criminal Affairs Department. By the time I got down to Criminal Affairs, I was really, really late. And that's when he gave me that huge speech...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I remember doing the same exact thing in elementary school. On the first day of school every year, I'd always wind up going to my old classroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>How pathetic for the Detective to be compared to a mere schoolchild.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim to be standing guard in front of the door to Lobby No. 2 during the recess. However, when did you receive the order to do so, and from whom?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... earlier, at around 3:20. and from Detective Badd, pal. Today's trial took a really crazy turn... ...so I was told to make sure nothing happened to Mr. Faraday.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And yet, something did happen to him, correct? It looks like it was a total waste of manpower to assign you to guard duty.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Owww! Your words sting worse than your whip, pal...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So it was Detective Badd who ordered him to stand guard, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Detective Gumshoe... Is there anything else you'd like to tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">............N-Nope, not a thing, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">In that case, allow us to take a look at what you are carrying on your personage.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Wait! You can't do that!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...There's nothing of any particular value here.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, my handcuffs and badge were confiscated by Detective Badd, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what is that open envelope I see sticking out of your coat pocket?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Hands off, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just show it to us already!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeoooow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Annual Bonus Check Within: $5.00 total"... Except there is no check inside.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You've had your look, now give it back, pal! It's my first bonus as a brand-new detective! I just got it and cashed it today! I had literally no cash on me up until I did, you know. So that envelope is really special to me! Now give it back!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You don't need rubbish like this. Don't worry, we'll throw it away for you later.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">How could you...!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bonus of $5.00? Even for a new, rookie detective, that's a bit low.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, even though I just got promoted, I guess I caught the attention of the higher-ups!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">At that amount, I'd have preferred to not receive one at all.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You just don't get it, pal! You don't get how great it feels to get your first bonus!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose not. I have yet to receive my own bonus as a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Well, I received mine from my papa last December, like I do every year.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That's not a bonus. That's a Holiday gift.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........Whatever you want to call it, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to ask you a little about this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm not saying a peep, pal! 'Cause I'm not the killer, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You misunderstand. I wasn't going to ask you about that...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All I've ever wanted to do was to become a detective, pal! So I'd never want to be a killer!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It seems that he doesn't want to talk about anything unrelated to his predicament...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Officer">I'm sorry, but I need to take him for questioning now...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I think I've asked him just about everything I needed to... No, wait... Since he became a suspect, there is one piece of evidence I should re-confirm.</thought> Officer, I ask that you wait a second. I still have one thing I'd like to re-confirm with Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Officer">Understood! But please make it brief, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I want to hear it from the horse's mouth... I must confirm whether or not his testimony about when the crime occurred is the truth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You told me earlier that you heard no sound, other than the gunshot, out in the hallway. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">No mistake about it, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... then, you are also claiming that no one passed through the hallway either? Is that also correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">......Yup! Not even a single ant passed through that hall while I was on duty!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Hmmmmm... You do realize that the lie you're telling is only making life more difficult for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? ............Oh. B-But it's true! I didn't see anyone go through the hallway, and I didn't hear anything else, pal! I bet the killer found a way to kill the two guys that's beyond what I can even imagine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......... <thought>So he intends to continue telling this ridiculous lie... But why would he do so, given the situation he's in? I believe a thorough investigation... ...of the hallway in front of the defendant lobbies is in order.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! You...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnghoooooooh!!</line>
<line speaker="???">*rasp* Phwwwwwwtt!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...How could you have not noticed that coming?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnn...nghhhh...! <thought>Wasn't that... the child I changed money for earlier...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???:">Thanks! That's exactly what I needed!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kids... can sometimes be so cruel...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like she dropped something.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Maybe we should arrest the girl? She might turn out to be a valuable lead.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Courthouse Special Swiss Rolls"... Is this being sold somewhere on the premises?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't recall seeing a restaurant of any sort in this courthouse...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I somehow doubt you'd find junk food like this on a restaurant menu, Franziska...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well then, where do they sell these things, huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Umm... a convenience store, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, I'm sure there's no convenience store in this courthouse, Miles Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk! <thought>...Where in the world did this come from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mnrgh... I believe some sort of punishment may need to be dealt the next time we meet...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe I've asked all that I need to of this man. Now, for Detective Badd and the Judge...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We have to confirm who is correct, the Judge or that scruff-face, right? I suppose we should inspect the hallway in front of Lobby No. 2 next, then.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose so. Shall we head on over, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That scruff-face's movements during the recess are really suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? I suppose you noticed it too, then.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course I did. Scruffy is giving us a testimony that is nothing but harmful to himself. Normally, criminals would tell the opposite type of lie in an attempt to escape.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... That is exactly the same point I'm having trouble understanding. <thought>It seems that I need to expose what he was really up to during the recess. And to do that, I should head to the hallway where he was supposedly standing guard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">May I have a word with you, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Argh... What in the world am I supposed to do, pal...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't think he'll be of much use right now. Let's continue with the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose so. I propose we go and inspect the hallway he was standing guard in next.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">So... did you see anything else...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... No, I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I see... Well, thanks for your cooperation...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, it's nothing. Just doing my duty as a defender of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...That'll be all for now. I'll ask again if I have any other questions.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anytime, Detective. Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a few loose ends I have to tie up... Oh! You're that new prosecutor Mr. von Karma recommended, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">My name is Miles Edgeworth, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And I'm Manfred von Karma's daughter, Franziska von Karma. I'm set to become the successor to my genius father any day now, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see, Mr. New Prosecutor Recommended by Von Karma Miles Edgeworth, and Ms. Gen-- ...Ack...! ...I-I bhit mai tonnge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Are you alright, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Please feel free to refer to me as just "Ms. von Karma", Your Honor. As for him... Just "Edgeworth" is fine.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Apparently, SOMEBODY doesn't feel that I'm worthy of a proper title.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oho! Very well, then. I shall call you Ms. von Karma and Mr. Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor, "Mr. Edgeworth" is fine, sir. Now, about your earlier testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes? What about it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would like to ask you a few questions about what exactly you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Alright. After all, it's my duty to clarify my testimony as a defender of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I greatly appreciate your cooperation, Your Honor. <thought>Now, the first thing I will need to do is figure out that detective's exact movements.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This pink, rubbery substance... I saw this in a different form earlier today. I believe this is a piece of a popped balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose that's possible.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The balloon probably got a little too close to our friend, the windowsill cactus.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...That would be the logical conclusion, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These bits of chocolate and cake... Could they not have come from a Swiss roll?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A Swiss roll? Why would a courthouse sell a thing like that?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It may not seem like the right venue... however, it IS being sold right over there.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The vending machine...? Ah, I see. "Stay neutral as the Swiss do until the end with these!" Two for $6!? Talk about expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Leaving the fact that it's on the expensive side aside... ...the fact that the cake crumbs and chocolate bits were found in this hallway... ...suggests that they came from a Swiss roll that was purchased from this machine.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">This is a pretty spacious hallway, but it's nothing compared to the ones at home.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... <thought>...because Mr. von Karma's house is a bit TOO spacious.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">However, even with this much space, there's nowhere for that scruff-face to hide. Well, other than the crime scene just beyond those doors.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I believe it's much too early to draw any conclusions. <thought>It was already proven that Detective Gumshoe was in this hallway the entire time. Now all we need to do is gather more information. And to do that, I'll just have to examine everything I see here by myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So, according to the Judge, someone looking through the restroom window... ...that you can see from the window at the end of this hall, can see into this hall? I wonder exactly how true that statement is, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it IS possible to get a pretty clear view of this hallway from that restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Is there really a men's bathroom window through the window at the end of this hall?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. ...Can you not see it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrnnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I demand that you show me this view at once!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose I should go examine that window once again anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">We've gathered so much information, but they feel like just random fragments to me. I wonder what really happened here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Random fragments...? No matter how related they seem at first, they might actually fit together somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........I grow tired of your inner monologues! Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arnngh! <thought>I'm going to end up in pieces thanks to that whip before I can piece the logic together.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Unnrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I pricked myself on one of this cactus's needles. I didn't think the needles on this thing would be so sharp.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well? What did you expect? Can you imagine how bad it would be if you were hit on the head by one of these? Anyway, this cactus seems to be unrelated to our case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think so? Because I believe that this cactus sitting on this windowsill <thought>Windowsill cactus - Potted cactus sitting on the hallway window's windowsill. Its needles are dangerous.</thought> is completely related.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Oh? Well then, I look forward to your explanation on how exactly it is related.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hm? What... is this? It's a pink-colored piece of trash <thought>Pink piece of trash - Piece of pink trash found on the windowsill of the hallway window. Made of rubber.</thought>... made of rubber. Hmm... I feel like I've seen something like this before...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, all I see is a piece of garbage. But you know... the fact that there is a litterer running loose inside this courthouse... It's simply unforgivable!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ack-! It's not like it was I who littered!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Rubbish belongs in a rubbish bin!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can look outside... however, I doubt the killer could've escaped through here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Of course not. This IS the third floor, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It appears that bars were installed on this to prevent people from falling out.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Bars? What bars?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Can you not see them from your vantage point?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? <thought>I must remember not to bring up that taboo subject again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So that window on the other side belongs to the men's restroom...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I can't see it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At your height? I'm not surprised.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghoooooooh! <thought>I guess short people have feelings too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The ants are hard at work carrying their food home. It's a marvel that they can pick up such comparatively large objects to their size.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, if you want to carry the mighty Von Karma name and not be squished under it... ...you'd better work extra hard, just like these ants.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........The same goes for you, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ants are pouring out of the hole in this bench as well. I wonder if the inside of this bench consists of nothing but ants...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't you dare continue with that gross line of thought!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unnrk! I-I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are these black speckles?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it's a pile of ants, eating away.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oooh... That detective...! He claims that not a single slipped by him... ...and yet, here is a whole hill of them!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnaaack! Wh-What are you hitting ME for!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">As a replacement for that pathetic detective!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... <thought>Perhaps I should add this deduction to the detective's growing tab of pay cuts...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Anyway, I wonder what the ants are eating?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">From the look and sweet smell of it, pieces of cake and chocolate from a Swiss roll <thought>Swiss roll crumbs - Found on the floor under the bench. A hill of ants are attracted to its sweet scent.</thought>.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Miles Edgeworth... The courthouse is to be kept pristine at all times!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghooooh! I-It wasn't me that dropped food on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The courthouse! Must be! Kept clean!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnghooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The dirt on this bench... It smells like some sort of sweet substance.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I can't believe there is someone going around dirtying the courthouse! For shame!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">C-Calm down, Franziska... Now, take a good look. Doesn't this smudge look kind of like a handprint to you?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I suppose it could be.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which means... ...that perhaps we can lift the prints of the person who sullied this bench!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I see... And then, we'll know the identity of our mystery slob.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You there! The lab technician! Could you please find out who this handprint belongs to?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I've got the results of the fingerprint analysis, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And? Do we know who they belong to?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! The fingerprints belong to Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh...? Interesting. Good work, officer.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And there you have it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I suppose so.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Now we know the identity of the person who dirtied the bench...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>.........I sense that you and I will be using this information in very different ways...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the one who sullied the bench turns out to be Detective Gumshoe. We know thanks to the fingerprints he left.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What a slob, dirtying the bench like this! That scruff-face is going to receive a good whipping from me when next we meet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As if he isn't being punished enough by everything that's going on, Franziska...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, I have something I wish to inquire about...</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hey! How about doing some actual work, you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I wish to inquire into Detective Gumshoe's movement during the recess.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...You're getting in the way of the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have an order from Mr. von Karma himself. Plus, I still hold investigative authority.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Tch.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So I hear you were the one who called for Detective Gumshoe to come down here.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Faraday... That guy was just accused... you know? I just knew something was gonna happen... My detective instinct told me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A lot of good it did you. You couldn't even protect one, lone prosecutor with it.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">............!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, you need to apologize.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Arghn...! ...I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm terribly sorry, Detective Badd. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Hmph. I used the phone on the first floor... and called the precinct... I told them to send somebody over. ...And that detective's the one that showed up.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... And only upon his arrival did you set Detective Gumshoe to stand guard, Detective Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah. I waited for him on the first floor... After he got here, we came up to these defendant lobbies together. ...As we entered this hallway, we ran into Yew... She told us... that Faraday was really mad... ...and that he'd dragged Rell off to Lobby No. 2 to have a word or something... And... that Faraday had said... to not let anyone interrupt them. ...So what choice did I have? ...All I could do was tell the big lug to stand guard outside.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And around what time did all of that take place?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Let's see... I think it was about... 30 minutes before I heard the gunshot. After giving the big lug his assignment... he never left the hallway, not once...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh? And how can you make such a claim?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... One of the guards out in this floor's main lobby swore to me he didn't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If the detective never left the hallway... then where did he disappear off to?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. That's simple. He must have gone into Lobby No. 2, just as I suspected.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Yew and I... We were in Lobby No. 1 next door. ...The only one without an alibi... is Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... It would seem that I am still missing some key pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, you also heard the gunshot, did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah. I heard it when I was in Defendant Lobby No. 1... That's why I... came running towards Lobby No. 2 together with Yew...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How much time elapsed between you hearing the gunshot and your arrival on the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Less than a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What were your movements upon hearing the gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">I grabbed the big lug, who was just walking around in the hall... ...and raced into Lobby No. 2... And that's when we discovered the bodies... in that order.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That makes you the discoverer of the crime scene, right?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah. I guess it does... little miss.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I am about to become a prosecutor very soon! You will treat me with the dignity I deserve, or else!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph. You wave that thing around any more... ...and I'll have you arrested for obstruction... little miss.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You wouldn't dare!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Ha ha... Just joking.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Gnnnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Detective Badd is really something if he can make Franziska behave...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Are we... about done?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is there anything else I should ask him about...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd... Where were you when you heard the gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...How many times are you going to ask that? I was in Defendant Lobby No. 1 when I heard the gunshot...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... It's exactly the same as what he said earlier when I asked...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Now, get out of here. ...You're getting in the way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm not through questioning you yet!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like to know a little more about the circumstances under which you heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Like I said, I was in Lobby No. 1 with Yew. ...I have nothing else to add.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Well, his testimony certainly corroborates with what Ms. Yew said...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, you already asked him about that, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>I suppose I should ask about something else...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like for you to tell me the exact time you heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It was around the end of the recess, and the trial was about to start again... I think. He was supposed to make time for himself to transfer the evidence he was holding... ...but I got the sense he wasn't gonna show for the hand-off... So I figured I should go get him, or he'd be late... And just as I thought that... Bang...! The sound of a gunshot hit my eyedrums...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he heard the gunshot right before the trial was about to re-start, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The KG-8 Incident... I heard that you were involved in this case as well.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Badd">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Th-That's all you have to say?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...It was an unpleasant case that I don't wish to recall... I've got a lot of regrets I'll never forget related to that. Regrets I'll take to the grave.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Does he really have that many regrets...? On the other hand, thinking back on what I know, I suppose he just might...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">Faraday...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It sounds like you lost someone close to you.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...He was a battle-buddy. We fought through a lot together... A boy with a silver spoon in his mouth couldn't understand society's dark underbelly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grr... <thought>Although, honestly, I suppose he's right. I don't have anyone I relate to in that way... Well, it's not as though I long for someone like that... Nor am I good at getting close...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">It's just as I said... I have nothing further to add. But if there's one thing a detective honors, it's that... ...you must have confidence in, and take responsibility... for anything you say... That's what it means to be a detective...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>In other words, you're just another stubborn horse, aren't you, Detective?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Badd, I'd like to ask you about this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. What a narcissist! He'd rather look at his face than the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Don't trust your eyes all the time, little girl... I can see the evidence... and keep an eye on the two of you with this mirror...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What--!? Then why don't you answer!?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Because I've got nothing to say... That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Understood. <thought>Why couldn't he have just said that at the beginning?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Are we done here? I don't have any time to waste...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oh, come on. All you're doing is standing in front of this door, doing nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I get the sense that he is somewhat investigating this crime scene... Or rather, that he is keeping us under surveillance... But to what end...?</thought> ...Detective Badd, may I ask that you cooperate with us for just a bit longer?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...I don't have anything else to say.. to the two of you... You guys... were the ones who said you wanted to investigate in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Fine then! Be obstinate! We'll just do as we please! Come on, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You may no longer be willing to help us, however... ...may I ask for the forensic scientists' cooperation?</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Do as you like...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, I'd like to ask you a few questions, if you don't mind. Where were you at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I-I-Do you suspect me of something!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, nothing of the sort, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! V-Very well, you may continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Your Honor, it's your testimony I'm after.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I had no idea you were chasing after me or my testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm beginning to sense that I might want to avoid being in a trial run by this judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Today's trial may have ended abruptly, but we will meet again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. I'm looking forward to that day, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">When I become a prosecutor, you might even see me in your courtroom a few times. I hope you'll treat me with even greater respect than now.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I only ask that you please do not bring a whip into my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. I'm afraid that issue is not up for negotiation.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>As long as the whip can't reach his seat, I'm sure His Honor will be safe... I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! It's a Courthouse Special Swiss Roll! It has such a nice, fluffy texture, and just the right amount of sweetness to it. And it's made from all-natural ingredients... ...so of course, it's easy to digest as well!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Actually, they decided only recently to sell these rolls as the Courthouse Special. Of course, I've been sending in my special requests all along. Why don't you try sending in a request once in a while?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I suppose I'll just have to think of a good suggestion by the next time I come here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You wish to ask about Detective Badd? Well, he is one well-honored detective. He doesn't say much and he doesn't really like people, but he has quite a few wounds.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I figured as much...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He has such a bad habit of randomly treating people as through they were children.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, but if you were in pursuit of a criminal, there's no one I'd trust more with my life. Even in the middle of a fierce gunfight, Detective Badd doesn't lose his cool.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aren't you exaggerating just a bit? I mean, what detective doesn't value his or her life?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no, you don't understand. He got all those holes in his jacket from all the gunfights he's gotten in fighting crime! You should learn about him if you want to be a part of the world of law enforcement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Something tells me that I should strive to stay on that detective's good side...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, I'd like for you to please take a look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will accept this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-No, wait! That's not what I showed it to you for!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Edgeworth. If I may, I suggest you bone up on court procedure a bit more. When evidence is shown before me, it goes into evidence. That is the law of the court.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... I'm sorry to say this, however, that rule does not apply to the outside world.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, come to think of it, I suppose court is not in session right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Being passionate about one's work is one thing, but to confuse it with real life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see here... Now then, how should I put this...? When you get to be my age... you need to pay more frequent visits to the restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you go take a look through the window at the end of this hall, you'll see a small window. That is the window to the men's restroom. In other words, you can see clearly into this hallway from the men's restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">When I was going into the restroom, that detective... Gumshoe, is it...? Well, he was standing in front of the vending machines buying something from it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">However! And this I couldn't believe... When I was about to exit the restroom... ...there was not a soul in the hallway anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... If you could please calm down and explain it to me rationally...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I'm really sorry. Please let me regain my composure... It was really suspicious! That's what my finely-honed judge's intuition said! Although, well, until the murders occurred, I just sort of brushed it off. Ho ho ho.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Apparently, this judge doesn't understand the concept of "staying calm"... That's probably all I'm going to find out from His Honor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth, may I return to my other duties now?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I'm sorry to have held you up. Thank you for your cooperation, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. Anytime, Mr. Edgeworth! Anytime!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">The judges in this country seem rather friendly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes... if not a little wishy-washy. However, I hear that they are known to hand down very fair verdicts.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmm... It would appear that this vending machine <thought>Vending machine - A vending machine that sells Courthouse Special goods. A few sweet items are for sale.</thought> sells snacks and various other foods.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just lovely. What will they think of next?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"Don't be a jerk in court like these beef jerks!" ......One packet for $9. "Defendant's Fresh Milk!" ......One half-pint for $7. "Stay neutral as the Swiss do until the end with these!" ......For $6. ...They're awfully overpriced.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The line-up is simply awful. Period.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Speaking of snacks... I wonder if that Swiss roll the little girl dropped is from this machine?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm, I was wondering about that myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I've already finished examining this area, but it never hurts to look again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"When you're in hot water, you might need a hot dog." .................. Hmm... It looks like this slogan was decided through a public contest. And the winner was... Prosecutor Winston Payne...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. What a pathetic slogan. No presence at all! Now if it was up to me, it would read... "If you leave matters in a Von Karma's hands, everyone in court will be found guilty dogs!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Overruled!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Don't be a jerk in court like these beef jerks!" I see...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! Wouldn't you agree that it's a very clever pun?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you really think they that much effort into the product name?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Even a foolish fool could understand the foolish thinking of the fool who made it up! You're acting so foolishly that I got so thoroughly mad, and am now utterly famished!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......If you wanted a pack of these, all you had to do was ask like a normal person.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Don't let the prosecution and the defense make a ham sandwich out of you!"...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It sounds like it's directed at that ham of a Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, it certainly isn't directed at me. I can out-maneuver him any day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"When it's looking bad, blind your opposition with some OJ!" Are they promoting violence?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't worry. My whip will make sure that anybody following this advice won't be for long.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Compared to the sting of a whip, the sting of orange juice may not be so bad...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">"Defendant's Fresh Milk!"... What exactly is that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I bet it means that the milk is freshly milked by various defendants on trial right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No, I think it might mean that this was milked right here from the various defendants.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... You can't possibly be serious!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">"Stay neutral as the Swiss do until the end with these!" ...The end of what?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I assume it means the end of the trial. I suppose this means that one should eat these during a recess...?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You can't eat during a trial, so I suppose the only time you can eat them is now, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wouldn't mind if you wanted to eat one now. They come in packs of two, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. We're in the middle of an investigation! Besides, I don't have $6 on me!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you want, we can pool our money and buy a pack together.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If I have to split it with you, then I don't want it!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It doesn't look like there's anything contradictory left in this area...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose not. <thought>Perhaps I should check somewhere else.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Did you find something, officer?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">I think there's a 5 dollar bill back there! ...Come on... ...Just a little more...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Is there no one working this crime scene who isn't a total waste of living tissue?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately, there doesn't seem to be a single person we can deem useful here.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Have you found any suspicious fingerprints, officer?</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Nope. Just the fingerprints of those involved with the case, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I guess we know all of the players in this case then, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that way... but I have the nagging feeling that we're missing something. <thought>And I suspect that what we're missing is hiding right here in this crime scene somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...He's making a most ridiculous-looking face.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That may be, but at least he doesn't look like someone who would tell a lie on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I suppose. But to a Von Karma, evidence is the only thing that carries any weight.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. At any rate, this poster seems to be of no use to us right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are mo signs that this fire extinguisher was used in the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If you could already tell from a distance, then why are you wasting your time examining it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, let's not try to rush absolute genius.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I think I have a pretty clear picture of what happened here now.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Naturally. After all, I'm here, aren't I?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe must have sat on this bench as he ate a Swiss Roll. And as he ate, he dropped it on the floor, and sullied the bench.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Ugh! How could he have not cleaned up after himself!? How utterly despicable!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't dare you whip me again! It wasn't I who made the mess in the first place! Anyway... If it was indeed Detective Gumshoe who bought the Swiss roll... ...that creates a rather interesting contradiction of facts.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">A contradiction... Where?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... I think another look at the special courthouse vending machine is in order.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! That contradiction you were talking about... I demand that you show it to me at once!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... <thought>If Detective Gumshoe really did buy a pack of Swiss rolls for himself... ...that fact creates a contradiction with what I know about this case!</thought> Hmph... Are you telling me that you haven't figured it out yourself, yet, Franziska?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">O-Of course I've figured it out! But I thought I'd let you have the glory, just this once.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She really doesn't like to lose, does she...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like this Swiss roll was bought from the vending machine in the hallway. I heard that it has a nice, fluffy texture, and just the right amount of sweetness. And it's made from all natural ingredients... ...so of course, it's easy to digest as well! ...Or so I've heard. ..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.................. ...Franziska, if you want one, I'd appreciate it if you would just tell me so.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I-I never said I wanted one! And besides, if I did, I'd make you prepare me some milk to go along with it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At that time, I hope you will be more direct, instead of playing these mind-games.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I won't rest until I've inspected every suspicious-looking nook and cranny.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I already checked this area earlier, but it never hurts to take another look.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Is this spot somehow connected to any of the evidence I hold...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Eureka!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is clearly a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Do you think so?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I think there is one.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I think there should be one.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Do not anger me with a foolish game of semantics, Miles!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnuurk! <thought>Nngh... I'd better look a bit more carefully through my evidence once again...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">About Detective Gumshoe's finances, he said that until this morning... ...he didn't have even a single penny on his personage.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Just how poor is that guy!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If his bonus really was only $5... ...then, he should not have been able to purchase a pack of Swiss rolls! However, facts being as they are, we found cake crumbs on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Meaning Scruffy must've bought a pack somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... <thought>That detective should not have been able to purchase a pack, and yet he did... The question is, "How?"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I can't believe they're selling Swiss rolls like these in vending machines these days.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, and I can't believe it's $6 for two... I mean, who charges that much for a commoner's junk food!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... If you want one, all you have to do is buy one for yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh--!? I'm working right now! It won't do for me to eat while there's a case to be solved!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrgh! <thought>Your idea of working must be vastly different from my own!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I believe I now have a very firm grasp on what happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Arnngh! ...W-Well, I do, too!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Alright, Franziska. Would you care to share what conclusions you've come to?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-Why should I do that!? We're still in the middle of a competition, you know! We should be checking to see if your conclusions are wrong first, so you go ahead!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It's almost cute that she's going this far to ensure that she wins... Almost.</thought> Very well. But first, we need to pay His Honor a visit to correct his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, if I may, I'd like to test your witness testimony to see how it stands up.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">D-Do you doubt me!? Am I your new suspect!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...In a sense, I suppose you could say that.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Even you, a judge... ...is nothing but a common witness before a Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Silence in the courtroom! Silence, I said! Mr. New Prosecutor Recommended by Manfred von Karma Miles Edgeworth... ...and Ms. Genius Prosecutor Successor to Manfred von Karma Franzisk...ack...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...You bit your tongue again, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ahem. As a defender of the law, I could never give false testimony! You can even place me under oath if you want!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well, then. Your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">During the recess... I, um... I went to the restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... Can you please try to remain calm?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I'm so used to simply listening to testimonies that I got caught up in the excitement.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I'm sorry, Your Honor, but I'm afraid I'm going to have to spoil your fun now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">During the recess... I, um... I went to the restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... Why exactly did you pay a visit to the restroom, if I may ask?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Well, isn't it obvious!? What else do you go to the restroom for!? Or, maybe... I-I-I-I-I knew it...! You suspect me of some sort of tomfoolery, don't you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please stay calm, Your Honor! <thought>This is going to be much harder than I anticipated...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I'm sorry... You're right... I need to think things through with a level head. I'm just nervous because so much has happened today with this trial. Let's see... I announced a recess, and a time for us to reconvene... But having done all that, I still wasn't able to go the restroom right away.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And why couldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Faraday had been accused, so I had a paperwork to process regarding a new prosecutor. Once I had finished that, I was finally able to make a mad dash to the restroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>At least he stayed consistent on the "going to the restroom" part of his testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is a window on the hallway side. In other words, I could see into the hallway.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, did you really go to the men's restroom?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh--!? What is the meaning of that statement!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I simply meant... that perhaps you went to a restroom on a different floor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I had to go for such a long time... It was all I could do to dash to the closest one to the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... I suppose that's only natural, given his circumstances...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I ran from the courtroom, through this floor's main lobby and down the hallway. Once you enter, you can see there's a window just above the urinals.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And it was through that window that you witnessed Detective Gumshoe, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, exactlyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Y-Your Honor! There is no need to yell! I can hear you just fine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I guess I put a little too much into that last answer. Now then, let's continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I entered, I saw that detective buying something from the vending machines.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Are you sure that the person you witnessed was Detective Gumshoe, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I'm absolutely sure. It's hard to miss someone of his statue, even from as far away as the restroom. Besides, I can't think of anyone else with that kind of hairstyle and big, beige coat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, I was simply wondering if you were mistaken in what you saw...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Preposterous! My eyes are as sharp as can be! Ready to see through lies to the truth! Although, recently, things do seem to become a bit fuzzier than they used to be...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Clearly, his eyes are not the only things that have gone fuzzy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">But allow me to say with all the honor and dignity of a judge... ...I am not mistaken in what I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But when I was about to exit the restroom, he had completely disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He disappeared? But Your Honor, didn't you just say... ..."I saw that detective buying something from the vending machines"?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes! Yes, I did! The restroom window looks over the courtyard and right into the hallway. But! Just as I was about to exit, I took another look, and there was no one in sight! .................. That led me to the only solution to this mystery. That detective must've gone into the crime scene, Lobby No. 2 at that pooooooooooint!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So he looked into the hallway from the restroom, and over the courtyard, did he...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">A detective that goes missing while on duty... That sounds mighty suspicious to meeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, I ask that you please remain calm.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Nononononononononono! I-I-I-I'm cerfectly palm!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>You're being anything but "perfectly calm"!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It appears that His Honor could not have been mistaken in what he saw.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, I suppose so, given his line of sight. However, Franziska, why do you suppose our lines of sight are so different?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...If you're referring to my height...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">C-Can't you hold that whip still for just a second!? Now, about His Honor's testimony... ...I believe his line of sight to be an important factor.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">If it's that important, why don't you hurry up and tell him already?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I will, but there is one more thing I need to do if I am to correct His Honor's testimony. I am going to need to retrace Detective Gumshoe's movements!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What was that finger wag for, Mr. Edgeworth!? And don't you know it's rude to shout "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" while someone is giving testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah. If you truly are a man of the law, then you must always be vigilant. For example, I, myself, never let an opportunity to shout "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>" pass me by!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth. It's one thing to be passionate about your job, but this is real life.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This is what some people may say is the pot calling the kettle black...</thought> Your Honor, I wonder if you might take a look at this for me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is that filth!? How dare someone dirty the hallway bench like that!? Who is the culprit!? That party is hereby found GUILTY of uncleanliness!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you must know, the uncouth bench sullier... ...has already been placed under arrest, thanks to your earlier testimony, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? ...Well that's good. But who was it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">We were able to discover something from the smudge on the bench. Namely, Detective Gumshoe's fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not happy with committing just murder, he had to go and dirty the courthouse, too!? GUILTY!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Please calm down. While it's true that the detective is the one who made the mess on the bench... ...we have not yet established that this action is related to the double murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe that the Detective bought a pack of Swiss rolls from the vending machine... ...and then, promptly sat down on the bench to eat one. The cake crumbs and pieces of chocolate on the floor under the bench... ...and Detective Gumshoe's fingerprints prove my conclusions to be true.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh... But I still don't understand. Is the whole thing related to how I couldn't see him as I was leaving the restroom?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... It is indeed! The window in the hallway was built rather high up into the wall... ..at around a grown adult's chest height. As evidence, I submit that Franziska herself was unable to see out of that window.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">.........</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghooooh! <thought>I knew I shouldn't have used her height as evidence!</thought> ...B-Basically, what this means is that the area directly under the hallway window... ...is a blind spot when the hallway is being viewed from the men's restroom!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... It seems that you have made the connection. If someone were to sit on the bench under the window... Yes, even someone as large as Detective Gumshoe... ...would effectively disappear from sight!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Do you finally see, Your Honor? Your testimony has just proven that Detective Gumshoe was in the hallway the entire time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ah! Sorry! I didn't mean to say it with that much enthusiasm. All I wanted to do was try saying it once. Here, let me try that again... "<cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is there something of value that you'd like to say?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, actually, there is! I remembered something else just now! Mr. Edgeworth! Please allow me to testify to the court one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Even if we overruled him, he'd just keep on talking, wouldn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That might not be a bad thing. The more info the better in a perfect investigation, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose it's possible you can't see a seated person from the restroom window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnnrrrrrk...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How was that!? That is the testimony of one who judges the crimes of others!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... Could you try to state the important facts first next time!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I agree! Before you go around judging others, you should learn to judge your own words!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eeeek! ...I-I'm sorry! But honestly, I thought that sound was just a noise popper until just now!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Now that he mentions it, right before we re-started the trial, he did talk about that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, by the way, was there someone celebrating a birthday during the recess? I could have sworn that I heard a popper going off... Come to think of it... The other day with my grandson...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The most critical point in this argument is when did the Judge look into the hallway? And whether that lines up with when the gun was actually fired.</thought> Your Honor, if I may... I'd like to clarify a few details in your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose it's possible you can't see a seated person from the restroom window.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, do you concede that you were overconfident in your last testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">N-Now hold on there! I just said that it's possible you can't see a seated person from the restroom this time! But you know something? I don't think you know when the prints you referenced were left on that bench, do you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While you have proven that it's possible the Detective was sitting... ...I still have a problem with just when those fingerprints were left.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>He's right. I have yet to prove when the fingerprints were left on that bench... While he feigns ignorance. His Honor has seen a lot of life... This Judge... I mustn't underestimate him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">However, that doesn't mean that the Detective was sitting there when I looked!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As we established, you went to the restroom during the recess. However, at what point in the recess did you look into that hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... After I called for a recess, I handled the change of prosecutor paperwork... Maybe about 20 minutes until we reconvened...? Yes, that sounds about right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Just as I expected.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What were you expecting? And I demand to know what that all-knowing smile is for!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... That statement you made just now is very important. I'd like for you to append it to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Alright. If you insist.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Let's see... I looked into the hallway about 20 minutes before we were to reconvene."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see... I looked into the hallway about 20 minutes before we were to reconvene.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Twenty minutes before we reconvened... Very well, what did you do after that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see... I had to make some preparations, so I rushed straight back to the courtroom. I also had to track down a few pieces of paperwork for the various bailiffs.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you rushed back to the courtroom, despite having just heard a gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, at the time... I thought it was just the sound of a noise popper. I really couldn't think of any other explanation than someone having a birthday party. But now... Now that this has happened...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... <thought>Thinking back, the Judge did mention something to that effect when we reconvened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Anyway! I forgot to testify earlier about probably the most important detail...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If it's something that forgettable, I don't need to hear it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eek! B-But! All I did was forget to mention it!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That sort of excuse may work on other people, but not on a Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! But it's such an important piece of testimony! Please give me a chance to present it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I suppose I have no choice in the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As I was leaving the restroom, I heard the loud "BANG!" of a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, about what you just said...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I know! I couldn't believe it myself! But I heard it! "BANG!" went the gunshot! I heard it loud and clear! And then I had a knee-jerk reaction, "Aah!" and jumped into the air! Like this! Yes, just like this! With a quick, "Aah!"</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">......Your Honor. Please remain calm when you're trying to explain yourself to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, sir! Sorry about that. Now then, I must gather myself, yes... When I heard the gunshot, there was no one in the hall! I should know! I looked! There was no one theeeeeeere!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This judge's emotion circuits appear to be stuck on "overreact".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">At this point, nothing stands out to me as a contradiction in his testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Franziska. If I'm correct, this testimony is hardly precision quality.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...I know that. And that's why I said, "At this point."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I think my first line of attack will be to draw more information from His Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I belive... that we've finally found the flaw in His Honor's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yet sadly, he's completely oblivious to it. But I guess I can't really expect him to be aware of it. Well? What are you waiting for!? Hurry up and fill him in! ...At least that thing finally came in handy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Now let's see what happens... ...when I present it to His Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Hon--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I cannot allow you to make an objection.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? Your Honor... I'm really sorry, but... ...I cannot allow you to not allow me to make an objection!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Egads! I've been overruled!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, there are simply too many holes in your testimony for my taste.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh-What do you mean by that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim that you heard the gunshot during the recess, but that is simply not possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">! Mr. New Prosecutor Recommended by Manfred von...ack...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Instead of biting your tongue, why don't you bite your tongue on those preposterous names!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see you have no mercy for the elderly either, Franziska.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Don't talk back to me, unless you want to be whipped in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>With your height, you'd need a step-ladder or four to accomplish that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! Mr. Edgeworth. My ears are not that far gone yet, I'll have you know! I can still hear just fine! And I heard the sound of a gunshot loud and clear with my own two ears!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah... Your Honor, I have here an interesting bit of testimony. It's from Detective Badd. And according to him, he heard the gunshot "right before the trial was about to start again".</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What did you just say!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, you just said... ...that you heard the gunshot "about 20 minutes before we were to reconvene". How do you explain this glaring contradiction!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That can't beeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunately... that is the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But! I heard it clear as day! "BANG!" The loud sound of a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>The sound of the gunshot... We keep returning to this point of contention. And that piece of evidence... I always did wonder why I found it where I did. However, now I understand what that gunshot the Judge heard really was!</thought> Unfortunately, Your Honor, this is what really produced the gunshot you heard!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... I have no idea what you are trying to say with that piece.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska... You're just still too young to understand.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Stop trying to fool me, and start being mature enough to admit when you're wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrrk! <thought>Perhaps that was not the piece I needed to show...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I found this object in the hallway earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What is that pink substance?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It may not look it, but this is actually a piece of a balloon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And I suppose you would like me to accept that pink balloon into the court record?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor... I present this piece of evidence in order to overrule your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor, your argument goes as follows: You saw no one in the hallway when you heard the gunshot. Now, there is no guarantee that the detective was sitting on the bench at that time... ...therefore, you believe he must have been at the crime scene, Defendant Lobby No. 2. ...Am I correct?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that's exactly right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Let me ask you something. Do you think that the gunshot you heard was produced by a real gun?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I think I've said enough that even you can figure the rest out on your own. Your Honor. You were fooled by the popping of this balloon into thinking it was a gunshot!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What manner of trickery is thiiiiiiiiiiiiis!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That was a good effort you put forth, Miles Edgeworth. But if it was me, I'd have wrapped this thing up before the Judge even testified.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Care to elaborate on how one ends something before it even begins...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, to be honest... I did think that the sound was a bit off from a real gunshot sound... But who could've guessed... that someone would pop a balloon in a place like this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's true... One doesn't usually think "balloons" in conjunction with "courthouse".</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Umm... I want to trade these coins with you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That's it...! That balloon that girl was holding... it explains everything.</thought> Your Honor, if it makes you feel any better, you didn't lie once in your testimony. However, I can't really vouch for its accuracy...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mmnngh... Who knew... that giving testimony could be such a difficult thing to do...? What have I done? I owe Detective Gumshoe a very, very big apology... I will see to it myself that he is released...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait... There are still a few things I have yet to resolve about what happened in the hallway. Your Honor, I request your permission to further question Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But why!? I thought we just cleared his name!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Whether we did just now or not... I still cannot say. The only think I can do for now is to continue in my quest for the perfect explanation. And to that end... ...I must resolve the remaining issues pertaining to the events that occurred in the hallway!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff! Please bring Detective Gumshoe into the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I must fulfill my mission, and find the perfect explanation to this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What is it now!? Is it time for my trial already!? I've already told you a gazillion times, pal! I didn't do it! </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll be the judge of that, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">No, you won't! I'll be the judge of that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, no, no, no, no! I'M the judge around here! And I'LL be the judge of that!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Why can't you guys be a little less judgmental...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, well, speaking of hasty judgements, Detective Gumshoe... I'm afraid I must apologize for an error in judgement on my part.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. I don't believe you should apologize just yet. We have yet to prove he is completely innocent of this crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">? Um, what are you guys talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...In any case. I would like you to testify as to your actions while you were on guard duty. And please remember, you are not on trial. This is all just a part of the investigation. As such, you may still be found to be innocent... ...however, if you should give false testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeoooow!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">My whip will object, loud and clear!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you are found to be lying, you will be held indefinitely. Understood?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.........I gotcha, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Thinking back on the state of the crime scene and the Judge's testimony... ...it's obvious that Detective Gumshoe is lying. And if I can't break his lie, then we may never get a break in this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I came down here to this courthouse on Detective Badd's orders.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He's still singing the same tired tune.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. In that case, I'll just have to change the melody. <thought>I know he's lying, and it's time I pulled the information I need out of him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I came down here to this courthouse on Detective Badd's orders.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, was it really Detective Badd who called you down here?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You bet it was, pal! I was left in charge of the precinct while everyone was out, and this call comes in... "I want you down here in one minute flat!" he said! Well, I thought this was my big chance, my first case, so I made a mad dash down here! Although, I couldn't exactly get here in a minute flat...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So how long did it take you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... About then minutes, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And what was Detective Badd doing when you finally made it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was waiting for me down on the first floor in the entrance way, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As soon as I got here, he ordered me to stand guard in front of Lobby No. 2.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And by "he", you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Badd, of course! And, this being my first time at this courthouse... ...he also walked with me up to the 3rd floor hallway in front of the defendant lobbies!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And did you meet anyone along the way?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm... Well... Just as we entered the hallway, we ran into Ms. Yew. When he heard from Ms. Yew that Mr. Faraday was not to be interrupted... ...that's when Detective Badd told me to stand guard in the hallway, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>So far, Detective Gumshoe's testimony is matching up with Detective Badd's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">From that time on, until I heard the gunshot, I was in the hallway the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You claim to have been in that hallway the "whole time"... ...however, is it not a fact that you did something while you were in that hallway?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">O-Of course I did something! I guarded the door to Lobby No. 2, pal! What else!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well, then. And what exactly does guarding that door entail?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm... Well, to put it simply... Oh, I know! It was my job to stand in front of the door without moving an inch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Detective Gumshoe, you mean to tell me... ...that you didn't take a single step away from the door to Lobby No. 2? Is that really what you wish to testify to the effect of?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got it, pal! I didn't take a single step away from that door, just like I was ordered not to!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why is everyone so quiet all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Because we are all in shock... ...and in awe of your utter stupidity.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Scruffy! If you're going to lie, at least tell us a more believable one!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeowch! B-But I... I'm not lying...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should hurry up and bring this insipid testimony to a close.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change statement">"From that time on, until I heard the gunshot, I was in the hallway the whole time!" to "And until I heard the gunshot, I didn't take a single step away from the Lobby No. 2 door."</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And until I heard the gunshot, I didn't take a single step away from the Lobby No. 2 door.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'm only going to ask you one more time, Detective Gumshoe. Are you sure you stood in front of the door to Lobby No. 2 the entire time?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yup! After I was told to by Detective Badd... ...I stood guard in front of that door without a single break! S-So believe me when I say that I was in that hallway the whole time already, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">..................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">..................</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Why did everyone go quiet all of a sudden again...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Apparently, someone has a bit of trouble reading between the lines.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What's that supposed to mean!? I don't...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Be quiet!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeowch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should hurry up and bring this insipid testimony to a close.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">On my honor as a detective, I swear it wasn't me, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Would you also be willing to swear that there was no one else in that hall besides you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about!? I just swore to you that I was doing my job, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Then what are you acting so nervous for?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What!? I'm not nervous at all, pal! Anyway! Not a single person other than myself was in that hall the whole time!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I should just let it go... Pursuing this train of thought at this time would just be a waste of time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">He's still singing the same tired tune.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. In that case, I'll just have to change the melody. <thought>I know he's lying, and it's time I pulled the information I need out of him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">To have such a foolishly foolish contradiction... ... in such a foolishly foolish testimony is just plain old foolish.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Indeed. However, in the pursuit of the perfect investigation, I'm afraid we have to deal with it. By Squashing it under the weight of the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have... an objection.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh--!? Wh-Wh-Wh-What is it, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe... I wonder if you might recognize this from somewhere?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! It's one of those things! The Courthouse Special Swiss Rolls, right pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph... Precisely. In that case, I suppose... ...that you also recall the sullied hallway bench?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You know what!? I think it was probably me that did that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Gumshoe! You know you can't go around dirtying up the courthouse like this!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You inconsiderate, slovenly pig!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeek! I promise to clean it up later! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, shall we get down to business? About the fact that you didn't move even a single step from in front of that door... If that really were the case, then how were you able to buy a pack of Swiss rolls!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Furthermore, if you didn't move a single step from in front of that door... ...how did you manage to get the bench dirty with your grubby hands!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeeeeeeeeowwwwwwwwch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears that Franziska's whip can do more damage than my words alone can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">A-Alright... I confess, pal. I was hungry, so I bought a pack for myself, OK!? I thought I'd get chewed out again if anyone found out about me eating on the job... ...so I didn't want to say anything!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, unfortunately for you, I saw you do the whole dastardly deed! I clearly saw you buying a pack of Swiss rolls from the vending machine!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">*sigh* OK, OK, I'm sorry for lying! But that's all I'm sorry for, you got that! Because I'm not holding anything else back!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That last statement... It may sound like it makes sense... ...however, there is something I don't quite believe about it!</thought> ...Are you sure you're not withholding further information from us?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? O-O-O-O-Of course not! I've got nothing else to hide, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Oh, if only that were true, Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">B-B-B-B-B-But it IS true, pal! I swear there's nothing else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe, I'm sure you are aware of the price of a pack of Swiss rolls, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Umm... Remind me again, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That vending machine out in the hallway... ...is selling packs of two Swiss rolls for $6 a pack.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mmmmnnnnrrrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And yet, according to you... ...you didn't have any cash on you until you cashed your $5 annual bonus check. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oooooooooonnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let me ask then, how did you managed to purchase a pack all by yourself? Can you provide me with a proper explanation to that?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aaaaaaaargh! I told you, I bought it by myself, pal! There wasn't anyone else in that hallway with me... ...so there's no one who could've helped me buy it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait, don't tell me... You've got some kind of proof that there was someone else in the hallway, don't you!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As if you could! I mean, what are the chances of that... Wait, you do...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course I do.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whaaaaaaaaaaaat!? Hooooooooooow!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What proof do I have that there must have been someone else there in the hallway...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What the heck is that!? Heh, I knew you didn't really have anything! You prosecutors are all the same, always lying to people. You should stop, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghhhooooh! I refuse to be lectured by the likes of you, Detective!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles! How long do you plan on being strung along by this moronic detective!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I have no intention of falling for his lie, because there was definitely a second person. <thought>Because if he was truly alone all along, then that piece of evidence should not exist!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! You showed that to me not two seconds ago, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah... I think you're under the mistaken impression that I bought this pack of rolls.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wait, if you didn't buy it... then that means you must've stolen it! You thief!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? I would never do such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">All you liars are the same; you start out as thieves! You're under arrest, pal!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe you meant to assert that all thieves start out as liars. And in that case, what does that say about you, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Gnnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This particular Swiss roll was dropped by a certain someone.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.........Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There were two rolls in this package. You ate one of them... ...but you then gave the other one to a certain other person, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-N-N-N-N-N-N-N-No way, pal! You've got it all wrong! I ate both of them...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that we've caught you at last.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! Don't you dare do anything bad to that girl!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would appear that they DO know each other after all...</thought> So, why do you continue to come up to me and kick me? Have I wronged you somehow?</line>
<line speaker="???">I have a name, and it's Kay!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay what...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Kay Faraday!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Faraday... Are you perhaps, Mr. Faraday's daughter?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm not a "you"! I'm "Kay"!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mnnrgh... Kay. You know... good little girls don't kick other people. Especially not hard enough to leave big, nasty bruises like the way you do...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Well, then you shouldn't have put Gummy under arrest, mister!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">G-Gummy...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My guess is that she's talking about Detective Gumshoe.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...What a cute nickname you've given him.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy didn't do anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that I will need to speak with her in a bit more detail...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Rwaaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">That girl... She seems to know that scruffy detective. Maybe she knows something about him that we don't.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Agreed. However, she seems to be rather... uncooperative at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">She's like a stray alley cat. Ha ha ha. I wonder what would happen if we feed her.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... Perhaps I will try feeding her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears that we've caught you red-handed, eating a Swiss roll.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ack! Look, I'm sorry about lying to you, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And? Do you have nothing else to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure do! It was so fluffy! And sweet! And big! Ah, it was perfection, pal! And totally worth every penny of my bonus!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............I see. Well, good for you, Detective.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I can't believe it, but it's almost funny when a fool is this unbelievably foolish.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh dear... *sigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is the matter, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I claim to hand down fair verdicts, but I unfairly cast suspicion on the big fella. If this had been a trial just now, I would've destroyed his life! I... am the guilty one! *siiiiigh*...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...We all make mistakes, Your Honor. "To err is human, to forgive divine," as they say.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Although, if you were to make a mistake during a trial, then it would be quite unforgivable.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">*hiss!*</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...She's like a stray cat.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder if I should feed her something...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Kay">*hissss!*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She swatted it back at me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Graaaaaaawr!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, I demand that you do something to calm her down this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, I promise to give this to you if you calm down.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! A Swiss roll!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It really belongs to you, though, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Yeah. I was saving it for Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Your father... He's...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ah! Don't you say another word, pal! She doesn't know yet!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Thanks for watching out for me, Gummy... But... I... I already know about Daddy. I overheard the guards talking... ...about how Daddy's... he's... not here anymore...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm sorry... I'm sorry I couldn't protect him...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I-I'm not gonna cry! I'm not... gonna... ...cryyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's alright... Let it all out... Your father just passed away, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I, myself, was also involved in a case at this courthouse when I was a young child... A case in which my father, who was a defense attorney, passed away. All of my dreams of becoming a lawyer were crushed into fine ash on that nightmarish day. Even now, the wound festers deep in the depths of my soul. Even since that incident... I've dedicated myself to locking away every criminal I can. And now, to have this happen right in front of me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>This child... I feel a certain shared fate, a common bond between us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Miles Edgeworth! What sort of gentleman are you!? Are you going to just stand there and watch a lady cry?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, you're right. Sorry about that. Kay... Here, How about we use this handkerchief and dry your little eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">*quiver*... ...Uuuugggh... *Hooooonk!*</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnnnghooooooh! My cravat! Don't blow your nose on that!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...I feel better now. Thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like the girl has finally calmed down.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I believe I can take my time and talk with her now.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's so disrespectful for a child like that to be running around inside the courthouse! Does no one have respect for this country's judicial system anymore!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Didn't Mr. von Karma say the exact same thing earlier...?</thought> But Franziska, I don't think you two are that far apart in terms of age...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I'm about to become a prosecutor, so understand that I'm nothing like that little girl!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It looks like some sort of exchange diary that girl shared with her father. We're alike, that girl and I. Because they're both admirable prosecutors... ...we look up to our fathers. The only difference is that her father is now dead. If my father, who is the anchor of my life, were to die, I don't know what I'd do...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You needn't worry about that. Even if he were to be killed, Mr. von Karma's spirit would still go on living. Urrrnghk!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Don't talk about Papa like he's some sort of ghost!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That was supposed to be a compliment...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, are you going to be... alright?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup, I'm already alright!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Somehow, I highly doubt that, but I'm not going to push it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I promised Daddy I'd never cry in front of strangers.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">And you're a good kid, aren't you, Kay!? You always keep your promises, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Eheheh! That's right! Even if I can't see Daddy anymore, I'm still going to keep all my promises!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're a very brave girl, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You're a very good child for keeping the promises you made to your papa. I'll even testify that you didn't cry, just for you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Thank you very much, lady!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......Hah. It's nothing. I'm only teling the truth, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It would appear that because her father was a respected prosecutor... ...Franziska is sympathetic to Kay's feelings...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, what kind of person was your father?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Daddy was a Hero of Justice! His job was to catch all the bad people in the world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, to you, a prosecutor is a Hero of Justice, huh? I suppose we are in a sense, as we are the ones who seek guilty verdicts for criminals.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Plus, you know what? Whenever I came to the courthouse... ...Daddy would buy me my absolute favorite treat, Swiss rolls!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh...?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I wanna be a Hero of Justice someday, just like Daddy... ...so I've been working really hard!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. And what have you been working hard on?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I've been working hard to keep all the promises Daddy and I made together!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A promise notebook...? May I take a look inside, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sure, OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>It appears to be an exchange diary of sorts between father and daughter. Mr. Faraday's writing conveys a sense of the kind of man he was. This little notebook just might come in handy later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thank you for showing it to me, Kay. I hope you'll continue to work hard and become a hero just like your father.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm gonna try!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, Kay! So, I'm a detective that catches the bad people, right? That makes me a hero, too!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! You're really cool, too, Gummy!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, aren't I, Kay!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is with the two of them...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I hand down Verdicts of Justice, so that makes me a hero, too!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Yes, and thanks to your oh-so-heroic testimony... ...you almost painted that detective as a vile criminal and sent him off to jail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">! I-I'm really sorry about that...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy is not a bad man, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>That poor Judge. He's being treated like a vile criminal rather than a Hero of Justice.</thought> It appears that you and Detective Gumshoe are good friends, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! We're friends!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In that case, would you mind telling me a little more about him?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So I take it that you ran into Detective Gumshoe earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yup! I was on my way to see Daddy when I saw Gummy standing there. He was standing in the hallway staring really hard at the vending machine, so I said hi.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And when was this?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Oh... Umm... Before everything got crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">How long were the two of you together?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">U-Umm... We only talked for a little while. And then we went on our own ways.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That's right, pal! Kay and I only talked for a little while, and that's it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh...? Which means... ...we have now confirmed that Kay was in the hallway during the recess, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">.........Ack! You got meeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I told you to stop picking on Gummy, mister!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Very well, then. I'll just have to speak with the good detective in private later.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Were you the one who bought this pack of Swiss rolls, Kay?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... Well... I didn't really have a lot of money... ...and I somehow made a dollar out of all the pennies and quarters I had... But that still wasn't enough, and I really, really wanted one...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Come to think of it... ...she did come and ask me to exchange a handful of change for a dollar...</thought> And that's when you came and asked me to change your money, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! Thanks a bunch for doing that, mister!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sure... But let me ask you, even with that dollar, you still didn't have enough, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... Well... that's why...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! If you bully Kay any more, I'm gonna have to arrest you, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Need I remind you that you're the one already under arrest!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeeeeow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I sense that Kay is going to be less than forthcoming with this question...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! Daddy showed this to me before!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, he was a prosecutor, too, so it's only natural that he had one as well.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Daddy would pin this badge on me a lot, just for fun.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Pinning a Prosecutor's Badge on a child for fun...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Daddy said that if he put it on his clothes, a scary prosecutor would get mad. He also said that the scary prosecutor said it was more "fashionable" to not wear it.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I wonder who that scary prosecutor could be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I wonder... Could Kay be talking about Mr. von Karma...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">You really need to stop picking on Gummy, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Aarghn...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ho ho, Kay! Attagirl! You're a great kid, you know that!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>What is with their chummy relationship...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What the heck are you doing, reminding her of her father's death, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... didn't think of that.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">She may look all happy, but she's really hurting deep down inside, you know! So have a heart and be more sensitive, OK, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I-I'm sorry... <thought>For once, this detective is actually the voice of reason...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">I came here with Daddy for his work, and I wanted to eat with him... Daddy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>She looks so sad and lost... I can't bring myself to make her recall any more about today's events.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kay">It's the Promise Notebook Daddy and I made! I have to be a good girl and keep all of the promises we wrote in here!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... May I take a look inside for just a second?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Sure, OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm... It appears that there are more than just the five I thought there were... Promise VI... "If you ever have a boyfriend, you must bring him to meet Daddy right away." Promise VII... "Even when you have a boyfriend, never forget that I love you the most."</thought> ..................</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I certainly don't envy the poor sap she falls in love with...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Kay, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Huh? Are you giving it to me? Umm, but... ...I promised Daddy that I wouldn't take things from strangers. I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's alright. I wasn't intending to give it to you anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh, OK. Eheheh, guess I thought wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles, even if you show that to her, she isn't going to magically know all about it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I suppose you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Umm... Sorry... about your ruffly thing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...*sigh* <thought>Yes, well, now that it's positively drenched in your nasal mucus...</thought> Don't worry, Kay. I have a spare. So here, you can have this one.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...Ummmmm... But Daddy said... "Never take things from a stranger."</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ah, it's one of the promises you made in your Promise Notebook, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! Look, see! It's right here on this page!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... Alright then, I'm not giving this to you. I'm merely allowing you to borrowing it. You can take it home, wash it nice and clean, and then give it back to me next time we meet.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...OK! Daddy never said I couldn't borrow things from strangers!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now then, Detective Gumshoe...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Uh oh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe it is now crystal clear... ...that you were with little Kay in that hallway!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Ooooonnngh...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Grr! I told you to stop being mean to Gummy!!!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! There is still something you have yet to resolve.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You still haven't offered an explanation for why that man would lie to us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-That's...! Well...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">! Gummy... Don't tell me you lied for my sake...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey! don't worry about it, Kay! Everything's gonna be OK!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Ah, so that's why...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So, what was Detective Gumshoe's motive for lying? If you can't explain that, then you can't call this a perfect investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. His reason for lying is very simple.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Here is what I believe to be his reason: From simple observation of the Detective's actions and his interactions with Kay... ...it's obvious the Detective was lying for the young girl's sake. And this piece of evidence will show you exactly why. <thought>Which piece of evidence proves that Detective Gumshoe was lying on account of Kay?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is that piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">What are you showing me that for? It doesn't seem to add anything to the conversation.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Umm, I don't get what you're trying to say with that. Or do you just like showing it off?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Are you gonna give that to me, mister?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't feel that the court needs to enter that into the court record at this time.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnnrk! <thought>What is wrong with everyone!? Why are they ALL teasing me all of a sudden!? Although... it's possible that perhaps I made a mistake, and that's why... Now then, back to the topic at hand. Detective Gumshoe lied for Kay's sake. And I know I hold the evidence which shows the reason why!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Mr. Faraday and Kay's Promise Notebook? How does this explain anything?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you could take a look at this page, it's clearly written that Kay should... "Never take things from a stranger." When Detective Gumshoe heard about that promise, he tried to cover for Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">......... What a foolishly foolish fool's fool of a foolish reason for a fool!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Eeeowwwwww!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy... You lied because of me, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Because I'm your friend, Kay! That's why!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Gummy...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...At long last. Detective Gumshoe, can you please tell me the whole truth now?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Guess there's no beating you, huh, pal? OK, OK, I'll spill the goods! I'd been standing guard for a while... I was getting really hungry, and that snack vending machine was taunting me.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">But all the cash you had on you was $5, and that wasn't enough to buy anything, right? After all, the cheapest item in that machine is a $6 pack of Swiss rolls.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah... But then, like an angel from heaven, Kay showed up...</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I was thinking about sharing a snack with Daddy... ...so I wanted to buy a Swiss roll. But I only had about a dollar in coins.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">So we pooled my $5 and her $1 together... ...and bought a pack of Swiss rolls together.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But I was worried... ...about breaking one of my promises. So then Gummy said...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Mr. Faraday's one scary guy when he gets mad! But, don't worry. You won't get in trouble if I don't tell, right!? Besides, you bought it with me! So you didn't really get it from me, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">...He told me it'd be OK... And he gave me a whole roll to save and give to Daddy.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Who knew that Scruffy could be so considerate...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed... Detective, I take it that you then sat down on the bench and ate the rolls together?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, we split the other roll and ate it right then! The sweet taste of that cake's chocolate... I'll never forget it as long as I live, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Anyway... Kay, I believe this also belongs to you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Oh! That's from the balloon I popped...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's bad manners to leave garbage lying around, Kay.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Well, I guess I can't blame you for not throwing this one piece away. It was sitting high up on a windowsill where you couldn't see it. So just this once, I forgive you.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">But that balloon... I wanted to surprise Gummy a little, so I popped it on purpose... ...and because of me, Gummy dropped his half of the Swiss roll.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Aha ha ha! Wow, you really got me there, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">So I thought maybe I should give Gummy this other roll. And then, I saw you picking on Gummy, mister...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you kicked me, is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">You sure are a feisty one.</line>
<line speaker="Kay">I'm really sorry, mister...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's alright. I'm perfectly unharmed. But about this Swiss roll... Would it be alright with you... ...If I held onto it until Detective Gumshoe is cleared of all charges and free to go?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">Yeah! Sure! Just make sure you give it to Gummy afterwards, OK!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. I promise. Now then, I believe we have proven beyond the shadow of a doubt... ...that Detective Gumshoe was in the hallway for the entire duration of his duty. Which undeniably proves... ...that Detective Gumshoe could not have committed the double murders.</line>
<line speaker="Yew"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Actually, it proves just the opposite, Edgeworth. You've just shown... ...that Detective Gumshoe is the only one who could have committed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What do you mean!?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It's quite rude to eavesdrop, Ms. Yew.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh... Ahah... Ahahahahaha! Mnnphwwwwh... I'm getting lectured on manners... ...by a girl with a penchant for whipping people! Phwwwwkkkgh!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Wh-What!? How dare you talk back with such insolence!?</line>
<line speaker="Kay">You're wrong, lady! Gummy's not the bad guy!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, and what have we here? What is a child doing here in a courthouse? Bailiff! Please take this child in!</line>
<line speaker="Kay">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? Ms. Calisto Yew! That girl is Mr. Faraday's...!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I know. So what? You think that just because she's the victim's daughter... ...she gets to just run wild all around the crime scene? I think it's actually quite dangerous for her, to speak nothing of getting underfoot.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I suppose you're right, however...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">As long as we're in agreement on that point, let's get back to the real issue at hand. Now then, Detective, you were in front of the door to Lobby No. 2 the entire time, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Y-Yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">You see! Isn't it obvious that it could only be the detective? He is the only person who could've gone into Lobby No. 2 at the time of the murders!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arngh! <thought>I... have no counterargument to that...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Yew">Don't worry, I've already put in the necessary paperwork for his formal arrest.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnrgh! But the investigation is far from over!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Oh, that's right. I was going to speak with you about that. Don't you think it's reckless to talk to the suspect out in the open without a guard?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I suppose it is...</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, as someone with more experience in law than you, allow me to share something: Always keep a good eye on a criminal, or you may regret what comes of your negligence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Oooooh...! Miles, I can't believe you're letting this woman lecture you like this! This is unforgivable as a disciple of Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ha ha ha. Down, tigress. Now then, I'll be looking forward to the results of your investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">So. We're back to square one.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Actually, this is our last chance. I can tell that if we fail to solve this case... ...Detective Gumshoe will be formally charged under all of the circumstantial evidence. <thought>This investigation is not over yet. There's still one location we have yet to inspect. It's where Detective Badd and Ms. Yew were at the time of the crime -- Lobby No. 1!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Hmm, the pieces don't fit together quite right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>I can't see a clear connection between these two pieces of information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>...Not exactly a shining example of the perfect line of logic.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence that proves the flaw in your theory!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! You dare try to bluff through this by presenting unrelated evidence? You're a disgrace to the Von Karma name!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>Could I have it all wrong...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Franziska, I advise you take a look at this piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And what are you trying to say with this?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I'm saying that this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">...Doesn't contradict with my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arrghnn...!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth... Just face it; I'm going to win our little competition.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! I have to calm down and do a better job of finding a flaw in her logic!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a clear contradiction in your line of logic!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">And where, pray tell, would that contradiction be?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe... nowhere?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh! <thought>Could I have it all wrong...? At this rate, I'll lose the truth for all eternity... I need to pay more attention to her testimony...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew, what do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Well, as someone with more experience in law than you, allow me to share something: Use your own brain and figure it out yourself. That's my advice to you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. Well, I'm terribly sorry to have bothered you with such a mundane question.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwwwh! No need to be so serious! Tell you what, I'll toss in another piece of evidence. In no way does my testimony contradict with that piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh......... <thought>I should've known...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I believe this piece of evidence contradicts your statement just now.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">..................</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Ms. Yew! I insist that you please take a good look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I don't need to do anything. I can already tell you it doesn't contradict a thing I said.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... I... I see...! <thought>She's fearsome when she's not doubled over in laughter! I must treac carefully here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is a glaring flaw in your testimony, and this piece of evidence will prove it!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh...! Mnphwwwh! Ahahahahahahahahahahahahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">! What exactly is so funny!?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Phwwh! You say you're a disciple of Von Karma...? Phwwwwwwh! I can't wait to see what kind of prodigy you really turn out to be in court! Phwwh! Because, right now, you're a prodigy among mistaken buffons, that's for sure! Ahah!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles Edgeworth! You will take your punishment for soiling the good name of Von Karma!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnghaah! <thought>Your simultaneous reprimands are punishment enough!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor! There is a very large flaw in your statement just now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm? I don't understand what you're talking about. Where is it, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">N-Nevermind, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Making such accusatory statements... I don't know how I feel about that.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-I'm truly sorry, Your Honor! <thought>Arghn! I have to find a flaw in his testimony before the truth escapes me completely!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement and this piece of evidence... contradict one another!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't feel a contradiction in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Arghn!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth... I advise you to be a little more cautious with what you say.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmmrrrgh... <thought>It would appear that I was mistaken.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That statement right now contradicts with this piece of evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">R-R-R-REALLY!? Well then, I guess we're still alright. Please continue with the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The two of them overruled me!? <thought>At this rate, I will lose the truth to the darkness forever... I need to stay calm, think carefully, and find a flaw in his testimony, fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There is clearly a contradiction here!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">There is?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Do you not recognize that there is one?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Not at all, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see. In that case, I retract what I said...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Why can't you ever just admit when you're wrong!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Gnnrrrk! <thought>Curses... I can't keep on doing this. I must regain my composure, and think it through again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Detective Gumshoe. There is a problem with that statement you just made!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What are you talking about!? There's nothing wrong with my statement, pal! So don't go around slamming what I have to say for no good reason, alright!? Unless you do have a good reason! In which case, can you explain it to me in a way that even I can understand, pal!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmnnrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Hmph. Miles... It looks like that evidence will be of little use to you in breaking Scruffy's lie.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, I can see that! <thought>I guess I was wrong... I need to pay attention and listen carefully to his testimony one more time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This piece of evidence proves the contradiction in your statement!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? What exactly does it prove?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Um, I suppose it doesn't "prove" so much as...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Looks like a meaningless piece of evidence. The court refuses to accept it into the record.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mmrrrrnngh... <thought>It would appear that I was mistaken... Arghn! If I continue to make mistakes like this, the truth will slip from my grasp!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Manfred">What are you hesitating for!? I should have known you weren't ready yet.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sir! Please, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Manfred">This matter should not have taken more than three minutes to resolve! Period! Franziska, you disappoint me as well. Now get out of my sight, the both of you!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Papa! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! Is this the best I could do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">It would appear... that I am the victor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">W-Wait a second, Franziska!</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">I don't need to hear any more from you! As I've always thought, only I am worthy of the Von Karma name!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! Was that really the best I could do...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahaha! Is there anything else you'd like to share?</line>
<line speaker="Franziska">Miles! Why aren't you fighting back!?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nngh... Because I have nothing to fight back with at this point in time.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-What!? But I didn't do it, sir! Please, help me!</line>
<line speaker="Yew">And that's the way it is, Mr. Badd.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........Gumshoe. Just come along quietly, alright?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">But sir...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Badd">...Afraid I can't let the two of you mess things up any more than you already have. So don't get me wrong. but... get out.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh--!? But I have an investigation to run!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">Hmph... I don't care if you do or don't... The fact is... that you're in my way. You there! Take these kids outside.</line>
<line speaker="Forensics">Sir! Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, but I have to prepare for my next court hearing. Don't worry, I'll make the necessary arrangements for Detective Gumshoe's arrest...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Please wait, Your Honor! There is still much we have yet to resolve...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Unfortunately for you, this court sees no reason to further prolong the issue. That is all. The court is abjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! THIS was the best I could do...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Yew">Ahahahahahahahahahahahaha! That's as far as you go, Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it now, Ms. Yew?</line>
<line speaker="Yew">I don't have any more time to waste babysitting the two of you. I think we have enough to take Detective Gumshoe in as a "material witness". Don't we, Mr. Badd?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What!? Since when!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">N-No way, pal! I swear I didn't do anything!</line>
<line speaker="Badd">.........We can talk more down at the station.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Detective Badd! Please, you've gotta believe me, sir! I'm innocent, sir! Honest...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth"><thought>Nngh! Is this all I could do for him...!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thus the truth was lost for all eternity.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There's nothing unusual about this area.</line>
</xml>