<xml>
<title>Turnabout Time Traveler</title>
<line speaker="Man">I'm not completely heartless! I'll even throw that time machine you cherish so much overboard with you!</line>
<line speaker="Bride">Please, take me back... back to that blissful moment...!</line>
<line speaker="Bridesmaid">It's almost time for the reception, m'lady.</line>
<line speaker="Bride">It actually... really worked...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, lemme make sure I've got this straight. When your magic panties appear... ...I do a backflip into a handstand, then blow out the candle...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, no, Athena, you've got it all wrong! You do a backflip through the ring of fire, while holding the candle in your mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh... There's no way I'll ever be able to do that.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure you can! I believe in you, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Trucy, what are you and Athena up to?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Athena's agreed to be a part-time performer in my magic show!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I couldn't say no to some extra cash, but I probably should've thought it through first... Now it's "human cannonball this," "guillotine that"... It's not like I have nine lives, y'know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've made your bed, Athena. Now you've got to lie in it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooo... I'm too young to be taking out a life insurance policy already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My name is Phoenix Wright. I'm the head of this law office.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And since when did you become the head of this office, Daddy? I mean, who exactly does all the cleaning, accounting, and scheduling around here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. You've got me there, Trucy. This is Trucy Wright. She's my adopted daughter, and a magician.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And I'm Athena Cykes. The rising star lawyer of the Wright Anything Agency!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or rather, the rising star assistant to Trucy, you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If I don't get back in a courtroom soon, I'm going to forget everything I ever learned...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Speaking of the courtroom... we haven't exactly had any clients lately, have we?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Business is as slow as ever, huh, Nick? Bet you made more money back when you played the piano.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yo! Long time no see!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......L-L-Larryyyyyyy?! I-I haven't seen you in years! What brings you here, all of a sudden...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">..........Some big news, that's what.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, okay...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Who's this guy, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Larry Butz. He's, um... Well, let's just say he's an old friend of mine. So, Larry, what's so big that you had to come and tell me in person?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...There's somebody I want you to meet. Hey, you can come in now!</line>
<line speaker="???">...All right. How do you do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, hi...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Th-That dress! Is that... a wedding dress?!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Yes, it is. My name is Ellen Wyatt. I'm a domestic servant -- a maid of the Sprocket household.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Sprocket"...? As in "Sprocket Aviation"?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Yes, that's the one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, Mr. Wright! Sprocket Aviation is a really big airline company! You've heard of Rainbull Airlines, right? The one they call "RAL" for short?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that does sound familiar.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it's run by Sprocket Aviation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... But what is a Sprocket family maid doing here in a wedding dress?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">So, actually... we've decided to get married.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You what?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I'm not so young anymore, ya know? I figured it's time to finally settle down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Y-You're... getting married?! <thought>No way. I don't believe it. Besides...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why would someone as well put together as her choose someone as flakey as Larry...?</thought> Y-You're kidding, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Jealous? I don't blame ya, but green's really not your color, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... *sigh* All right, Larry. Lay it on me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I haven't played this old thing in a long time... Not that I could ever play it to begin with... And considering all the complaints I'd get, I guess I'd better just continue to not play it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe I should tidy this place up every once in a while. Still, I bet we're going to use all this stuff sometime soon again anyway... So it's probably better just to leave things where they are.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I bet we're the only office in existence that uses magic props as furniture. At this rate... ...Trucy's props are going to wind up taking over the whole office. I mean, they're already halfway there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Charley looks as lush and green as ever... ...thanks to Athena taking such good care of him. I guess I should pitch in every once in a while, too, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This office might look messy... ...but at least I keep all of my clients' personal info safe under lock and key. That's what a successful man does, right? Puts his efforts where they count!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Apollo's jacket, Athena's notes... ...and Trucy's magic props. Not that I'm complaining... It's nice to know my friends and family are always close by.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In all seriousness, Larry, are you really getting married?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Not right away, but that's the plan. We're gonna elope, see -- like, love on the run, I guess you could say! Isn't that right, Elly?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">................................................ Larry. I do believe there's been a major misunderstanding here. My heart already belongs to another.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I'm in love with Sorin... ...not you!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">S-Say whuuuuuuuuuut?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>......That's about what I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">B-But, Elly, baby! W-Weren't you running away with me so we could get married?!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">As I said, you misunderstand! You said you'd help me escape. That's the only reason I ran away with you!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...U-UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! This is NOT happening! I even shook off the police for you... And for WHAT?! That's it! If we can't be together, my life is over! I'm gonna end it all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, back up... Did you say you shook off the police?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yes! We HAD to, 'cause we're lovers on the lam!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sorry, Ms. Wyatt, but can you maybe fill me in on what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">To tell the truth, I'm being pursued by the police as a murder suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Murder? They think you killed somebody?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I happened to find a dead body at my reception, so the suspicion fell onto me. They had me confined in a separate room... ...and that's when Larry came along and helped me escape.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'm sorry, but what...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Ohhh, Nick! Me and Elly were going to elope -- we were gonna put it all on the line for true love! But the police tried to stop us, so we had to scramble to shake 'em off! Where did it all go wrooooooooooong?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I feel a migraine coming on.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Please help me! The police are sure to be intensifying their search...! Look! It's even on TV!</line>
<line speaker="TV">More news on the murder suspect and an unidentified man on the run from the police. A photo of the suspect, Ms. Ellen Wyatt, has just been released by the police. Sources say that the 21-year-old is suspected of clubbing the victim... ...25-year-old Dumas Gloomsbury, to death in the wedding reception hall after her banquet. The two fugitives are said to be highly agitated and dangerous. If you see them...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got to be kidding me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, brother...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess this means we're technically harboring a pair of fugitives here, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">*sniffle* Oh, Nick! What's a guy to do?! Elly's dumped me hardcore!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'M the one who should be crying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I haven't seen you in ages. Where have you been all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You mean you don't know? You've really gotta stop living under a rock and get out more. I'm the hippest, hottest picture book author in the business -- Laurice Deauxnim! I can't believe you didn't know that I'm taking the picture book world by storm!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! But I know you! You're the one who wrote "Franzy's Whippity-Whip Trip," right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, I think I did hear something about a one-hit wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">O-One-hit wonder?! What the heck, Nick! I'll have you know I just created a BRAND NEW character, to moderate acclaim! He's mildly popular with 18 to 24-year-old women everywhere! Look! You can see his cute self all over this jacket!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? That heart-shaped pork chop?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">He's not a pork chop! He's the main character of my latest picture book! A lovable little soul who pierces the hearts of lovers with his arrows of amore -- Cupiglet! And you can see this adorable fellow make his debut in... "Cupiglet's Lovey-Dovey Lark"! In stores now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure...? Because I've never seen that book "in stores," now or ever...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, if you ever do see it, do me a favor and buy a copy or ten, will ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I thought you were "taking the picture book world by storm"...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-What are you showing me your attorney's badge for? Wait, are you saying you want me to take up your badge and hit the courtroom?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Absolutely not. With you as the defense, you're liable to bring the whole courthouse down. Literally.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">All I want is ONE chance to defend somebody in court...! OBJECTION! How was that? Pretty good, huh? ...Ready to let me borrow your badge now? You saw how awesome I am at pointing, right? I'm starting to think I'm a natural!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not lending you my badge, and that's final. Besides, pointing isn't all that a lawyer does!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Aww! Pretty please?! Whaddya got to lose?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My reputation, for one! <thought>I never should've shown him my badge.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Anywho, you'll defend Elly in court, right, buddy?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Please! I'm begging you! I didn't murder anyone! I swear I'm as clean and pure as this pure-white dress!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No Psyche-Locks. I guess that means she's telling the truth. But helping a fugitive on the run? What am I getting myself into?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">......There's... actually one more thing I really need to tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">You might find this hard to believe, but... ...the truth is... ...I'm a time traveler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? I-I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">After the wedding reception, I was... attacked... I was moments away from my death... But then, in that instant, I made a wish upon this pendant around my neck... ... and I went back in time to just before the reception started.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...............</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Only, this time around, the man who was trying to kill me was already dead. And... somehow, I became the suspect for his murder. It's as if... history had been rewritten.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...N-Now, wait just a minute here. I don't understand. Are you saying tha--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's going on?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Wright! There are police cars outside! And not just one or two, but a whole bunch!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! A whole squad of officers has the building surrounded!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">This is the police! There is no escape! Drop your weapons and come out with your hands up!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Eeeeeeeeee! Nick, what do we doooooooooo?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Heck if I know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see a bunch of armed officers out there... One, two, three... ...forty-four, forty-five. Wow. Talk about overkill...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Listen here, you criminals! Think about what you're putting your poor parents through. I'm sure this isn't how they raised you! Think about their smiling faces, and their warm, home-cooked meals! Ack! Who in the heck are you...? A detective?! N-Now, hold on there! H-Hey! You can't go in there! It's too dangerous! WAIIIT!</line>
<line speaker="???">Is everyone okay in here, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm sorry for all the commotion.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Um, so, what in the world is going on?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I raced on over as soon as I heard that it was Mr. Butz who'd holed himself up in here... ...with the murder suspect after he made off with her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the fleet of patrol cars?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The police are being extra careful... ...because apparently, a certain somebody yelled out... "Stay back! I have a bomb!" I'm sure you can guess who I'm talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, the police were being so persistent, I had to do something! So I tried bluffing! You know, like you do in court, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please leave me out of this...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, Mr. Wright, I'm bringing this young lady in for questioning. So if you want to talk to her, you'll have to do it down at the detention center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh* I suppose I should thank you for your thoughtful gift of trouble and mayhem, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">C'mon, Nick! We gotta get down to the detention center right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Listen, Larry... I haven't even decided whether I'm going to take on this case or not.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">But I know you will! 'Cause it's you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess I've got no choice but to tag along and help, then!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? And skip out on me?! We've only just started practicing your repertoire, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You'd better stay and practice with Trucy, Athena. A promise is a promise, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's cold, Boss! You've gotta get me out of this! I can't take it anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Let's get practicing, Athena! Next up is some training for the water tank escape trick! Stick your head in this bucket of water and hold your breath for fifteen minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eep...! Noooooooooooo! Stop! I'm begging you!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! She's getting away! You get back here, Athenaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. I guess the only person cut out to be Trucy's assistant is Apollo. Well, guess we'd better get to the detention center and ask Ms. Wyatt some questions. Especially about that whole "time traveling" business she was talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">......Oh! It's you, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Wyatt, would you mind if I asked you a few questions?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick is gonna defend you, Elly! Isn't that great?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Larry! I told you I haven't decided yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Wh... Wh... Wh... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Y-You're not going to... take my case? *sniffle* WAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH! I'm NEVER gonna be happyyyyyyy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Wyatt?! <thought>What the--?! Did I do something wrong?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Wyatt, please calm down!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I'm innocent, I tell you! *sniffle* But the police won't believe me! And neither will anyone else! I'm gonna die all alone in a jail ceeeeeell!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right, all right! I'll do it! I'll take your case -- just please stop crying!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The fact that Larry was the one who brought you to me had me a little worried, but... ...you don't seem like a killer to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">OH, THANG YEWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW! WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Thanks, Nick! I knew you'd come through!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did I really have a choice?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I guess not, heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In any case, it doesn't seem like Ms. Wyatt killed anybody. Plus, it's not like I'm up to my ears in work at the moment.</thought> Ms. Wyatt... Ellen, let's do this -- together!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Oh, THANK you, Mr. Wriiiiiiight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There, there. It's going to be okay. Now, try to pull yourself together.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">A-All right. Just give me a moment... I'm truly grateful to you for taking on my defense, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sure. No problem. <thought>Wow, she literally pulled herself together...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That camera... What is it pointed at anyway? If they're trying to film the defendant, shouldn't it be pointed more this way?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Look at that guard... He's standing right in that camera's blind spot. From that position, I bet he could even doze off and get away with it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This mic has been here for a long time. It looks pretty worn out. But this little guy has made thousands of conversations possible... ...so I'd probably end up feeling kinda sad if they just up and replaced it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen, please tell me everything you can about the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">...All right. It happened after the wedding reception... I... was attacked... ...by Mr. Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wasn't "Gloomsbury" the name of the victim in that news report? Maybe I should listen to what she has to say first, though, before I start asking questions.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">How dare that guy lay a hand on somebody else's blushing bride! What a creep!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's rich, coming from you. Do you have any idea why he'd attack you?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No... But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But what?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Well, to tell the truth... ...Mr. Gloomsbury didn't seem very happy about me getting married.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Geez, jealous much?! What a loser!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Gloomsbury had forced me onto the vista deck, and was going to push me off... Oh, how frightening it all was! I was just about to lose my life -- on what should have been the happiest day of my life! So that's why I... ...I made a wish upon this pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Yes, it was a gift from my husband-to-be, Sorin. He said it's a symbol of our love.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And so you made a wish on it?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Now, you may think that what I'm about to say is very strange, but... I begged the pendant, "Please, take me back... back to that blissful moment...!" And do you know what? It worked! It brought me back to just before the reception started!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, so that's the "time traveling" thing you mentioned back at my office? I'm sorry, but I have to say... it's pretty unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">U-UNBELIEVABLEEEEEE?! I-I KNEW you'd never believe meeeeeee...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick, Elly here is an honest-to-goodness time traveler! Don't you believe your own client?! The magic of that pendant sent her back in time before the creep could kill her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aha ha ha. Sure, Larry, sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">But it's really true, I tell you! This pendant is an important part of the time machine Sorin made. I begged it for help, and it really DID send me back in time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I-Is she listening to herself...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I even experienced the reception again, even though we'd already held it once before. And during it, everyone there acted as if nothing unusual was happening at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... Could you not cook while we're talking, please...?</thought> All right. So when and how did you come under suspicion for murder?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Well, after the reception ended -- the second reception, I mean... ...I went back to the reception hall and started cleaning up the place by myself...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-Hold on. Cleaning? Why were you cleaning on your own wedding day?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">For my last task as a servant of the Sprocket household... ...I offered to take on the preparation and cleanup of the reception banquet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I started to move one of the decorative lanterns in the room... ...but it was so heavy I lost control of it, causing it to topple over and break open. That's when I saw... Mr. Gloomsbury's dead body inside the lantern...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you simply happened to be the first to discover the body, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">That's right! I just came across it by accident! But I became confused, and didn't know what to do. That's when some of my in-laws saw me... and jumped to the conclusion that I had killed him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this Gloomsbury guy tried to kill Ellen... ...but then wound up dead himself after Ellen traveled back in time...? A time machine and a magic pendant... How could any of this be possible?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Elly, why don't you tell Nick about that other thing, too? About that shadowy figure you saw when you were being attacked?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Yes, good idea, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you and Larry here were never planning on getting married, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">That's right. We've only had a few brief interactions, so I can't say I know him at all.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, Elly! How can you say that?! You and me are bound by fate, I'm telling ya! We're meant to be together!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Y-You're wrong, Larry! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I've never been so right, baby! It's as plain as the goatee on my chin!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, don't make me send you to time out. Now, can you tell me about the groom, Ellen? What's he like?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">His name is Sorin Sprocket. Oh, he's the most wonderful man! He is, truly, my destiny.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you say "Sorin Sprocket"? As in...?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">That's right. The next president of Sprocket Aviation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, he's in line to take over the company?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hmph! He's nothing but a rich, spoiled brat! I'm clearly the better choice. Clearly!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Larry, you and Sorin are as different as night and day. There is no comparison.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Ellyyyy, you're breaking my achy-breaky heart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So she's marrying into money, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I can't believe Sorin chose me, a simple house servant. He's my knight in shining armor, my prince... *sigh* Oh, my Sorin...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's this shadowy figure you saw, Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">It was... It was when Mr. Gloomsbury was attacking me... Right after I made a wish upon this pendant, I started to pass out... .. but just then, just as I lost consciousness... ...I saw somebody strike Mr. Gloomsbury from behind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You did?! Then that person... ...must be the true culprit! Did you see who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I-I'm afraid not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you told anybody else about this?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I told some of my in-laws, but nobody took me seriously. They said it was all just a dream.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't exactly say I blame them... I mean, time travel...?</thought> .........Larry, for my peace of mind, please tell me that figure wasn't you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Of course it wasn't!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Ooooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I just remembered our reception... We were supposed to be so happy together! Oh, where did it all go wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't blame her for being upset.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Why did this have to happen to me? UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ellen! Please try to calm down! Okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">A-All right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, she stopped crying, but... ...how can I ask her about anything when she's still so clearly distraught?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What can you tell me about this?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oh, never mind that! What about Sorin? Oh, Sorin... Do you suppose he hates me now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I really couldn't say...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oooooh... What if... What if...  What if he doesn't love me anymore because of all this...? Whatever shall I...? *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, no! She's going to start crying again!</thought> I really don't think he hates you, Ellen!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Y-You don't? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, really! <thought>...Probably?</thought> So don't cry. You'll only cause him more heartache if you do.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Y-Yes. Yes, you're right. As a Sprocket bride, I have to hold my head up high at all times!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better really watch what I say around Ellen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I've asked her all I can for now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Spick and span! Spick and span!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Ellen? What are you doing?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I want to make everything clean and beautiful for when Sorin comes! I can't have my future hubby come into a dirty room, now can I? It has to be spotless, just like this white dress! Spick and span! Spick and span!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's hope we can wipe away all suspicion from you soon, too.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nick, we'd better get to the crime scene right away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What, you're coming, too?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Of course I am! If I solve the crime and reveal the true killer with my super sleuthing skills... ...Elly might change her mind about me, ya know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You never get the message, do you, Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Next stop: the mooring dock in Sprocket Park. C'mon, Nick! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is Sprocket Park... but where's the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">The reception hall? Oh, that's... ......Wow! Looky there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I just spotted me a cute mamacita! Don't wait up, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hold on! Where's the reception hall?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Sorry, Nick! A man's gotta stop and smell the roses when they appear! I am an artist, after all! Oh, miiiiss! Yoooooooo hooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh. I thought he was going to take me to the crime scene! Ah, well. I'm sure he'll come slinking back when he inevitably gets rejected. I'll just take a quick look around until then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, that huge airship is moored to just this skinny little tower. I know it's tied down and all, but it still looks like a good breeze could send it flying...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So this bench hit that sign, huh? Hopefully, it didn't hit a person, too! That would be a catastrophe. I guess from now on, whenever I'm walking around outside... ...I'd better be on the lookout for unidentified flying furniture, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, that airship is huge! <thought>Oops. Didn't mean to say that out loud. I've only seen airships like this up in the sky. But I've gotta say, they're mighty impressive when you can see them up-close like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. This thing's really banged up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Youth">You looking at the sign? They say it got damaged by heavy winds yesterday. A big gust sent that bench flying into it. Well, that's what they're saying, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... <thought>The wind caused that?! More like a tornado!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Youth">The repair guy was saying, "Don't touch. It's dangerous!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. Thanks for the heads up. <thought>Poor guy... Looks like it was a lot of work.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey, sorry about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I actually thought you'd be back sooner. Didn't work out, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Lay off, man! I wasn't on my game today!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So now that you're done, would you mind telling me where the reception hall is already?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whaddaya mean? It's right there in front of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Right in front of...? Wait. What's that say? "Flying Chapel"...? Do you mean to tell me...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yup! Elly's reception was on that airship!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! A sky-high reception hall?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yep, and that's where you'll find the crime scene. Man, not only does that airship fly through the sky, but the space-time continuum, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the happy couple's honeymoon got left far behind when it made that time skip, though.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Here, check the airship out for yourself with this pamphlet.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">By the way, I figured you could use some backup, so I called in some help for you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yup. Should be here any minute now...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That red sports car! Larry, don't tell me you called...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You know it, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="???">I trust you've been well, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Surprise! Now, admit it -- that was a pretty good Mr. Edgeworth impression, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry called me up! He said something about it finally being time for him to "tie the ol' knot." But that's funny... I'm pretty sure he mentioned something about being here with his bride...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............ Maya! I know this is sudden, but... please marry meeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............ N-Nick, what's Larry talking about?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He was dumped by his bride. Well, by his imaginary bride, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......Wow... Poor Larry. That's a new low, even for him. ......But, hey! Imaginary girlfriends never hurt anyone, right? More power to him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is Maya Fey. She's been abroad for her training as a spirit medium. But now that her training is over, she's back home here in the States.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! The new-and-improved Maya Fey is on the scene... ...spirit and girl power at the ready!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Heh, look at you, Maya -- all grown up and as cute as ever! Ooh! You know what? I just realized something! If I ever got married, I'd miss out on all the fun of always meeting somebody new!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hmph. I see you haven't changed a bit, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Edgeworth! I figured that car belonged to you! But when did you become Maya's chauffeur?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's nothing like that. I just happened to run into her en route, and picked her up. And by "run into her," I mean she jumped out in front of my car. I nearly ran her down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is Miles Edgeworth. He's a friend of mine, and the district's chief prosecutor. I heard he's been busy lately...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what brings you here? Wait... Don't tell me Larry called you up, too?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He did. However, I have business of my own here at the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Business? What kind of business?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't believe that Edgeworth's still driving around in that bright red car. Maybe it's time he pimped it out by slapping a cravat on its hood or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just so you know, Wright, I am the lead prosecutor on this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! You?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. It appears we'll be standing on opposite ends of the battlefield this time around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I'll be up against Edgeworth tomorrow...</thought>  ......But I don't get it, Edgeworth. What about this case warrants the personal attention of the district's chief prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's a bit... complicated, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The groom is a member of the Sprockets, a family with immense influence. If his bride were to stand trial in court, it would sully the Sprocket name. So they tried to apply some pressure on the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Pressure to settle it amicably, right?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you mean, "settle it amicably"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It means that they're trying to sweep this whole thing under the rug.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. Sprocket Aviation really has that much clout?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes. They have especially strong ties in both the political and the judicial worlds... ...to the point where no one dares to oppose them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't tell me that includes you...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't be ridiculous, Wright. It's quite the opposite. The Prosecutor's Office is filled with cowards, as I found out. Every last one of my subordinates was loath to prosecute a Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that's why you decided to take on the case yourself, right?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's right. I will personally see to it that justice is served. I always prosecute to the utmost of my abilities, regardless of who I'm up against. For that is a part of my creed. Nothing and no one can sway me from that -- not even the almighty Sprockets.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If they think they can use their influence to bend the truth... ...they have another thing coming.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know, I almost feel sorry for them. They were only trying to protect their interests... ...but all they got instead was you.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Edgey! C'mon, man! How can you prosecute my poor, sweet Elly? What kind of heartless jerk are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I'm simply doing my job. And I'm warning you, Wright. I won't hold back, not for you or anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks for the warning, Your Righteousness.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, how's it going, Mr. Chief Prosecutor? Busy as always, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course. Unlike SOMEBODY who has too few clients and too much time on his hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh, guess that explains why your brow is more furrowed than the last time I saw you. Maybe you should learn to relax a little, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Nice try, Wright. But as always... ...I have no intention of showing anyone any mercy... ...including you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As inflexible as ever, I see.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Besides, I think I've mellowed out a bit with age. So if anything, those furrows should have smoothed out a little as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Honestly, Edgeworth, are you really that blind to yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">E-Excuse me?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's really self-conscious about those lines, isn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There doesn't seem to be any rust on that badge... ...but can the same be said of its owner?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! I'm practically rust-proof.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh. Let's hope you stay that way.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the suspect is claiming that she made a wish on that pendant... ...and was transported back in time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hah! Of all the ridiculous things in this world! And you actually believe this fantastic story of hers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... W-Well, I, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You should drop this case if you can't bring yourself to believe in your own client's words. Not that I can blame you for your skepticism, mind you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnngh... <thought>I may not have a good answer for him right now, but if I just do my job... ...I'm sure the truth will make itself known in the end!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Already started your investigation, I see. I suppose I should praise your enthusiasm.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't need to patronize me, Edgeworth... Just because you're chief prosecutor doesn't make you better than me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. My title is my title. But when I see a lawyer from some tiny, obscure office hard at work... ...it's only natural that I should want to do my part to help the socially impoverished.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nnrgh... Well, you can help by providing me with some info!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A flying wedding chapel... That's a rather romantic venue, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Romantic"?  I never thought I'd hear THAT word come out of your mouth. Are you feeling okay there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What? Am I not allowed to think such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait. You're not thinking about finally settling down and getting married, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why do you always have to jump to such extreme conclusions? For your information, I have no intention of doing such a thing... What about you, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No plans here for now, even if I wanted to... <thought>Well, at least I found out how Edgeworth feels about marriage. Not that it has anything to do with the case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth, about this incident...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't forget, Wright: I'm the prosecutor for this case. Need I remind you that I'm not in the habit of sharing information with my "adversaries"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No... <thought>I guess we ARE "adversaries" for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And you, Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'd like you to come with me. You have a lot to answer for after that little stunt you pulled with the suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">But, Edgey! We're old pals, aren't we?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Personal appeals won't work on me, Larry. Now, come along!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Waaaaah! Niiiick! Help me out heeeere!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Is it just me, or is Mr. Edgeworth as relentless as ever?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess some things never change. So much for "mellowing out."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick, we'd better hop to it, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hop to what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Investigating the crime scene, of course! What else? It's been a long time since you and I teamed up like this! This is going to be fun!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">F-Fun, huh? <thought>It HAS been a long time, though... since we were last together like this...</thought> All right. To the crime scene, then!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! And awaaay we go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's not every day you get to see an airship up close like this. So I'm pretty psyched for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me, too... if it wasn't for the fact that it's the scene of a murder...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, right... I almost forgot about that part...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. That sign really got smashed up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There were some really high winds yesterday. And they say that that bench was blown right into the sign.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! I wish I could've seen that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you'd been there, you would've gotten blown away by the wind too, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That sounds kind of fun, actually! Don't tell me you never tried to use an umbrella to fly when you were a kid?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think I'll take "staying alive" over "fun," thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Might as well just jump right in, I guess. So, what do you think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, let's see. I think... the inside of Mr. Edgeworth's car smelled heavenly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, no. Apart from Edgeworth's car. I mean, do you have any ideas about this case?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Sorry, I can't think of a thing... But what are we wasting all this time with thinking for? There's investigating to be done! Ooh, I can't wait to see what kind of evidence we'll find!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You seem really excited.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You bet, Nick! The dynamic duo is back in the saddle again! Let's go round 'em up, pardner!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. All right, let's get to it, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what do you think we should do, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't it obvious? We start by investigating every single place that has anything to do with the case... ...and then grill every single person involved!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Her enthusiasm is kind of overwhelming...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now, go forth, Phoenix Wright! Search out the truth! ...Well, don't just stand there! Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, ma'am...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Louder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-YES, MA'AM!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's more like it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Your attorney's badge looks so nice and shiny on your lapel! It's so cool -- like the mark of a true hero!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I can be a hero to my clients, that's good enough for me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">In that case, I'll be the commander that controls the hero from behind the scenes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, are you saying you've been manipulating me all this time?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go, RoboWright! To the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess that makes me a RoboLawyer...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! What a beautiful pendant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It belongs to Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I love its design of a gear with a rose in the center. I wonder if it has any special meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"May the gears of our love keep on turning"... ...or something like that, maybe?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think their love will get in gear once we solve this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I sure hope so.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">An aerial wedding... sounds so amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It sure would make for the memory of a lifetime. <thought>But I bet this wasn't the kind of memory poor Ellen hoped to make...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">You gotta wonder, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">After the wedding, do you think the couple gets to ride the airship to their honeymoon?! That would sure make things a breeze!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I guess it would...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks suspicious, but also, not. It could really go either way, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what if you had to come down on one side or the other?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Then I guess I'd have to say... it's probably neither.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks for the non-answer, Maya.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is the reception hall...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">According to the pamphlet, we're right here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yikes. We're pretty high up... But at least we're indoors, so it doesn't seem so bad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, look, Nick! It's Ema! Hey, Ema! Over here!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, Maya. Does this mean you've taken the case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, that's how things kinda turned out. So do you mind if we take a look around?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Be my guest. We've pretty much wrapped up our investigation, so go right ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now's a good chance to find out more about the case from Ema, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a hot-air balloon -- a symbol of humanity's ambition to take to the skies... It's kind of a romantic notion, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! But I just noticed that it doesn't seem to be tied up to the ceiling all that well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sure it's fine... <thought>Please don't let it fall on my head...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A model airplane, the perfect decoration for an airline company wedding.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And a propeller plane like this lends the room a great, old-timey feel! Ooh, I'd love to see the Steel Samurai fly a plane like this! Can you picture it? The Steel Samurai, zipping through the clouds over Neo Olde Tokyo?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Sprocket Aviation ever becomes a sponsor of the show, I could see it happening.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why didn't I think of that?! I think I'll go suggest the idea to them later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Please at least wait until after the trial is over...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like... a business card wallet. I wonder whose it is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That face looks awfully familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Yes it does... <thought>Guess I'll bring it to him later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, look at the horns on this flying bovine! He must be a bull. It seems he made it through the ceremony in one piece.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">By the look of those wheels, I bet he can be rolled around rather easily, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I bet it would be quite a hassle if you had to lift and carry him everywhere. And this is what the backside looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's that by the bottom of his tail? A wheel handle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I get it. This way they can get inside to change the light bulbs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see they left the wheel handle on the inside unpainted.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess they figured nobody will see it, so why bother. It makes sense to cut costs where you can. Well, overall... ...I can't say I see anything strange about this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder what this partition is for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I imagine people like the reception staff or entertainers use it. They probably wait behind it when they're on standby.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I see... With a partition this size, I bet they could even fit an elephant back there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Not that anyone sane would.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one big partition screen. Industrial size, even.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet it'd cause an industrial-sized mess if it fell over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's why you're not allowed to touch it, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! Then who's going to test how stable it is?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just leave it alone... please?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a fog machine for the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Pretty cool, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you dare touch it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww. Spoilsport.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's because I know how you operate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a fog machine. I wonder if they used it during the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! ...Hey, Nick. Go stand over there for a sec.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, why...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just because! Now, go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-All right... <thought>I've got a bad feeling about this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Fog-Master 9000... ON!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, noooooo! ............Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww, nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it won't work without some dry ice.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Darn it. All I wanted to do was surround you in a thick cloud of smoke...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">*sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Get a load of that huge set of doors! I bet all sorts of things come and go through there! Like an elephant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm pretty sure it's just the bride and groom... <thought>This is a banquet hall, not a circus...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's the vista deck out there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I bet the view is amazing! But I guess it must also kinda freak you out, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, kind of. <thought>Mostly because there's no surviving a fall from way up here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the sweetheart table where the bride and groom sit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Where they gorge themselves on the wedding feast, you mean! I'd be too nervous to eat in front of a bunch of guests like this, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They say that newlyweds are usually really busy during the reception, you know. They have to greet and talk with all the guests that came to give their blessings. They don't actually get all that much time to enjoy their dinner.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... I wouldn't be able to stand that... I can't imagine having a huge feast right in front of me and not being able to eat it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They say brides tend to have an especially hard time because of their wedding dresses. With those tight corsets squeezing their waists, they can barely eat a bite.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really...? It sounds like wedding receptions are absolute torture...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess food still wins out over romance in Maya's book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be where the time machine was placed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe that such a beautiful memento was used for murder! It's just awful! Nick! We have to prove Ellen's innocence, no matter what it takes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree! We can't let this go down as the saddest flying wedding reception in history.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think that about does it for this area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the lantern the body was found in. Ellen managed to move it quite a ways. It looks like... a cow, but it's pretty badly broken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not a cow, Nick. That's Pegasus, the flying horse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way. It's definitely a cow. It's got horns and everything.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But look, it has wings! Cows don't have wings! So it's Pegasus, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I know! That pamphlet should tell us! Let's see... Apparently, it's called a "Pegamoo."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I did not see that coming.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yet somehow, the name really captures the essence of what this creature is, you know? ...Huh, that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, this Pegamoo is definitely a male "Pegabull," right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I'd say so, what with the horns and all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, well... That Pegamoo over there is also a Pegabull. But take a look at the pamphlet. See? The one on the right says "Pegabull," but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The other one says "Pegacow" -- a female Pegamoo.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right. The pamphlet goes on to say how they have Pegamoos for the happy couple.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So for Ellen's ceremony, there should have been a male and female pair of Pegamoos... ...but, for some reason, there are two males here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Maybe somebody made a mistake when they were setting up the room?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's hard to believe a fancy place like this would make that kind of blunder, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In any case, we'd better check this thing out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take another look at this lantern, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did this come from the lantern...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ick. It's covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it got on there when the killer was putting the body in the lantern?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Can you imagine going to open a door and finding the knob covered with blood...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That'd be... bloody awful, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this is where the body was found... And the first person to find it was... Ellen. Ema, what can you tell me about the condition of the body when it was found?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let's see... The victim was apparently hit on the back of the head. Here's a photo of the scene as we found it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, what do you think this is, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It looks like a flower petal to me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What an unusual shape for a flower petal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you suppose it's from one of the flowers here in the reception hall?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I don't see a single flower like this at any of the tables. I wonder where it came from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, what's this?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, let me take a look! "Grab Ellen when convenient, then send her off from the vista deck." ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a note outlining the murder plot...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoever wrote it has better handwriting than me, but it looks like they wrote it in a rush.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why do you say that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because the writing is only smudged starting from the middle of each line. That happens when a right-handed person with a slight hook writes in a hurry. I do it sometimes myself when I'm not paying attention to where my hand is on the page.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess I'll take your word on that, Ms. Bad Handwriting Expert.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Even I don't smudge my handwriting this badly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, all right. Let's get back to the note...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That note was apparently written by the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would he feel the need to write instructions to himself like this? Are you sure the victim wrote it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I sometimes write a note to myself before I go shopping. Potatoes, carrots, onions, flour...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, Maya? Are you craving curry rice or something?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoops.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Ema, where's this "vista deck" the note mentions?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's that heliport you see right outside the window over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he'd planned on pushing Ellen off from there? What a monster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess that about does it for this lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth wouldn't tell us anything about this case. So do you think you could give us a rundown?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, seeing as he's going to be prosecuting, I'd expect him to be tight-lipped about it. The incident occurred yesterday, on September 20th. It happened after the wedding reception, which lasted from 7 PM to 10 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">7 PM to 10 PM, huh? Got it. Um, by the way... ...you didn't hear about any time traveling or anything, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Time traveling? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, nothing. Forget it. <thought>That's pretty much the response I expected.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The victim's name is Dumas Gloomsbury. He was a servant in the Sprocket family household.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen was a maid for that family as well, so that means... ...the two of them were coworkers?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. They apparently knew each other. Mr. Gloomsbury was the lead servant, after all. He was very serious about his work, but he was also a very closed and private man... ...so the other servants called him "Mister Doom-n'-Gloom" behind his back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he was the lead servant, he must've been higher-ranked than Ellen. What makes the police think Ellen killed this man, a guy who was essentially her boss?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We don't know the defendant's motive yet... ...but the circumstances surrounding the discovery of the body don't bode well for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what circumstances are these, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, some of her in-laws saw what looked like the immediate aftermath of the murder. The suspect was standing in front of the body with the murder weapon still in her hands.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would a bride, who was just about to start a happy new life, kill someone? Do the police have an explanation for that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, about that... They believe the victim attacked the suspect and was killed when she fought back.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why did he attack her to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, a mere servant girl was going to suddenly be the wife of the future president. Mr. Gloomsbury must've been more than just a little jealous of her...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So this "Mister Doom-n'-Gloom" attacked Ellen first? But if she was only trying to protect herself... ...wouldn't that count as justified self-defense on her part, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would. There's a good chance she'd be acquitted if we could prove that, but... <thought>I wonder what Edgeworth will have up his sleeve to counter that claim?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">But, wow. A servant girl marrying the future president of such a huge company... It sounds like a modern-day fairy tale!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It does, doesn't it? Thing is... ...not everyone was on board with their union, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what was the murder weapon, Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This clock with a secret mechanism built into it. It was on display here in the reception hall. The suspect was holding it when the murder was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the victim was clubbed to death with this, huh? But that's funny. There's no blood on it as far as I can tell.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe it was wiped off in an attempt to tamper with the evidence? But there was definitely a luminol reaction... ...and it matches up with the shape of the injury, so it's gotta be the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What a funny-looking clock.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They call it the "Time Keeper." The idea is that it's a time machine. Every time the couple sees it, it'll bring them back to the memory of their wedding day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A time machine, huh? Come to think of it... Ellen said her pendant was part of a time machine... I wonder how the secret mechanism in this thing works.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">The suspect never had any family or relatives to depend on... ...so she was working as a live-in maid for the Sprocket family to support herself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So a maid with no family or fortune was set to marry the president's son, huh? I guess it's not surprising that ruffled a feather or two.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. Apparently, the groom's parents and all of his other relatives were strongly opposed. But that didn't stop the young couple from deciding to go ahead with their wedding.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Love flourishes in the face of adversity! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Is that how it works?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! If you ever have any questions about love, just ask me! I'm a qualified expert! I spent all of my spare time in Khura'in watching soap operas on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure that's enough to make you a qualified anything, Maya...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, and by the way... I heard the suspect faced her fair share of harassment, too. And from the sound of it, it got pretty ugly for her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... So even though this incident could cause a huge scandal for the company... ...it might be a boon for those who opposed their marriage to begin with. After all, with Ellen's arrest and everything, the marriage is most definitely off now...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's absolutely unbelievable. What kind of monster would plan to commit a murder on somebody's happiest day?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I take it this means you don't have any significant new leads...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, I'm afraid not. You?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've got nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I wish I could be of more help.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, thanks anyway. I appreciate it. All we can do is keep on keeping on, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you're sure this is the murder weapon in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Positive. The shape of the victim's injuries and the shape of this clock are a perfect match.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I daresay that if somebody were to get knocked over the head with this thing... ... it's more likely to cut off their future than send them to the past!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't disagree with you there.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is there something I can do to help you with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I was hoping it would help me move my investigation along...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry, but that's not going to do much for you here, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Aww, don't look so glum. You have to keep a positive outlook! Why don't you take a break with something sweet? I highly recommend Snackoos, myself. You want to try some?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no thanks. I appreciate the offer, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Suit yourself... You don't know what you're missing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I guess that just about does it for the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick. I want to see the rest of the airship! We might as well, since we're here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>True. We might even run into some of the other people involved in the case.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick, how long has that guy been standing there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't even notice him until just now.</thought> Excuse me. Are you with Sprocket Aviation?</line>
<line speaker="???">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! He wrote something on that paper airplane!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess we're supposed to read it, then?</line>
<line speaker="???">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see here... "Get out, intruders." <thought>Well! That was a rather cold welcome.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mr. Wright, Maya, meet the lone son of the president of Sprocket Aviation... ...Sorin Sprocket. Or, to put it another way: the future president of Sprocket Aviation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So he's Ellen's fianc? </line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, there he goes...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He's kind of an eccentric. I hear he's the genius inventor behind many of Sprocket Aviation's business successes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An inventor, huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yup. He even designed this airship.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's pretty impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! This is no time to be standing around gawking! We have to go after him! We need to ask him some questions about Ellen!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. R-Right. <thought>It looked like he was heading outside.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, are you thinking about a new look, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That red jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. That's Apollo's.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Maybe you should wear a little red every once in a while... But... Hmm... It's not really your color, is it? Then again, you never wear anything but blue... so why not give it a try! Here you go, Nick! Put it on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, like I said, it's not even mine...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's Charley! His branches are as handsome as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Charley seems happy to see you, too, Maya. His leaves are greener than usual today.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, he looks super healthy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We always make sure he's watered and well-cared for. <thought>And by "we," I mean Athena and Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">These are all your case files, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, and there's private information on my clients in there, too... ...so no snooping.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hm? What's this? "Perfecting Teleportation Magic"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Trucy must've swapped out my files for her magic books!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa! It's one of those Zig Zag cabinets for dividing a person into three! I've never seen one in real life before!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's one of Trucy's magic props. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! Let's try it out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know... It's probably dangerous to get in that thing if you don't know how it works.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aw, come on, Nick! Just hurry up and get in there already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why am I the one on the chopping block here?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! There's all kinds of interesting stuff here! Like this hoop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha. Maya, that's not a hoop for hula hooping, you know. It's a--</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A hoop used for levitation magic, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh! <thought>How did she know?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come to think of it, you used to be a pianist, right, Nick? So play something for me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not really good enough to play in front of other people...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Can I play, then?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No way! We'll get complaints from the hotel next door.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No fair! It's just a glorified shelf if nobody plays it, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This poor Pegabull. He used to be so handsome, and now look at him. I wonder if I can fix him?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait, Maya! You can't tamper with important evidence like that! So don't even think about it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I bet Ema would let me do it if I asked!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not like building a plastic model, you know. Just leave it to the professionals.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess you're right. But I could've remodeled him into something even cooler!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure "remodeling" falls under the category of "evidence tampering," too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm dying to find out who killed Mister Doom-n'-Gloom. So let's hurry up and find some evidence, and solve this case already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then why don't you lend me a hand?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think I'm doing here! Now, let's find the truth together!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ol' Gloomsy's handwriting sure is neater than mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe it's because the other servants had to be able to read his writing, too?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But some of the words in this are smudged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess he rubbed them with his hand as he was writing. Judging by the content, I'm guessing he wasn't in the best frame of mind when he wrote it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'll say... A scary note like this would rub anyone the wrong way...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Time Keeper... If you really CAN travel through time with this thing, I'd go back to before the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's it? Come on, Nick! You can think bigger than that! We could go back to the age of the dinosaurs! Or even the heyday of samurais and ninjas! Can you imagine how much fun it would be?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can imagine how much it would screw up our present day...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There he is. Excuse me. Could we talk to you?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me. Do you mind if I ask what you're doing?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............! ............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-He sure is writing up a storm!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">It IS possible. If an enormous change in mass could be detected at that observation point... ...then theoretically, matter can retain its form, even as it crosses the event horizon...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Let's just see what he has to say about Ellen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but we'll be representing Ellen in court tomorrow... ...so, could we ask you about the case?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ow! Wh-What the...? "Not interested." "Not interested"?! How can you say something like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is about your fiance! She's under arrest, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ ...The diameter of the airship is approximately  eighty feet. The amount of energy necessary to move matter comprised of that amount of mass is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's off in his own little world.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I can't believe he said he was "not interested" in talking about his own bride's arrest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll just have to talk on his level, then, with something he might be interested in.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......... What are you showing me that for? ............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...........</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't read him at all. Not even with an item as loaded with sentiments as this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does this bring anything to mind?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ ...........</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even some small, vague detail will do...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">........... ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>This guy really doesn't want to talk, does he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">! I-Is that... Ellen's?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen told us that she traveled through time during the incident. She said it happened after she made a wish on this pendant.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...... You mean to say you two are Ellen's lawyers?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. I told you that just a minute ago.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Sorry. I was lost in thought.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He wasn't even listening?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, boy. <thought>He's not at all what I expected... based on Ellen's gushing testimonial, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'd like to ask you about Ellen's case, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ I don't know a thing about it, so why don't you go ask the police?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>In other words, "Not interested"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">This guy is the worst! Now I feel sorry for poor Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, can I ask you about how Ellen traveled through time?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess that got your attention...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... is time travel really even possible?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Yes, it IS possible.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A-All righty, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">At the same time, it is also impossible. The pendant I gave Ellen... ...is not supposed to operate as a time machine by itself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The Time Keeper, that clock we had displayed in the reception hall... ...THAT is the body of the time machine. The pendant is simply a part.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That clock was the murder weapon, wasn't it? But it's a time machine, too?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">What Ellen experienced is akin to traveling down a road by a car key. Physically and metaphysically, it should be impossible. ......Unless... maybe the quantum system inside the pendant... ...somehow accidentally interfered with the natural flow of the fourth dimension...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......We're losing him again... ...Maybe we'd better ask him some more about the time machine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you've been researching time travel, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Moving through the space-time continuum would be man's ultimate means of travel.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Time travel as a mode of transportation?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Since the dawn of time, man has developed multifarious methods of transportation. Horses, steam engines, gas engines, airplanes, spaceships... But they are all fundamentally similar, in that they constitute three-dimensional movement. Time travel through the space-time continuum would shift mankind into a new paradigm.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">......I don't why,[sic] Nick, but I'm getting awfully sleepy all of a sudden...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">For generations, Sprocket Aviation has advanced the development of transportation. Therefore, it's only natural that I would research time travel as man's next great leap.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">*yaaaaawn* Oh! Is he done? So what exactly does all that stuff he was saying mean, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, basically, it's like taking a hamburger joint... and adding a drive-thru to it, I guess?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I get it! It's the same burger, but with a quicker and more efficient delivery system! So what Sorin really wants to do is... ...lunch humanity into the future!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">"Launch," not "lunch." </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But do you really believe that time travel is possible?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">It only becomes truly impossible when man stops daring to believe. Besides... time travelers do exist, you know. But you wouldn't understand. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you hear that, Nick? Time travelers really do exist!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I know is, Sorin isn't the easiest guy to wrap your head around...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I don't know. I kind of like the way he talks. It's full of hope for the future! He's more passionate than I thought, too... When it comes to inventions, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah. His apparent lack of concern for Ellen is troubling, though.</thought> So, I hear that the rest of the Sprocket family was opposed to your marriage. What are your thoughts on that?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...............I...</line>
<line speaker="???">Master Sorin. It is time for the meeting on next term's project. </line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="???">What is this? Daydreaming about your inventions again? Tut, tut. You are the future president. You must consider the business side, too. It is I. I found Sorin. Send the car over at once. </line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......I'm not interested.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, Master Sorin. You do give me quite the headache at times. In any case, your attendant is waiting. Please go to him now.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but who are you?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, where are my manners? My name is Pierce Nichody. Please call me Pierce. I am the Sprocket family butler.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! A butler! I didn't know they actually still existed! I thought they were just on TV and stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">And who might you be, if you don't mind my asking?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm Phoenix Wright, Ellen Wyatt's lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And I'm his assistant, Maya Fey. I'm a spirit medium. </line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh! So it is you. I am most grateful to you for taking on Miss Ellen's defense. You have my sincerest thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">D-Don't mention it. So hey, speaking of the case...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh. One moment, please. ............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! What a beautiful pocket watch!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh, this? It's just a bit of a good luck charm. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's one expensive good luck charm... But I guess it makes sense. Knowing the time is pretty important in his line of work. So I guess that pocket watch is as important to him as my attorney's badge is to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">There is a little time before I must attend to Master Sorin again. Why not come to Sprocket Manor?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? You mean, to Sorin's home?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">As a token of appreciation for taking on Miss Ellen's defense... ...I would like to serve you some delicious tea and refreshments.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, boy, Nick! A fancy high-society tea party! With high-class snacks and everything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what about the investigation?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you kidding? What better place to investigate next than Sorin's house?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know. Do you really think his house is going to give us any new leads?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Of course it will! I say we take the butler up on his kind offer and go to Sorin's place!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, all right. You win.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Very good. To Sprocket Manor, then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! This place does NOT disappoint! Ooh, I'm so excited!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! Slow down, Maya! The mansion isn't going anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Now, then. We won't have to worry about anyone untoward eavesdropping here. I take it you wanted to ask me some questions...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! ...... THAT'S why you invited us here?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I am sorry to have tricked you like this. But this IS a murder, after all. I couldn't talk openly about it in public and risk sullying the Sprocket family's reputation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... And I was REALLY looking forward to all those fancy snacks, too...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There, there, Maya. Don't cry. <thought>Hmm... This Pierce guy is one shrewd man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Look at that cute vintage radio!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Radio...? Oh, that thing under there, under the stuffed bull's head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm gonna take a closer look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought I told you to settle down...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Not to worry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow, that little mech fixed it right up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I am not only the butler, but I'm also Sprocket Aviation's repair department director. One might say that "patching things up" is my specialty. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was incredible! What IS that little doohickey on your shoulder, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="NIchody">It's my "FXR-UPR" shoulder mech. Master Sorin made it for me. It has too many features and functions to effectively enumerate at the moment, though.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's so cool! I wish I had one of those!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Fixing things is a simple matter. But fixing people is a different matter... Even a skilled physician can't bring back the dead. Oh, but forgive me. I seem to have gotten sidetracked. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be in shock over Mr. Gloomsbury's death... Still, I do need to ask him some questions about the case. I should take a look around and see what I can find out while I'm here, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A bull... Come to think of it, there was a bull logo on the side of the Flying Chapel, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The president of the company must have a thing for cattle!</line>
<line speaker="Lady">The bull is the symbol of Sprocket Aviation. "To be as strong and steady as a bull." That's the company creed, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Probably for all the back-breaking labor they put their employees through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lady">By the way, that bull logo on the Flying Chapel -- the one with the rainbow wings? His name is "Rainy the Rainbull." Get it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I get it! He's a rainbow-colored bull, so he's a "Rainbull," right? What a memorable name, huh, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, for the lameness of the pun...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you dare touch that radio again. It looks like an expensive antique.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you worried about? If it breaks again, Pierce will just fix it up again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I really hope he's nice enough to waive the repair bill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look at that airplane propeller up there going round and round!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see they've got an aviation theme going on. Makes sense for an airline family. I wonder if it doubles as a fan.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh! What if the rest of the plane were on the other side of the wall?! And the wall would open up so the plane could take off in an emergency! How cool would that be!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If that's what's behind the propeller wall, then what's behind the bull wall across the way? Oh, I know! Maybe it's the rest of him! That must be where the Sprockets get their milk!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... First of all, that's a beef cow. And second, bulls don't make milk.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh. Right... <thought>That's what I get for trying to play along...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's the bridal bouquet. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Nick, how about I throw it, and you try to catch it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just because. I bet you'd look hilarious flailing around trying to grab it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But doesn't tradition dictate that it's the ladies that go after the bouquet?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Who cares! Just catch it! Here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow! H-Hey! You threw that right at my face!</line>
<line speaker="Lady">Oh, you don't want to catch THAT bouquet. Trust me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Lady">They say it's bad luck to catch the bouquet of a marriage that doesn't last.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But I already caught it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoops. Too late now, huh, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, are those pictures of the wedding reception?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Yes, I took them with my trusty camera here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Um... do you mind if we have a look at that photo?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Be my guest! Take as long of a look as you'd like. Well, what do you think of this gorgeous dreamscape? A thick fog billows across the room, making it look as if the couple were walking on clouds.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... Look at how beautiful Ellen is here! She looks a little nervous, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She does, doesn't she.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, look! There's Pierce!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right there, behind the sweetheart table!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, you're right. I bet he was there attending to the happy couple the whole dinner. </line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, what do you think, Nick? Does anything in this photo stick out at you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, not at the moment, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick? If Ellen really did travel back in time... ...do you think this photo is of the second reception -- you know, after the time jump?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I wonder. Excuse me. Sir?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Yes? Can I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen told us she traveled back in time. Would you happen to know anything about that? </line>
<line speaker="Man">Oh, um... N-No... I-I... I-I haven't the foggiest idea what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">? <thought>He clammed up faster than a clam!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, but there's a card here on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Man">Well, look at that. It's a Flying Chapel key card.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Flying Chapel? What areas on the Flying Chapel require a key card, if I may ask?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Mostly areas we want to keep the public out of... ...such as the staff room and the hold, which is chock full of machinery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you can't enter those areas without a key card?</line>
<line speaker="Man">That's right... Hm? This one here belongs to Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait, what's Ellen's key card doing here?</thought> Did Ellen come back here after the incident occurred?</line>
<line speaker="Man">I don't believe so. And she was arrested by the police straight away this morning. Although... there was a strange man with a gaudy jacket in here earlier. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was that man... wearing a beret, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Man">Yes, he was, as a matter of fact! He was also wearing sunglasses and a fake mustache!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it... The only question is, what was he doing here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Now, here's a real lady!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She looks smart as a whip, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder who she is? We didn't see her on the airship...</line>
<line speaker="Man">That is Selena Sprocket... Sorin's elder sister. Beautiful and capable, she was a great lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's sister... Hmm... I think I see the resemblance. <thought>Maybe I'll show Pierce this photo later and ask him about her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! Now, here's a real lady!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She looks smart as a whip, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder who she is? We didn't see her on the airship...</line>
<line speaker="Man">That is Selena Sprocket... Sorin's elder sister. Beautiful and capable, she was a great lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's sister... Hmm... I think I see the resemblance.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">About the incident Miss Ellen was arrested for... ...do you think she did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I can't prove it yet, but no, I don't think she could've done it. I guess you could call it a gut feeling.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...... I see. I guess we have different opinions, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do we, now?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">The prosecution says that when Gloomsbury attacked Miss Ellen, she fought back... ...and ended up killing him. I agree with this perspective. Or rather, that is the consensus of the entire Sprocket family.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Even so, I heard an interesting story from Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth. I heard that the Sprocket family had tried to pressure the Prosecutor's Office... ...into burying this case.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I fear you are mistaken. All we sought was merely a legal consultation. Besides, none of it matters now, as she is no longer a part of this family. Fortunately for us, they had yet to get their marriage license before holding the banquet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So basically, once they realized they couldn't sway the prosecution, they cut her loose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">......I realize how callous I must sound. But my duty is to protect the Sprocket family, and more specifically... ...Sprocket Aviation's future and Master Sorin, whose genius is essential to the company. I will do anything to achieve that goal. That is my job as the Sprocket family butler.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You know, I think Pierce and Mr. Edgeworth would get along really well. Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I could easily picture Edgeworth with a butler.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh, and by the way... I suppose I should tell you about this as well... It's about when the members of the extended family and I discovered the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, did Ellen say anything to you about traveling through time?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...She must have been delirious. There is no need to take such a claim seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin himself said that time travel was possible, though.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">! ......Master Sorin... said that? ......It sounds like he is still stuck in the past.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He's psychologically stuck, I take it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Excuse me. What is it? ............I see. I believe I told you the madam will be having milk tea. Still, have lemon slices at the ready, just in case. We must not disappoint her, understand?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sure are busy.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">All in a day's work. ...Still, we really do need Master Sorin to start focusing on the business side of things soon.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It was sometime after the reception. Some of the master's relatives and I went to clean up the reception hall... ...and that is when we saw it. A woman standing in front of the victim with the bloody murder weapon in her hand... It was none other than Miss Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Pierce, it wasn't what it looked like!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's right! She just happened to find the body!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I do not know what Miss Ellen has told you, but what we witnessed... ... was unmistakably the moment immediately after the deed had been committed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">And that is what I told the police who came in response to my call.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see... <thought>So Pierce was the one who reported it to the police, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin will become the next president of Sprocket Aviation. However, that wasn't always so. Miss Selena Sprocket, Master Sorin's elder sister, was next in line.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So why isn't she becoming the next president?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">......Because she died... in a car accident.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I had no idea...!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Actually, Master Sorin was also in the car with her at the time of the accident. Losing the sister he loved right before his eyes devastated him. Ever since then, he has buried himself in his research on time machines. He also became a quiet and meticulous -- almost compulsive -- note-taker around then.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He seems so stiff and robotic -- I had no idea he was carrying all that around inside him...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin has abandoned the company business and spends all his time on inventions. As the family butler, I am truly concerned. I believe it is high time he let go of the past.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin made the Time Keeper as a symbol of their love for each other. ...A symbol now tainted with blood. I can only imagine how shocking this must be for Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But surely Sorin believes in the woman he loves.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin has the future of Sprocket Aviation to think about. He cannot afford to let his personal feelings affect his judgment. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-That's awful!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You might think so, but that's the kind of responsibility he must bear.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All because he's in line to be the next president, huh? Sounds like it's not going to be easy to find out how Sorin really feels about anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">This incident has severely damaged the company's reputation. I expect reservations for weddings on the Flying Chapel will face an unfortunate decline.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce, you just lost a subordinate... ...yet, all you can think about is the business?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I am not made of stone, I assure you. But if this company were to go under because of this incident... ...countless employees would lose their jobs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">To be honest, I wish we could have hidden this tragedy from the public... ...but now that it's going to trial, I suppose there is nothing to be done about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the fate of this company depends on this trial... This is more than I bargained for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Gloomsbury... How could he do something so deranged? It is truly a shame. As a servant, he was a cut above the rest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Gloomsbury worked under you, correct? Were there any signs that he was going to do anything like that to Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">No, he gave no indication whatsoever. If only I'd realized what he was up to sooner...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pierce, the woman in this photo is Sorin's older sister Selena, right? I don't think we've met her yet.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes, about that... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He seems... hesitant, all of a sudden.</thought> If you wouldn't mind... ...could you tell us about her?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">A-All right. Very well. She's a big part of Master Sorin's past, after all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorin's... past?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">And what is this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just wondering if there is anything you can tell me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Hmm... I'm afraid not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I see.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Time is money, as they say, so perhaps you should learn to spend it more wisely.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right. <thought>Good advice, but his chilly attitude is giving me some serious goose bumps...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, Nick! What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, man! Edgey gave me a heckuva hard time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, what are YOU doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I came to promote my new character, Cupiglet! I was hoping Sprocket Aviation would do some kind of tie-in with me for it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. I didn't know Larry was such an aggressive businessman. You could learn a thing or two from him, Nick. Why don't you promote your agency to them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now's not exactly the time for that, in case you haven't noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">See? And this is why you'll never be rich!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, Larry, I've been meaning to ask you something. You were on the Flying Chapel yesterday, right?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Was I...? Er...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What were you doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">N-Nothing...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whatever it was, I bet it wasn't anything to be proud of. But never mind that. Did you see anything that had to do with the case? ......Scratch that. Let's start with, you weren't INVOLVED in this case, were you?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">! ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! He took off!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I just knew it... When something smells, it's usually the Butz... Come on, Maya! After him!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Oh, are you leaving so soon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We, uh, have to run... Thank you for making time for us.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I know you have to investigate, but please try to spare the family's feelings as you do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There he is. Hey, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">H-Hey, there, friend! Fancy meeting you here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's nothing "fancy" about it. All we did was follow you. So, tell me, Larry. Why did you run away like that?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? Me? ...I don't know what you're talking about. A bolt of inspiration for my new picture book hit me and I had to run is all. It was, like, a "Cupiphany!" You dig?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Riiiiight...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's just going to keep on playing dumb, isn't he, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Larry. I know you were on that airship, so what did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I-I didn't see anything! I didn't see anything 'cause I was never on that stupid airship!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! Psyche-Locks...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You say something?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The spiritual power of this magatama allows me to see... ...these mystical locks that appear when someone is trying to hide something from me. They're called "Psyche-Locks," and when I see them... ...I simply touch the magatama (X</thought> to try my hand at breaking them. If I can unlock them, I'm sure to finally get a straight answer out of him!)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I found this in the reception hall.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">........... Say, that's a pretty stylish wallet, ain't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you ever seen it before?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">............Nope.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll take that as a "yes"... Which means he must be trying to hide something from me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">I-I don't know anything about that wallet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll just have to take him to task later...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whoooooooa! Who is she? Who is this lovely vision?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... *sigh* This is Sorin's older sister. She died in a car accident.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Nooooooooo! How could such a beautiful flame have been snuffed out like that?! If she were alive today, I bet I could've made her happy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's funny. I thought you were in love with Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Don't get me wrong, Nick. I just wanna make all the pretty ladies of this world happy, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I think you're the one getting it wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hm? Do you really think you can prove Elly's innocence with that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I knew, I wouldn't need to conduct an investigation, now would I? Now, look at the evidence, Larry! Can you tell me anything about it?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hmm.... Hmmmmmmmmmmm... Hmm... Nope. Sorry! Can't think of a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Good thing I had low expectations from the start then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is no time for games, Larry. I WILL find out what you're hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I'm telling ya, Nick, you've got it all wrong. I've got nothing to do with this case, whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, come on, Larry! Even a baby could see through such a blatant and obvious lie.</thought> "Nothing whatsoever," huh? If you weren't involved, Larry, then you wouldn't have been involved with this person.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Huh? What are you trying to say, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oops. Looks like I got it wrong.</thought> J-Just ignore I said that!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Jeez. Get a grip, will ya?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're the one who brought Ellen to my office in the first place. ...And all those cops.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Nothing to do with the case, whatsoever" isn't gonna cut it this time, Larry! If you have to lie, at least do a better job of it!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">U... UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">D-Don't diss me, Nick! If you're so convinced I'm lying, then lemme ask you this! What makes you think I was on that stupid ol' airship, anyway?! Lemme see some proof! If you've got any!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doubling down, are you? Fine. You want proof, Larry? Here's proof that you were on that airship!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">You call that proof? Hmph.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I must've gotten it wrong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Seriously, Nick. You shouldn't doubt your friends like this. It only hurts the both of us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Uh-oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is your business card wallet, isn't it, Larry? I found it in the reception hall.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Gah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Time to come clean, Larry Butz. What exactly are you hiding?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">W-WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! ...... A-All right! Fine! Ya got me! I'll tell you everything!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">All right, I admit it! That super stylish business card wallet is mine! What more do you want outta me?! ...Wait. Don't tell me you were hoping to keep it for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why would I want a card wallet with your face on it?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Aww, don't be shy! Tell you what, Nick. I'll have one sent to your office. I'll even throw in a "good friend discount" on it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd still have to pay?! <thought>Trucy's going to take it out of my hide, too, once she sees that in the expenses book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">What are you showing me that for? Is this an interrogation? Okay, sure, I snuck onto that airship and was wandering around it all by my lonesome. But you gotta believe me! I didn't kill anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And WHY were you sneaking around on that airship in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Because... it was fate...? Yeah, that's it! I was just following my destiny! That's all I've ever done!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh, come on, Larry... Are you seriously going to blame all the trouble you've ever caused on fate?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry, what were you doing on that airship, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, I went there to deliver the "Welcome to Our Wedding" sign they ordered from me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh. I didn't know you took on real jobs like that, too.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, for your information, my wedding welcome signs are very popular on the Net!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's how you met Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Uh-huh. I mean, I'd seen her in the photo for the welcome sign, but seeing her in person... The way she smiled at me and said, "Thank you"... *sigh* I felt like I'd been hit by lightning!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's when you fell in love with somebody else's bride, huh? So, were you invited to the reception?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Can you believe they told me only family and relatives could attend?! They wouldn't even let me into the reception hall!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Smart move on their part, I'd say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">I got upset, and started wandering around the airship. That must be when I dropped my business card wallet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So somebody else must've found it... ...and brought it to the reception hall, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">But you know what? I saw something incredible while I was on that Flying Chapel!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Like...?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Get a load of this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What the heck is this?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Whaddaya mean, "what is this"? Isn't it obvious? It's a drawing! I sketched a picture of one of the cabins on the airship.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So what's so incredible about a cabin?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Look at what was outside the window! It's one of those flying dinosaurs -- a real live pterodactyl! I looked out the cabin window and there it was, just flying out there! That airship traveled through time, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Wh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">When I told that Pierce butler guy about it... ...he told me to never mention it to anybody ever again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would he try to keep you from spouting what is clearly just nonsense?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Maybe Sprocket Aviation is secretly developing a time machine!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...... N-No way...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick, this case is... ...totally amazing! Larry! You didn't tell Mr. Edgeworth about this, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Of course not! Edgey would just roll his eyes and think I was off my rocker. I didn't even tell him I was wandering around on the airship. I told him I met Elly at the mooring dock and we ran away together.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... I can see Edgeworth's eyes rolling right out of his head had he heard about this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So Larry also experienced the time slip somehow... But how is that possible...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey, Nick. I'll be taking my card wallet back now, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, yeah. This is for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">It's a picture of the hold. I took it when I was wandering around on the airship. See? There's Elly right there in the middle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, the hold?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Yeah, see? It's right here on the diagram.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay. So now I know where the hold is. But what was Ellen doing there?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Well, they were using it as a prepping area for the reception.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. And around when did you take this?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Before the reception. I took it while Elly was getting everything ready.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So this was taken before the incident occurred... I don't know if it'll be of any help, but thanks for this anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By the way, Larry. I heard that the door to the hold is controlled by a security system. So how'd you get in there?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Th-That's...! A trade secret! Can't tell ya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And the hits just keep on coming...</thought> Well, I guess that's basically a wrap on the investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not quite, Nick! I want to meet Ellen, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that's right. You haven't met her yet, have you? Okay. Let's head over to the detention center, so you can say hi.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Hey! That's the drawing I made. You'd better take care of it. I bet it's gonna be valuable some day! Oh, do you want me to add a character or something to it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ooh, could you? I'd love to see a true artist at work!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn> As farcical as this drawing is, there will be no doodling on the evidence until the trial is over.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Wh-Whaddaya mean, "farcical"?! I'm never gonna draw anything for you ever again! Not even if you beg me!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aww... Guess that's that, huh, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Need I remind you that it's still a piece of evidence, Maya...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The internal affairs of a powerful and wealthy family... I get the feeling this is going to get messy. What are your thoughts, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Prestigious families like this tend to try and protect their reputation, don't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. That's the thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But at least YOU don't have much of a reputation to protect. That means you can do anything you want to win this case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who says I don't have a reputation to protect?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I still can't help but wonder... You know this time travel thing Ellen keeps talking about... Do you think it really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, I believe it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You do?! Based on what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, it's not really based on anything, exactly... It's just that it's so much more fun to believe that it really happened! As soon as this case is over, I'm going to go talk with Sorin Sprocket myself. I'm going to ask him to send me back to medieval times!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I guess it's nice to have a dream... <thought>Just please don't let the fantasy of time travel turn real in this case...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry's a really good artist, isn't he? No wonder he's a famous picture book author!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, he's really good at something all right. Namely, at causing trouble wherever he goes.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But he's also helped you out of a bind or two before, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess so... <thought>But that's not usually until after he's made a mess of things first...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No! Why?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Please understand that this is in Master Sorin's best interest.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like Ellen's busy talking with someone...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">The next president cannot be married to a criminal. It would disgrace Sprocket Aviation. Miss Ellen, I need you to forget about this marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Pardon us...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">! ...If it isn't Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... their marriage is definitely off?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">There is no other choice. We cannot have a criminal in the family. For the sake of Master Sorin and the Sprocket family, this is what is best.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">*sniffle* Nooooo...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Um... in that case... ...what if Nick here proved Ellen's innocence? Then you wouldn't have a criminal in the family, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">! ..... I-I suppose you are right, but I am afraid that will be impossible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's not true! Not for Nick. He may look like a nobody, but he can do some pretty amazing things!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I don't take cases on lightly, so rest assured, I will prove her innocence.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Mr. Phoenix Wright... I understand your name is quite well-known in the judicial world... For better or for worse.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Pierce, I want you to promise me this: If I can prove Ellen's innocence... ...then you won't stand in the way of Sorin and Ellen's marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">......Hmph. Very well. But not even the most talented lawyer in the world can change reality itself. And the reality is, Miss Ellen is guilty beyond a shadow of a doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe that's where you're wrong, Pierce.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I'm clean! I swear I am! Obsessively, compulsively, clean! Just as clean and pure as this pure-white dress!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Fine. You have my word. But you will be the one to regret this promise. ......Now, if you will excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Now I have all the more reason to win this case.</thought> Ellen, we finished our investigation, and we'd like to talk with you about what we found.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Okay! So what did you find out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In the course of our investigation, we heard that... ...you had been standing in front of the victim with the murder weapon in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">! I-It wasn't what it looked like! It's true I was holding the murder weapon... ...but when I found him, he was already dead. I-I panicked... ...and I was hoping I could go back in time again, like I had done earlier. So I picked up the Time Keeper from the pedestal and brought it over without thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were so desperate, you were ready to try anything, huh... Unfortunately, that sort of behavior makes you an easy target for the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And as for your little trip through time... ...none of your in-laws could confirm your story, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The only exception is Larry. He said he saw something.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Really? Wh-What did he see?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Ooooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What's wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I just remembered our reception... We were supposed to be so happy together! Oh, where did it all go wrong...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I can't blame her for being upset.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Why did this have to happen to me? UWAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ellen! Please try to calm down! Okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">A-All right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, she stopped crying, but... ...how can I ask her about anything when she's still so clearly distraught?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I-I... don't feel very well...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! That photo is a bit much for most normal people, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah, I guess you're right. <thought>Oops, that was pretty inconsiderate of me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen, can you tell if this is Mr. Gloomsbury's handwriting?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">No. I'm sorry. I'm not very familiar with his handwriting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see... <thought>And unless the handwriting is very distinct, I know it's often hard to tell.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I-I'm sorry, but I'm not very comfortable with looking at a note which details... ...a plan on how to murder me written on it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, sorry... I guess that should go without saying...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">*sniffle* Oh, poor Selena... I feel so sad about what happened to her...! SELENAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yikes! Ellen, please try to calm down! Pretty please? With sugar on top?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Sorin and I were supposed to be happy -- for Selena's sake, too. WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We... should probably leave this topic alone, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can't say I quite believe it myself, but Larry claims he saw something incredible. He claims he saw a pterodactyl flying outside the airship.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Wh... WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not only that, but apparently Pierce Nichody told Larry to keep quiet about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">But why would Pierce do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry's theory is that Sprocket Aviation is developing something in secret. A time machine, to be exact.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Do you think... Do you think that's why nobody would confirm my story? Because it's a secret?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I really don't know. But speaking of your in-laws... ...we did manage to find your key card at Sprocket Manor. One of your in-laws said he'd keep an eye on it for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oh, thank goodness! I lost it while I was getting things ready for the reception. I'd looked everywhere for it! I'm so glad you found iiiiiit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A-At least they're tears of joy this time, for a change...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, Nick... It looks like you'll have to prove the existence of time travel in court tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">That's right! I swear that while Mr. Gloomsbury was being killed... ...I was busy traveling back through time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Great. With stodgy, skeptic Edgeworth at the helm for the prosecution tomorrow... ...we're really gonna have our work cut out for us. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I think I'd better take a step back and gather my thoughts a little more...</thought></line>
</xml>