<xml>
<title>Turnabout Time Traveler</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the one thing we found out yesterday is that Sorin was there at the crime scene. I only hope I can get some testimony from him that'll get to the heart of the matter...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning, Ellen. Look, I'm afraid you might not like the result of today's trial... Nevertheless...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">D-Don't tell me you're still thinking of going that route?! Sorin is innocent! He can't be found guilty! Take me instead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ellen, please! Try and get a hold of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I believe in Sorin with all my heart! So how dare you doubt him?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Regardless of which one of them is found guilty today... ...it's going to be devastating for Ellen, isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We'll just have to do everything we can. That's the best we can do, you know...?</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to begin, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. Let's go, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is back in session for the trial of Ellen Wyatt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The prosecution is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see, now. Where were we?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In yesterday's session, we found out about the Sprocket family's conspiracy... ...to cover up the murder of Dumas Gloomsbury with a second reception. Taking advantage of our collective shock, the defense, as usual, made a nonsensical claim. Namely, that there was a third person present who struck the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then I presume the defense intends to focus on proving the identity of this "third person"... Is that all right with you, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed, Your Honor. In fact, I predict that the defense will, most likely... ...attempt to name Mr. Sorin Sprocket as the true culprit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How did you...?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The driver during the accident that killed Mr. Sprocket's sister... was the victim. Therefore, Mr. Sprocket had a motive to murder Mr. Gloomsbury. That's what you planned to assert, is it not, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...! <thought>Am I that transparent?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Come now, Mr. Wright. Did you really think the police wouldn't uncover this information?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Congrats on getting it in one, Mr. Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="???">???:</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">You're wrong! Sorin didn't do it! He's innocent! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Wyatt! Please!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">HE'S INNOCENT, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is this, Mr. Wright? I thought your claim about the existence of a third person came from the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It did... This is just... a minor hiccup...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Did you not discuss your strategy for today with the defendant, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Starting off on the wrong foot again is seriously cutting into my life span...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It would appear that the defense is in disarray. Therefore, the best way to clear things up is to ask Mr. Sprocket himself what happened. Your Honor, the prosecution would like to call Sorin Sprocket to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Bailiff, please bring Mr. Sprocket to the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ </line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Ow! Hmm... There's something written on this paper airplane... Let's see... "Sorin Sprocket, managing director of Sprocket Aviation." Mr. Sprocket, please give your answers in words, not paper airplanes.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, then, Mr. Sprocket. Please tell that doubting lawyer there what really happened at the time of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Sprocket?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......All right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Grrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">You want me to talk about what happened when the crime occurred...? In other words... after the first wedding reception... ...when Ellen and I were in the reception hall, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not even the power of the court can stop him from marching to the beat of his own drum...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I was stabbed by Dumas in the reception hall, and I collapsed to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Wait just a minute here! You actually think Ms. Wyatt killed the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...That's right... Dumas was killed... by Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-This is unbelievable! How can you suspect your bride -- the woman you love?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">...No... I can't believe this... Sorin... I thought that at least you... would believe in me...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The best way now to show your love for your groom is to admit your guilt and try to atone.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Sorin...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah! That's so not cool, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. A court is where we seek the truth. And the truth is unyielding, even to the truly pitiful.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth. I find it distasteful to make a lady cry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nnngrrrrk...! Et tu, Your Honor...?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...So what are you going to do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the third person Ellen saw on the vista deck was Sorin... ...then we have to prove Sorin was there at the time of the murder. I don't see any obvious inconsistencies in his testimony, but we have to push forward!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I was stabbed by Dumas in the reception hall, and I collapsed to the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">After the reception, Ellen and I were enjoying a moment alone in the reception hall. Then Dumas appeared and stabbed me... He grabbed Ellen and the Time Keeper, and left the reception hall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did Mr. Gloomsbury say anything at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...I don't remember. After I was stabbed, I was immobilized by the pain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The next thing I saw was Ellen and Dumas on the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...The moon was out, so I could see them clearly. From the looks of it, Dumas was trying to push Ellen and the Time Keeper off the side.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you saw the defendant... ...about to be thrown off the airship, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In such a desperate situation, it would only be natural for her to fight for her life. And the murder weapon was right there within her grasp.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. This isn't going well at all... I've got to do something, fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I knew Ellen was in danger, so I headed for the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...I was desperately trying to push the pain out of my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. So adrenaline kicked in, and gave you strength, is that right? <thought>I don't see much of anything in this statement I can refute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">That's right. I almost passed out several times as I made my way to the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">But when I got there, Dumas was already...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the vista deck is just on the other side of the glass windows in the reception hall. Shouldn't you have been able to get there right away?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh...! <thought>Well, that's unhelpful... But Sorin had to have gotten there before the murder, or my claim won't stand!</thought> Do you have any ideas for me, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... It's definitely easier to prove that someone did go to the hold than not... I mean, you can't leave anything if you don't go someplace, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Can't leave anything"...? Wait a minute. I think Maya is onto something here! The lack of a certain something actually proves that Sorin didn't go to the hold!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the matter? Are you stumped already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No. I'm far from "stumped", Mr. Edgeworth. I know for a fact that Mr. Sprocket didn't go to the hold!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. You and your paper-thin bluffs! Mr. Sprocket's bloodstain on the lift proves he went through the hold! So what possible proof could you have that he did not, in fact, go through there?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You want proof, you got it! <thought>You can do this, Phoenix! There's gotta be proof that Sorin didn't go through the hold!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This proves that Mr. Sprocket didn't go through the hold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">............?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... So, maybe this isn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Maybe not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Definitely not.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Definitely not, it is...! <thought>Argh...! Come on, Phoenix! Get a hold of yourself and try again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I don't want to believe it, but it must've been Ellen. Nothing else makes sense...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...How should I know? That's just a theory you came up with yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright, you're trying to force the witness into the role of your "third person"... But isn't it possible that the defendant is lying, or that she simply misremembered?! Exactly how trustworthy do you think her memory is?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No matter how much I believe in Ellen... ...her words won't do us any good in court without proof...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">What makes you think I'm this "third person," anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, can you show proof that the witness was your theoretical "third person"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can! <thought>And I would...! If only I knew what that proof was...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Then let's see this proof of yours... ...that Mr. Sprocket is the mystery person Ms. Wyatt said she saw.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence proves that Mr. Sprocket was the third person Ms. Wyatt saw.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... I guess you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! Stop fooling around!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I can't quite prove who the third person is at this point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? Oh, n-not that! Please ignore that! Forget it ever happened!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick. Stop fooling around...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can do better. Just give me another chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at the moment, Your Honor, no.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I suggest you refrain from performing random guesswork in this courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnrgh... <thought>But the possibility that it was Sorin still exists! I just have to approach it from a different angle.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was some pretty damning testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Saying that Ellen must've done it -- I don't believe that for a second!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe it either. Let's hope this cross-examination gives us some insight into what actually happened. But first, we'll have to find something to latch onto in his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As anyone can see from the hold entry record... ...there's absolutely no mention of Sorin Sprocket entering the hold!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense asserts that Mr. Sprocket used a different route to get to the vista deck!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can assert all you want, Mr. Wright... ...but can you actually prove another route exists?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can I prove the existence of another route to the vista deck, you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I... <thought>Now that I really think about it, I guess it's going to be hard to prove... But I can't back down now. The trial will be over if I do! There's only one thing I can do at a time like this...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can prove it! <thought>Even if it's just a bluff, I have to present something... Anything that could prove the existence of a faster route to the vista deck!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then, Mr. Wright. Show us how Mr. Sprocket got to the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket made for the vista deck through here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... What if he just kinda wiggled his way through here...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid that's physically impossible, defense. Now, stop trying to wiggle your way out of a reasonable explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, Your Honor. Please let me try again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To save his bride from danger, Mr. Sprocket... ...opened the escape hatch and made his way along the outside wall to the vista deck! Isn't that right, Mr. Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That would certainly be a much faster route to the vista deck...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to agree. The defense's claim is really stretching it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So that's what you're going with then, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This is real life, Mr. Wright. Not some cinematic drivel or comic book! Do you have some sort of logical explanation to share that would convince us of your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... I do.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Are you sure, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... kind of? <thought>Actually, I have nothing... So I'll just have to wing it somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">On what do you base your theory that Mr. Sprocket made his way along the outside?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My theory that he was able to go along the outside wall despite the danger is based on...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...the power of authority. A man of Mr. Sprocket's considerable authority could easily move along that wall! I bet his men had ropes and cushions at the ready in case he fell!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, um... They'd pop up at the snap of Mr. Sprocket's fingers...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I have no idea what you're trying to say, Mr. Wright. Were Mr. Sprocket a man of such great power and influence... ...why would he voluntarily put himself in harm's way?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... a very good question, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A question you should have asked yourself from the start, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Men who appear at the snap of your fingers?! The judge might not appreciate it, but I do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thanks, Maya... <thought>I guess she's trying to cheer me up... Okay! I have to get it right this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...the power of money. Mr. Sprocket used the clout of currency to move along that wall! After all, you can make anything in this world move with money! Mr. Sprocket's a rich man, so he simply threw his money around to make it happen!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was... kind of a bogus thing to say, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I sense you have something against the wealthy.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Truly, a remark that reflects the meager state of your soul, and your piggy bank.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't think money could've helped Mr. Sprocket in this situation. What's more, I suggest you work on enriching your own spirit, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngaaah... <thought>Well, I still stand by what I said!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To save the bride he loves, the groom risked his life and rushed to her side. Mr. Sprocket was able to make it to the vista deck despite the danger... ...because of the power of love!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The power of love? ............ Hmm... That love is a source of strength that can help one overcome any obstacle... I think I can relate, thanks to my own long, happy marriage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wow. He actually seems to be buying it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid not, Mr. Edgeworth. You should never underestimate the power of love. You'll understand one day when you get marri--</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Which I won't!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Exactly what is so wrong with wishing to remain unwed?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Way to set him off, Your Honor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Never mind all this unscientific nonsense! Are you aware, Mr. Wright, that at the time of the crime... ...there was a huge propeller turning at full speed between the hatch and the vista deck?! Even if a person were to go outside through the hatch... ...they'd be blown away in an instant!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAUGH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Where does your "power of love" get you now, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A huge spinning propeller, you say? Hmm... In that case, I have to admit it does seem impossible...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh! <thought>I should've known...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Nick, you can't make that kind of face in front of your client! The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles! Right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Right! <thought>I feel like I just saw Mia looking out at me through Maya's eyes!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What's wrong, Nick? Why are you gaping at me like a giant sunfish?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Maya! You just helped me remember something really important!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There it is! There's that fearless smile I was looking for! Now give us a mind-blowing theory, just like you always do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to turn my thinking around! Instead of wondering how Sorin could've moved past that huge propeller... ...I have to think about what would've made it possible for him to do so!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Mr. Wright only makes that ridiculous face when his back is pressed against the wall. Therefore, please do hurry and give your ruling before --</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you talking about? The airship's large spinning propellers have already shredded it to pieces!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But if we think a little more outside the box... ...I'm sure we can find a way he could've made it!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Stop trying to stall, Mr. Wright! And show us how it could've been even remotely possible -- if at all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must agree with Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">V-Very well, Your Honor. <thought>There must've been a way! Some way that Sorin could've moved along the wall in spite of the propeller!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Mr. Wright. What specifically would've made it possible?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is how it would've been possible for Mr. Sprocket to get to the vista deck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Instead of going along the outside wall, the witness got to the vista deck some other way! That's why the propeller is irrelevant to this case!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Really, now, Mr. Wright. Because as I recall, you were the one who was arguing... ...that Mr. Sprocket made his way to the vista deck by moving along the outside wall. Why, then, are you now suggesting that he got to the vista deck some other way?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. This new argument is a complete about-face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... Yes, well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What we want to know is, what would make it possible to move along the outside wall? So please refrain from changing horses midstream, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor... <thought>I'd better think this through a little better...</thought> Please let me try again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I propose that the propellers were broken... ...and, therefore, weren't turning at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That does make the theory sound plausible, yes. What do you think, Mr. Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I haven't heard any report that the propellers were broken at the time. Besides, if the propellers had broken during the flight... ...the airship would've been careening out of control, would it not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would certainly put a stop to the wedding festivities, wouldn't it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I suppose that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright, you will refrain from spouting such groundless claptrap ever again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well said, Mr. Edgeworth. And Mr. Wright, here's a penalty to help you remember.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If only the propellers were stopped for some reason... ...it would've made it possible for Sorin to get to the vista deck...</thought> Your Honor, please let me start over!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What allowed Mr. Sprocket to go along the outside wall in spite of the propellers... ...is the location of the Flying Chapel at the time of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The location of the Flying Chapel...? But wasn't it flying high in the sky?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor, I'm afraid it wasn't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAT?! Th-Then where was it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time of the murder, the airship wasn't flying through the sky... But moored to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if the airship wasn't flying, then that means... ...the propellers weren't turning!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In which case... ...Mr. Sprocket could have gotten to the vista deck along the outside wall! Isn't that right, Mr. Sprocket?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Urk! ......I-I don't remember!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ow... He stabbed himself with his pencil. That's gonna leave a mark.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, but, Mr. Edgeworth, you're forgetting about the power of love.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, the amazing power of love...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Not this again...! V-Very well. For the sake of argument, let's assume this so-called "power of love"... ...made it possible for Mr. Sprocket to move along the outside wall of the airship. Can you prove that the airship was tied to the ground as you claim, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well, I... <thought>I don't have any evidence that proves where the airship was at the time...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can prove it, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urgh...! Maya... Can you think of anything we can use to prove it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Can't say I can... Oh, wait! Didn't somebody see something outside a window at the time of the crime...? I think I remember someone saying as much...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Do I have a piece of evidence that shows what was outside the airship?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, what are you waiting for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence shows what was outside the airship at the time of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, I'm impressed by your acuity, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean by that, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What I mean is, I can't see how that evidence shows what was outside the airship at all. Please present evidence that even us less perceptive individuals can understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no need for such sarcasm, Your Honor... Well, I'll just have to do better this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This piece of evidence shows what was outside the airship at the time of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What kind of lousy drawing is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a drawing made by Larry Butz!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. And what can you prove with that poor attempt at artistry?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry made this drawing before he switched the lanterns. So it must've been right around when the murder was being committed. Now, if I could direct the court's attention here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Is that a pterodactyl?! Does that mean... that the airship actually went back in time to the Cretaceous Period...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We did, and I have no intention of bringing up that argument again. But this drawing shows us an important piece of information. It shows us that the airship was actually moored on the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...And what makes you so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's easy. All you have to do is consider who made this drawing.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Larry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. It was Mr. Butz. And we both know what he's like. He must've seen something else and mistaken it for a pterodactyl.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I... I can't argue with you there.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Larry:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Niiiick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Some friends you guys are! What about the judge? You believe me, r-right, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, but I'm afraid you need to leave this courtroom. Bailiff, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Come on, buddy, let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Why doesn't anybody believe meeeeeeeee?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Don't take it personally, Larry... I know you're just being... well, you...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! Now, then... So you're saying that what Mr. Butz really saw... ...bears some relation to what was outside the airship at the time of the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor! <thought>At least, I think it does...</thought> What this pterodactyl really is will prove the airship was anchored at the mooring dock! <thought>It had better, anyway. If it doesn't, my whole argument is a bust!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're that confident about it, then please go ahead and tell us what it really was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Think, Phoenix! What could that pterodactyl have actually been?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. Don't you see it, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, quite frankly, I don't.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Nick. I'm afraid I don't see it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's unanimous, then. None of us understand what it is you're driving at, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In that case, I assume we're all in agreement regarding the penalty for such a blunder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, everyone... <thought>I'd better take a really good look before I answer again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a good look at this sign!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">At the sign? Hmm... It appears to have been broken, and then repaired. But what does this sign have to do with the pterodactyl?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please focus on this part of the sign.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The part that broke off and got reattached? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about if we turn it like this?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! Th-That shape! It's the pterodactyl in the drawing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What Mr. Butz actually saw was this chunk as it was being blown through the air by wind!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the murder, there were some heavy winds in the area of the mooring dock. But it's hard to imagine that this sign would make it up as high as an airship would fly. That means, the Flying Chapel must've been anchored at the mooring dock that night! Isn't that right... Mr. Sprocket?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Nngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phenix">Wh-What do you mean "too much conjecture"?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Even if the airship wasn't flying, that alone doesn't prove the witness went along the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">True... Even now, it's no more than a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then how do YOU propose Mr. Sprocket got to the vista deck, Mr. Edgeworth?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I noticed something as I went over the evidence. Please take a look at this hold entry record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about it? I don't see Mr. Sprocket listed on here anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't you remember? In yesterday's session, we had a very similar kind of argument.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did we...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Honestly, Mr. Wright. Are you going senile already? We talked about Larry Butz using the defendant's key card to enter the hold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... We did talk about that, didn't we...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">In other words, even if a person's name isn't on the entry record... ...it's still possible for that person to have entered by using someone else's card!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A-AAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sprocket. You entered the hold with Mr. Nichody, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">.......... ............I did.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Why didn't you tell us that in the first place?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">P-Pierce is indispensable. I didn't want to mention him unnecessarily, and risk having him wrongly accused. ...I couldn't do without him.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Sprocket, I ask that you testify in greater detail about your movements that night.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The truth is, I went to the vista deck with Pierce.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, this doesn't help me one bit...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Sprocket, you've concealed information from us time and time again. Who do you think you are, treating this court of law with such irreverence?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...That being said, I do appreciate the testimony you gave just now.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Thanks to you, we now know why your name doesn't appear on the entry record. Now there are no more inconsistencies in the witness's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's Mr. Edgeworth for you! He never leaves a loose end dangling! You okay, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wouldn't exactly call this situation "okay"... Somehow I'll have to coax the information we need for an opening out of him. <thought>If I even can, that is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The truth is, I went to the vista deck with Pierce.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I just didn't want the police to take up his time with all their questions, that's all. Neither the company nor the household would function smoothly without him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see. <thought>Wow. It sounds like Pierce is absolutely indispensible [sic] to the Sprockets.</thought> Anyway, getting back to your statement... When did you meet up with Mr. Nichody?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">We met up on my way to the vista deck. I think Pierce and some of my relatives were on another floor... But Pierce heard the commotion, and came running to my aide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He could hear the pandemonium all the way from another floor...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like the current statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Pierce heard the commotion, and he came running."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Pierce heard the commotion, and he came running.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...I believe some of his subordinates were with him, but... ...I don't remember exactly how many.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He may say there were others, but seeing how they pulled that "second reception" off... ...I can't completely trust anything he has to say, either...</thought> I see. So you, Mr. Nichody, and a few others headed to the vista deck, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">That's why my name doesn't appear on the hold entry record.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So I guess the hold entry record doesn't matter as much as we thought. But now that Sorin's saying he was with Pierce and a few others... ...it's pretty tough to refute that statement.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What's the matter, Mr. Wright? Cat got your tongue? Did you finally realize there's no point in continuing this trial any longer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Of course not! <thought>Grr... I'll wipe that smug look off your face!</thought> Mr. Sprocket, please continue with your testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I was badly injured from being stabbed, but I was frantic.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The knife wound is deep, and continues to throb with pain. Fortunately, my internal organs were spared... ...but one wrong move would've spelled the end for me there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Even so, I've seen you up and about all over the place since the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I'm only following my doctor's orders to perform some daily light exercises.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Would you like Mr. Sprocket's statement about his condition added to his testimony? ...Not that it appears especially relevant to me...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Should I have him add it to his testimony...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. I'd like to have it added to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's all right, Your Honor. I think we should leave it out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The knife wound is quite deep, and continues to throb with pain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Luckily, it missed my internal organs. Otherwise, I wouldn't be alive right now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">According to his doctor, his injury will take about three weeks to heal. There's no way someone with that kind of injury could have gone along the outside wall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngh... B-But he might've been able to with the burst of adrenaline brought on by the pain!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Adrenaline, adrenaline. Is that your answer for everything? In a court of law, the only thing that matters is evidence -- not rampant speculation!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At least admit it's scientific rampant speculation...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......May I continue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">By the time we reached the scene, it was all over.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Yes, that's right. Ellen must've killed him. There's no other explanation...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess whether Pierce was with Sorin or not doesn't change the outcome...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not... In fact, more witnesses actually makes it worse for us...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So another cover-up, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That Sorin has too many secrets! I bet he's still hiding other things, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's definitely a possibility. But in a situation like this, what we have to do is go back to the basics.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean go over the testimony and check for any lies or inconsistencies?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right, Nick. Let's go for it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket, you just said your injury is a knife wound, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the weapon you were stabbed with was this candelabra! A fact I know you're quite aware of.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Very well. This is what I heard directly from Master Sorin himself. As you surmised, Master Sorin was stabbed by Gloomsbury on the day of the murder. It happened after the first wedding reception. The happy couple was in the reception hall when, suddenly, Gloomsbury appeared... He attacked Miss Ellen and tried to take her away. Master Sorin went to stop him, and found himself in a struggle with Gloomsbury. That is when Master Sorin was stabbed with the candelabra, he said.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Unnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Grr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to agree, Mr. Wright. You hardly need to make such a big deal over such a small mistake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I contend that it's an important inconsistency! <thought>Besides, I couldn't find anything else. This is the only thing I have to go after!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And I say it's NOT important. Now, let's not waste any more time on this matter.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. Everybody has a little memory lapse every now and then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But can you? Can you really explain to this court what makes this slip so important?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I can, Your Honor! <thought>After all, it was Sorin himself who told Pierce that he had been stabbed by a candelabra. This is more than a simple "memory slip." There has to be some kind of reason for it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Well, Mr. Wright? Please explain why the witness's slip of the tongue is so important.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The point to focus on here is WHY the witness would mistake the weapon used to stab him. <thought>Think carefully, Phoenix. This could very well change the course of the trial.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So why did the witness make that mistake, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket identified the wrong weapon used against him because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... he simply misspoke!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Exactly. That's what I've been saying all along. It doesn't matter in the least that he named the wrong weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ack! Wait! I-I didn't mean to say he misspoke!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like you're the one who misspoke, Mr. Wright. And make no mistake, this penalty is quite intentional.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What happened to letting small slips-of-the-tongue slide...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Sprocket is trying to cover for someone!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He is? Hmm... And who might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, well... Mr. Gloomsbury, maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Exactly, Mr. Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah... Sorry, Nick, but I have to agree...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... I guess that makes sense...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Too bad there's no one to cover for you, Mr. Wright. You'll have to accept this penalty all by your lonesome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wouldn't mind having someone to cover for me every once in a while... Oh, well. I can't lose heart now! I've gotta just keep on trying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...he doesn't remember the incident, let alone the weapon used against him! Not only that... ...but I believe Mr. Sprocket has some sort of memory disorder! Therefore, the defense contends that Mr. Sprocket's testimony thus far is invalid!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Edgeworth is correct, Mr. Wright. Can you explain your grounds for making this claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Of course, Your Honor. <thought>Think of what Sorin has said, how he's behaved. That's where I'll find a clue...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's hear your argument, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My grounds for claiming that Mr. Sprocket has a memory disorder is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... his taciturn personality! He may seem standoffish, but in reality... ...he's desperately trying to memorize everything that's happening!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Those grounds are nowhere near sufficient to make such a claim, Mr. Wright. Perhaps you should take a cue from the witness, and speak less frequently instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to come up with a more convincing argument...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...that airplane pen he always uses. The truth is it's an external memory device!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It's a what?! What makes you say that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I mean, it transforms into an airplane and stuff... ...so I thought it wouldn't be a stretch for an inventor like him to make a memory bank.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That theory is simply amazing... Amazingly sloppy! I suggest you invent yourself some better ideas, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I guess the idea of an external memory device is pretty half-baked. <thought>I'd better think it over again... And this time, I'll put a little more thought into it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...the notebook he always has with him. I saw daily events and information about the people around him recorded in it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Like a diary, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Your Honor. It's much too detailed to be an ordinary diary. It's more on the order of a database, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A database, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. For some reason, Mr. Sprocket is apparently unable to retain memories. That's why he writes every little detail of his life down in his notebook!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I thought so, too, myself... at first. To be honest, we accidentally got a stain on that notebook yesterday...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean, YOU got a stain on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! YOU'RE the one who tried to grab it out of my--!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-Right... Sorry... Mr. Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The page Ms. Fey got a stain on yesterday... That's the page with the details of your stabbing on it, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">N-No! I only write in this notebook because I'm very compulsive! Now, drop the subject already!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I'm not convinced. I noticed an odd fact about your notebook, Mr. Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the earlier pages, you used it to write down invention ideas. But after a certain date, you started writing down a lot more, and in much more detail.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe your memory disorder... ...stems from what happened on that date!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Something so monumental, it caused a memory disorder, Mr. Wright...?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...You don't know what you're talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry, but I DO know what I'm talking about... And this is the proof. This is the thing that caused Mr. Sprocket's memory disorder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...That? And how would something like that affect a person's memory?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... what if one were to knock their head against it a few times...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And would you care to demonstrate that theory for us personally?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, thanks, Your Honor. I think I'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, I hope this knocks some sense into you instead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better take another good look at the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You were involved in this car accident, too, weren't you, Mr. Sprocket? And the shock of losing your beloved older sister... ...is what caused you to develop your memory disorder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Is this true, Mr. Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well? Is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ N-Nnrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Uuughhh...... I-It's true. That accident did something to my mind...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Ever since that day, every time I go to sleep, I lose my memories... And when I wake up, the most recent thing I can remember is the day I lost my sister. It's as if I'm constantly going back in time.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What...?! Th-That's... truly tragic...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">An inconsolable time traveler who goes back in time whenever he goes to sleep...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Besides... time travelers do exist, you know. But you wouldn't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So that's what Sorin meant... He was talking about himself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The reactions of the people around me each time I awoke made me aware of my condition. That's why I decided to write everything down in my notebook... So I could move forward.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So the only memories you have since that day are the ones written in that notebook?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And since the page about your stabbing got stained, you couldn't read from it, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's just one more thing I'd like you to clarify for me, Mr. Sprocket. Exactly what are your feelings toward the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Sprocket's feelings toward Dumas Gloomsbury?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Your Honor. The witness said that every time he wakes up from sleep... ...his mind goes back to the day his sister died.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...M-Mr. Wright! Y-You can't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your pent-up feelings of anger and resentment towards Mr. Gloomsbury for the accident... ...were renewed each and every time you woke, were they not?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............Ngh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you couldn't take it anymore, so you turned to murder! Isn't that right?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?! Mr. Wright, are you saying that the witness murdered Mr. Gloomsbury... ...for revenge?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Urgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...........I-I...</line>
<line speaker="???">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">............ Y-Your Honor... I did it... I killed Mr. Gloomsbury!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">NO--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Wyatt! What are you trying to do?!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">D-Don't tell me you're still thinking of going that route?! Sorin is innocent! He can't be found guilty! Take me instead!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-Ellen, please! Try and get a hold of yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess she really meant it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ellen">My Sorin didn't do anything wrong! I'm the one who should be convicted! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are we to understand that you're confessing your guilt?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, no, NO!</thought> Now, wait just a minute here--</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Sorin:</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I'll admit... I couldn't believe my ears at first... But... all I want is for you to be happy. Your happiness... is my happiness, Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">But without my notebook... ...I'd even forget those feelings of yours by tomorrow. Knowing that, do you still feel this way?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">You've loved me all this time... ...the same way you did before the accident. That's how I know... ...that you're the same person I've always loved. No disorder can change that!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">......Ellen... ......Your Honor, there are two things I'd like to correct.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Two corrections? What are they?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">First of all, I want to withdraw one of my statements. </line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...That's right... Dumas was killed... by Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Without memories to rely on... ...I took the police completely at their word.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can't be serious...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So that means... ...Sorin never really doubted Ellen in the first place, did he, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ellen really does love Sorin with all her heart... But, in order to save her... ...I'll still have to go after Sorin. I hope you can forgive me, Ellen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what is your other correction, Mr. Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............ The truth is, I never felt anger or resentment towards Dumas about my sister.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">That's because...... the one who caused the car accident... ...was me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Please continue, Mr. Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I'm the one who killed my sister... To protect my career and my future, my father made Dumas take the blame... ...in exchange for money and the position of lead servant.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">So you see, Dumas must've held a grudge against me, not the other way around. And he must've attacked Ellen... to get his revenge on me...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Are you sure about all of this, Mr. Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Very sure. It's all been written down in detail in my notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That notebook is important evidence supplying background to this case. I must insist you submit it as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The lawyer said I had "turned to murder," but that's just not true. However, it is true that... ...my older sister and Dumas are both dead because of me and my negligence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I just glanced through Mr. Sprocket's notebook. I wasn't able to read the part about when he was stabbed due to the bloodstain... ...but what's written here about his sister's car accident is exactly as he stated.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. As long as it matches what's written in that notebook... ...can we still take the witness's testimony as valid, in spite of his memory disorder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes, I believe we can.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I understand now that the witness's memory is in disarray. But if what Mr. Sprocket himself wrote in this notebook is true...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then that means, by the time Mr. Sprocket's party reached the scene... ...the victim had already been killed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth's right. I'm still in the same bind as before... But should I really simply accept the contents of the notebook... ...as a substitute for Sorin's memory?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? What do you think? Will you accept Mr. Sprocket's notebook as an official representation of his memories?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Will I accept Mr. Sprocket's notebook as an official representation of his memories...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I can accept Mr. Sprocket's notebook as...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Are you sure about that?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, not really. I mean, I already don't like where this is going... Your Honor! The defense requests a timeout!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are no "timeouts" in a court of law! Give me your answer, and no dawdling!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is an important point. I need to be careful in how I answer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a minute, Your Honor! The defense requests a chance to examine the notebook to see if it's trustworthy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. But be quick about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So, how should we examine it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we should look at it from all different angles to see if there's anything suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's no point if I don't look at what's inside. I have to open it. With your permission, Sorin... here I go! Yikes! Oh, it's just the page Maya got all stained. But I guess it's not going to be very helpful at this moment. I'll keep going. This is the last page where there's writing. Hmm... Something about this page doesn't sit right with me... I'd better take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing special about the cover...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are some mathematical formulas written here. It looks like he was calculating something to do with distance and time...? But I wouldn't know if this had anything to do with the case...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This page is blank.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? A page has been torn out. And it looks like there was something written on it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a page has been torn out here. Mr. Sprocket, do you know what was written on it?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Oh, that? I often tear out a page when I write somebody a note. I probably wrote something down for somebody, tore it out and gave it to them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, yeah...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That solves that, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But now that the page has been torn out... ...how can we determine what was written there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well... Let's see. To find out what was written in the notebook, we should...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know! We should hold the notebook up to the light! Hrngh... I don't see a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What are you flailing about over there for, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, just a minute, Your Honor... I just need a little more time to...</line>
<line speaker="JUdge">Mr. Wright, this court does not accept answers in the form of pantomime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh. I think the judge misinterpreted my movements...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know! We should heat the notebook with a lighter! Maybe the heat will reveal what was written! Your Honor, do you have a lighter I could borrow?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A lighter? And what exactly are you planning to do with one?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to heat this notebook up over an open flame.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have any reason to believe there's something to be gained by doing that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... it's just a hunch, Your Honor, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I won't let you take a lighter to evidence over some simple hunch! Have some sense, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The judge is right. Setting the notebook on fire would be a disaster. I'd better look at this more logically, like he said...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we use fingerprint powder on the notebook, we might be able to see what was written!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Fingerprint powder? How would that help us find out what was written there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if the writing left indentations on the blank page behind it... ...fingerprint powder could make those small indentations visible to the naked eye.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh, stop. Fingerprint powder would only sully the notebook further.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, if you use the powder and still don't find anything... ...then you must accept the notebook as a representation of the witness's memories.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, Your Honor. I understand. <thought>If I don't find anything, it's all over anyway... Powder, don't fail me now!</thought> I will now use fingerprint powder on the blank page... ...to find out if we can see what was written on the torn-out page. <thought>First, I touch a spot to dust it with fingerprint powder. When I've dusted on enough powder, I blow into the mic... ...to blow the excess powder away. If something should appear... ...I should touch "Analyze" (L</thought>... ...point to what came up, then touch "Confirm" <thought>X</thought>.)</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like I didn't get quite enough fingerprint powder on the page. I guess I'd better dust on a little more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... I'm not seeing anything... I'd better make sure I've got the right spot...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It says, "I struck and killed Dumas"... <thought>Th-This is huge...!</thought> "I struck and killed Dumas..." That's what was written on the torn-out page!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I-It can't be...!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Ellen:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Ms. Wyatt!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, please get the defendant to the infirmary at once!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Apparently, the defendant got too worked up. She's resting in the infirmary as we speak. Now then, please continue, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor... This notebook is all Mr. Sprocket has to remember things by. With this critical page torn out... ...not even Mr. Sprocket himself knew the truth of what he'd done.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...I'm the one... who killed Dumas...? So it wasn't Ellen... Oh, thank goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket, does this mean you were at the crime scene during the murder after all?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...I guess I must have been.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But, Mr. Sprocket... ...can we really believe what's written in this notebook?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Nobody touches this notebook but me. And when I sleep, it's under lock and key. I don't remember writing that I killed Dumas, but I guess I must have...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">W-Well! Now that we have a confession... ...I'm afraid I must render my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of all the...!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Yes, Your Honor. Please give your ruling now, while Ellen is asleep. I want the woman I love to be set free as soon as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorin really does love Ellen after all, doesn't he...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah... <thought>So this is how it ends... But is that how it really went down? Is there really no way for them both to be happy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I know we should consider anything written in the notebook to be the truth, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I myself wrote of the crime in my notebook. No further proof is necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorin himself wrote it in his notebook...? Wait a minute...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well... I will now give my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ellen is about to be found not guilty, and Sorin will be convicted for the crime instead. And yet... Am I really ready for the judge to give his ruling?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the judge declares his verdict now, Ellen will be found not guilty. As her defense lawyer, that's my job: to prove her innocence. Still... will this verdict really make Ellen happy?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No... Not when there's still one more avenue left to explore...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Ellen Wyatt...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What are you doing, Mr. Wright?! All you have to do is keep quiet, and your client's a free woman!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know... but I think there might be more to this case than meets the eye. <thought>I'm not quite sure yet... but I think there still might be a way... ...a way for Ellen and Sorin to be happy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What do you mean by, "more than meets the eye," Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe the question here, Your Honor, should be... ...why was the incriminating page torn out in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, to destroy the evidence, I would imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But removing it from the notebook is the same as removing it from Mr. Sprocket's memory. Which means he wouldn't have been able to trick the police if he came under suspicion. No. If he wanted to cover up his crime, he would have to remember that he had done it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Just what are you getting at with this line of inquiry, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, please explain it so that we can all understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. The page was torn out of the notebook because...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Sprocket wanted to forget all about this incident!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you claiming that Mr. Sprocket tore out the page himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But you just said a moment ago that Mr. Sprocket wouldn't do that! To your inconsistent claims, I say, "<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I didn't expect one of those from the judge... I can't have a contradiction between my own claims! I'd better be more careful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The page must've been torn out by accident.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No. I'm sure it was very well taken care of...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Then it's not very likely a page would get torn by chance, now is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, not very likely at all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is what happens when you try to abuse the system, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh...! I'd better be more careful with my answers...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The incriminating page... ...was torn out by somebody else!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?! Order! Order! Are you claiming a third person interfered with the notebook?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not all that surprising if you consider what's happened up until now. After both the car accident, and the murder of Dumas Gloomsbury... ...there was always a cover-up not far behind!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Sorin:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you? Because I remember you were in a panic yesterday because you couldn't find it!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Th-That's true...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So who orchestrated this particular cover-up, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we think back over the course of the trial, it's pretty easy to guess. <thought>The one who may have tried to tamper with Sorin's memories is...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That person?! Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe so, Your Honor, but I might also be wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That isn't the kind of line you should deliver with such confidence, Mr. Wright! Claim returned to sender!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rejection received, Your Honor... <thought>Okay, slow down... Time to collect my thoughts!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one who tampered with the notebook in order to manipulate Mr. Sprocket's memory... ...is Pierce Nichody!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Pierce...? Pierce tried to tamper with my memories...? Pierce was... manipulating me?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Case in point: the two receptions that were held to cover up the murder. It was Mr. Nichody who directed the guests and orchestrated the entire scheme.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">N-No... It can't be... Which of my memories are mine, and which have been rewritten...? When did he start rewriting my memories...?! Who wrote this?! And this?! And this?! And this?! And this?! And this?! And this?! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-H-He literally took off!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">AAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Look, Nick! He's coming back down!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">My... memories... Ellen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Please get Mr. Sprocket to the infirmary! On the double!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Sprocket has been taken to the infirmary. We don't have to worry about him running away, so let us resume where we left off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor. The defense would like to call Pierce Nichody to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This time it's different. The notebook... or, rather, Mr. Sprocket's memories, have been tampered with. That means the only person who knows the whole truth... is now Mr. Nichody.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Don't tell me... Are you actually trying to drum up a third suspect... ...in order to exonerate the defendant and her groom?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not drumming up anything, nor do I have grounds to accuse him of anything... yet. All I know is that Mr. Nichody is the only one who knows the truth! <thought>And I think he's still hiding something! Something we don't know about yet!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. No grounds "yet," is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Edgeworth? Does the prosecution consent to calling the witness to the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It does, Your Honor. ...However, I would like a little time to talk with the witness before we do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. We will break for a twenty-minute recess.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now we'll have to face Pierce on the stand... I'm not sure if I should be surprised or not. One thing's for sure... He won't be an easy adversary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So... do you think Pierce did it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too early to say anything at this point. But I do think he's still hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Larry">NIIIIIICK! Why didn't you pin everything on Sorin Loser back there?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like Larry still hasn't given up on Ellen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">If this Pierce guy is the real bad guy... ...then Sorin and my Elly will live happily ever after together!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... that's not the kind of thing a decent human being says...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Shame on you, Larry!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, booo-hoooo! Y-You think I don't know?! I know I have to give up on my Elly... But, Nick...! Promise you'll make her happy! She deserves a "happily ever after"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh, I'm sure Sorin will make her happy, once all of this is said and done...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial is about to resume, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. You ready, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yup! Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">I'll be rooting for you, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is now back in session. ......Witness, please take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">My name is Pierce Nichody. I am the Sprocket family butler.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's get straight to the point, Mr. Nichody. Someone tore out a page from Mr. Sprocket's notebook to manipulate his memories. And that person was you... wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">......That is correct. What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, that was easy!</thought> So why did you do it?! Why did you tamper with Mr. Sprocket's notebook?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Please allow me to explain. It pains me to do this, but I will tell you the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It pains you...?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...That is correct. For my testimony will go against Master Sorin's wishes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorin's wishes? What is he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I rushed to the vista deck, but the crime had already been committed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait a second...! What Mr. Sprocket was writing in his notebook at the time -- could it be...? <thought>It was meant to be a confession -- an admission he'd killed Gloomsbury himself!</thought> He wrote that message to take the blame for Ms. Wyatt?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">That is correct. Master Sorin did hit Gloomsbury with the Time Keeper to save Miss Ellen...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then Mr. Sprocket was the culprit after all!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">However, that blow did not kill Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That makes sense. Mr. Sprocket's injury wouldn't allow him to put much force into it.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Enraged, Gloomsbury tried to attack Master Sorin, who was already seriously wounded. But just in the nick of time, Miss Ellen hit Gloomsbury from behind... ...and finished him off, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So the one who inflicted the fatal blow was the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Yes, that is correct. But Master Sorin tried to take all of the blame onto himself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-No way...! This... is pretty bad, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding... <thought>"Pretty bad" is an understatement...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, well, Mr. Wright. It seems your decision to call for Mr. Nichody has backfired. For the true culprit behind this case remains the defendant, Ellen Wyatt!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arngh! <thought>Could this get any worse?! But Pierce was involved in the cover-up plot... And I bet he still has something to hide!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I rushed to the vista deck, but the crime had already been committed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Actually, that is not true.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I found this out afterward, but... ...Master Sorin went to the vista deck alone. He went out the escape hatch in the reception hall, and went along the outside wall.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You can't be serious! You mean, Mr. Wright's addlepated guess was actually correct?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with the "addlepated"?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose truth really is stranger than fiction!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Mr. Nichody... When you got to the scene, you saw Mr. Gloomsbury, Ms. Wyatt... ...and Mr. Sprocket. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">That is exactly right.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I saw Miss Ellen and Gloomsbury collapsed, and Master Sorin writing in his notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...That is correct. Gloomsbury had already been struck. Miss Ellen had lost consciousness, probably from the shock of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...And how did Mr. Sprocket appear?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">He was bleeding from the stab wound he'd received from Gloomsbury. Barely conscious, he was writing something in his notebook.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the mysterious third person Ellen saw really was Sorin, then...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin said to me, "I'll take the blame for the murder, so please take care of Ellen."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Yes. That notebook is the only form of memory Master Sorin has. So you understand what his action meant, I trust?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What did it mean, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To Sorin, everything in that notebook is true. So Sorin tried to take the blame... ...by altering his own memory to make himself think he did it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Master Sorin truly loves Miss Ellen. It must have been love that made him do that.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">But I went against his order. I tore the page out of his notebook, and hid the body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">"That," you say? Which part do you mean, Mr. Wright? Could you be more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh... all right. <thought>What part do I want to know more about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please tell me more about the hiding of the body.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Very well. After saying he would take the blame, Master Sorin passed out. That's when I hid the body. I quickly took the lift down to the hold... ...where I hid Gloomsbury's still-warm body in the spare Pegabull lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it was you who hid the body, not the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">To think Mr. Butz would move the lantern containing the body to the reception hall... Well, I did not see that coming.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't blame you. Not even Larry can predict what Larry will do next... Maybe I should take another look at the lantern in evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like that statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please add that statement to your testimony, Mr. Nichody.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"In the hold, I hid the still-warm body in the spare Pegabull lantern."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I guess not, Your Honor. <thought>I'd better be a bit more cautious here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">No? All right. Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why did you go against Mr. Sprocket's order and tear out the page?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...That is a silly question. As I told you before... Disposing of anything that may harm the Sprocket family's reputation... ...is simply a part of my job.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right. You did say that before, didn't you.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I tore the page out of the notebook in order to protect Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like that statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please add that statement to your testimony, Mr. Nichody.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I tore the page out of the notebook in order to protect Master Sorin."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, I guess not, Your Honor. <thought>I'd better be a bit more cautious here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">No? All right. Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">In the hold, I hid the still-warm body in the spare Pegabull lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">As I told you yesterday, it was to make it as though the murder never happened. But thanks to Mr. Butz, things did not turn out as planned.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So holding the second wedding reception wasn't Mr. Sprocket's idea... ...but yours, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It was all for Master Sorin's sake... and Sprocket Aviation. If I am accused of a crime for trying to cover up the incident... ...I shall accept it willingly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He really doesn't seem to even care about himself!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I tore the page out of that notebook in order to protect Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I knew it went against his wishes... ...but I just could not let Master Sorin bear the blame for something he did not do. As his butler, I believe that was the right decision for me to make.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was all for Sorin's benefit, huh? I bet Pierce would do just about anything in the name of keeping Sorin's image "safe"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This testimony of Pierce's... I wonder how much of it we can actually believe.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah. Who knows what parts are true and what parts are more spun tales?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. But we can't just stand around mulling it all over. We have to try and draw information out of him, and see if there are any contradictions!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So he's talking about the cover-up after the incident, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. That's information only somebody who was actually involved could know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So it might be a really important piece of testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think so, too. I'll really have to tread carefully here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>C-Could it be...? Is that what happened...? If what I'm thinking is true... ...then maybe I can prove neither Ellen nor Sorin did the deed!</thought> Mr. Nichody, you said the body was still warm when you hid it, correct? So then, what if... ...Mr. Gloomsbury was still alive when you went to put his body inside the lantern...?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, this shows that the victim might have still been alive while inside the lantern!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid you'll have to point out which part you're talking about, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This part here shows that the victim might have still been alive inside the lantern!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is something the matter, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if you stare at this spot reaaally hard, doesn't it become a little clearer?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not in the least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......How about now, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How could I understand without a word of explanation?! Clearly you need to take responsibility for your actions!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd better paint a clearer picture next time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see, the back end of the lantern is a door. And there's blood here on the wheel handle!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I disagree, Mr. Edgeworth. For you see, in putting this lantern back together... ...the police inadvertently placed the inside handle on the outside, and vice versa. In other words, the wheel handles got swapped!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! So they got swapped?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, they got swapped!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What? But that's ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not at all. If you compare the other male Pegabull lantern in the reception hall... ...it's quite obvious the wheel handles were attached backwards!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Th-The detective in charge of the restoration will see me in my office later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorry, Ema... And good luck.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-In that case, what does the bloodstain on the wheel handle mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The bloodstain didn't get there by chance. When the victim was put inside the lantern, he was only unconscious, not dead. When he regained consciousness, he probably tried to get out of the lantern. So he grasped the inner wheel handle, and that's when the blood got on it! This proves that the victim was still alive when he was inside the lantern!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">At the time, I was completely convinced Gloomsbury was dead. Had I checked more carefully, he might have survived...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Unfortunate, to be sure... but not significant enough to change this trial's outcome.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Again, I disagree, Mr. Edgeworth. It actually has a very significant impact on this case.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The victim was struck by the defendant, then died from his injuries some time later. There's nothing more to it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the one Mr. Sprocket gave him, and the one Ms. Wyatt delivered to finish him off.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, the defense would like to submit a different interpretation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A different interpretation?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The victim was knocked unconscious by the first blow, and was then put into the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-Then, what about the lethal blow by the defendant that the witness talked about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, well... that didn't happen. After some time... ...when the victim regained consciousness and tried to get out of the lantern... ...that's when he received the second blow that finished him off!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Taking into account the fact that the victim was alive for a period after the first hit... ...and that he did receive a second blow to the head... It does seem entirely possible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. As long as the first blow didn't kill the victim instantly... ...then there's a possibility that... ...someone other than Mr. Sprocket or Ms. Wyatt delivered the fatal blow!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's elementary, Mr. Wright. After the reception, when the defendant was cleaning up the reception hall... ...the victim, who was supposed to be dead, suddenly came out of the lantern. The defendant grabbed the murder weapon, which was right there, and finished him off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That theory sounds awfully familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of course it does, Your Honor, because it's exactly what I proposed at the very start. The second blow was inflicted by the defendant after all!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see! It seems a tangle of mysteries has unraveled into a single thread!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Give it up, Mr. Wright! Unless you have something to prove the presence of your precious "third person"?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I, uh...!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick! Just relax! You can do this! Come on, now. Take some deep breaths!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good idea. Deep breaths... Deep breaths...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There! Don't you feel better already?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's right. I should calm down, get my focus back, and go over everything again. And then, hopefully, I'll be able to find something to prove there was a third person!</thought> ...Let's see. First, why did Gloomsbury attack Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Because... he was tired of taking the blame for the accident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... But something about that line of reasoning just doesn't feel quite right to me...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No? How come?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, if it's just a personal vendetta, he had already stabbed Sorin. So why, then, was he so determined to go after Ellen?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're right. This whole thing feels too premeditated for a crime of passion...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Gloomsbury didn't seem to have a personal grudge against Ellen... <thought>If Gloomsbury didn't have a personal reason to attack Ellen, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You've taken long enough, Mr. Wright. Now it's time for some action. What proof do you have that a third person was involved?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. I'll show you. <thought>I'm not completely sure of what I'm doing yet, but it looks like I'm out of time!</thought> This piece of evidence proves the involvement of a third person!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I would love to hear the defense explain its way out of this.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Go ahead, Nick! Tell 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you see... Um... Huh? It looks like... I was wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Next time, try to involve your brain before you blurt out an answer!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Not one word! Just look over the evidence again, all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, ma'am... <thought>I'd better try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I get it now... Now I see why this note bothered me so much when I first saw it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like a note outlining the murder plot...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That note was apparently written by the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But why would he feel the need to write instructions to himself like this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, please take a look at this note.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is... the victim's murder plan, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's definitely "a" murder plan, but what if... ...Mr. Gloomsbury didn't write this note himself?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">THIS is how you intend to conjure up your mysterious third party, Mr. Wright? Can you even prove that that note wasn't written by the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes. Yes, I can.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well, then. Please present your evidence, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This evidence proves the victim didn't write the note.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It doesn't look like anything of the sort to me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I have to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just close your eyes and concentrate, Your Honor. Is something coming to you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............No, nothing at all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Nothing, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Close your eyes and concentrate. Do you see something coming to you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I should've seen that coming... Looks like I'd better try again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the weapon Mr. Gloomsbury used to stab Mr. Sprocket.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was wondering what you'd pull out this time. Dare I ask what that could possibly have to do with the note?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Gloomsbury's prints were found on this candelabra. And the prints were from his left hand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, that makes the victim left-handed, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor. The police looked into it, too, and confirmed as much. Now, take a look at the smudged writing in this note. Notice how the smudging only starts from the middle of each proceeding line. Had this been written by a lefty, the writing would be smudged from the far left end. This means that whoever wrote this note was definitely right-handed. In other words, somebody other than the victim wrote this note!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Hmm... But if someone other than Mr. Gloomsbury wrote it, then what does this note mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Gloomsbury followed this note to the letter when he attacked Ms. Wyatt. So, clearly, this note isn't a murder plan written by Mr. Gloomsbury, but rather... ...these are instructions to kill Ms. Wyatt, issued by somebody else!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">He is correct. The majority of the family and their employees who were on the airship... ...are indeed right-handed. I must say, that is a very rough and slipshod conjecture you've proposed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnngh! <thought>I admit I haven't figured out who wrote it just yet...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Leave it to Mr. Edgeworth to go for the jugular...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This culprit who ordered Gloomsbury to attack Ellen... ...what could their motive have been?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">It doesn't seem very likely Ellen did anything to incur anybody's wrath, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... <thought>Not too likely, anyway...</thought> In that case, it has to be about Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">If somebody were to hold a grudge against Sorin, what would it be about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That accident, I'd guess. I could understand if Gloomsbury felt resentful about having to take the blame.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But the one who lost the most to that accident was Sorin's sister... She lost her life, after all. Sorin suffered, too, of course. He was crushed by losing somebody so precious to him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Somebody precious," huh... "Sorin's sister"... Wait! There's one more person! There's someone else who must hold a grudge against Sorin!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Did you figure something out?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think so... I think this "somebody else" used Gloomsbury to try and get revenge against Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Did you say somebody tried to get revenge against Mr. Sprocket, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who manipulated and used Mr. Gloomsbury was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Sprocket's father. I heard that the marriage to Ms. Wyatt didn't have the family's blessing. Sorin's father must have used Mr. Gloomsbury to try and stop their union.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If he just wanted to stop the marriage, there were a multitude of other, better ways.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>H-He's got a good point, there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Edgeworth is right. It doesn't sound very plausible. And it's irresponsible to throw suspicion around without good reason, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Then who could've been manipulating Gloomsbury...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...the family elder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The family elder...? Has this "family elder" person come up in the deliberations before?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, not really, Your Honor. But don't rich families like the Sprockets usually have somebody like that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you can't just make up people whenever you want! Heck, even I only get to hand out penalties when necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>D-Does that mean he'd penalize me more if he could...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The person who used Mr. Gloomsbury to try and get revenge on Mr. Sprocket... ...and then finished Mr. Gloomsbury off to silence him... ...was a man dear to Mr. Sprocket's older sister: Selena Sprocket's fianc! <thought>Not that I'm positive, but it's certainly possible... This fianc could have made Gloomsbury attack Ellen to get his revenge on Sorin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Her fianc?! Order in the court! Order, I say! Yes, it does seem quite believable that Ms. Selena Sprocket's fianc... ...would bear a grudge against Mr. Sprocket for his role in the accident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor. Maybe her fianc was trying to murder Ms. Wyatt... ...in order to make Mr. Sprocket experience the same pain he'd felt.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That may be, but then that just means that Ms. Sprocket's fianc must have been... ...among those who attended!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course. Otherwise, how could he have killed Gloomsbury?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... I see what you're doing... This is just another giant bluff, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">All right. I'll bite. Who exactly do you claim this fianc to be?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes! I would like to know as well!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A-Are you sure you're gonna be okay, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maybe...? <thought>When it comes to suspicious people, there's only one person on my list... I need to find something that connects him to Selena...</thought> This will help us identify Ms. Sprocket's fianc!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yes, I believe it will. At least, I hope it will, anyway...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'd like you to show me another piece of evidence, Mr. Wright. Evidence that you're taking this job seriously!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>I'd better think things through a little better... I have to find something that connects Selena and her fianc!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this photo, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Th-That photo...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Notice Ms. Sprocket's pocket watch. Haven't we seen it somewhere before?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, yes. Now that you mention it, I do feel as if I've seen it somewhere before...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe we've all seen it... right here in this very courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Augh! I-Impossible...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. The pocket watch in this photo... ...is the same pocket watch Mr. Nichody has on him right now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is clear proof... ...of a strong connection between Pierce Nichody and Selena Sprocket!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Nichody? Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Nichody... You were once engaged to Selena Sprocket. That pocket watch... You keep it as a memento of her, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Nichody, you planned to rob Mr. Sprocket of his loved one... ...to make him feel the same pain as you. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Sprocket managed to fight back, and knocked Mr. Gloomsbury unconscious. You thought Mr. Gloomsbury was dead, and hid his body in the lantern.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But then you noticed Mr. Gloomsbury regain consciousness... ...and so you finished him off to prevent your plan from being exposed. This is the defense's take on what really happened in this murder case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, does this mean... ...you wish to officially accuse this witness of the murder of Dumas Gloomsbury?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Does the defense accuse Mr. Nichody of the murder...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait. If I back down now, it's all over. I have to take the plunge and chase this down to the very end!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense indicts Pierce Nichody on the charge of murdering Dumas Gloomsbury!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! M-Mr. Nichody, would you care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ Man, this lawyer just yaps on and on and on... As you guessed, this watch is a memento of Selena. It stopped working at the time of the accident, though...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Then, you really are...!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">......Yes, I was Selena's fianc. And not just her fianc... ...but the surgeon beside her deathbed.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Shut it, you useless prosecutor. I thought you could be of use, but apparently, this case was too much for you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What did you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">If your office hadn't stuck its nose all up in this, I could've swept it under the rug. Not only did you interfere with the case, but you even let me fall under suspicion!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's because you kept trying to cover things up on the sly!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Urrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But covering things up wasn't your only involvement. The only person who had a motive to use the victim to try and kill Ms. Wyatt... ...was you!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">N-Nngrrrrrrrr! Malignant tumors... There are malignant tumors in this courtroom, lesions oozing with false charges! The tumors are one idiotic lawyer, and one useless prosecutor! After the truth is revealed, I'll have the both of you incised from the legal world!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. I'd like to see you try.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">With the power of the Sprocket family, it'd be a cinch. I will now begin the operation!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-What in the world happened to Mr. Nichody...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like he's finally showing his true colors.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Look what he did to that shoulder mech!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Quit your yapping, before I suture your chatty lips shut.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It's like he's a completely different person...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure looks like it, huh. We can't let our guards down now! Mr. Nichody, it's finally time for you to testify... ...to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It seems we're entering the final act at last. Witness, your testimony, please.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Mr. Nichody! Why didn't you say anything?! Ack! <thought>He just took a picture of me... or something...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You want me to voluntarily testify, hoping I will make a slip of the tongue. Not a very impressive plan... or brain, I might add.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ow... That was uncalled for...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">If you want to know something, YOU ask the question. I will answer, but I have no intention of making any voluntary statements of my own.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's he trying to do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He's using the silent treatment as his strategy to avoid getting tripped up. Clever guy...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">No more lies, Mr. Nichody. You will tell us nothing but the truth from now on! Augh! Wh-What do you think you're doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">No one asked you to speak. Just keep quiet over there and play with your frills.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">H-How dare you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! This is a rather unconventional situation, but please proceed, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ </line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ </line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it true that when Mr. Gloomsbury regained consciousness inside the lantern... ...you murdered him in order to silence him?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...He was an excellent employee, and very loyal to me. Gloomsbury was my right hand man. I'd suffer the most from losing him. You really think I'd kill a guy like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That would make sense only if you were innocent. But since your goal was revenge, you don't really have to care about something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">But I AM innocent, I tell you. Don't try to force your conjectures onto me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>I guess without decisive evidence, I can't pursue this line of questioning any further...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like that statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please, Your Honor. <thought>Every little bit I can drag out of him helps, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change first statement to">"Gloomsbury was my right hand man. I'd suffer the most from losing him."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, thank you, Your Honor. <thought>I'd better tread cautiously here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've been nursing a grudge against Mr. Sprocket over the loss of your fiance. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...I'd be lying if I said I felt no resentment whatsoever. But Master Sorin didn't cause that accident on purpose. ...Master Sorin himself has suffered greatly!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But you quit being a surgeon and found a way to get even closer to Mr. Sprocket. Wasn't that so you could carry out your revenge on him?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Don't insult me. Supporting Master Sorin and Sprocket Aviation with my life's work... ...is my penance for not being able to save Selena. This is how I honor her.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel your devotion as both a fianc and a surgeon. ...Your statement breaks my heart.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I've never thought of exacting revenge on Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>"Never thought of it," huh? I guess I should probably take that with a pound of salt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like that statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, please, Your Honor. <thought>I have to find an opening somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Change second statement to">"I've never thought of exacting revenge on Master Sorin."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not, Your Honor... <thought>But on second thought, I have to get some kind of testimony out of him, don't I?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On the day of the incident, you were constantly surrounded by your subordinates. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Absolutely. I was in someone's line of sight at all times. After all, I was busy taking care of every detail of the event. Mr. Edgeworth, I believe your investigation backs up my claim?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Hmph. I got statements that said groups of his subordinates worked with him in rotation... ...so he was always with someone.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">As the prosecutor just said... ...I couldn't even get close to the lantern containing Gloomsbury by myself... ...let alone kill him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Pierce didn't have a chance to get close to the victim alone, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, would you like that statement added to the witness's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. I'd like to have that statement added to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Change third statement to">"I was always in the company of others. I didn't have the opportunity to murder Gloomsbury."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess not, Your Honor. <thought>It doesn't seem all that important...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Gloomsbury was my right hand man. I'd suffer the most from losing him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">He got his position as the lead servant in exchange for taking the blame. It wasn't exactly a bad deal for him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But he must have felt some sort of indignation...?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Who knows? Now that he's dead, we'll never know for sure. It's pointless to talk about it any further.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right... <thought>Dead men tell no tales, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I've never thought of exacting revenge on Master Sorin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...Of course not! Selena wouldn't have wanted that! I've thrown my own life away, and lived solely for the sake of the Sprocket family. That's how I show my love for her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All righty, then...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, one thing's for sure... Pierce gets really emotional when it comes to Selena...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding... I'm not sure how he feels about Sorin, but his love for Selena is pretty obvious.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I was always in the company of others. I didn't have the opportunity to murder Gloomsbury.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I was surrounded by family members and staff as we prepared for the reception. During the reception, I was stationed behind the sweetheart table to attend to the couple. When could I have possibly committed murder?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not buying it. If Pierce is the true killer... ...then there must have been some time when he was out of everyone's sight!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ugh... This isn't going to be easy, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can say that again... All I can do is just... ...try to draw as much information as I can out of him, and look for any inconsistencies.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">This is the moment of truth, huh, Nick? Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What do you think, Nick? Is there a chance for us here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, as long as we have some kind of testimony from him, there has to be! I'll just have to compare his testimony against the evidence and...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Find an inconsistency, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. <thought>This is it! I have to do this right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Nichody testifies that he was always with someone at the time of the incident... ...and never had a moment alone to commit the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. And the police investigation backs that statement up, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But there WAS an opportunity, in fact -- one and only one. A moment when Mr. Nichody could have killed Mr. Gloomsbury without anyone noticing!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And the one thing that made that moment possible... ...is shown here in this photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Nichody:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">N-Nnrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Mr. Wright, let's see this "one thing" you mentioned. But be warned, this had better not be one of your offhanded claims.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who do you think you're talking to, Mr. Edgeworth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. Please point out for us the "one thing" that made the moment of the murder possible!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That one moment when it was possible for Mr. Nichody to kill Mr. Gloomsbury... The one thing that made that single moment possible... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?! That?! That's what made it possible?! ...And how exactly did it do that, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, uh... First, it flings away loose sand with its flippers to make a hole on the beach... And then, eyes glistening with maternal affection, it takes this nest and...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, are you describing how a sea turtle lays her eggs?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh... I was so focused on answering that I forgot what we were actually talking about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You can't just say whatever comes to mind, you know. It seems you have truly jumped the shark at last, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Your Honor... <thought>Just saying any old thing isn't good enough. I have to get it together!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The one thing that made the moment of the murder possible... ...is this thick mood fog that engulfed the entire reception hall! It is under the cover of this fog... ...that Mr. Nichody murdered the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Nichody was standing right next to the lantern that Mr. Gloomsbury was in! This was the only moment the murder could have been committed without being seen!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nnrgh! <thought>I was so caught up in finding a foothold that I forgot to think that far ahead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Well done, Mr. Edgeworth! It's time to call this trial's time of death!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Mr. Wright? Can you prove the murder happened during the reception?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Don't even bother! His claim is dead on arrival! Victory is within your grasp, Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Quiet, witness. I have no interest in "victory." All I care about... is the truth. One that we can only arrive at through further deliberation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth...!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Enough of this! Your Honor, this trial is over!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, Mr. Nichody. That is for me to decide. Mr. Wright, can you prove it? Can you prove that the murder was committed during the wedding reception?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Why is there no verdict yet?! The lawyer's obviously out of answers! The prosecutor, the judge -- they're all infected! Their malignant stupidity is so advanced, not even the best surgeons can save them! In fact, not even a brain transplant could cure them! This court is infected with idiocy! It's a pandemic!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Finally ready to give up, are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, just the opposite, actually. I'll prove the murder was committed during the reception... by you!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Agnk! ...You'll prove it...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Can you really, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, I can, Your Honor! <thought>To be honest, I don't know exactly how I'll do it just yet... But if I want to get to the truth Edgeworth was talking about... ...I'll just have to find that way!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. Let's have your proof.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Enough of this foolishness! He's just bluffing! Stop him from speaking, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I will do nothing of the sort.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">You are just a district court judge! With the power of the Sprocket family, I'll--!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough of YOUR foolishness, Mr. Nichody. This judicial body will not succumb to the influence of money or power. </line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Urk...!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Now, then. Let's hear it, Mr. Wright! Let's hear your truth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Think, Phoenix! Remember everything you've learned so far! You can do this! You can find the definitive evidence that will lead us to the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Think, Phoenix! How can I prove the murder took place during the wedding reception? If Pierce committed the murder during the reception, then he had to have used...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His shoulder mech, FXR-UPR. He must have hit the victim with that, and... No, wait. That can't be right. I've gotta calmly think my way through this...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The photo of the reception. Okay, sure, it does show the scene of the murder... ...but it doesn't show anything conclusive! I have to think harder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, the weapon that was used to strike the victim twice! According to the autopsy report, the victim was hit by the same object both times. So, without a doubt, Pierce used it to commit the murder! The weapon used to kill Gloomsbury was...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The candelabra? No. The candelabra was used by Gloomsbury to stab Sorin. Think... What was the murder weapon in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Phoenix! Nobody could beat a person to death with such a tiny little key! Calm down, and think things over one more time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If Pierce struck the victim during that one, single moment... ...then he must have used the Time Keeper! Come to think of it, wasn't it also used for something else during the reception? During the reception, the Time Keeper was also used for...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The cutting of the time machine...? What does that even mean?! They could never get a knife into that thing! It's not a cake, after all... Where's my head at? I'd better focus...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "first taste of love," huh? That's where the bride and groom feed cake to each other, right? Sorin and Ellen might have done that, too, but it'd have nothing to do with the case! This is the final stretch. Think hard, Phoenix!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right! The Time Keeper had been activated during the reception! If we activate the Time Keeper again now, and find any trace evidence of the murder... ...that would be conclusive proof that Gloomsbury was killed during the reception!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A special ceremony took place during the reception in question.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What kind of a special ceremony?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was called, "the First Startup of Love." Apparently, the couple activated the Time Keeper for the first time during it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does that mean the Time Keeper here in evidence isn't activated at the moment? And what would happen... if we were to activate it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why don't we see for ourselves? It would give us a chance to examine it. And while we're at it, we just might find some conclusive evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">N-No! Y-You can't activate it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Nichody! Keep quiet, or I'll have you thrown out of court!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Nnrgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">By the way, Mr. Wright... This is supposed to be a time machine, right? We aren't going to travel back in time to the Stone Age or anything, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I don't think we have to worry too much about that, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm still a little nervous, nonetheless... but the truth must be known. Very well. Go ahead and start up the Time Keeper!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know how, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I think so...? Maybe...?</line>
<line speaker="Maid">The bride and groom each had a symbol of their love, and when they put them together... Oh, how romantic it was!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... I think the symbol of the groom's love must be the Time Keeper itself. What symbol of the bride's love would fit together with the Time Keeper? <thought>Oh, I know! That has to be it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Are you ready to activate the time machine now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. The symbol of the bride's love that's necessary for activating the Time Keeper is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Set it in place where? It doesn't look like it fits anywhere...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You don't think so? Not even if we kind of... jammed it in?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, you know what's coming, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A penalty, Your Honor...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm glad you understand. That will save us some time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh...  <thought>All right. I'd better take another good look at what I've got to work with...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Wyatt's pendant... ...is the symbol of the bride's love that is necessary for activating the Time Keeper!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Then does that mean you can start it up with Ms. Wyatt's pendant?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I believe so, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Please try it now, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, here I go. <thought>But first, I have to figure out where the pendant goes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The outer casing is made of metal. I sure wouldn't want to get hit with something like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a propeller. It's designed to look like the hands of a clock. I don't think it has anything to do with activating the Time Keeper, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This hole looks like a good spot. I'll try setting the pendant in here... It fits! This must be a right spot! Now I have to find a place to insert the key...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This hole in the middle of the pendant... Could this be it?! It worked! The Time Keeper's been activated! Now all I have to do is find the proof that the crime was committed during the reception!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The Time Keeper has already been already activated. [sic] Now I just have to look for proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I... I think I found it..! Conclusive evidence that the murder was committed during the wedding reception!</thought> Just as I suspected, there's evidence of the murder inside the Time Keeper, Mr. Nichody. The Time Keeper was only activated and open during the wedding reception, right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo! Stoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooop!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, that means... ...this is conclusive proof that the crime was committed during the reception!</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">ACK!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After you killed the victim under the cover of fog... ...you closed the Time Keeper to hide the bloodstain, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">N-No! You're wrong! Ellen killed Gloomsbury! It wasn't me, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Edgeworth:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I-It was... the family...! Yes, all the family members conspired together to kill him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">NGHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH! ACK! No... This isn't over yet... I won't give up...! Oh, no! I cut the artery! This stupid thing! We must stop the bleeding now! Give me forceps! Forceps, I said! Hey! Where is everyone?! Fine... I'll manage this alone! I'll do it all by myself! I can fix anything! Repair anything! So you have to get better! You have to live! You must! ...I... I would've been able to save her... If only I hadn't listened to her... If only I had treated her first... If only that Sorin... hadn't been there............ Augh! S-Selena... No...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............ Witness... Are you finally ready to tell us the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">It's just as the lawyer deduced...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So it was all a revenge scheme against Sorin Sprocket?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">............ Do you have any idea how hard it is to lose someone you love, right in front of you? Selena's condition was clearly more critical than Sorin's, but, in spite of that, she said...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Sprocket's last words...  <thought>So that's what she really meant by those words...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I was able to grant her wish, but at the price of her life...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you got a job with Sprocket Aviation and waited for your chance to get revenge. You got close to Mr. Gloomsbury, and hatched this plot. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Gloomsbury already bore a grudge against Sorin... ...so when I tempted him with an even better position, he immediately took the bait.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He was your accomplice, someone who shared the same goal as you... Why was it necessary for you to kill him?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I didn't expect Sorin to strike Gloomsbury out on the vista deck... ...and I certainly never imagined he'd make his way there along the outside wall.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sorin's love is the real deal after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nichody">My plan had been compromised, so for the time being, I hid his body in the lantern... ...and tried to think of my next move.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then Mr. Gloomsbury came to during the second wedding reception.</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">As soon as I saw Gloomsbury, I instantly hit upon an idea... ...to pin the blame of Gloomsbury's murder on Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You tried to break up the couple by making the bride out to be a murderer... How despicable! </line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Sorin was getting the company and a wedding... Both things that were supposed to be Selena's! He took every happiness from her. Who's the despicable one here?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Do you think what you did would make her happy?</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">I know it wouldn't! But I couldn't just stand by, watching Sorin enjoy his happiness... I was going to have Sorin taste the same pain I had, and then take over Sprocket Aviation... I would take back from him all the happiness that was rightfully Selena's...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">............</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Time stopped for me the day I lost her... Just like this pocket watch of hers.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ellen:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Wyatt?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I believe Selena would've said... "Leave this ill will behind. Your time is yours to live."</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...It's too late for me. Time will never advance for me ever again...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">...What? I-It can't be... I see now, Selena... What I did... was wrong...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see no further need to continue this trial. Bailiff, please take Mr. Nichody away.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Pierce Nichody... Another inconsolable time traveler... ...who lived in time that stood still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, I must render my verdict regarding the defendant... Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Your Honor... Before you give your ruling, would you please allow me a moment?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Ellen, there's something I need to say to you...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Y-Yes, Sorin?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I've put you through something truly horrible. This whole thing happened... all because of me. I... I would understand if you wanted to call off our marriage...</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">...Whaaaaat? O-Of course not! I've never once thought that!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">If you stay with me, you'll only face even more trying times in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">...What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">The truth of this incident, and the car accident before it... ...I'm going to tell the public everything.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">............</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I expect the company's reputation will suffer, and I'll take a lot of criticism. But I feel... ...I can only really start over once I get everything out in the open.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Sorin...</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">After all that's happened, I might not have the right to ask you this, but... ...Well... Um... How should I say this...? Um... Maybe I'll just... A life with me probably won't be very easy, but... ...will you marry me?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">............Yes, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Your Honor, thank you for this time. Please, continue with your ruling.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. But, first, I have one question. Do the two of you pledge your eternal love for each other to the goddess of justice, Themis?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I do, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">I do.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the prosecution or defense have any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph. Well done, Your Honor... No, no objections here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense has no objections either, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court finds the defendant, Ellen Wyatt... Ah, that's not right... This court finds the defendant, Ellen Sprocket...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen, Sorin, congratulations!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Mr. Wright! I can't thank you enough! If you hadn't exposed the truth, Sorin and I wouldn't... We wouldn't... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But now you can finally start your new life together, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">OH, THAAAAAAAAAANK YOOOOOOOOOUUUUU!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...Mr. Wright. We'll be holding our real wedding ceremony in the near future. Would you do us the honor of coming to it? I want you to witness our fresh start.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course! I wouldn't miss it for the world. And, Ellen, this time, it'll finally be "happily ever after," right?</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Oh, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The two of you have persevered, and overcome this trial together. Now, no matter what obstacles come your way, I'm sure you'll be able to handle them. And there's another thing I'm sure of, too. This person will always be watching over the two of you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ellen:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh! Uh, never mind this!  <thought>Oops, that wasn't it...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Come on, Nick! What were you thinking?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ellen and Sorin... I believe that Selena will watch over the two of you, always!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Selena... Yes, I think you're right. And we promise to live life to the fullest -- for Selena's sake, too! ...Right, Sorin?</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">...That's right. Well, we'd better be on our way.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Yes, my love!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow! The ol' "threshold carry," huh? Way to show off!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">We'll be seeing you! Goodbye for now!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll be looking forward to that wedding!</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">Hold on tight, Ellen.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">You better believe I will! I'm never letting you go!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There they go...</line>
<line speaker="???">You're not thinking of going to that wedding by yourself, are you, Boss?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're taking us, too, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, boy! I bet there's gonna be all kinds of fancy food there!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena? When did you get here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just now. I would've been here to cheer you guys on earlier, but... ...Trucy never gave me a chance to slip away!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You're going to be in even bigger trouble with her later...!</thought> Speaking of the wedding... ...maybe I should ask them to invite Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Edgeworth?! Really?! But he thought Ellen was guilty all the way to the end!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That may be true, but...</line>
<line speaker="Nichody">Don't even bother! His claim is dead on arrival! Victory is within your grasp, Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Quiet, witness. I have no interest in "victory." All I care about... is the truth. One that we can only arrive at through further deliberation.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he hadn't stood up for us when he did, the trial probably would've ended there.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You mean Mr. Edgeworth gave us that chance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe... Though, knowing him, I doubt he'd ever tell, even if I asked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... Well, if that's how you feel about it, Nick, then why not try to get him invited!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, Maya! Have you ever tried to catch the bouquet?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What?! Um, no...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I never have, either! Fighting over a bouquet that's been tossed by the bride... Talk about a fierce competition! I'm totally stoked!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not sure it's really supposed to be all that competitive...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm a pretty good jumper, so I think I've got a chance!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's... definitely missing the point of the whole thing...</thought> ...And Larry, how did you manage to stay so quiet for so long?</line>
<line speaker="Larry">...Shut up! Wishing the lady you fell in love with every happiness is what a real man does!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm pretty sure that "relationship" was over before it even began, Larry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Larry">*sniffle* Darn it all! If only I was ten years younger, things would've gone differently... Hands of time, why won't you turn back for meeeeeeeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Today is Ellen and Sorin's third wedding ceremony and reception... I heard the bride and groom insisted it be on the Flying Chapel again. In the end, they were nice enough to invite me and Maya... And Athena kind of invited herself... They also invited Edgeworth, Ema, and even Larry! They say third time's the charm, right? I really do hope it's "happily ever after" for them this time around! Still, I get the feeling it's going to be one rowdy party...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ready when you are!</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Okay! Here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Larry">Oh, heeey! Look who's next!</line>
<line speaker="Maya/Ema/Athena">[indistinguishable angry chatter]</line>
<line speaker="Sorin">I'm truly blessed to have you.</line>
<line speaker="Ellen">Aww!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A "feeling," defense?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor... Or, rather, a "hope" that it indicates a contradiction...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright. Is there or isn't there a contradiction here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there is... but there really isn't one, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you asking me, Mr. Wright? Because what it really seems like to me is you're asking for a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks for that definitive answer, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">*sigh* With a lawyer like you, Mr. Wright, even I feel bad for the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, you don't have to feel bad for her for long! I'll get it right next time, you'll see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Will it start saying something anytime soon, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ ............ ...It's not speaking up at all, is it? Maybe it's being shy?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Your evidence has said nothing at all to this court. But your choice of tactics speaks volumes about you, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Even I knew that wasn't a very smart move, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Arrrngh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Mr. Wright. Would you care to tell this court what percent sure you are of your claim?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why, of course! I'm a hundre--! Well, er... ninety... Wait, maybe eighty-ish...? W-Would you accept... fifty percent?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! I won't have such half-hearted bluffing in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Honor. Might I recommend that the defense be penalized with one-hundred-percent severity?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I intend to, Mr. Edgeworth! You can be sure of that!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... <thought>Guess I can't say I deserved zero percent of that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what do you think we should do now, Maya?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That one statement sounds awfully fishy to me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So now it's just a matter of deciding which piece of evidence to present, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. I'll take another look at the evidence and compare it to that statement, then.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So... what now?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, you can press the witness some more... ...and try and get new information out of them, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. <thought>Guess I'd better get down to pressing the witness, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Ellen Wyatt...</line>
</xml>
