<xml>
<title>Turnabout Storyteller</title>
<line speaker="???">Sh-Shisho's dead...? No... D-Do you think... HE did it?</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, no! I-If he did... then wh-what do we do?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, pull yourself together!</line>
<line speaker="???">Don't worry. I have an idea...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What the heck! Who brings a defendant to his own trial late?! Plus, the request was so last-minute, I didn't even have a chance to talk with my client!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">He's late, he's late, for a very important date!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My name is Athena Cykes. Armed with analytical psychology, and a full arsenal of legal know-how... I'm a fully-competent defender of the Wright Anything Agency! Though I wish my client would show up already -- the trial's about to start...</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh. It appears we made it just in time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Where have you BEEN?! The trial's about to start, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You needn't get so worked up, Athena. His Baldness can wait.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no way he'd wait for me! And besides, why would I want to start off on the wrong foot with him right out of the gate?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Dealing with such matters is part of being a lawyer, if I'm not mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, well, covering for your lateness is not!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Still but a rank amateur, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is Simon Blackquill. He might not look it, but he's actually a prosecutor, and a psychology specialist. He and I go way back... As for our shared specialization in psychology... ...we're both disciples of the same person so to speak, but he's kinda my senior, I guess. But twisted sense of humor or no, I wish he'd stop treating me like a child all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, where are Wright-dono and Justice-dono?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright is abroad, and Apollo is helping Trucy with her magic show. Didn't I tell you?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">They're what? So neither one of them are here? ...Leaving you to take this on alone?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yep!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ye gods... Call Wright-dono back. It's not too late.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh no, not too late at all! He would only need to know how to teleport.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tsk. Very well... Then I will settle for Justice-dono. Go grab him by the horns and drag him here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo is literally in the middle of a show, Simon! You may not want to admit it, but I've got what it takes to take on this case! Just leave this to me and go watch from the gallery!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...As your defense derails in a spectacular fashion?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No... As I win the heck out of this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">..........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll be okay -- promise! So wipe that look off your face already, will you? Anyway, I take it the guy behind you is...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, he's your... ......Tsk, he's asleep again. Hoy, Bucky! Wake up!</line>
<line speaker="???">Giyaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Owwwww... Whadja do DAT for, Simey...? *hic* ..........Hrrnhhh...? Who's dis yeller chickadee?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">She is your lawyer, such as it were. I'd say she's more "green" than "yellow" however.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Lawyer? She sure duzen't look it, dush she...? Is she, like, yer fellow apprentice or sumfin'...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Heh, something like that. I've known her longer than I've known you. You could say we're bound to one another.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Ohhhh, m'kay... Well den. Geussh I better call 'er MIZ chickadee, den.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Simon... This guy's not only rude, but he's three sheets to the wind at his own trial...</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Eh heh heh, heh... *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know we just met, but... I'm about ready to give him a piece of my mind!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do as you will. Just save it for after the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Miz Chickadee...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Don't call me that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bucky">How'd y'da...? Simey here'sh an old frienda mine... I'm the fourth-generation head chef o'"Whet Soba." "Whet Noodle No. 4," Bucky Whet! Nice to meetcha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-It's... nice to meet you, too, Mr. Whet. <thought>So he CAN pull himself together when he wants to! Grr... If only the trial wasn't starting in a few minutes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Having been accused of a murder that only occurred yesterday... ...I'm afraid it's taken a toll on the poor boy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And you happened to be there at the theater where it all happened, too, right? They said they found a rakugo storyteller murdered in his dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Indeed. The victim, master storyteller Taifu Toneido, was a long time patron of Whet Soba. Master Toneido had been looking after Bucky ever since Whet Noodle No. 3 passed away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. So the victim was kind of like a father to the defendant, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Dat shtupid ol' fart... Like a father...?! Naw way! He was alwaysh disshing my soba...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How dare you speak ill of him? Running your mouth like that is why they suspected you of his murder in the first place! Now, pull yourself together. No. 3 must be rolling in his grave.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">...B-B-But Siiiiimey... *hic* Da police... None o' dem believesh me... Dey won' lishen t'me *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>It looks like he's still in shock from the whole ordeal</thought> Don't worry, Mr. Whet. Everything's gonna be all right! I'm going to defend you with everything I've got. You're in good hands now!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Y'mean... you believe me, ma'am...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! No matter what I'll believe in you to the very end!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Gee whiz, Miz Chickadee...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Now c'mon, I need you to shape up -- just like those al dente noodles of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yesh, ma'am...! My soba ish the freshesht... *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Whet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, uh, how exactly do you know this guy?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I used to frequent Whet Soba -- and still do, in fact -- so I've known him since he was a lad. That's why his father and Master Toneido were always so good to me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I didn't know you liked soba so much, Simon.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I wouldn't expect one such as you, who eats meat slapped between slabs of bread... ...to understand the delicate taste, and the subtle textures imparted by buckwheat flour.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, that's just rude!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But I digress.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmph! I'm all about flavor and subtlety and stuff!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If I let Whet Soba end like this... ...I'll never be able to face No. 3 or Master Toneido in the next life.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, I see... And that's why you came to me! You wanted someone you could trust!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It was never my intention to ask YOU.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Grrrrr... <thought>I'll show him! I'll show him I can handle it just fine!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, I believe it's about time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! But we haven't even properly discussed the case yet!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter? You look nervous, Athena. Don't tell me you're "chickadee"-ing out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm just trembling with the excitement of battle -- that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Auf geht's! Let's do this! Come on, Mr. Whet! Get up off the floor -- we've got a case to win!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yesh, Miz Chickadee... I'm gonna do my besht... *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yello! Two bowls of noodles...? Sorry sir, no can do... Kinda busy at the courthouse... Huh? Dey, dey hung up... Eh heh. Okay! Let'sh do dish... *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...He's not going to do himself or his case any favors like this, Simon. Maybe we should let him go get some rest somewhere...?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Lemme resht? Hah! Mehbee if I were a lump o' regular flour dough fer udon noodles! But I'm fresh, like my soba! 'N y'don't let soba dough resht... 'S all about the "three freshes"! Grind da buckwheat seeds fresh, cut da dough fresh, and boil da noodles fre-- *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">H-He's blacked out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, boy. I just KNEW something like this would happen</thought> Simon, what are these "three freshes" of soba he was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">First, buckwheat seeds, or "groats," are ground to make buckwheat flour. Then dough made with the flour is cute with a large, rectangular knife into noodles. And, finally, the buckwheat noodles are boiled. Each step is done immediately, one after the other, so that the soba is fresh when eaten.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so that's what he meant. <thought>I wouldn't want him to make me any soba right now, though, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Athena, this is no time for idle chatter. You need to get into the courtroom, now. Just remember: as a prosecutor, I will be unable to lend you a hand. So don't expect any help from my quarter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There you go, treating me like I'm incompetent again! For your information, I wasn't planning on asking you for help anyway! <thought>Grrr! Just you wait, Simon! I'll show you! Mr. Wright and Apollo may not be here... ...but that's all right. I can do this on my own!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Bucky Whet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The defense is ready, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The prosecution is fully prepared, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? No prayer this time, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is correct, Your Honor. To expedite these proceedings, I completed them beforehand in the lobby.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How very thoughtful of you. By the way, what brings you back to this country?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth himself called on me to handle this case. Besides, I have a debt to repay. And though my opponent is yet a callow thing... I have no qualms with sending her down to hell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Then what is that yellow attire, if not proof of your immaturity, you small, spring chick? Now, cease your shrill chirping.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, now, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. She is still only a teenager. Please go easy on her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Great! Now even the judge is giving me the kid treatment!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Very well. Shall we begin, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm, I suppose we should. Now then, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, please give your opening statement.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'll show them what I can do! They'll be sorry they underestimated me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Certainly. Let the last rites of the victim commence. The incident is believed to have occurred at around 4 PM yesterday, May 12... at a storytellers' theater called "Kurukuru Tei." The victim was a great master of the Toneido school of "rakugo," or "comedic storytelling." His name was Taifu Toneido. The scene of the murder was the theater's dressing room. It is accessible via the stall entrance hallway, and has an inner and outer sliding door.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The estimated time of death is between 2 PM and 5 PM. The cause of death is suffocation, though how the victim suffocated is yet to be determined. The autopsy report found nothing unusual in his lungs or stomach, and there is no murder weapon. I will now submit the incident report to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! How can you name Mr. Whet as the culprit... when you don't know how the victim was killed -- or even with what?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">While it is true that the weapon and precise method are, as yet, unknown... the accused is the only one who had the opportunity to commit the murder. I will explain this assertion in further detail as we continue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ugh. I guess this means he has some kind of evidence to present...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, would the accused care to plead his case?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Come to think of it, where IS the defendant, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry, Your Honor. But I'm afraid Mr. Whet isn't feeling very well, and is resting in the infirmary.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Surely it is the lack of a clear conscience that impedes him from facing this court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Great. Starting off on the wrong foot already...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Mr. Whet is the head chef of a soba shop frequented by the victim. On the day of the incident, Mr. Whet went to the theater at the victim's request. Taifu Toneido was a connoisseur of soba. As you can see in these photographs... he was apparently making soba himself in his dressing room that very day. The soba found at the scene is likely the soba he himself made there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Liking soba is one thing, but making it in a theater dressing room's a bit much, non?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Master Toneido truly had a passion for soba, didn't he? For a man like that to be murder by a soba chef is simply unthinkable.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And yet, the accused had ample motive. For in the victim's safe, we discovered the deed to the accused's shop. Mr. Whet was to inherit Whet Soba when he lost his father recently. However, it's believed the victim stole the shop's deed during the transfer process. The prosecution believes the accused killed the victim in order to get the deed back.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... A murder over the deed to a shop... That does sound like a plausible motive.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So THAT'S what this case is about... I wish Simon had filled me in a little better... I could've contributed more than just a thousand buckets of cold sweat if he had...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Defense. From your demeanor, I gather you know very little about the details of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You are dishonoring the soul of the victim by appearing in the courtroom unprepared. You are an embarrassment to your profession, you putrid egg yolk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! I-I'm sorry! <thought>Apollo's a "red pepper," and now, I'm an "egg yolk"?! We've only just started and I've already been demoted from "spring chick"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I am ready to call my witness, Your Honor. Let us listen to the words of one who was present when the crime was discovered.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Someone who was there when the victim's body was found?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Witness, please take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Simon Blackquill... Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Prosecutor Blackquill! You didn't tell me you were going to take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There simply wasn't time.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What a shame, Prosecutor Blackquill. Had you shared the damning scene you witnessed beforehand with the defense... we could've moved this trial along, and saved the victim's soul that much faster.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>"D-Damning scene"...? What in the world did Simon see?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, was it? Before I give my testimony, there's something I'd like to confirm.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">By all means.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This case involves "rakugo," a very traditional form of Japanese comedic storytelling. Do you have enough knowledge of this art form to handle the case competently?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you implying that I am not qualified for this case?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Not yet -- I am simply trying to ascertain your familiarity with the topic... for now.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is the prosecutor's duty to learn the background of any case he takes on. I did some rakugo last night, and have grasped the overall idea of it.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How much could you possibly grasp in a single night?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Rakugo is a form of entertaining storytelling that originated in the land of Japan. In it, the storyteller sits alone on the stage, with only a fan and a towel as... and the rakugo artist tells long, whimsical stories, giving each character a distinct voice. This traditional art was originally invented by monks to make sermons more interesting. Are you satisfied? If not, I could explain the twelve types of endings to such stories... or shall I perform the famous story of Jugemu instead?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Augh! I-It appears you have put in a bit of study...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your acknowledgement is most welcome, Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can see why you are know for being quite thorough in your research, prosecutor. Now, I would love to see you perform that story you mentioned, if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If that is Your Honor's request... Jugemu, Jugemu--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, right! Of course. I nearly forgot!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Seriously? Of all the things for you to forget...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem! Now then, back to the case. Prosecutor Blackquill. Please tell the court what you witnessed.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I went to the theater yesterday, and arrived at... approximately 4 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Now, wait just a minute here, Prosecutor Blackquill! W-With a testimony like that... you're practically accusing Mr. Whet of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">All I can do is state what I saw. I can't help how it appears. But a "qualified and capable attorney" such as you should be able to dispatch with it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, yeah, duh! <thought>A-All right. I guess I'd better start by getting all the info out of him that I can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I went to the theater yesterday, and arrived at... approximately 4 PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I went because I had received an invitation from Master Toneido. Here, see for yourself. It was a special show commemorating his junior disciple Uendo's promotion. It was also an occasion to announce the boy's succession to the stage name of "Uendo II."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, so what exactly does it mean to "succeed to a stage name"?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You really don't know, do you? In the performing arts, a name succession is when an artist inherits a predecessor's name.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. So there was another "Uendo" rakugo artist before, and this disciple succeeded him, huh. And what did your invitation say?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It contained a simple letter of salutations and an outline of the show's program.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Oh! It appears Taifu Toneido was going to perform "Tokisoba," or "Time Soba." He's famous for his masterful pantomime of eating soba, using only his fan as a prop. And Uendo was to peform "Soba Sei," or "Soba Glutton." A soba-themed show, I see!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It seems you know a thing or two about rakugo yourself, Your Baldness. The first to perform was the senior disciple, Geiru, followed by Uendo... and, lastly, Master Toneido.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. So that's why you happened to be at the storytellers' theater yesterday. So what happened after you arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I went straight to Master Toneido's dressing room to say hello.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I went with the intention of greeting him, but ultimately, we didn't actually meet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You didn't see him? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Geiru escorted me to the dressing room... but we heard the sound of rakugo being performed from within. Thinking the master was rehearsing, we decided to wait in the hall until he was done.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You heard rakugo being performed in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes. Not just me, but Geiru as well.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In other words, you can confirm that the victim was still alive at around 4 PM?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Correct. I couldn't hear him clearly through the doors, but I'm sure it was Master Toneido. I could tell because it was "Time Soba" routine being performed in there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... So that means the victim was killed sometime after that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bucky went into the dressing room thereafter, only to come storming out a while later.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Geriu and I were waiting in the hallway for Master Toneido to finish practicing... when Bucky appeared and entered the dressing room with his thing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What happened after that?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We heard what sounded like Bucky shouting inside the room. About ten minutes later, Bucky came back out of the dressing room looking rather irate.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyura">This is most likely when the murder was committed. The victim was an elderly man. It would've been entirely possible to kill within the span of ten minutes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Arngh...! I'd better come up with some kind of counterargument, and fast!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Master Toneido's junior disciple, Uendo, apparently then entered the room soon after.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No, I couldn't. I wasn't able to see the dressing room door from where I was standing at the time. But Geiru was right in front of it, so I'm sure she saw it all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see. And why do you suppose Uendo went to the dressing room anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">He had just finished his routine, so he was making a courtesy call. A disciple is to pay their master respect tight before and after each performance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And all disciples are expected to do this?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, it's common courtesy among rakugo artists.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. Could you tell us what happened after Uendo went into the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Certainly.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That's when Uendo discovered Master Toneido's body.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">After Uendo had been in the dressing for two or three minutes... we heard a scream from inside the room, and Uendo came flying out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you hear any signs of a struggle at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No, just Uendo's woeful scream.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Simon has no reason to lie, but I also don't have much to go on. I'd better ask all the questions I can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Thank you, Prosecutor Blackquill. And now, please allow me to summairze your testimony. While Prosecutor Blackquill and Geiru were in the hallway waiting for Master Toneido... the accused came along and entered the dressing room with some items in tow. He was heard shouting for a time inside the dressing room. About ten minutes later, he came back out of the room, seeming rather angry. A short time after the accused had come and gone, Uendo Toneido went into the room. A few minutes later, after having discovered the victim's body, Uendo gave a scream... and came running out into the hallway from within. Prosecutor Blackquill and Geiru then ran into the room and saw the body for themselves. From the circumstances, it is quite clear that the accused murdered the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This is crucial testimony indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Defense. An eyewitness has given conclusive testimony. Why not let it all go now, and allow the victim his last rites?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Not on your life! If Uendo went into the dressing, too, and was the first to discover the body... then who's to say HE didn't commit the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Uendo was in the dressing room for a mere two, perhaps three minutes. He could not have possibly committed the murder in that time, nor without making any noise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Ooh, Simon! Why did you have to give that awful testimony!</thought> Prosecutor Blackquill! Can't you give me something a little better to work with here?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Isn't it up to you to ask the right questions? I am certainly willing to tell you all that I know. So, if you are truly capable as you claim, then draw out what you need yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is no time for your twisted games, Prosecutor Blackquill! Just admit that you don't remember it all that well!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How dare you treat me like some evil spirit to be exorcised. I'll remember this, you blackguard...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't worry, Prosecutor Blackquill. I've got this!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Would I have my way, he would not be the only one here to step down... you half-boiled, putrid egg yolk!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Eww... I object to the notion that I'm a gooey, smelly mess!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Prosecutor Blackquill's testimony was like the lowly opening act of a rakugo show. He may hold the title "prosecutor," but this time, he stood on the side of the defense. To restore balance to this trial, I would like to present an actual witness for the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who is this witness?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The person who was with Prosecutor Blackquill when the body was discovered. She is another entertainer of the Toneido School: Ms. Geiru Toneido.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please state your name and occupation, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Hello, everyone! I'm here to represent the Toneido School with a twisty, twist, twiist! And BLOOOON! There you have it! A stunning balloon hat! It's me! The balloon artist you all know and love, Geeeiru Toneidoooo! Just call me Geiru, sweetie! One, two... BLOOOON!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What a way to capture your audience's attention! I daresay I can't take my eyes off those balloons.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please tell me you're talking about the hat, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Oh Mister Judgey! I'm so glad you liked my performance! Would you consider joining my fan club, pwetty pwease?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, absolutely!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And please save your fanboying for after the trial, Your Honor... Anyway, Geiru... I can't help but notice, you seem awfully cheerful for having just lost your master.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Of course I'm sad... But Shisho would scold me if I didn't put on a big smile. Never show sadness! Smile, smile, smile! With a twisty, twist, twiiist! And BLOOOON! There you have it! One gorgeous cake!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see. I guess an entertainer's gotta do what an entertain's gotta do... <thought>Her balloon art's worse than a Rorschach test. All I saw was a severed monster head...</thought> Geiru, you're obvious a balloon artist. So how did you come to be a member of a rakugo school?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, my father -- my late father, that is -- was a rakugo artist, you see... So I joined the Toneido School to be just like my daddy someday!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">My father and I owe so much to Shisho, our master! But that Bucky Whet... Oooooh, how could he?! I want to see him pay for what he's done as quickly as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your distress is entirely understandable. And my condolences for your loss.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">And, and, not only that, but he...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You have more to say about Mr. Whet?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Every time he comes to deliver soba to us, he yells at me! He always tells me to "get away!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is there any reason why he would say such a thing to you?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">He says the smell of my perfume will get into his soba and ruin it! Like, how can he say that?! This is a greaaaat scent!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph! How very rude of him. I don't blame you for being upset.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Excuse me, Your Honor! But please don't let Geiru's "balloons" bias your judgement! Mr. Whet hasn't been proven guilty yet, remember?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. It will be interesting to see how long that fire of yours will last, defense. Now then Geiru. Please share the truth with this court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes Geiru. Your testimony please.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">From 4 PM to a little after 4:20 PM, when Shisho's body was found...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Prosecutor Blackquill, do you have any objections to this witnesses's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">........No. Tsk! Make up your bloody mind, Sad Monk Sahdmadhi. First you exorcise me, now this.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. You only do as you are instructed by this humble servant of the Holy Mother. As there are no objections, Your Honor, let us move on to the salvation of the victim's soul.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is a passage in the sacred scriptures of Khura'inism. "To stir the wind is beyond the power of a spring chick." In other words, the inexperienced are useless. With that in mind, it seemed more judicious to consult with Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ha ha ha! He doesn't even see you as an adversary Cykes-dono!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I won't let either one of you insult me! I'll show you I'm no inexperienced "spring chick"! Your Honor! I'm ready to cross-examine the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I hope you can make Prosecutor Sahdmadhi see you as a worthy adversary, Ms. Cykes. I'll allow your cross-examination, so you'd better strike while the iron is hot!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">From 4PM to a little after 4:20 PM, when Shisho's body was found...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I don't know... I mean, what do you want me to saaay? That's what happened, y'know? Isn't that right, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes. Geiru and I can both confirm that Master Toneido still lived at around 4PM.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, yeah... You can, can't you?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Seeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Simon and I were standing in the hallway in front of the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Of course! O-Or are you insinuating... that I was daydreaming or sleeping while standing up or something?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, of course not...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I saw everything, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">F-Fine. <thought>So you say, anyway. But did you really?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Before Uendo discovered the body, the only person who had gone in there was Bucky.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">That's right! That's why it must've been Bucky who... who killed poor Shishooo...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, let's take a deep breath, okay, Geiru? So not a single person set foot into the dressing room during that time?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I already told you over and over, didn't I? There was nobody else.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I must apologize on the lawyer's behalf. Even her memory is that of a spring chick's. Please overlook her transgression as best as you can.</line>
<line speaker="Geriu">Oh, I see... Poor thing! Hang in there, sweetie!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hey! Who are you calling a birdbrain, buddy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Come to think of it, a little while before Bucky showed up, Jugemu was barking like mad!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Thats my doggie! I keep him at the theater. Let's see... With a twisty, twist, twiiist! And BLOOOON! There you have it! My cute widdle Judgemu!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's... kinda creepy-looking...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Oh, but he's a really, really good boy!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And why was Jugemu barking? Do you think it's because he saw someone suspicious? If so, then we'd have a new suspect in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Hmm... Now, why he was barking again...? Oh, I remember! Because it was time for me to feed him! So I went into his yard and gave him some food.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Nope, the door out into the yard was wiiide open. I would've seen if anybody went into the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Blackquill, come down to the stand for a sec... please!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How many times must I do this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You saw what Geiru was talking about, right? So why didn't you mention it before?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! I can't be expected to remember every minute detail!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, remember them now -- please! Did Geiru go out into the yard?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes. I remember now that she went to feed Jugemu. And I saw her looking towards the dressing room quite frequently as well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you recall anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It looked as though she were feeding the dog a great quality of dumplings or something. Jugemu couldn't finish them all, so he buried the rest in a corner of the yard. That's about all I can remember.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... It looks like Geiru was telling the truth.</thought> Your Honor, I'd like Geiru's last statement added to her testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As you wish, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Change this statement to">"I was in the yard, but the door was wide open, so I could keep watch on the dressing room."</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I was in the yard, but the door was wide open, so I could keep watch on the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, okay, so I did go out into the yard, but it was just for a second. And the yard door was wide open, so I could still see the dressing room the whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The door was open, so she could still see the dressing room?</thought> Prosecutor Blackquill, I need you on the stand again -- please!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What am I, your lady-in-waiting?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you remember anything about the time Geiru was in the yard?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Simply that Jugemu buried the food he couldn't finish in a corner of the yard. That's about all I can remember.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you. <thought>I didn't really need to her about the dog again, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">When I finished feeding Jugemu, I returned to the hallway. And then, I saw Bucky go into the dressing room! No question about it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Okay, so, around the time of the murder... Geiru and Simon were hanging out just outside the dressing room. Guess I'm going to have to find a flaw in there somehow if I want to get anywhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, you were able to keep an eye on the dressing room while you were out in the yard. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">That's right. The door out into the yard was wide open.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, but that makes zero sense. Take a look at this diagram of the backstage area. There is a clear contradiction between this diagram and the witnesses's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh...? I'm afraid I don't understand, Ms. Cykes. Please point out what contradicts the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I'm afraid I don't see anything contradictory about that spot, either. A heavy penalty for lightweight thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Urk. I-I promise to point out the contradiction this time, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Now then...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru was in the yard near the doghouse. Prosecutor Blackquill even saw her there. And while she was there, the door to the yard had been left open.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah! I see!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, if the door to the yard was "wide open," as Geiru said... it would've blocked her view, making it impossible for her to see the dressing room!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">What?! No waaay!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But even if there were admittedly a few moments Geiru was not keeping watch... how much would that really affect this case?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It would greatly affect the case! From the spot Prosecutor Blackquill stood, he couldn't see the dressing room door, either. Anyone could have entered the dressing room during that time without being seen!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru, why did you try to hide the fact that you weren't watching the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">What? I-I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well... I... I was so shocked by what happened I was just confused, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Even though she is trying to keep up a brave front as an entertainer... the truth is that she is being torn apart by grief. For her mind to be in turmoil is hardly unexpected.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, it must be very difficult, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">To a disciple, one's master is akin to a real parent. Surely, her shock is immense. The way this lawyer tries to pin the blame on this poor soul at first opportunity... All I can say is... defense attorneys are heartless creatures indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I wasn't...! That was't what I was trying to do...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Is it beyond your comprehension, defense? Your unskilled argument is scarring this witness even further. And is we ask the people of this courtroom, I am sure they would agree.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! The gallery doesn't get a say in this!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you afraid to find out that they think ill of you? Or perhaps you are in the wrong? Listen to them now with that keen sense of hearing you are so proud of.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">He's right. That was harsh. She didn't have to go that far!I feel kind of sorry for the witness... And why is the lawyer's outfit so yellow?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No... I was just trying... to find the truth... <thought>Why is the whole gallery siding with Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The people understand... They know what is right, and what is wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">That lawyer's still in training, isn't she? Why is she all by herself?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I hear the voices of the gallery... I can hear the voices of their hearts...! It's so intense... I feel so alone up here, fighting by myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you afraid, child? It is ludicrous to come to a trial with such paltry preparation of the soul! I command you to leave this courtroom at once!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>B-But I can't give up... I have to... I have to... keep pressing on...</thought> As long as there was a moment when nobody was watching the dressing room door... the defendant can't be convicted solely on Prosecutor Blackquill and Geiru's testimonies!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. Even now, you would continue to resist? You are childish in defeat as well, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not out for the count yet, buster! I'm just getting started!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Despite your posturing, is it not true that your resolve could crumble at any moment? With a little push, you would surely succumb to despair. A little push such as with this piece of conclusive evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"C-conclusive evidence," huh?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That is correct. We found a critical piece of evidence at the scene of the crime: The victim's dying message, which clearly implicates the accused, Bucky Whet! Look at these Japanese playing cards -- known as "karuta" -- lined up on the table. These special English-version karuta cards spell out a message. That message: "WHET NO 4."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"WHET NO 4" ...? Y-You mean, "Whet Noodle No. 4"?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, "Whet Noodle No. 4," as the fourth head chef of Whet Soba is also known. The message points to none other than the accused, Bucky Whet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Noooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That makes perfect sense, doesn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Wow! Great job, Mr. Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh, no! This is really, really bad! What do I do, what do I do?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Would you still carry on your futile fight in the face of this irrefutable evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You can say whatever you want, but we won't know until we--</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It is cruel to give the accused false hope. You will only compound his suffering. Wise people of the courtroom, do you not agree?</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">He's right. It's cruel to make him suffer when there's conclusive evidence. What an incompetent newb! I feel bad for the victim AND the defendant!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wh-What?! But I'm trying to prove Mr. Wher's innocence here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I know you can hear them, defense. Their voice implore you to save the accused's soul. It is time for you to let it go, and move on, you inexperienced lawyer. You lack the competence with which to accomplish anything meaningful here!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I-Is he right? Is this too much for me to handle on my own?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gallery">What good is she doing anybody? She should just quit right now!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Grrnngh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, defense. Leave everything to this humble servant of the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Simon...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And you fopdoodles in the gallery! Can't a man watch a trial in peace?! This inexperienced amateur is about to turn the trial around!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Does that prosecutor really think she can turn things around...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The mood in this courtroom is starting to change!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill! What are you doing at the defense's bench?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I grew bored of watching from the gallery. Besides, if I were to leave this trial to this spring chick... and lose my favorite soba shop in the process, I will be quite cross.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You voluntarily stand on the side of impurity and sin? Truly, what a fool you are.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">To think, you were so easily manipulated by his parlor tricks... What happened to "qualified and capable," Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I just let my guard down a little bit! But it won't happen again!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Then gird up your loins, and steel yourself for battle!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not girding up anything in this skirt! But I AM ready to get serious!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It seems there is now yet another soul I must cast down into hell...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I was in prison for a long time. And "hell" sounds no worse than "cell," to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah, but the fires of hell will not be the end of your suffering. For the sin you have just committed, you shall surely be reborn as a panda in your next life. A white and black, reverse panda, that is. And you shall be put in a zoo, to be exposed to public ridicule.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A threat like that won't work on Prosecutor Blackquill! After all, he's already used to looking like a panda in THIS life!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Who are you calling a panda?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see that you are both prepared to face the fires of damnation. Geiru, thank you for your service. You may step down now.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Okey-dokey! Bye-bye-ballooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Does EVERYTHING have to be about balloons with her...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Now, then. I have a witness prepared to testify about the karuta cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And who is the witness this time?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The first to discover the body, and someone who witnessed the crime scene firsthand. Mr. Uendo Toneido. The time has come for that ponytailed pair over there to finally let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let's bring in this witness, then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness, please state your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I am the rakugo storyteller Uendo Toneido. Even if my performance isn't worth watching, I will certainly watch my words. I wouldn't want to say anything thoughtless and get arrested. After all, that'd be... a "raku-no-no"! Hee hee! Thank you, everybody! Good night!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Oh, my, my! Are you a fan of mine, miss? Would you like my autograph? One moment...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ow! What do you think you're doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">No need to stand on ceremony! My fan deserves a fan, after all. A "fan" for a "fan"! Nice one! Hee hee! Oh, why if it isn't Simon! How are you on this fine day, sir? Quite a dilly of a pickle we've found ourselves in, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't believe I've ever seen you talk quite so much, Uendo.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Never performed in a place like this, y'know. I got butterflies here, can't you see? Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Why do I always get the weird ones?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pardon me, witness. As much as I enjoy your banter, I believe we had better return to the case at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Ah, I suppose you're right. In that "case"... I was promoted to "futatsume" yesterday, and received the stage name "Uendo." The show was our way of celebrating my new name and "middle rank" standing! Hee! And then THAT happened... Haah... I never dreamed something like that'd happen, not in a million years. And just as I got my chance to start repaying my debt to Shisho, too... Yeah... Plus, I'm worried about Geiru... The way she clung to Shisho... Poor thing. I told her to keep a stiff upper lip... Stiff like rigor mortis... Keep telling those lame jokes, and Shisho'll come scold you from the grave! I wouldn't mind getting yelled at, you know, if it meant seeing him again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo, please... As charming as your various characters are, this isn't a rakugo stage.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let us hear your testimony now, witness. Tell the court about the evidence left at the scene -- the proof of the accused's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I noticed Shisho's dying message right away.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! That was certainly a more entertaining testimony than usual. The variety of characters performed by the witness was absolutely splendid!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But he shouldn't be performing any characters in the first place, Your Honor! And, Uendo! The murder weapon hasn't been determined yet! So how can you say that the victim was drowned in soba broth?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">It's obvious. All you have to do is look at the crime scene. He was found with his face shoved in a bowl. It's only natural to assume he was drowned in the broth for noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Except we're not here to assume things, Uendo, so please stick to just the facts!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">My, my! It's so like a soba chef to kill someone this way, wouldn't you say? And with the karuta message he left behind, it's clear Bucky Whet did it!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Setting aside the issue of the murder weapon for now... that dying message certainly does seem to be irrefutable evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Indeed. It proves the absolute guilt of the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Urgh... Even I've gotta admit that I can't see how that message could mean anything else...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Bucky used soba for the deed, all to get back the soba shop deed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nngh! <thought>This testimony makes Mr. Whet look super guilty. I have to do something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. That's his "conclusive evidence"? What a farce!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's this? I thought you said you weren't planning on asking me for help?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arngh...! I did, and I won't, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Simon must've found an inconsistency in the testimony. I'd better listen carefully, and try to see what he found!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I noticed Shisho's dying message right away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, it was a coded message right there next to the body. I'm sure anybody would've thought that they were  there to name his killer. I love murder mysteries, and often watch them on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh? I see.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I saw a similar scene during a murder mystery marathon last Tuesday. That's what made me think, "This must be a dying message!"</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">The stiff cards were right next to the stiff, you see?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">As I said, the stiff cards were right there next to the stiff, so they were hard to miss.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But wouldn't it have been more natural to notice the victim rather than the cards?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">The message just caught my eye, because the stiff cards were right next to the stiff.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, but the fact hardly seems significant enough to make a person take not of them.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Stiff cards... next to the stiff...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So basically, there was no real reason for them to catch your eye, was there?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Hey now, enough with the silly puns already! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But look at all these wonderful people in the audience! It's only natural for an entertainer to want them to have some fun! Hee hee! I guess we can let a few jokes slide, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, the inevitable bleeding of your work into other areas of your life. I know how that is. I find myself being unwittingly judgemental in my personal life, too.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Right, right! That's exactly what I'm talking about! Well done, Your Honor! Guess you can't judge a judge by his cover!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho. I advise the defense not to be so critical of the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Much obliged! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Anyway, I got the meaning right away. I knew it must've been talking about Bucky!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">There's only one "Whet Noodle" around here, and you've seen that giant "4" on his back. It's the only interpenetration that makes sense!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I guess so... But wait a minute!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Wh-What is it?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What if there's another "Whet Noodle" in the area! Wh-What? Did I say something strange?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bucky is the sole heir to the shop. So enough with the ludicrous straw grasping!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Hey! How was I supposed to know...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just listen to the testimony again, and find the glaring inconsistency.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That was the master's final message, left as he was drowning in soba broth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I know Shisho. He would never let someone get the last word on him, even in death. With his face in soba broth, and his consciousness fading away... he left a message that pointed toward Bucky as he left this world. It's the only way it could've happened!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait! "The only way"?! Now you're just speculating!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Look, a dying message is something you leave as you're dying, right? I saw a scene like that in a detective show.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Uendo, we have a saying in my country: "Silence is more precious than diamonds." Please do not speak any more than is necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But talking is my livelihood, you know. I talk all the time. This and that, truths and untruths... I can't stop myself from talking!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hopefully, he'll stick to "truths" without any of those "untruths"...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">It's so like Shisho not to write Bucky's name outright. "Plain and simple" wasn't his style.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Even in the throes of death, it was in Shisho's nature to throw in a twist somehow. Truly the consummate entertainer till the very end, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Was he really that great of a man, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It would've been no easy task, to be sure. But who knows? He wasn't an entertainer for fifty-five years for nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">If I ever bite the big one like that... I wanna leave a dying message as good as Shisho's! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, let's hope it never comes to that...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Simon, are all rakugo artists like this?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It's hard to say. It could simply be the eccentricity of an entertainer, or perhaps he's hiding something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Well, he doesn't have to entertain people in a court of law. And if he IS trying to hide something, maybe it'll show up as a contradiction or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's a contradiction in Uendo's testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And would you care to explain where, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Certainly, Your Honor. According to the autopsy report, nothing unusual was found in the victim's lungs.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, yes. It does say that, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If he HAD drowned in a bowl of soba, then there should've been soba broth in his lungs! But since there wasn't any... it means the victim was suffocated with something other than soba broth!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Pyoooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is the contradiction you noticed, isn't it, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. Not bad. Not bad at all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh heh. I guess I showed you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But if drowning in the soba broth WASN'T the cause of death... then when was the victim's face thrust into that bowl?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Taifu Toneido's face was thrust into the bowl...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The culprit first shoved the victim's face into the bowl, and then murdered him.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...And for what reason, may I ask?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uhh, well... they did it on a whim!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And you have proof of this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... Well... it's certainly not impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Enough of the runaround, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Argh... Well, if it wasn't BEFORE the murder, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The culprit killed the victim... while holding the victim's face in the bowl!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You just claimed the victim was "suffocated with something other than soba broth." And yet, he could only have suffocated from the broth had his face been in the bowl.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Now I'm all confused...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"I'm all confused"?! is that all you have to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Well, that cleared my mind right up... Okay, if it wasn't DURING the murder then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because no soba broth was discovered in the victim's lungs... his head would've been placed into the bowl AFTER he was killed! And that's when the soba broth must've been spilled onto the karuta cards. In other words, the victim could NOT have lined up the cards as he was drowning!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. So it was done AFTER he was already dead... But why would the culprit do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... I'm afraid I don't know yet.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What, and I supposed YOU know why?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Of course. Desecrating the body in that manner... indicates a strong sense of enmity on the part of the perpetrator.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that does make sense... It certainly paints a clear picture of the culprits intense feelings toward the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Feelings of resentment over the theft of the soba shop deed, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Just great. Now the judge has an even more unfavorable impression of Bucky!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Good point... The cards WERE right in front of his body, after all... Rationally speaking, there's no way the culprit could've missed that, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">M-Me?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You saw the karuta cards firsthand, did you not? Would you care to tell us about them in a bit more detail? Those tiny crime scene photos show us precious little of what I wish to know.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, those cards are from Shisho's special "Soba Scenes of Tokyo Past" set. Each card is related in some way to soba.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Spare me the history lesson! Just tell me how the cards looked at the scene, and no more!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, uh, there was soba broth spilled all over them...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's not much help, I'm afraid. Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, do you have a photo that shows the cards more clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............I do. Please accept this meager offering, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my. What delightful-looking cards!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Well, well. Tearing Prosecutor Sad Monk's "conclusive evidence" apart should be a breeze with this.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't tell me you haven't noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Don't be silly! Of course I have! <thought>...Not noticed anything. But I can't exactly say that now, can I...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, do you really see a problem with the prosecution's claim about these cards?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, go on, then.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-All right... <thought>It's do or die...! All I have to do is study the picture and...</thought> These cards...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">These cards contain a contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do they? And what exactly is this "contradiction" you speak of?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Oh... Well... You know... Stuuuuuuuff...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe this will stuff some knowledge in that noggin of yours!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I may have said that the accused was not rational at the time of the crime... but it appears that the defense is rational at no time whatsoever.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arngh... Please let me try again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">These cards are a kind of riddle revolving around the number four. "Knock, knock. Who's there? Four. four who?"</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I do hope there is a punch line.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"'Four goodness sake, open the door!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Not bad, defense. But please allow me these four words.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Certainly, Your Honor. What are they?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's that riddle "four"?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arngh... Please let me try again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">These cards were rearranged!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But how can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please take a good look at these cards, Your Honor. The answer is right in front of us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Where exactly should we be looking, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Each and every picture is related to soba in some way. This can't be mere coincidence!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">-*sigh* As was stated by Uendo... this set is called "Soba Scenes of Tokyo Past," and was designed by the victim. So it is quite natural that each card would be related to soba in some way.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You'd better believe this penalty is not "mere coincidence," either, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yikes! <thought>How are these cards natural in any way?!</thought> Fine. Let's take another look at these cards then, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, all these cards are... exactly the same size, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes. Yes, they are. And I have to wonder, defense, if your brain is the same size as these cards?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, Your Honor. Let's just take another look at these cards, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please focus your attention on the soba broth stains on these cards. The outline of these stains don't match up with the larger stain on the table.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, would you look at that! You're absolutely right! And...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please recall that the soba broth was spilled and got on the cards AFTER the murder... when the victim's face was placed in the bowl.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, go on.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By the stains, we can see that the culprit deliberately rearranged the cards after that. In other words... this message was altered in order to pin the crime on my client!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?! Th-Then, if we put the cards back in their original positions...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We can restore the evidence, and see who the cards were really pointing toward!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's true!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Pohlkun--!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then what are we waiting for?! Let's do this! <thought>All I have to do is rearrange the cards so that the stains match up!</thought> Let's see. Where was this "W" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Perfect! Okay. The "H" card is next. Let's see. Where was this "H" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes! Now the "E" card! Let's see. Where was this "E" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A perfect match! Next up is the "T" card. Let's see. Where was this "T" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Great! That fits right in there! Now the "N" card. Let's see. Where was this "N" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There! That looks good. Now "O"! Let's see. Where was this "O" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nice! Almost done now! The last card is "4." Let's see. Where was this "4" card originally?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Hmph. The stains don't match up if you place that card there. How can you not see that? Are those ridiculous bangs obscuring your vision?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you don't have to be so rude about it! Ugh, whatever. I'll try again...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the message "WHET NO 4"... was originally supposed to say "OWEN 4TH"! And this original message is our clue to the identity of the true culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh! That indignant look on Prosecutor Sad Monk's face is positively priceless!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This is absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">It wasn't "WHET NO 4"? Maybe the lawyer is smarter than we thought!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! Well! I never would've imagined that there was more to these cards than meets the eye!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So now that that's settled... what does this "OWEN 4TH" mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Wait. Am I...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Who else do you suppose is to provide an explanation?! Of course it's you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But I hadn't thought that far yet...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Change the cards around all you'd like, but if you cannot explain what the message means... then it is as worthless as you are, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Nooooooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And so the spring chick that fancies itself as a graceful swan is brought back down to Earth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I have to do something! But what?!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Still your thoughts for a second. There's a perfectly good witness to question over there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! Right! That's a good idea! <thought>Come on, Athena! Get ahold of yourself!</thought> Uendo, does the phrase "OWEN 4TH" mean anything to you?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">No. There's no one named "Owen" in the Toneido family, or our circle of friends. Go ahead, ask anybody you'd like!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can't be serious...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Having rummaged through you empty mind, I see you have, as expected, turned up nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquil">Tsk. Why didn't you point that out eariler if you already knew?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry. In any case, there were two opportunities for someone to rearrange the cards. The first was when Mr. Whet entered the dressing room...and the second was when Uendo discovered the body.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Are you accusing me of rearranging the cards? ME, who came to testify out of the goodness of my heart?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, you didn't exactly come running out screaming straight away, did you? Even a mere two to three minutes is more than enough time to get up to some devilry. So what exactly were you doing in there, Uendo?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">*sip* *sip*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Put down the tea, and spit out your answer!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Eep! M-Mr. Prosecutor! What's a guy supposed to do at a time like this?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">"Silence is more precious than diamonds," witness. Therefore, you need only remain silent. The defense is devious. They are waiting for you to make a slip of the tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Oh, I see. So that's what you're after, is it? In that case...Your Honor, I've decided not to say another word.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Very good. After all, your right to remain silent is protected by law.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, Prosecutor Blackquill? Any other brilliant ideas you'd like to share?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh heh heh... Ha ha ha ha ha! Did you hear that, Cykes-dono? A rakugo artist who's afraid to speak! Who's ever heard of such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Are you trying to taunt him into talking? Such a petty trick will never work.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's right. I'm not going to fall for it.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'm only asking to hear your story. Besides, is it not your job to tell tales if there is an audience to listen?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">E-Even so, I have a right to refuse to answer.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The more you keep quiet, the more we want you to talk. That's simply human nature. Isn't that right, people of the gallery?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...........</line>
<line speaker="Blackquil">Even with this wonderful audience in front of you, you still refuse to talk? If so, then perhaps you chose the wrong line of work, my friend!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Are you saying I should quit?! Because I'm not afraid to speak my mind, I'm have you know. Oh, no! Never mind what I just said! It IS scary to talk! It's absolutely terrifying! But, no! As a rakugo artist, I must talk! If I don't, how can I ever show my face on stage again?! Your Honor, I'm ready to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>H-He did it! He managed to convince Uendo with the power of suggestion technique!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Bully for you, Uendo! That's as a REAL rakugo artist should be!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-All right... If the witness wishes to testify, then by all means, please do.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">To be turned by such an obvious ploy... What a man of weak spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">From what I can tell, there do not appear to be any inconsistencies in the testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Of course there aren't any. Because I'm not trying to hide anything.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's right. I don't see anything inconsistent, either. But I did pick up on some faint discord in Uendo's heart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. Ponder all you would like, defense, but it is pointless. Your Honor. I believe there is no need for further deliberation...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Are you saying... what I think you're saying, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor! The defense would like to conduct a quick therapy session on this witness!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">It's fine by me! I have nothing to hide. Bring it on!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Impetuous fool! Why will you not listen to the guidance of this humble servant of the Holy Mother?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the witness wishes to proceed, I see no problem, Prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh heh heh. In one ear and out the other. It seems this performer has no need for your so-called "guidance," Prosecutor Sad Monk.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Just know this Uendo: your folly will surely earn you divine retribution.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Simon! I'm going to make the most of this opportunity you created for me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. Just keep your wits about you. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I will! Uendo, could you tell us again about what happened in the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I called to him from outside the room...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...but he didn't reply.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I entered the dressing room, I saw Shisho slumped over the table, motionless!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I didn't really notice any unexpected emotions in that testimony...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But it isn't always a question of the presence of an emotional response, but the absence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know... You're right. <thought>It's not always the emotions I do see. Sometimes, It's a matter of what I don't, but would expect so see... I'd better carefully compare Uendo's statements to his emotions again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo, I'm noticing something strange with these emotions.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">"Some thin stranger with cheesy toe skin," you say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! "Something strange with these emotions"! How could you have heard "some thin stranger with cheesy toe skin"?! </line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I don't know. Maybe it's me who's got some cheese in my ears...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Did he will the floor to open up and swallow his cushions out of shame for that bad joke?</thought> The point I'm trying to make is that I noticed something unexpected in your emotions! Now stop hiding and come out where we can see you!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff, please bring the witness a few replacement cushions.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">So what was this unexpected thing you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, come on! His Honor said a few cushions -- not a few dozen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that we've all had a good laugh, please continue, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Who's laughing?! Argh! Focus, Athena! Don't let yourself get rattled!</thought> When you entered the room and saw your master slumped motionless over the table... you weren't the least bit shocked, Uendo. Don't you think that's a little odd?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I-Is it, though?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The lack of surprise means you were prepared for what you saw. <thought>And I think I know why... The reason Uendo wasn't shaken when he saw his masters dead body is because...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe you weren't shaken because you were zoned out!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Yeah, you got me! I'm a total space case! Ha ha ha! Well, get your head out of the clouds and go do some work for a change! Don't worry, honey! I found a wallet the other day. We have plenty of money to live in now!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Correct me if I'm wrong, Simon, but did he just start doing a routine?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes. I believe he's telling the famous "Shibahama Fishmonger" story. It seems your answer lulled him into such a sense of security that he's zoning YOU out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A penalty for our spacey defense attorney!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe you weren't shaken because you are an entertainer. Entertainers gotta have guts!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Sadly, I busted a gut laughing at Shisho's bits last week. Now I'm practically gutless... Does my tale of woe pluck at your gutstrings?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh, don't you mean heartstrings?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Sorry, I was just trying to match... the level of nonsense coming out of your mouth, lady! Hee hee! If you don't like it, just say so! Go on, spill your guts!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness has a point. You have a lot of guts wasting this court's time!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There must've been some other reason Uendo wasn't shaken...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo, I think maybe the reason you weren't shaken was because... you already knew you would find your master dead!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Pyooooooooooo! Wh-Whaaat?! What kind of a thing is that to say?! You've got it all wrong...! O-Oh right! I just remembered something! I thought Shisho was just sleeping when I first saw him! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You thought he was sleeping? <thought>It sounds plausible, but...</thought> What made you think he was asleep?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, he had his head and arms up on the table, as if he were taking a nap. Oh, and one other thing! There was that note, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A note? What note?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah, he must be talking about this. It appears to have been written by the victim. Allow me to read it. "Resting. Do not disturb."</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Yes! That's the note I saw! After reading that, who wouldn't think Shisho was napping?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That is a pretty reasonable assumption.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Y-You've gotta be kidding me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's right. I saw this note, so that's why I thought Shisho was asleep. I want to change my testimony to include that statement! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right. I'll run an update.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I called to him from outside the room...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...but he didn't reply.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I opened the door, I thought he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But something seemed off, so I rushed over to him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I was shocked to find him dead! I couldn't believe my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There was one emotion that seemed out of place given Uendo's action's and statments. I wonder why he felt that particuar emotion then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you've noticed something, then hurry up and point it out already.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know! I'm just trying to be thorough, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It looked to me like you were being timid.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was not! You just watch me pinpoint the heck out of his emotions!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo, I noticed something funny in your emotions again.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">"Funny," you say?! I guess an entertainer of my caliber can make people laugh, even with my emotions!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't mean that kind of "funny"! Quite the opposite, actually! When you entered the dressing room, I see that you suddenly felt anger. What I want to know is, what made you feel angry all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">What? Hmm... Let's see... Oh yeah! Now I remember! As I was going in, I whacked my little piggy on something. I was annoyed at my own clumsiness! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, you mean you stubbed your pinky toe?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">J-Just a little bump on my little piggy. N-N-No big deal... I-It's embarrassing, really...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Sounds more like he's hiding something. I'd better dig a bit deeper.</thought> No need to be embarrassed, Uendo, but I'm afraid it's something we need to look into. Hmm... I don't really see anything you could've stubbed your toe on... in the area around the dressing room door in this picture. <thought>But maybe there WAS something there at the time...?</thought> Uendo, what exactly did you stub your toe on?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">You tell her. Really, who doesn't stub their toe every once in a while? You really gotta fuss over every small detail like this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, well... The thing is...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">E-Even the most subtle of fluctuations in a person's psyche can clue us in to the truth. That's why it's important to get to the bottom of this question! <thought>Plus, if we back down now, who knows what new insult Simon will hurl my way... Is there really no trace of what Uendo stubbed his toe on by the door? What in the world might've been there then, but is not there now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wait a minute... While it does appear that something hit the table and moved it... Uendo said he stubbed his toe as he was entering the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... And the table looks pretty far from the door. <thought>Could what bumped into the table also be a clue as to what Uendo stubbed his toe on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Careless answers will only hurt us here. So think carefully before you speak again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Right! <thought>Is there really no trace left of what Uendo stubbed his toe on by the door?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Oh, I could never stub my toe on that! That would really be starting things out on the wrong foot! Right, Mr. Golden-Ager?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Golden-Ager"? Don't you dare send me off to the retirement home yet, sonny! Anyway, I hope Ms. Cykes didn't stub her toes on her teeth as her foot entered her mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Well, defense? Are you ready to let it go, and move on now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course not. What Uendo stubbed his little toe on... is a vitally important question!<thought>I think. Is there really no trace left of what Uendo stubbed his toe on by the door?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please take a good look at this photo of the crime scene. Do you see it? This long track that goes from the door, all the way across the room?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Now that you mention it, I DO see traces of something getting dragged.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And the drag mark ends... there at the TV. This implies that the TV was originally by the door. I'm convinced that this TV is the object the witness stubbed his toe on. Well, Uendo! How about it?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Y-Yes you're right... It was the TV!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There! The noise level dropped again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Y-Yes, I stubbed my pinky toe on the TV. B-B-But what of it? Why is this so important to you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So the nosie went down, but it hasn't completely dissapeared yet. Which means he's still hiding something... Okay, let's try this tactic instead.</thought> Uendo, why was the TV moved there? </line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Shisho must've moved it so he could watch my routine. But what a place to put it! Right in the middle of the doorway like that! I didn't want to bump into it again, so I put it back where it belonged. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Performances onstage can be viewed in the dressing room using that TV?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's right. It's a closed-circuit monitor that shows the stage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see. <thought>Now what? I can't find anything else out of place. And I still haven't gotten the noise level down to zero yet...</thought> Simon... I'm stil getting noise here, but... I don't see anything else fishy.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. This is precisely why amateurs are such a bother.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'm in no mood to play nursemaid here, but if that's what it takes to save the soba shop... Hoy, Uendo. Here's a curiosity for you. This table master Toneido is slumped over looks like it was moved. Did you happen to bump into it while you were moving the TV back?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">O-Oh my! Yes, you're right! The TV hit the table, and Shisho's body moved with a jolt... That's when I first realized that Shisho was dead! Oh! But how scared I was!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I see. Thank you. We're finally getting a more precise picture of how the body was discovered. But I'd wager you need to put the spurs to Uendo just a trifle longer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Right! <thought>I can't keep asking Simon to bail me out like this! It's time for me to regain my footing and really stand on my own!</thought> Uendo, what you said now about discovering you master's death... Could you please describe all of that again for the court in detail?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But, before you do, let me plug in the latest information...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I called to him from outside the room...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...but he didn't reply.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I opened the door, I thought he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I tried to enter the dressing room, but stubbed my toe on the TV.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I put the TV back in its normal spot, I realized that Shisho was dead!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Seeing him slumped over that cluttered table... *sniff*... Oh, Shisho...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I'm not really seeing any emotions I'd consider out of place. How about you, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">How many times are you going to come running to me?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tsk. Well, take another good look at the flow of emotions. Don't just look for simple inconsistencies. Look at the intensity of his emotion, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see... Thanks, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's odd... After the initial shock of finding the victim dead, you reacted with surprise again! What was it that surprised you, Uendo, besides your master's death?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's more, you were even MORE surprised the second time than the first! WHat could've surprised you more than finding your late master?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">S-Search me. Your little thingy must've made a mistake!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That... was a compliment, right...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, I... Er...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! We've pushed him too hard, and he's mentally all over the place! His emotions are completely out of control!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Out of control"? Care to explain how that's relevant?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know how normally, I listen for the hidden emotions in a witness's voice, right? From there, I look for inconsistencies between their testimony and these emotions. But sometimes a person's feelings can run too high, making it hard to get a proper reading.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So that's how your matrix program works. Fascinating!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ordinarily, it's just one emotion that runs out of control... But it seems there's nothing ordinary about this time!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Nnnngh... I... I-I...!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I called to him from outside the room...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...but he didn't reply.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I opened the door, I thought he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I tried to enter the dressing room, but stubbed my toe on the TV.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I put the TV back in its normal spot, I realized that Shisho was dead!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Seeing him slumped over that cluttered table... *sniff*... Oh, Shisho...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I knew it...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. What's got your knickers all in a bunch now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo has multiple emotions running out of control at the same time! I've never seen anything like this! Ever!</line>
<line speaker="Blackuill">So how does one bring a situation like this under control?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll have to find the root cause of this tangled mess before I can treat him. If I can identify what is causing this emotional rampage... then I can touch "Probe" <thought>L</thought> to dive in further. I'll need to point to what I think is the root cause, and touch "Probe" <thought>X</thought> again. Through this process, I can identify exactly what's causing Uendo so much distress!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And that will help bring his emotions back under control? In that case, let's get started, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right! I can't guarantee success, but it's definitely worth a shot! <thought>Time to look for the root cause of Uendo's rampaging emotions!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">After my performance, I went to visit Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I called to him from outside the room...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...but he didn't reply.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I opened the door, I thought he was sleeping.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I tried to enter the dressing room, but stubbed my toe on the TV.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">When I put the TV back in its normal spot, I realized that Shisho was dead!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Seeing him slumped over that cluttered table... *sniff*... Oh, Shisho...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What could be the root cause of his out-of-control emotions...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Having trouble, are we?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Duh! I can't find the cause of his distress!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Isn't it obvious?! It's that bloody question you asked -- that's what pushed him over the edge, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, you're right...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's odd... After the initial shock of finding the victim dead, you reacted with surprise again! What was it that surprised you, Uendo, besides your master's death?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Simon's right. The answer to my question is what sparked this madness!</thought> I get it now... The cards were the root of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I, er...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't try to deny it! You can't hide your feelings from me! The dying message that was left at the scene of the crime... is what was causing your distress!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And if the dying message was the cause of all those feelings... then that means the phrase "OWEN 4TH" must mean something to you!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Nnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There! Noise level, zero! Finally!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The dying message consists of two words: "OWEN" and "4TH." But neither of these two words have anything to do with this witness. This topic warrants no further argument.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sure, there may not seem to be any direct connection... between Uendo and the message... for now. But why don't you wait and decide what's necessary AFTER you hear my theory?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. I trust you've hit upon something, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! If my theory is right... we can finally solve te case of "Uendo and the Mysterious OWEN 4TH"!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. Well, go on, then!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can already tell this promises to be interesting. Now, please share your theory with the court, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There was something puzzling to me about Uendo's out-of-control emotions just now. Namely, that there are three distinct reactions present. I had never seen that before, and I wondered how it could be possible. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Is there a conclusion to this meandering musing of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hold your horses, I'm getting there. So, could a person flip between three distinct emotions of such intensity like a switch? In the end, I concluded that it just wasn't possible. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ha ha ha! So that's it, is it?! A bit unconventional, but I'll grant that it's possible within the realm of psychology. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Within the realm of psycology...? I'm afraid you'll have to explain it for the old man up here on the bench.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"> Your Honor, my theory is that Uendo...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'll be surprised to hear that Uendo is actually a robot! Why not show your true self now, Uendo? Give us an old "beep boop boop"!</line>
<line speaker="U.3.N.D.0">YOU. ARE. CORRECT. I. AM. A. ROBOT. BEEP BOOP BOOP!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Hah! What a space cadet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, very nice! What a good sport the witness is for playing along! With the defense's joke of a theory, that is!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay... So he's not a robot...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Beep boop booooop...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe Uendo has supernatural powers?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Oh, yes! I make these butterflies dance in the air with psychokinesis. Hee hee! NOT! They're floating on the breeze from my fan, that's all. I'm very sad to say I don't have any supernatural powers.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, you switch between funny and serious characters so seamlessly! Marvelous! If only the defense's conjecturing was as well-practiced.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right... So no supernatural powers...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">With so many distinct personas, it's clear to me that... Uendo has dissociative identity disorder!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">PYOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Wh-Wh-What does that even mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............ Your Honor, the defense would treat this trial as a child's jest. Multiple personality disorder? A preposterous proposition indeed. Would you not agree, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">H-H-How did she know? How did she figure it out?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">P-P-Pohlkunkaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe it... I-I did it! I did it, Simon! I've read papers on it before... but to think I'd see a case of it for myself...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blimey. Rakugo artists tell stories as different characters, but as different personalities?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Hey, you! Lawyer girl! You got a problem with us?! Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No... No problem at all...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is all very hard to believe... but now that we've established that the witness has multiple personalities... could each of them please introduce themselves to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Uendo Toneido. I'm a rakugo storyteller, as you know.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Hello everybody! Patches, the friendly jester here! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Hmph. Kisegawa. Courtesan.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And is that all of you?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Yes, that's all of us.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So there are three personalities in total: Uendo, Patches, and Kisegawa, huh. ell, Simon! What do you think now?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. That you're one lucky duck. Just be glad they were dense enough to help you out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! Can't you straight up say I did great for a change?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You appear to be quite proud of yourself, defense...but all you have done is infringe upon the privacy of the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I couldn't disagree more, Prosecutor! Now that we know there are three personalities...a new way for us to interpret the meaning of a certain piece of evidence has arisen. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">A new interpretation? </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ooh, now I'm very curious. What is this piece of evidence you're talking about, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"> Knowing what we know about Uendo and his personalities, this now makes perfect sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Patches:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Amazingly heedless"? Why, Patches! Was that a compliment?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Fool! "Heedless" means "careless." In other words, you guessed wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A needless mistake by a heedless attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please let me try again, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The karuta cards?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right, Your Honor. Recall the original dying message left at the scene. We didn't have a clue as to what "OWEN 4TH" could've possibly meant. But now, with this new information about Uendo and his personalities... isn't it possible that "OWEN 4TH" actually means... a secret fourth personality of Uendo's -- a personality named "Owen"?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pohlkunka!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo must have kept his dissociative identity disorder from us because... he didn't want to be associated in any way with that dying message!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">N-No! That's not why! We kept our disorder a secret for a diffrent reason altogether. </line>
<line speaker="Patches">We've been taking advantage of our affliction to act out various rakugo characters. If word of this got out, well...</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">...our reputation as a rakugo artist would be tarnished, as would he Toneido name.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's why we kept it a secret from evreyone except members of the Toneido School. But really, there is no "fourth personality." It's just the three of us in here. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A plausible-enough sounding story...but it doesn't prove you didn't rearrange the cards, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">B-But...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I will concede that it is highly likely that the witness rearranged the cards. </line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Is Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... actually agreeing with us...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">However, is it not also possible...that the accused killed Master Toneido...and then left that message in order to frame the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Urngh!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And upon noticing the cards when he found the victim's body, Uendo rearranged them. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah, that is a true, but ultimately meaningless point. The witness was only in the dressing room for two to three minutes. That's far too little time to commit murder, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Simon's testimony? ............Oh!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Geiru escorted me to the dressing room...but we heard the sound of rakugo being performed from within. Thinking the master was rehearsing, we decided to wait in the hall until he was done. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That's right. Until a few moments before Uendo entered the dressing room... Taifu Toneido was confirmed to still be alive!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Arnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooooooooooooooooon!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Not only that, but Uendo was on stage until just before he discovered the body. A bulletproof alibi that I have already confirmed with several audience members. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, noooooooooooo...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I also heard that his rakugo performance that day was "a steaming pile of"... Well, you get the picture.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Y-Yes, I'm afraid so! Really stunk up the stage, I did! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">And yet, I have a perfect alibi!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Indeed. Why not land the coup de grce on the defense by describing your alibi, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Okey-dokey-smokey!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I was onstage until just moments before I went into the dressing room. </line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">The entire audience was my witness.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">But my performance was a huge bust. Not a single soul laughed!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I'll never be able to live down how terribly I bombed during that very important show.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Uendo was onstage before he found the body, so he could not have committed this crime. It is time to let it all go, defense, and move on. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ngrrr...! Well, get this, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! The Wright Anything Agency NEVER gives up! We fight to the bitter end!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Feh! Allow me to say this once more... Let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And allow ME to say once more, I'm never giving up!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............... This is pointless. You should have taken advantage of this opportunity while you could, you foolish child! Your worthless convictions only serve to prolong the accused's suffering. If words will not sway you, then perhaps pain will.  </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, no! A-Anything but this!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeek! Nnnngyaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh! What's the big idea, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That was but a small dose of punishment for your misguided convictions. Are you now a bit more inclined to give up, as instructed?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As if!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In that case, you must require another dose!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Not bloody likely!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't give two flips about your beliefs. But if Cykes-dono were to submit to you here, I won't be able to eat good soba anymore. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-That's right! For Mr. Whet's future, and Prosecutor Blackquill's stomach...I will NEVER give up!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You will rue those words, defense. Of that, I can assure you. </line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I was onstage until just moments before I went into the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Are you asking whether it could've been some imposter?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Unlike a big arena, a rakugo theater is a cozy, little place. It would be hard to fool an audience in such an intimate setting, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, I guess you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Good. I'm glad we could clear that up, because I guess you could say...</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">The entire audience was my witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Not a thing. Everything was the same as always. Mr. Prosecutor, you questioned the audience, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, of course. Apparently, nothing seemed amiss to them except, well... one small thing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">One small thing?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Oh... it's so embarrassing! I tried my best! Really, I did...</line>
<line speaker="Patches">But my performance was a huge bust. Not a single soul laughed!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you have any idea what went wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Hmm... I'm not sure if it was my performance, or if it was just that particular audience... Or maybe it was the story I picked. But every entertainer knows that this kind of thing happens from time to time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess that makes sense...<thought>Still, I wonder how he could've flopped at his own commemorative show? Hmm... Maybe I should dig into things a bit more...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">How many people were there in the audience when you were onstage?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Well, let's see. We drew a full house, so... I think there must have been fifty, maybe sixty people in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's quite a lot, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Exactly! I dropped a big, stinky bomb in front of all those people. It was a catastrophe, I tell you! I was sweating buckets from start to finish!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That sounds exactly like how Apollo performs in court sometimes...</thought> I-I see. Thank you. As for that statement, Your Honor, I'd like to...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, could I please have that last statement added to Uendo's testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... very well.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I think there must have been fifty, maybe sixty people in the audience."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Can you tell me which rakugo story you performed?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I could, but I'm not sure if it would mean anything to the uninitiated.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, even if I might not get it...can't you at least try me?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">All right. If you insist...The story I performed is called "Tokisoba" -- otherwise known as "Time Soba".</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Time Soba", huh? (Maybe Uendo's right... He's only said the name of the routine, and I'm already lost.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ah... So you performed "Time Soba", did you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! You know it, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">In the course of my studies last night, I became familiar with a number of stories. I must say, defense, you would do well to prepare yourself better for your next trial.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nnrrgh... Simon, what's "Time Soba" about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Look it up yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Allow me to give an overview. The story takes place on a winter's night. A man orders a bowl of soba at a street stall. "How ya doin', sir? What can I get for ya?" "I see you've got seaweed-topped hanamaki soba, and mixed topping shippoku soba." "I'll have a bowl of shippoku, my good man. It sure is cold tonight, isn't it?" "But there's nothing like a hot bowl of noodles and soup to warm the soul!" "Ya know it, sir! One skippoku, comin' right up!" "So, how's business?" "Not so great, sir." "Is that so? Well, that's great, because things can only get better from here, right?"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wow, Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The customer talks on and on like this. Finally, when he is done eating, he goes to pay for his soba. "So how much do I owe you?" "That'll be sixteen mon, sir." "I see... Sorry, but I only have small change on me." "I'll count the coins into your palm, so could you hold out your hand for me?" "One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight..." "Hey, what time is it?" "It's nine, sir." "...Ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen. Thanks, and bye!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha ha ha! very well done, Prosecutor Sahdmaadhi! That was excellent!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? I don't get it! What was so funny about that?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tsk. Don't you see? The customer paid with coins, counting them out one by one. Then, just after counting "eight", he asked about the time...and the soba vendor answered with "nine."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! Now I get it! He made the vendor say "nine," and then he continued counting from "ten"!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Exactly. He cheated the soba vendor out of one mon with his smooth talking. The story continues with another man who saw the whole things and tries to do the same. But he bungles up the trick, and ends up paying more than sixteen mon for his soba. The story ends on that as the punch line. You can look up the rest of the details yourself. Or, I'm sure Prosecutor Sad Monk over there would love to perform it for you after court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, basically, it's a story about a man cheating on his soba bill! That's kind of petty, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. Is that really ALL you have to say about this classic story? "Time Soba" is such a well-known staple of rakugo that the skill of the artist is critical in--</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aww... I wanted to hear a bit more... But, I suppose it is off-topic. Getting back to the matter at hand, Ms. Cykes, the witness stated that... "All right. If you insist...The story I performed is called 'Tokisoba' -- otherwise known as 'Time Soba.'" Would you like to add this statement to his testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor. I'd like to have it added.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The story I performed is called "Tokisoba" -- otherwise known as "Time Soba.""</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>The show's program doesn't seem all that relevant to this case...</thought> I don't need it to be added at this time, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I'll never be able to live down how terribly I bombed during that very important show.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Well, aren't YOU a regular rude daisy?! Do you really think a rakugo artist who regularly bombs would get promoted? In fact, I'm known as the Toneido School's "Whirl-Uendo of Laughter," I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-Is that really true, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That nickname is a bit of a travesty, if you ask me. But his rakugo is solid and well-received, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see...But, yeah. "Whirl-Uendo of Laughter" IS a big ol' stink bomb of a name, isn't it? Whew! What a relief! I thought it was just me!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I mean uh,"Whirl-Uendo of Laughter" is great! Funny stuff!</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Hee hee. I'm glad you like it!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I think there must have been fifty, maybe sixty people in the audience.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's right. Everybody was just staring in silence at me. It was simply awful.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yikes. That does sound awful!</thought> But with an audience of that size...is it even possible for not even one person to laugh?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm saying, are you sure there were even people in the audience?! After all, no one would be laughing if there was no one there to begin with. </line>
<line speaker="Patches">O-Of course here were people in the audience! It was a full house, I tell you! Lots of regular. Want me to ask 'em all to come here? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No... That's all right...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't just press him on every statement at random. You have to put some thought into it! Use your head, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! <thought>Simon's right. I have to be more careful with the testimony I draw out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">The story I performed is called "Tokisoba" -- otherwise known as "Time Soba."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Well... I suppose I was a little nervous... It's a lot of pressure when you're the star of such an important show, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You? Nervous? I thought you'd be all calm and collected, but I guess even you can get stage fright, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I wanted so badly to live up to the great name of "Uendo" that I inherited...that I guess I overperformed a little this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, "Uendo" was the stage name of a former member of the Toneido School, right?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">That's right. The name belonged to one of Shisho's former disciples who died of illness at a young age.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">With the weight of a new name like that to carry on your shoulders...I can see why you were feeling the heat -- just like me! I'm carrying the weight of my entire agency on my shoulders right now!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">In that case, can I count on your sympathy, and have you go a little easier on me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You're not giving up, are you? Where's that "never-say-die" spirit you displayed earlier?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course I'm not giving up, Simon! I just KNOW Uendo has something to do with this case!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But how will you connect him to the crime when he has an alibi as strong as that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I don't know just yet... But I'm going to press his testimony and keep an eye out for contradictions! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo, isn't there something odd about the routine you performed?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Odd? N-No, I don't think there's anything odd about it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But that's exactly what I find odd -- the fact that you don't think it's odd.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">N-No. Wh-What is it...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is an invitation to the show, sent from Master Toneido to Prosecutor Blackquill. Included in the invitation is a rundown of the show's program, which clearly states... ...that "Time Soba" was to be performed by Master Toneido himself!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">PYOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo! Why did you perform the routine your master was scheduled to do?!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Well... You see... The reason for that is...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">How do I say this... You see... Um, let's say it was a, uh... a prank...</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Th-That's right! It was just a little joke, you see! H-Hee hee! I was trying to surprise Shisho by performing his routine before he did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I don't know if I buy that. Was doing the victim's routine just for laughs, or...? Hey... Didn't Simon happen to hear "Time Soba" coming from the dressing room...during Uendo's performance onstage? It seems like too much of a coincidence... Wait, can it be...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter? You look like a hen with a dozen eggs to lay.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Stop comparing me to birds!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then cease this birdbrained timidity. If something has occured to you, then lay it out for us already! Don't breed resentment in those watching your performance!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Okay, okay! I don't have a ton of confidence in this theory, but... here goes! It looks like Uendo's alibi checks out, Your Honor, but...even though he was onstage at the time...he may have been trying to obfuscate a crucial detail about this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you referring to... the soba bill the man tried to skimp on in the witness's story?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not talking about the rakugo story, Your Honor! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! I-I'm sorry! But then, what are you talking about, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What Uendo may have been trying to deceive us about was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By performing "Time Soba," a story that featured soba noodles... Uendo tried to fool us into thinking that the victim had been drowned in soba broth!</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Come on! Not even a jester like me thinks the cops would be fooled by such a silly trick.</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Besides, the story I was originally going to do, "Soba Glutton," also features soba.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh. Right. I-I knew that...I just wanted to see if YOU knew that I knew.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes! Who's the one trying to deceive the court, again?!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Crash and burn!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sorry, Your Honor. I'll get it right this time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo tried to deceive us about what rakugo routine the victim was to perform! Taifu Toneido wasn't actually supposed to do "Time Soba" at all!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But Shisho's scheduled routine is written right here in the invitation. </line>
<line speaker="Patches">Here, why don't you read what Shisho was gonna perform out loud? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um... It says "Time Soba"...</line>
<line speaker="Patches">"You just earned yourself a penalty, defense!"</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-Hey! That's MY line!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm sorry, Your Honor. I'll get it right this time. Promise.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo tried to deceive us about the time of the victim's death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Eeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know. But he only testified that way because he and Geiru had been completely taken in!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You mean... by the soba bill thing?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Would you please forget about the story for a second, Your Honor?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I was deceived...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pray tell, how did Uendo manage to deceive two people while he was performing onstage?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's easy. All he had to do was use a certain "prop" in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh?! And what might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The prop Uendo used was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You just tried to take ME in, didn't you, Ms. Cykes? Now it's your turn to take in a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I believe you are right to suspect the use of a prop. It's just a matter of finding something he could use to fool someone outside the room with.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This TV was used to view what was happening on the stage. Prosecutor Blackquill, when you came to the dressing room, what was Uendo doing? </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">He was... performing "Time Soba"! Blast! Could it be...?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. It could, and it was! What you and Geiru heard was NOT Master Toneido practicing his routine. It was Uendo's performance, as heard through this TV monitor's speakers!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Pyoooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">With the TV just inside the inner door of the dressing room...it could easily be heard from the hallway outside.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And because we knew that Master Toneido was scheduled to perform "Time Soba"... ...we were easily manipulated into thinking he was still alive at the time, rehearsing!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. Your knowledge of the day's program is why the two of you could be fooled this way. Simon, did the voice you hear belong to Master Toneido?</line>
<line speaker="Blakquill">Hmph. With the doors in the way, I couldn't tell exactly who the voice belonged to. But because I heard "Time Soba", I just assumed it was Master Toneido. I can't believe I was taken in by such a simple mind game.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ngh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And there's one more thing about Uendo's actions that's suspicious. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The fact that he flopped so badly on such an important occasion.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's so suspicious about that? Even pros slip up once in a while, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But I believe that this time, it was intentional. Because Uendo knew it'd be strange to hear laughter coming from the dressing room!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's all just a bit too perfect to be sheer coincidence! Plus, if the voice Prosecutor Blackquill and Geiru heard was due to Uendo's scheming... then the victim's time of death could have been earlier than 4 PM! In other words, Uendo could have killed Master Toneido himself!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">PWOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We've got you by the stones now, Uendo! So you'd better confess everything!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, witness? What do you have to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We demand an explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Nnngh... I-I confess. I-I tampered with the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Is it the defense's claim that Uendo Toneido is the true murderer in this case?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If he tampered with the crime scene, then we have to at least consider him a suspect!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Kisegawa:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then why did you tamper with the crime scene?!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">I... I refuse to answer that question!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you suspect this witness, then I have a question for you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>What could it be this time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Uendo had absolutely no reason to murder Taifu Toneido. After all, why would Uendo kill the man who recognized his skills and promoted him?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">OH! W-Well... His motive... was, um... <thought>I can't think of a single thing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It appears you are also not aware of one other fact. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-And that is?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That the accused visited the dressing room before 4 PM as well. Is it not natural, then, to suppose that the accused killed the victim at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHAT? Nobody told me Mr. Whet had also gone there BEFORE 4 PM!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">We were only discussing the time frame after 4 PM, so I didn't think to mention it. But now that you have made the time period before 4 PM relevant...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Uh-oh. I don't like where this is going...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So, you really do not know what our client was doing during that time frame, do you? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it was all very sudden, and, uh... <thought>Why did you wait until the very last second to contact me, Simon?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't you give me that look! And just so you know, Bucky never told me he had visited the master before 4 PM, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Argh! This sort of thing is exactly why that prosecutor keeps calling us "unprepared"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will stop squabbling this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Sorry, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Thank you, Your Honor. Defense. You know of the soba-making implements in the dressing room, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Athen"><thought>Is he talking about the equipment for making soba noodles?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You speak of the large bowl that is used to mix buckwheat flour and water... the long rolling pin, and the special knife that is used to cut the dough into noodles?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Precisely. These tools all came from the accused's soba shop. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean, they didn't belong to Master Toneido?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Mr. Whet had visited the dressing room to give the victim a soba-making lesson. And that visit was before 4 PM. I'm afraid that after the accused kneaded the dough and made those noodles... he committed the act of murder. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But wait! That doesn't add up! If Mr. Whet killed the victim before 4 PM, why would he return to that room at a later time?!</line>
<line speaker="???">Bucky:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Hiya, Miz Chickadee... Heya, Simey! The reashon I went is 'cause Master Toneido ordered uncooked noodles. *ulp* </line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Whet...</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yeshterday, I brought noodle-making toolsh to the dresshing room at around 2 PM. Dat'sh when Master Toneido ordered uncooked soba noodlesh t' shtock up on. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uncooked noodles to stock up on?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yesh, ma'am. Master Toneido kept a supply of soba noodles from my shop in hish fridge. He only had one sherving left, so I went back t' my shop t' get some more. *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>One serving of noodles in the fridge? But I thought the fridge was practically empty...? Hmm... Anyway, the whereabouts of the missing noodles isn't all that important now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You ran into me and Geiru when you came back to deliver the uncooked soba, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Dat'sh right, Simey! I made time outta my bust day to deliver him the noodlesh! And ya know what? He ignored me when I called to him from th' inner doorway! He just kept mumbling rakugo lines fer ages! So I got mad and went back to my soba shop!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, so that's why you got mad. <thought>If what he's saying is true, then there's no way he could be the murderer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bucky">I shwear I'm telling the truth, Miz Chicka--- *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Bailiff, quick! Get this man to the infirmary!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well. I daresay he's quite a handful!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, please accept the statements Mr. Whet made just now into evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That opens up the possibility that the crime was committed between 2 and 4 PM. That's some critical information! </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, Your Honor. But other than that one point, Mr. Whet's statements are dubious and without proof. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. He has a point. If I were the prosecutor, I wouldn't accept them, either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While I understand the defense's feelings on the matter... this court is unable to accept anything other than the time the defendant made his visit.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>N-Now what do I do...!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I trust you have no further objections, defense. At last, the time has come to send the soul of the victim onward to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>We do? Like what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, don't just stand there!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But we don't have any evidence left to present!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Have you forgotten already? Isn't there still a hidden witness you have yet to question?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>A hidden witness...? Oh! That's right!</thought> Your Honor! There's still one more issue we haven't finished discussing yet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And what is this bit of unfinished business?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We haven't finished discussing this issue related to Uendo...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We need to discuss Uendo's alibi in further detail. </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Let it go, and move on. Uendo does not have an alibi, but he has no motive, either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you, Ms. Cykes, don't seem to have much of a clue. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. I know you know what's left to discuss.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That "Time Soba" story... You can't fool somebody just by asking them the time!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see. That's fair enough. Incidentally, do you know how many people there are in this courtroom right now? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? Let's see... One, two, three...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What time is it, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, It's around ten-thirty. ... Hm? Where was I again? ...Thirty-one? Or was it thirty-two?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wow, it was surprisingly easy to fool you, Ms. Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. I know you know what's left to discuss.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We still have to discuss the possibility of a fourth personality -- the one named "Owen"! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you suggesting that this fourth personality of Uendo's might be the true culprit?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">...Geez. Not that again. I told you we don't know anything about this "Owen"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look. Uendo. I know you don't have any motive to kill your master, but... this "Owen" may have one for all we know!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Come clean now, Uendo. You've got another personality stashed away, haven't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please tell us everything you know about Owen!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That's enough! The witness has already stated that he knows not of any "Owen" character!</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Bravo! You tell 'em, Mr. Prosecutor! Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hey, Patches. If you claim you don't know Owen when you really do, that's tantamount to perjury. If you want to exercise your right to remain silent, however... well, that's a different story.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Do not listen to the depraved prosecutor, witness. You will be tainted with his evil. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you have nay idea how dark and cold a prison cell is? Heh heh heh.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">I-I exercise my right to remain silent!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's this, now? Changing horses in midstream, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Sh-Shut up! I will remain silent, and that's it!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Patches, you fool! You stay out of this!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ha ha ha! Patches is not the brightest bulb in that box you call a noggin, is he? The fact that he switched from "I don't know any Owen" to "I will remain silent"... is proof that he DOES know about Owen! </line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Th-There it is again -- Simon's formidable psychological manipulation tactic. I'm sure glad he's on MY side today...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose only this witness can confirm or deny the existence of Owen for us... Very well. I will allow the defense to proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Grrngh... Pohlkunka...!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I've never met any personality named "Owen."</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Patches was just blurting out nonsense in a panic.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">We're always aware, so we'd definitely notice if a personality like that showed up!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">How dare you treat me like a criminal based on mere conjecture?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wow. How am I supposed to deal with the testimony of three personalities...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Unless you can prove the existence of Owen here, it's all over. You'd best screw your courage to the sticking place and attack their testimony head-on!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-All right. I will! Just stop piling the pressure on me! <thought>I have to draw out some info -- anything to drag Owen out into the open!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I've never met any personality named "Owen."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, it's more like all three of us are always here. And the personality that's most suited to the moment is the one that comes out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So when you're out, Uendo, what are the other two doing?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Well, we never know when our turn will come, right?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">So we stand by, and listen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means all three of you share the same memories?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I never really thought about it, but I guess that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see. Thank you. Please continue.</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Patches was just blurting out nonsense in a panic.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Hee hee! Why, hello! You rang?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You said, at first, that you didn't know anybody named Owen. But then you exercised your right to remain silent. Were you afraid of committing perjury?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Well, er... You see...</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">I'll take over from here, if you don't mind! Listen, I hate to say it, but Patches is about as smart as a sack of rocks. If you grill him with a bunch of highfaluting words, he's going to want to keep silent.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...I see. So looking after loose-tongued Patches... is your role, is it, Ms. Kisegawa?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Well, I don't know about that. But, anyway... I do know that Patches was just flustered, and that's why he decided to remain silent.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">We're always aware, so we'd definitely notice if a personality like that showed up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Wh-What would happen? I'm not even sure what you mean...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I mean, you three share the same memories, right? But what if Owen is different -- what if he has memories separate from yours? Maybe Owen emerges when the three of you are unaware or unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">N-Ngh..!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, we've already seen three personalities! A fourth wouldn't be a stretch!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You dishonor the victim and this court by jumping to such conclusions without proof.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Have you ever heard these old sayings, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi? "What happens twice will happen thrice." "If you see 1, there are likely 30 in your home." I'm basing my theory on such premises!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Comparing us to cockroaches -- do we bug you that much, girlie?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">But how do you intend to prove it? How will you prove that all three personalities became "unconscious," as you say? Unless you can do that, all of this talk is merely empty speculation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well... I...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't be so timid! If you don't have it, then find it! Look for something that could render Uendo and the others unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Simon's right. I can't back down now. For my client Mr. Whet, I have to...! ...Wait, Mr. Whet?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Lemme resht? Hah! Mehbee if I were a lump o' regular flour dough fer udon noodles! But I'm fresh, like my soba! 'N y'don't let soba dough resht... 'S all about the "three freshes"! Grind da buckwheat seeds fresh, cut da dough fresh, and boil da noodles fre-- *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">H-He's blacked out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Mr. Whet... Falling unconscious... Wait a minute! I think I've got it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes? Do you have proof to back up your theory?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is?! In that case, please point out what supports your theory.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This, most likely, is what caused Uendo to lose consciousness!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Patches">I may be soft in the noggin, but I don't see a single bruise on my head. Do you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, then, maybe it wasn't so much a "smack" as...a swing and a miss!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! What a coincidence, defense! Your assertion was a swing and a miss, too!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Athena, Uendo didn't need to be hit over the head to lose consciousness. Lord knows Bucky has passed out several times today without being "smacked."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, please point out this proof of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is probably what made Uendo lose consciousness!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ah, yes, the sak. And isn't it just like Master Toneido to pick a fine brand like "Camel."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Sak"...? Oh, you mean "rice wine"?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Kisegawa:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I must agree -- you need to become more cultured, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Tomayto, tomahto. It's made of rice, and people get drunk from drinking it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It's called "sak." End of story.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fine! "Sak" it is, then. <thought>Ay, caramba! Everybody's so touchy about these things!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I recall Master Toneido would often have a drink or two before performing. He said it made him more eloquent. Drinking too much of the stuff can make one lose consciousness, though, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And look! There were two glasses on the table! Uendo, I believe you master offered you some rice w-- I mean, sak. And then, you must've drank too much and passed out. That's when your fourth personality, Owen, emerged!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">I drank sak? Oh, that's a good one!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">We have a real sweet tooth, you see, so, yes, we did accept a sugary, red-bean bun...but since we really dislike sak, we said no, thank you to that.</line>
<line speaker="Patches">Believe it or not, we're real weak when it comes to booze. Hee hee! Even a tiny drop can knock us right out!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">So, you see... I had a sweet manju bun, but I didn't drink any sak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? But that can't be right! The defense demands that the glasses be examined right away!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You amateur! Did you really think I had not already done so? Your foolishness is beyond the pale.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Don't tell me...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There was no trace of the witness having touched either of the glasses, naturally.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Right... Of course...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, would you like the witness's statement added to his testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yes please, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I had a sweet manju bun, but I didn't drink any sak."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm afraid not, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Of course you do, Athena! Have another good look at the crime scene photo.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-okay...</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">How dare you treat me like a criminal based on mere conjecture?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But how can you be so sure that that's what the cards really mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What else could they possibly mean?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, for example, "Owen, the fourth hitter!"</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-Who in the world is that?</line>
<line speaker="Patches">He's a baseball player! A really great one, too! Owen Gonzales</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If such a famous baseball player was there, hanging around in the theater... he would've drawn a lot of attention to himself, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, then, how about this? <thought>Patches</thought> Maybe it means "OWE N 4 TH", like, "I owe 'N' four thousand."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And who is this mysterious "N" person?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">What? "N" isn't a person! It was Shisho's favourite hobby shop, "N-Joy." He was a huge model train collector.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Maybe he owed the hobby shop some money. So he left a note to remind himself.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In karuta cards on a table?</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Shisho worked in mysterious ways.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you even taking this seriously?!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">I'm being completely serious! The point is, "OWEN 4TH" could mean just about anything!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arngh... I-I suppose you're right. <thought>I guess I'd better approach this from a different angle...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I had a sweet manju bun, but I didn't drink any sak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then maybe you ate something that had sak in it as an ingredient?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I don't recall doing anything like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... He doesn't "recall" doing it... But that doesn't necessarily mean he didn't. He just might not have known that he did... I'd better take another good look at the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I should've figured that he's not going to just give in like that...</thought> There's gotta be some sort of key to unlocking Uendo's fourth personality...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Personally, I can't wait to see who will slip up first. But it'd better not be you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it won't! <thought>And if I can't find any inconsistencies, there's always one thing to do, and that's press!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So he didn't drink any sak, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh boy... Now we're in trouble...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That kind of answer is exactly why Sad Monk keeps insulting you. Now, use your head! There are countless ways Uendo could've gotten sak into his mouth besides drinking it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, I don't know about the "countless" part, but...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But nothing. Give it some thought, and you'll figure something out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So the witness must've had something that contained sak... Is there anything in the Court Record that hints at something like that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">This shows what, most likely, made Uendo lose consciousness!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That note...? Are you feeling lightheaded, child? Or perhaps a bit peckish?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm not hungry, and my head feels just fine, thank you very much! Look at the paper this note is written on. Isn't there something familiar about it?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What exactly is your point, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This faint design here reminds me of the paper from...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yup! It's a piece of the wrapping paper on the box of manju buns by the victim on the floor! Uendo, you may not have drunk any sak... but you did eat a sweet red-bean bun, right?</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Well, yes... That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know if you are aware of it or not, Uendo... but I believe the manju you ate caused you to fall unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The bean bun? But how?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because those buns contained a secret ingredient! A very "punchy" secret ingredient, at that!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "punchy secret ingredient"?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. The design on the wrapping paper matches that of something else in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-it does?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The design on this object matches that of the manju box's wrapping paper!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Considering it is part of the same package, that is hardly surprising. Now, why don't you tell us what this "secret ingredient" you speak of is?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-That, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, is a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes, are you even taking this seriously?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I am, Your Honor. And I promise to do better next time.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Not in the slightest.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But to young people like us, I assure you it DOES look vaguely similar...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As one of these "young people," I can assure you that it does NOT look similar at all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But to young... um... women... who, uh, wear yellow clothes...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arrrgh... Fine.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And here's what you get for treating me like an old fogey!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The camel pattern... It's the same as the one for "Camel" brand sak!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, just as Uendo said, he didn't drink any sak, per se...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...but he DID eat some.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I-Impossible...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo had a "Camel" brand red-bean bun... which boasts a nice shot of sak as one of its ingredients!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the defense is claiming that Uendo passed out after consuming a "Camel" sweet bun... which allowed a fourth personality named "Owen" to emerge. Is that correct?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor! That's exactly what I'm claiming!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">PYOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But there's one thing that bothers me. Wouldn't the alcoholic content of the buns evaporate as they are steamed?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">In order to give them a stronger flavor... some manju are specially made to retain as much of their alcoholic content as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">H-Hmph! What kind of lightweight do you think I am?! Even I wouldn't pass out from eating a simple manju!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then how about we test that theory? What do you say, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... "Seeing is believing," as they say. ...Very well, I will allow a test.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks, Your Honor! Simon! Go buy us some "Camel" manju, on the double! And don't forget to get me one, too, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wh-Why must I--?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And while you're at it, Prosecutor Blackquill... you will get one for me as well!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tsk! I'm not the courthouse stable boy, you know. But just this once, I'll acquiesce. Taka, I'm counting on you. ...And all of you had better pay me back!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Aww... But I thought it would be your treat, Prosecutor Blackquill... What a shame... Now then, let us adjourn until the manju arrive by carrier hawk. Court will reconvene as soon as Taka returns.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that the sweet buns have arrived, this court is back in session!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Go on, Uendo! Eat up!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">............Ngh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">*chomp* *chew* Mmm. Nice flavor... You can really taste the sak... *munch* *gulp* That was delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, a unique sweetness and the faint aroma of sak... Yet, I hardly think that anyone could pass out from eating something like this.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter, Uendo? You're not afraid of a tiny manju, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Or are you scared of how many calories it has?!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">D-don't be ridiculous! A sweet little snack like this couldn't possibly... I-I mean, it could never...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Less bleating, more eating, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Ngh... F-Fine! Whatever!</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">*chomp* *chomp*... *gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">See? I told you... It don-- don't affect me in th suh-- slightess! *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Patches">We might be a liiightweight, but c'mooon, nnnobody's THAAAAT l-light. Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Kisegawa">Hmph. Sh-Sheriouslyyy... Nobody ge's drunk offa wuh, wuh, one lil' bun... *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-It looks like it worked!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! W-Witness! Please tell the court your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oooooh... *sniffle*...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Oooh... *sniffle*... M-My name is Owen... I'm...five.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You're five years old?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">A-Am I in trouble...? Please don't yell at me... Oooh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So HE'S Uendo's fourth personality?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I'd hardly think a child like him could have a motive to murder the victim. And even if he had a motive, could he have actually committed the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's a very good point. Owen does appear to be very timid and weak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It seems the defense was hoping this hidden personality would be the real killer. But now that he is standing here before us... it is clear that none of Uendo's personalities can be the killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeek! <thought>Wh-Where can I even go from here!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Owen">Shisho... Shisho...! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen...? Do you know something about what happened to your master?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Uwahhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...C'mon, buddy. Won't you tell Auntie Athena what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Uwahhh! Whatta scary lady!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm not scary! Look! Look at auntie's biiiig, biiiig smile! Tell me about your master, please? Pretty please, with sugar on top?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">O-okay... Shisho was... super nice... He always played with me... Just like.. Just like a real grandpa. I loved Shisho... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Athena, do you sense anything behind his words?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I sense his sadness -- sadness so pure it's heartrending -- but no discord. Prosecutor Sahdmadhi is right. Owen isn't the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But then, don't you find it odd?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Find what odd?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Let's review what we've learned so far. Uendo rearranged the karuta cards to pin the blame on Bucky.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, that's because the original message implicated Owen. But Owen is only five years old, and absolutely adores Master Toneido.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Exactly. The other three personalities also have no motive for murder. If Owen isn't the true culprit, then the person who first laid out the cards...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Probably wouldn't have been Master Toneido! So then, who did it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense? Did the appearance of Owen help you figure anything out? </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor. I now know who it was that first laid out the cards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But I thought it was the victim! ...Right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, Your Honor. I don't believe it was. The one who first arranged the karuta cards on the table was none other than...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Could it have been Whet Noodle No. 3, the previous owner of Whet Soba?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You do realize that the old man has already kicked the bucket. This trend of giving wrong answers -- I suggest you buck it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey... Was that an attempt at word play there, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Your Baldness! Do your duty -- swiftly, now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Y-Yes, sir! It isn't every day that the defense requests a penalty for itself!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Eep... He's going to really let me have it later... I just know it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If it's not the fourth personality, Owen, then it must be a fifth personality!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And why would a fifth personality try to pin the blame on the fourth? They both inhabit the same body, after all. Well? O psychology expert...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears our psychology expert has run out of expertise!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. Review who rearranged the cards and their motives, O psychology expert!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Argh! I DO have a name, I'll have you all know!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I believe the person who laid the cards out is the very person who killed Taifu Toneido!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How quickly you move on to a new target when your Owen theory proves false! You pohlkunan!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know what a "pohlkunan" is, but I know I am definitely not one! And before you start with the sermons, why don't you hear me out?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, let's hear the defense's reasoning. Please proceed, Ms. Cykes. But if you are bluffing, I won't go easy on you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I understand, Your Honor. Now, then. Please recall the original crime scene. Who did the karuta cards name when the scene was discovered?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's see... I believe they implicated the defendant, Bucky Whet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. But we then found out that the message originally read "OWEN 4TH."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Which implicated the young boy, Owen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Exactly. And the person who rearranged the cards was undoubtedly Uendo.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Uendo may have kept silent, but we can be sure he already knew his master was dead. His tampering with the crime scene using the TV all but proves it.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Nnngh... ...I-I confess. I-I tampered with the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The reason Uendo rearranged the karuta cards and moved the TV was because... ...he saw the "OWEN 4TH" message, and was convinced Owen had committed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right on, Prosecutor Blackquill! It would seem that Owen and the other three personalities don't share the same memories.</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">But really, there is no "fourth personality." It's just the three of us in here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uendo feared that Owen had killed Master Toneido, so he tried to hide Owen from us.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Ooohhh... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But it turns out, Owen is but a five-year-old child, incapable of hurting a fly... ...let alone his beloved master.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So naturally, the culprit must be somebody else. And this somebody else -- the true killer -- tried to pin the crime on Owen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I see. That does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I believe Owen might know something about that.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your desperation is disgraceful! You should realize when it is time to let it go, and--</line>
<line speaker="???">I-I saw it...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I saw Shisho getting...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen! You DO know something, don't you!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! Is this true? If so, we must have Owen testify immediately! Don't you agree, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nnrrgh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It's all right, Owen. Go ahead and tell us what you know.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Shisho was standing with a knife in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Th-This is eyewitness testimony from the moment of the murder!</thought> Owen! Can you tell us anything else about what you saw?!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I... Ooooooh... I was so scared...! *sniffle* Oooooooh... So... So scared...! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Owen! <thought>His emotions are spiraling out of control! Something must've really frightened him!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Is he all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His emotions are running wild because he's trying to recall something frightening to him. I recommend a therapy session right away!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see. Yes, please do whatever you can to help the poor boy!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Will do, Your Honor! <thought>I'd better find the cause of these out-of-control emotions, pronto!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Owen">Shisho was standing with a knife in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Blood was dripping onto Shisho's face, getting it all red...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I couldn't move at all!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I was so scared... I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Poor kid. He's absolutely terrified of something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whatever it is, it might be the root cause of his out-of-control emotions. <thought>I'd better take another careful look at the images...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Owen">Yeah... Blood was dripping down onto Shisho's face...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Blood...? I don't remember seeing any blood in the crime scene photos... Besides, if the victim was standing upright, how could blood drip down onto his face?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As I expected, all we managed to obtain from this child is a tale he dreamt up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Urngk...! I guess it's a little weird for blood to drip onto the victim's face if he was standing up... Unless it dripped down from the ceiling or something? What do you think, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't know. Owen's one confused and upset kid right now, so who knows how accurate his memory is. Maybe it's time for that thing instead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? What thing?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">That thing that you and your cohorts do. What do you call it? "Rotate your thinking about"...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! You mean "turn your thinking around"!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yes, whatever. It's the same thing, either way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, it isn't! Who's ever heard of "rotating" your thinking? I mean, "rotate" is-- Hey, wait a minute... </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know what, Simon? In this case, I think "rotate" just might work perfectly after all!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All I have to do is rotate things by ninety degrees!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">When he saw his master, Owen must've been...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen must've been doing a handstand when he witnessed his master's murder. the victim must've been doing a handstand, too!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Or not. It's "not," isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Looks like all that rotating threw you for a loop, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Guess I rotated my thinking a little TOO much, huh... Maybe what I need to do is rotate my thinking a little less...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen must've been pressed flat against a wall when he witnessed his master's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that would make it look like blood was dripping onto the victim's face, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or maybe not...? I mean, it's not a big deal, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........What do YOU think, you big drip?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, all right. This time, I promise to rotate my thinking by ninety degrees!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen must've been lying on the floor when he witnessed his master's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's the conclusion I arrived at when I rotated my thinking by ninety degrees. Which means that all of the visuals in my matrix were off by ninety degrees.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This means Master Toneido was also lying on the floor, which solves another mystery!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And which mystery is that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The mystery of how blood could've been dripping onto the victim's face. It becomes much easier to imagine how that could happen if he was lying down. Like, someone bleeding onto Master Toneido from somewhere up above him!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I-I remember now! Somebody was sitting up on top of Shisho!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So trying to recall his master's bloody killer is what spooked Owen originally.</thought> The blood that stained the victim's face red came from the person sitting on top of him. The victim was holding a knife, so he likely nicked his attacker as he was fighting back!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This means his assailant was injured on their face somewhere, like the forehead, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Assuming the victim and his attacker were face-to-face, then, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see. So that is what happened. But if I recall correctly, the accused has a fresh bandage on his forehead, does he not? That injury of Mr. Whet's... ...is conclusive evidence that he committed this murder!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WHYYYYYYYYYYYYYY?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It seems you have dug yourself into a pit you cannot crawl out of.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nooo!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Even though I figured out the reason for Owen's out-of-control emotions... ...all I did was raise further suspicion against my own client... What do I do now...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter? You aren't thinking of throwing in the towel, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But it looks so bad for Bucky! I mean, he had both motive and opportunity... Plus, he has that injury on his forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Your Honor. I sense that the defense is finally ready to let it go, and move on.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? I understand that you don't want to give up on your client... ...but I won't allow you to prolong this trial without a good reason.</line>
<line speaker="Gallery">Well, that lawyer did her best, but all the signs point to the defendant's guilt.Maybe it's time she gave up? She tried everything she could...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I really, REALLY don't wanna back down, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I wouldn't say THAT... It's just...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you remember what you said to Bucky earlier this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Y'mean... you believe me, ma'am...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course! No matter what, I'll believe in you to the very end!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Were those just empty words?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Of course not! It's just that all the cards are stacked against us...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Are you still stuck on that line of thinking? Motive, opportunity, and an injury to his forehead -- Is that all it takes to make you stop believing in your client?! Tell me again, who are you to Bucky?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh... I'm... I'm his "Miz Chickadee" lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Then do your duty, and believe in him until the very end!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I... I will! <thought>Simon's absolutely right. I'm Bucky's lawyer. And he's depending on me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Defense team, please! No fighting in my courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The defense is ready to resume, Your Honor! Prosecutor Blackquill was just giving me a pep talk, that's all. Thank you, Prosecutor!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I didn't do it for your sake. I did it for the future of Whet Soba.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, yeah! I got it! The defense would like to now continue with Owen's therapy session!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Owen, would you be all right with that?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">O-Okay... Um... So...  somebody was sitting up on top of Shisho, bleeding from their head... ...and smooshing something into Shisho's face!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's funny...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still hear discord in Owen's voice... ...but I don't sense any inconsistencies between his statements and his emotions. And there don't seem to be any contradictions in his testimony itself, either.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ahh, so that's it, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you figure something out?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your ability to sense emotions is making you focus too much on his feelings, Athena. But there's actually something he's being very vague about in his testimony. If you can clarify what he's feeling uncertain about with some evidence... ...you should be able to move forward from there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Okay, that makes sense. I'll give it a try! I'll just update the Mood Matrix with the new information, and then we'll be ready to go! <thought>So I just need to present some evidence on what Owen is being vague about, huh...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Owen">Shisho had blood on his face and a knife in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">He was on the floor, and somebody was smooshing something into his face...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I couldn't move at all! I was so scared... I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So now, let's see what Owen is feeling uncertain about. It should manifest as something Owen isn't being specific about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter? Is this too tough for you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, I'm thinking! So stop distracting me! <thought>I think I can guess what Owen is uncertain about... I just don't know which piece of evidence will pull the info I need to the surface...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You can't solve this with a rigid thought process. Try kneading your mind as well!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Kneading my mind?! It's not soba dough, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. Looks like you've learned a thing or two about making soba, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think?! I've only been hearing about it all day today!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>That Simon! He's figured something out again, hasn't he...? And what does the soba-making process have to do with what Owen is unsure about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's put a name to the thing Owen's uncertain of, shall we... ...by identifying the murder weapon that was used to suffocate the victim. Fortunately for us, I spy the murder weapon right here in this crime scene photo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Unfortunately for you, I spy nothing of the sort. And the police... ...did not spy anything of the sort during their investigation, either. Pray tell, where is this "murder weapon" you see?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You don't see it because it no longer looks the way it did when it was used as a weapon. This is what the killer pressed into Master Toneido's face!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You really think that that's what the murderer pressed into the victim's face?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or maybe it was this right here...? Or, wait, maybe that over there...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Stop moving your finger around and around until you get it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. Athena Cykes "psyches" out the judge... Or tries to, at any rate.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah... I'm not real psyched about how that went...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The mystery person that Owen saw pressed soba into the victim's face... ...thereby suffocating him!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I grow weary of your tasteless jokes! How could anyone commit murder with soft, delicate soba?! The noodles would instantly fall apart if they were pressed into someone's face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I disagree. There is a way the soba could've been used to suffocate the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What? You will explain your theory at once, Ms. Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">To kill Master Toneido, the culprit must have smothered him with...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The culprit must've pressed uncooked soba noodles into the victim's face...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Soba noodles are even softer and more apt to fall apart before they are cooked than after. I verified this for myself by preparing and cutting my own buckwheat noodles yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How thoroughly studious of you, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. You would do well to follow his example, Ms. Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I should've known he'd find a way to study soba-making last night, too... All right, Your Honor. Please let me try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The culprit must've balled up some cooked noodles and used that clump to kill the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">There is a type of spice called myoga ginger, which is said to help with memory loss. Perhaps the defense should try some. It pairs very well with soba.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Because you appear to be suffering from severe memory loss, child. As I said earlier... ...the soba noodles would instantly fall apart if they were pressed into someone's face!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. Just like the defense's crumbling assertion!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I was kinda hoping you'd forget about the penalty, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Guess I'll give myoga ginger a try...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Anyway, Your Honor, please let me try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The culprit must've used the soba before it was cut into noodles! In other words, the murder weapon was raw soba dough!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Order! Order in the court! Yes, soba dough could definitely be used to suffocate someone, couldn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Are you all right, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I was just letting the soul of the victim know... ...that the accused will finally face justice, thanks to the foolish lawyer before me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Allow me to summarize your statements. As the accused was killing the victim, he was slashed in the face by the victim's knife. The weapon he used to suffocate the victim with was the dough in the dressing room. He then disposed of the murder weapon by cutting the soba dough into noodles.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Agnrk! Why, you smarmy...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Afterwards, the accused put the victim's face into the bowl of soba noodles and broth... ...to wash off the blood that had dripped onto the victim's face from his own. And there you have it: the true sequence of events behind this foul affair.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Now, wait just a minute! I never once said that Mr. Whet was the culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Who but the accused knows how to cut dough into noodles, defense?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Gurk!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That's a very good point, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. I heard that cutting soba dough into uniform noodles requires considerable training. But then, what about the dying message? How do you explain that? The defendant wouldn't have known about Uendo's "Owen" personality.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Perhaps the victim was simply playing with the cards, and they hold no other meaning. Perhaps he spelled out Owen's name in jest, sometime before his murder.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's true. From Owen's testimony, it's clear that Master Toneido cared for the boy. Hmm... It appears we've arrived at a compelling conclusion. Taken together, all of these points paint a convincing picture of the defendant's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Oooooh... Y-You're scaaaring me...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! I'm sorry, Owen! Auntie Athena didn't mean to raise her voice. <thought>I have to be gentler with him! I can't forget he's only five years old.</thought> No need to be scared, okay, sweetie? Just tell us anything you can remember.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Well... Wh-When I woke up... the person who killed Shisho... was standing over me... ...bleeding from their head...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen! You saw the killer's face?! <thought>Oops, I did it again...</thought> S-So who was it, Owen? Do you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Oooooh... I... I don't know who it was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I'm picking up some noise...! That means there's still something to uncover in Owen's testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I don't know what Owen saw, but suffice it to say, we are analyzing the dreams of a child. You've wasted enough of our time, defense. Let it go, and move on!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! There's still discord in Owen's heart that needs to be addressed! Therefore... I can't give in here! Owen, do you think you can continue your testimony for us?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">*sniffle* Okay...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'll enter the new info, and run an update, then!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Shisho had blood on his face and a knife in his hand...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">He was on the floor and somebody was smooshing dough into his face!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I couldn't move at all!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I was so scared... I passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">And when I woke up...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">...the person who killed Shisho was standing over me...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Owen saw the real killer's face! This is ultra-critical, eyewitness testimony! He must've been so scared... ...Wait a minute. What's that one emotion doing in there...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Despite witnessing the culprit's terrible crime first-hand... ...Owen experienced a positive feeling -- one of... relief?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The person the witness saw was no stranger. Rather, it was the accused. Therefore, it is only natural that he felt some level of relief when he saw a familiar face. Defense, end this madness and sully your soul no more.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen... Who did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">That nice smell... I love the smell... of that perfume...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I-It's the smell of... of... Ungh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You can do it! Try to remember, Owen!</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Ooooooh... Th-The smell of... of... Ooooooohhhhnnnnngh...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Owen!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems Owen is now resting in the infirmary. They certainly have their hands full today down there. Let's continue with the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Despite Owen's testimony, it is the opinion of this humble servant of the Holy Mother... ...that the child's words were insufficient to clear the accused of suspicion.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But what about the scent of perfume Owen mentioned?! I believe it's a clue that will lead us to the true culprit!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... But there are thousands of perfumes in the world.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It could even be the scent of the hair product the accused uses.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">He does have one amazing hairstyle, so that's certainly possible.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The witness is a five-year-old boy. He cannot tell the difference between conventional perfumes and hair products.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Argh... Why couldn't you have gone for a crew cut or something, Bucky?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What's more,  the only person who can cut soba noodles with such precision... ...is the accused, and no other.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Oh man... How am I supposed to argue with that...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And so, the person Owen saw at the scene of the crime can only be... ...the accused, Bucky Whet!</line>
<line speaker="???">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What the--?!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Hey, hey, hey! I never use hair productsh or anyding with a shmell! *hic* If I wore someding like dat, th' shmell'd get into th' soba! Boom! Check it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Uh... Mr. Whet? Aren't you supposed to be resting in the infirmary...?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Whaaaatever! ou dink I'd let my soba shtink o' perfume?! Try dat chillled soba fer yershelf and see!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe we have no choice but to try it... Strictly for examination purposes, of course. Now then, let's dig in, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mmm... That was delightful. *Ahem!* Well, I'm satisfied that there are no traces of hair products or perfumes in Mr. Whet's soba. First, sweet bean buns, and now, savory soba! What a delectable trial this has been!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">This texture is different from the soba I had the other day. It reminds me of a dish we have in Khura'in called "banu'puun."</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Whatcha dink, Miz Chickadee? My soba'sh pretty good, ishn't it?! *hic*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mmm-MMM! It's delicious! Don't you think so, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh. It still pales in comparison to his late father's cuisine.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">S-Simey! Why you alwaysh gotta be so hard on me?! *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Take the defendant back to the infirmary at once for some rest!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Resht?! Hey, I ain't a lump o' plain ol' wheaty udon dough, y'know! I'm fresh like my soba! Y'don't let soba dough resht... It's about the "three freshes" of soba! Grind the seeds fresh, cut the dough fresh, and boil the noodles fre-- *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good grief. What a defendant...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>At least Bucky wasn't the source of the perfume smell... Wait. Smelly perfume...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It looks like you remembered something.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The phrase "smelly perfume"... reminded me of a certain somebody!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And who might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's only one person that comes to mind!</thought> The phrase "smelly perfume" reminded me of this person!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............ <thought>Uh-oh. Something tells me I got it wrong.</thought> There's no doubt about it -- it's NOT this person!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What the--?! No take-backs, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Come now, Athena. There's only one person it could be.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. If it's perfume we're talking about, it's gotta be that person!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Geiru Toneido? Hmm... Yes, she DID smell very nice, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Just a moment, defense. You would throw suspicion on Geiru now because of a scent? Your Honor, there is no need to go along with these ever-changing claims of the defense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I suppose their claims have been awfully inconsistent...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Geiru could've been at the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, but...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'll get to see those "balloons" of hers if we call her back to the witness stand! </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How vulgar! His Honor is not interested in such things!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............Ahem! Setting the matter of her "balloons" aside entirely... ...I do believe it's appropriate to ask Geiru some questions, given the circumstances. This has nothing to do with her "balloons"... of course.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pohlkunkaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Thank you for calling this disciple of the Toneido School of rakugo back for an encore! It's me! The balloon artist you all know and love, Geeeiru Toneidooo! Onnne, twooo... BLOOOON!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What wonderful balloon artistry!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Your Honor... Please.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Now, then! What would you like me to make for you this time?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, actually, I called you back for more testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">But I'm all talked out! This case has left me completely deflated.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">What? You didn't find that funny? A-Anyway, what exactly is going on, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It seems the person who murdered Master Toneido was wearing perfume.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And you were the only person I could think of who wears perfume.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Wait... you mean I'm a suspect now?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru, you knew about Owen, right?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">W-Well, yes. I often played with him at Shisho's request.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means you could've left that fake "dying message," right?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Wh-What? Just because I wear perfume and know Owen... ...you think I'm a murderer? Oh, how could youuu?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The witness is absolutely right. With no evidence but the distorted memories of a small child... ...it is outrageous of the defense to accuse this woman!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Th-Th-That's right! You don't even have any proooof...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You may step down from the stand, Geiru. The defense does not have one scrap of evidence that connects you to the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait just one minute! I may not have proof, but Owen's testimony is still--!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Enough! Please feel free to leave, Geiru.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>B-But I'm so close! There must be something I can do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, if the prosecutor says it's okay, then I guess I'll be going now...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Eeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-There's a bandage on Geiru's forehead...! And since we know that Master Toneido's killer has a cut on their face somewhere...!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I-Impossible...!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How did you know, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I didn't. But I had to take a chance and see for myself. Otherwise, your theory would remain a groundless accusation.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor! Prosecutor Sahdmadhi! The scent of perfume, an injury on the forehead... These things are completely consistent with Owen's testimony! In short... ...the mysterious individual Owen saw in the dressing room... could have been Geiru!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes... ...does this mean you are formally indicting this witness for the murder of Taifu Toneido?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Satorha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Should your accusation prove to be false... I hope you are prepared to pay the price in full.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-Simon, what "price" is he talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I thought that should be obvious. Prosecutor Sad Monk is saying he'll see to it you never stand in a court of law again!  must say, though, he knows how to make a trial interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Just whose side are you on, Simon?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Go on, then. Into the deep end with you. You really have but one choice anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? I'm waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-With regards to the witness, Geiru Toneido, the defense wishes to...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Geiru definitely seems suspicious, but what if she really isn't the culprit?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hoy. You'd better not be getting cold feet. It's all up to you and how much you believe in your client now. So put up your dukes, and fight!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>There's no reason for me to hold back! Not if I really believe in my client!</thought> The defense wishes to formally indict Geiru Toneido for the murder of Taifu Toneido!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I have tried to be merciful, but now, not even your pleas will reach the Holy Mother's ears! You will have plenty of time to regret your decision... in the pit of hell!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Except I won't need to! The person who murdered the victim was NOT Mr. Whet. It was Geiru Toneido!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">That bandage is... It's just from a silly slipup I made while cooking yesterday, that's all!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What kind of "extreme cooking" were you doing to cut yourself on the forehead?!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, what can I say? That's what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You also don't have an alibi for the period before 4 PM, do you, Geiru?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">But... But... I really didn't know anything was wrong until Shisho was found dead! If you don't believe me, then, with a twisty, twist, twiiist! And BLOOOON! There you have it, an adorable little kitty! How could you suspect a cutesy widdle balloon artist like me, hmmmm?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru, I've been meaning to say this for a while now, but... ...could it be that you don't have an eye for balloon art?!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">D-Don't you think I know that?! You didn't have to come out and say it! I'm the daughter of a great rakugo artist! I never wanted to do stupid balloon art! I was supposed to be a rakugo storyteller, too, just like my late daddy. B-But Shisho told me to do balloon art instead... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I guess the victim thought she had no talent as a rakugo artist, either...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">So you're still gonna suspect a poor, lil' thing like me?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">P-Please stop trying to skirt the issue! It all comes down to the scent of perfume, and the cut on your forehead! You and the culprit in Owen's testimony share these two traits!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">You're dead set on accusing me, aren't you?! Well, here's what I have for naughty little girls like you! With a twisty, twist, twiiist! I'ma cut ya, witch! Go ahead, make me testify all ya want! When the truth's revealed... ...it'll be yer balloon or mine that goes POP! Got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! Is this yet another hidden personality?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Simon, is everybody in the Toneido School like this?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">H-How should I know?!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah, I visited the dressing room during that time to make a courtesy call after my act.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Geiru's saying she went into the dressing room, but then left right away.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Don't take her at her word.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, do you really think I would? I'm just trying to figure out how to get her to talk about what really happened.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Ms. Cykes. You may proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah, I visited the dressing room during that time to make a courtesy call after my act.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah, a visit to yer master before and after yer routine... That's just common courtesy with us rakugo artists and entertainers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that means you paid the victim a courtesy call before your performance, too, right? What did you see at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">He was having a drink and getting himself into a festive mood! He liked to say that drinking gave him a silver tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So he was already drinking by then.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Uendo wasn't there in the dressing room yet at that time. He musta gone in there during my act, 'cause when I went back...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Shisho and Owen were in there, but they were both snoring up a storm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">They were both stretched out on the floor, snoozin' away.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>So sitting the victim up and over the table must've been the culprit's doing. After all, who wouldn't stretch out on the floor if they could to take a nap? Plus, that matches up with what Owen said in his testimony.</thought> But if he was asleep, how could you tell it was Owen?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">How did you know it wasn't Uendo?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I've known the guy for ages! One look at his face, and I know which one I'm dealing with.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I saw the note Shisho left, so I just left. Didn't wanna disturb 'em, ya know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I dunno. Can't remember. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you notice anything else unusual or out of place in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, there was the sak and a half-eaten manju on the table. But I didn't see anything else out of place or whatever in the room, though.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh, is that a fact?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">O-Of course it is! Whaddaya think?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And you didn't change anything around while you were in there?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I didn't do anything! Look, I'm tellin' ya! I didn't see anything funny near Shisho, and I didn't touch anything in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Your Baldness, I request that that statement be added to Geiru's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Simon! What's a statement like that going to do for us?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Just play along and you'll see soon enough.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I have no problem with adding that to the testimony, but how about you, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I have no problem with it either, Your Honor. <thought>What is Simon thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I didn't see anything funny near Shisho, and I didn't touch anything in the room."</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">The perfume Owen smelled musta been left over from when I visited.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah, sure. Why not? All it proves is I was in the dressing room anyway. It don't do a thing to prove I killed Shisho!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-That may be true, but...!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Bucky's the one who bumped off Shisho!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I didn't see anything funny near Shisho, and I didn't touch anything in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I already told ya! Nothin'!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And you didn't touch anything at all in the dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">How many times I gotta say it?! No, I didn't touch anything!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wait... But then, is she saying she didn't see... ...what Uendo immediately saw when he checked the victim's body? Does that mean it wasn't there yet at that time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Oh, hold on! I guess there was something...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">The soba-making equipment was already there in the room. That means Bucky must've been there in the dressing room before me, doin' something!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Arngh... Thanks for the non-help...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Geiru is insisting that she visited the dressing room... ...before Master Toneido was killed.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So it would seem. But if you keep on her, she may slip up under pressure.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sounds like a plan!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, a new statement has been added... ...but she's still sticking to her guns.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">She said she didn't see anything unusual in the dressing room. But that strikes me as a little strange on its own.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If Master Toneido really is the one who left that, you'd think Geiru would have noticed it. And if Master Toneido wasn't the one who left it, then we must ask, who did? You know what I'm getting at, don't you, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I think so...! <thought>I really appreciate Simon's help, but I've got to come up with the answer myself this time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru, you said that you didn't notice anything odd or unusual near your master. You also said you didn't touch anything in the dressing room.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">That's right! What about it?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Then, I wonder who left that "dying message" with the karuta cards?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">What're ya going on about?! It hadta been that Bucky!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, but that's not possible. Because only three people knew of Uendo's personalities: Uendo, your master, and you!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If Bucky had left that karuta message... ...he wouldn't have spelled out "Owen." He would've spelled out "Uendo."</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What it boils down to is this: As a member of the Toneido School, you, Geiru Toneido... ...are the only one who could've left that "dying message"! And as the person who left that message... ...it's clear that you are Master Toneido's killer!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Grrrrragh! Will ya EVER quit yer yappin'?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Would you quit butting in whenever things start to go my way!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Silence, child. Playtime is over.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">As the witness stated, she went into the dressing room and soon came back out again. But the victim's note was not the only reason she left with such haste. There was another reason that compelled Geiru to leave at once. Geiru, would you please relate said reason to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There was a reason why Geiru had to leave the dressing room...?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, I didn't wanna show ya this, but I guess I got no choice. Keep yer eyes peeled! 'Cause here it comes!	</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your hand is all swollen and red...! What happened, Geiru?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">If ya must know... I'm allergic to buckwheat!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Allergic reactions to buckwheat can vary, though they're usually on the severe side. With Taifu Toneido making soba noodles in his dressing room... ...Geiru is lucky to still be alive, considering all the soba flour that was swirling in the air.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Good thing I left pretty quick! I managed to escape with just a mild reaction. But I touched Shisho as he was being carried away, and look what it did to my poor hands! There musta been soba broth on his clothes or something. If I'd inhaled any of that soba flour, I'da had a seizure, and it'd been "Good night, Geiru!" I never coulda stayed in that dressing room for very long!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A person allergic to buckwheat couldn't be in a room with soba flour in the air... ...and certainly couldn't use soba dough as a murder weapon, either.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-This isn't good...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You knew it would come to this, didn't you?! That's why you never mentioned her allergy!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Hmph. As if I would do anything so underhanded. I was simply trying to protect the privacy of this witness.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I'm sick of all these accusations! Why don't I just testify and get it all out in the open, yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">If I come into the slightest contact with buckwheat, I get an allergic reaction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I still can't believe it. Nobody told me she had a soba allergy... Did you know, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Does it look like I knew? "Protect the privacy of the witness," my foot! What a dirty trick!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-Now what do we do...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There's only one thing TO do. Put Prosecutor Sad Monk to shame with your cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right! No matter how small, I'll find us an opening, and break her testimony down!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">If I come into the slightest contact with buckwheat, I get an allergic reaction.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Of course not! I swear on the grave of my father up in heaven! I can even get ya a doctor's certificate, if ya want.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>She...seems to be telling the truth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I've had this allergy for as long as I can remember... But I never dreamt in a million years it'd clear me of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And you'll come out of this smelling like a delicate buckwheat flower to boot!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well said, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">And with that much soba flour in the air, that room coulda literally killed me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah, but, like I said, I came right back out. I mean, the soba-making tools were right there! Ya better believe I was careful not ta breathe any of it in!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But you still could've committed this crime if you'd held your breath while doing it!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Don't be ridiculous! I woulda suffocated to death before Shisho did!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yeah, I guess you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Geez. Get a grip, will ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Look at my hand! Just touchin' Shisho's body caused this much damage.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">You kidding?! Bring my lil' Jugemu in here! I'll hug n' squeeze 'im like there's no tomorrow! I'm telling ya! I have a genuine, honest-ta-goodness soba allergy!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Defense, the witness clearly has an authentic allergy to buckwheat. Any further deliberation on the matter would be meaningless! Pointless! Worthless!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">You heard the man, lawyer girl!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All. Right. Fine! I was just starting to think the same thing myself! <thought>Doesn't mean I have to like it, though...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I probably got this allergic reaction on my hand here 'cause I touched Shisho.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">There musta been soba broth on his clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Well, the buckwheat from the noodles can dissolve into the broth, so, duh. Touchin' soba broth can be just as deadly for me. Don't ya know anythin'?! What an amateur!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm sorry... <thought>Do I look like a doctor to you?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Look. Anything that has soba in it, or anything that has touched soba, is like poison to me!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">So I never coulda committed that murder in the dressing room!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I have to agree. The defense can't go around suggesting new premises without basis.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Unfortunately for you... ...Shisho didn't take a single step from his dressing room around the time of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, that IS unfortunate... for everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I don't see any particular inconsistencies in her testimony. And she seems to be telling the truth about her buckwheat allergy.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. What is your point?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My point is, I can't find a single foothold!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Well, if you can't find one, make one!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You want me to just make up some baseless accusation?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">When will you stop behaving like such an amateur? If you don't do something fast, the trial will end here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know, I know...! <thought>I can't let that happen! I-I have to do something -- anything!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pressing all statements leads to">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nrrgh...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Wh What would Mr. Wright do at a time like this?</thought> Auf geht's! There's only one thing TO do!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What are you smiling about? Has the pressure overwhelmed you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nope! It's just, the worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I see. You have no rebuttal, and so the only thing left to you is to smile.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ohhhhhh, ho ho ho ho ho! That's where you're wrong! I DO have a rebuttal! <thought>Turn your thinking around, Athena! Don't try to figure out how Geiru, who is allergic to soba, could commit the crime. Figure out how Geiru could be in that room and not have an allergic reaction instead!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Lemme resht? Hah! Mehbee if I were a lump o' regular flour dough fer udon noodles! But I'm fresh, like my soba! 'N y'don't let soba dough resht... 'S all about the "three freshes"! Grind da buckwheat seeds fresh, cut da dough fresh, and boil da noodles fre-- *urp*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">H-He's blacked out!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It appears to have been written by the victim. Allow me to read it. "Resting. Do not disturb."</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Yes! That's the note I saw! After reading that, who wouldn't think Shisho was napping?!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">If ya must know... I'm allergic to buckwheat!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Mon dieu! <thought>What if... that certain piece of evidence doesn't mean what we think it means? If that's the case, I might be able to prove that Geiru could have committed this crime!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No matter how hard you search your mind, you cannot overturn facts.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Ms. Cykes? If you have no further objections, I'll hand down my ruling...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">True, I can't overturn facts, but what if we got our "facts" about a piece of evidence wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">"Got our facts wrong"? What are you talking about now?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And which piece of evidence do you mean, Ms. Cykes? Please point it out to this court!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This evidence proves that Geiru could've killed her master, even with her soba allergy!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">*sigh* It is time to let it go, and move on, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How could that possibly be used to avoid triggering an allergic reaction? There are cases in which people have died from inhaling even a tiny amount of soba flour!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How very scholarly of you, Prosecutor. I see you've studied up on allergies as well.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It's not "How did she avoid an allergic reaction?" It's, "Why didn't she have an allergic reaction in the first place?" That's your puzzle to solve.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why she didn't have an allergic reaction in the first place... Right! Thanks, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's Master Toneido's note!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-The note?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Preposterous! What possible connection could there be between the witness's allergy and that note?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The answer lies in the true meaning of this note.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Its true meaning?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This note does not mean "I am resting. Do not disturb," as we had assumed. But rather, it actually means "This dough is resting. Do not disturb it"!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wait a minute, Athena. That doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're right. It doesn't. After all, as Bucky told us many a time: "You don't let soba dough rest"!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Wh-What's all this jibber-jabber got to do with anything?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>This is it! The home stretch!</thought> This note and Mr. Whet's words have led me to the conclusion that Master Toneido was...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Master Toneido wasn't making anything, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Let it go, and move on, defense. Even if the victim had not been making soba, Geiru still could not have entered the room. The reason being, that the room was covered in buckwheat flour.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems it's the defense that isn't making anything, let alone progress!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Arngh... Could Geiru really not set foot inside that room...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Master Toneido was making soba, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes? And what of it?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, of course, Geiru would have had an allergic reaction, and... Huh? Wait a minute...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah. So?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, of course, the defense gets a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Maybe I should try thinking outside the soba bowl, as it were...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The victim, Taifu Toneido, was not making buckwheat noodles. He was making ordinary udon noodles instead!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pohlkunkaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That layer of flour in the dressing room wasn't soba flour, but plain old wheat flour for udon! So, actually, it was totally possible for Geiru to be in that room and kill her master!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Nnngang ngang ngaaaaang!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What! But if that's true, it changes everything!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor, the defense requests that the flour in the room be tested immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um! Well...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Even were it udon flour instead of soba, you still cannot prove Geiru committed the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't lose your nerve now! Keep charging forward or you'll feel my blade at your back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">E-Enough with the threats already! I got it! <thought>Talk about pressure! All right, Athena. Take a deep breath and go over everything again!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm going to revisualize the case from start to finish! I have to find conclusive evidence that Geiru committed this murder! What was Master Toneido making in his dressing room?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No. It couldn't have been soba. If it was... ...Geiru couldn't have gone into the room! I have to remember more carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ramen?! Where the heck did that come from?! Nobody has said a single word about ramen today! I have to remember more carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">By my logic, Master Toneido must've been making udon noodles in his dressing room. But something at the crime scene indicates otherwise. What was found in the bowl on the table?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, that's not right! It if had been udon, it wouldn't conflict with what was actually found at the crime scene. No, there weren't any udon noodles at the scene. In that case...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Of course there wasn't any ramen at the scene! Athena! I forbid you to think of ramen ever again during this trial! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Even though the master wasn't making soba, soba noodles were found at the scene. So that means the noodles had to have come from somewhere. Wait a minute. One mysterious serving of soba noodles...? Hmm... That sounds familiar... Where did the soba in the bowl on the table come from?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, no, no. Geiru is allergic to buckwheat. Just touching it made her hand swell and turn red. She couldn't have made soba noodles. So, in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If a catering service brought it... Wait a minute! If it was a catering service, then somebody must've delivered it! And nobody testified about any delivery person! So that means...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The soba noodles found at the scene were from the master's stock of uncooked noodles! But then, why would the culprit go out of her way to cook that soba and put it in the bowl? Why did the culprit cook the soba noodles and put them in the bowl?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru likes soba? What am I talking about? She's allergic to buckwheat! Even if she likes it, she couldn't eat it anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Soba was found at the scene... ...so that means the culprit must've taken the udon with her to hide it. But why did the culprit take the udon away and hide it? It must've been because she...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She has a grudge against udon? That's ridiculous! And, anyway, a person who hated udon certainly wouldn't take it with them! But really, who's ever heard of holding a grudge against an inanimate object?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No, that's not it. Geiru is allergic to soba. She couldn't even handle soba dough, let alone kill somebody with it! Whew! Poor soba dough! I almost falsely accused it of killing someone!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's it! The udon dough was the real weapon used to kill Taifu Toneido! And the reason why no weapon was found is because Geiru got rid of the dough somehow!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The real murder weapon was the udon dough the victim made! If we can find this dough, that'll prove my theory correct! And undeniably prove Geiru's guilt!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Nahyuta:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please recall Owen's eyewitness testimony, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi. If the injury on Geiru's forehead was caused by the victim's knife... ...then Geiru's blood must've dripped down onto the dough used as the murder weapon! That would make the dough pretty conclusive evidence, wouldn't you agree?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Ahh, but where IS this "conclusive evidence"? Let us hear your theory on where this "murder weapon" is!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well, it's... <thought>If I can't find the answer in the evidence I have on hand, we'll lose this trial! So how did Geiru get rid of the udon dough? Think, Athena! What do I have that points to suspicious behavior on Geiru's part?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, then, Ms. Cykes. Let's hear your answer. Where is the "real murder weapon" hidden?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Nice barking you did there. I assume you have the bite to back it up?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Stop distracting me! Especially not right now! This piece of evidence can point us to the location of the hidden murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">............What do you think, Geiru? This piece of evidence does not seem to point us toward anything in my eye.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Ya reckon?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But it's not a given, right?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I recall learning a phrase for this once! "Reckgiven!" And with this here defense, "ya reckon, that's a given" that this don't point us to nothin'.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Um, please stop slaughtering the English language, Your Honor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Huuuh? What is it? I'm just an innocent girl. I don't know aaanything about a muuuuurder!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Stuff that cute act in your balloon hat!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Kuh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru got rid of the dough she used to kill Master Toneido in a bold and daring way. She did it right in front of Prosecutor Blackquill's nose by feeding it to her dog!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">N-No! I-I...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ha ha ha ha ha! Of course! Now it all makes sense. I was puzzled as to why Geiru, who should know her own dog's eating habits... ...would feed Jugemu more than he could possibly finish!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your Honor! Please order an investigation of the yard right now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what should the police at the theater be looking for, exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Jugemu must've buried his leftover dumplings somewhere around his doghouse. Dumplings that Geiru made out of the udon dough with her blood in it!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Graaagh! Ngaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Th-This is preposterous!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I want to thank you, Simon. If you hadn't kept me going, I might've given up along the way.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. What are you blathering on about? You still have work to do! Now, by your hand... finish this wretched case off, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it! Geiru, do you remember what you said would happen when the truth is finally revealed?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">When the truth's revealed... ...it'll be yer balloon or mine that goes POP! Got it?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, now the truth is out, and it looks to me like... ...it's YOUR balloon that goes POP!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Pohlkunkaaaaa!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I... I...  I'm... a rakugo artist... I was the one... who was supposed to... inherit that name...! But then... ...then... Shisho... Why are my balloons burstin'...? Daddy... are ya mad at me...? I... I've been a bad girl... I... I...  AAAAAIEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEYAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">*sniffle* Ooooh...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you ready to tell us everything now, Geiru?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">The whole reason... I entered the world of rakugo in the first place... ...was to follow in my father's wonderful footsteps, and inherit his stage name.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">His stage name...? You don't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">"Uendo Toneido"...</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I knew I wasn't very good at storytelling, but I thought that... ...if I did the stupid balloon thing like Shisho wanted, I'd inherit the name someday. But Master Toneido gave the name to his junior disciple... Yeah... That's why I took my revenge on Shisho during the show celebrating the name succession.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that... was your entire motive...?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">I doubt anybody else could understand, but... ...inheriting my father's name was everything to me. It was my whole reason for living.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Of all the days you could have taken your revenge... ...why did you choose the day of the show?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Because I wanted to pay Uendo back for stealing what was rightfully mine... I wanted to pin the blame on him at the show where all the Toneido fans were gathered...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But then, Uendo tried to shift the blame onto Bucky Whet... And now we know the whole story...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There's just one more thing I want to know. Did you know Master Toneido was making udon in his dressing room yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">No, I didn't. When I saw the soba-making tools, I was worried about my allergy... But it was my only chance to get my revenge on the two of 'em, so I went ahead and did it.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So it was a premeditated crime, but in the end, you only went through with it on impulse. Then, the allergic reaction on your hand... Is it from touching the soba in the refrigerator with your bare hands... ...when you were tampering with the crime scene after your master's death?</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">Yeah... By that time, I wasn't clearheaded enough to worry about my allergy.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Geiru... How could you do all this, you idiot...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Geiru... ...I get your desire to inherit your father's name. But what you really should've inherited from him wasn't his name... ...but his heart.</line>
<line speaker="Geiru">H-His... heart...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you have anything to add, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi? Any objections?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...No, Your Honor.  ............Ms. Athena Cykes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-Yes? <thought>That's the first time he's used my name!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I shall... be sure to remember your name.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............Really?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It seems he finally recognizes you as a proper adversary.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thanks! That's all I ask, Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like there are no further objections. Bailiff, please bring in the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, good. It seems you have made a full recovery. Now then, this court finds the defendant, Bucky Whet...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Congratulations, Bucky! I'm so glad you were found innocent!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Thanks for everything, Miz Chickadee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But it still sucks that you were accused of a crime you didn't commit! Did Uendo have it out for you or something?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">I don't think so...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Uendo said it was a spur-of-the-moment idea he got when he saw the soba-themed cards.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Simon! Where have you been?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I stopped in at Uendo's questioning. Only you, Bucky... could get framed for a crime on a whim.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">No way... I almost got convicted out of convenience...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, at least you've been completely cleared of all charges, so... buck up, Bucky! On a more important note, what I really want to know is... ...why didn't Master Toneido let Geiru inherit her father's name?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Wh-Whattaya mean, "on a more important note," Miz Chickadee?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww, don't be such a "Whet" blanket -- just go with the flow! Now, come on! You think the master was trying to encourage her to quit the entertainment business?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Naw, that's not it. He didn't give the name to her because he wanted Geiru to find her own calling in life... ...to perform whatever she wanted without being bound by her father's name or rakugo. Making udon was his way of showing his support for her in her new endeavor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that's why he called you to the theater, huh? To teach him how to make udon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. A more roundabout way, I've never seen, but that's Master Toneido for you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So this entire incident happened because of a misunderstanding? How sad...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">By the way, Geiru wasn't the only person Master Toneido was trying to cheer on. Even though the person in question still seems unaware of the master's intentions.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">What? You talking about me? Come on, no way! All that old man ever did was criticize my soba!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's not true, Bucky... <thought>There must be a way to make Bucky see just how much Master Toneido cared about him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Bucky:</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Huh? I thought this would do the trick, but I guess not...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Bucky">I knew it -- that old man never expected much outta me...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. You're so dense, the both of you. Bucky, take a good look at this deed, and at the holder's name, in particular.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">I-It's still in my name...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Master Toneido was just up to one of his tricks when he said he "stole" the shop from you. He was trying to force you to grow into a truly capable owner in your father's stead.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He probably used some tough love on you so that the shop wouldn't just go belly up.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">...I-I see... I-I never knew... Oh, Master Toneido... I'm so sorry...! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Keep working hard, Bucky, and pay him back by living up to his expectations.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Thanks, Simey! And you too, Miz Chickadee! One day, my soba's gonna be so good, it'll knock that old man's socks clean off! After all, I'm the fourth-generation owner of Whet Soba, Whet Noodle No. 4! Well, I'd better be getting back to my shop. I gotta get ready for the lunch rush! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hold on! Could I place an order for delivery, Bucky?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Yes, Miz Chickadee?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Could you deliver a bowl of udon to Geiru -- on behalf of her master?</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">...You got it! I'll make sure it's got all the TLC Master Toneido would've packed in it, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">Well, see you! Be sure to drop by the shop sometime!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I will! And I'll bring the whole agency with me!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do us all proud, Bucky.</line>
<line speaker="Bucky">I'll have the best soba in town waiting for ya when you come! Peace out!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ahhh... It's nice to see somebody giving it their all, isn't it? I wonder if I leveled up any thanks to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Don't kid yourself. The trial would've been a spectacle and a half had I not been by your side.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Y-You don't know that!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. For a lawyer who's versed in psychology, you're too full of weak points. You need to learn to analyze yourself more objectively.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Or, you could just teach me your famous mind tricks, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Way to shut someone down! And why not?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Because the more pesky lawyers there are, the harder my job becomes. So it's in my best interest for you to remain green forever!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! What about what's in MY best interest, huh?! Besides, weren't YOU the one who had the wool pulled over your eyes by Uendo?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Must you remind me?! How could I have known Uendo would do "Time Soba"?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, speaking of "Time Soba," I just thought of something funny!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Oh, goodie. I can't wait.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, here it is. In "Time Soba"... ...why didn't mon number nine get counted? Come on. Do you know, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How should I know?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because... seven ate nine! Thank you, thank you! I'll be here all week!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">ROTFL!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph! THAT, I should've known. Come on, let's go get soba or something and go home.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Your treat?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I'll treat you to 50% of the tab! And don't forget -- you still owe me for that manju!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really, Simon? It wouldn't hurt for you to pay for me every once in a while, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Quit squawking and start walking, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">H-Hey! Wait for meeeeee!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I may still have a ways to go as a lawyer... ...but just like Mr. Wright, Apollo, and Simon before me... ...I'm going to get there someday! After all, I've inherited their passion for our courts, and the law! Je peux le faire! I can do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Wild guess incoming!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Widget! Shush! You're not supposed to tell!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... That strange device says what you're really thinking, doesn't it, Ms. Cykes? In other words, the only real "nonsense" here is your wild guess, isn't it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeowch! <thought>Et tu, Widget?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Oh? Well, let us ask that panda over there what he thinks. Is there really a contradiction here, O noble panda?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Gnrgh... No... there is no contradiction...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And there you have it: if Mister Panda says there is none, then it must be true.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Yikes! D-Down boy... Nice panda...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. That's not even the proper call and response for a knock-knock joke.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">And what's more, her claim does not even make any logical sense.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your performance merits neither applause, nor leniency, defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Everyone's a critic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Widget">Cut me some slack!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>I don't see any inconsistencies in his testimony... I guess my only option here is to press him for more information.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... I don't see any contradictions in her testimony at the moment. I think I'd better press her some more and try to draw more information out of her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>This statement seems a bit fishy to me. I mean, did Geiru really have her eyes on the dressing room the whole time?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you're not careful, your scrunched-up face might freeze that way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I see... Thanks for the concern, Your Honor. <thought>This from a man with a scowl on his face... In any case, I think I'd better take another good look through the evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, uh... do YOU notice anything about the testimony, Simon?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Surely you jest. Are you trying to trick me into helping you?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, at least I'M not the one trying to hide the fact that I don't have any ideas!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Rats. The one time I didn't need to be right. Well, if even Simon doesn't see anything, then I guess there are no contradictions. There's only one thing to do at a time like this: press until we get some new testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's the matter, Athena? Have you been bested by Prosecutor Sad Monk already?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Of course not! <thought>I just don't have any idea what to do...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Your expression tells me you have no idea what to do. Then, here's my advice: Why don't you try focusing on this statement here? Though what it contradicts with, well... I'll leave that to you to puzzle out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Why can't he stop with the mind games and just tell me which piece to present already? Anyway, I'd better try comparing the evidence with the statement he showed me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">Match, match... Ahhh, I see. "MATCH," as in... Manage to Assert a Thoughtful, Calculated Hypothesis. In other words, YOU are the something here that didn't "MATCH," correct?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. It appears you've met your match.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No worries! That was just one match. There's still the rest of the game to go!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Uendo">I can express many emotions, such as surprise, sadness, and anger upon my cushions. To me, these expressions are simply an act. If I lost control over such things, I wouldn't be very effective on stage, now would I?</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Uh-oh. Looks like I got it wrong.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Keep it simple, Athena. Thinking too hard will only drive you mad as well.</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmm... Maybe Uendo saw something to make him feel this way...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Owen">*s-sniffle* Waaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Can't you be a bit gentler on him? He's just a five-year-old. Come on, little one. Is this what made you so sad?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Ooooooh... Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Like you could do any better, Simon!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">......Blame your shoddy answer, not me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! Okay, okay! I'll get it right next time!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Um... no. Not at all, lady.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"L-Lady"?! B-But you're technically older than me...! Look, Owen, don't call me "lady," okay?</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Oh, no! Now the lady is mad at me! Waaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ms. Cykes! Please don't make the witness cry!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Hmph. It's not THAT funny...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Owen, this emotion is inconsistent with your statement.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">"Incon..." Huh? What does that mean?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, let's see... It means your feelings and what you said don't match each other.</line>
<line speaker="Owen">Y-You mean, I did something bad?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No no, that's not what I'm...</line>
<line speaker="Owen">I-I'm sorry, really! I'll try to be a good boy from now on, honest! *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, boy. I'm not getting anywhere here. <thought>Hmm... Maybe I'M the one who did something wrong. I'd better rethink this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims. This court finds the defendant, Bucky Whet...</line>
</xml>