
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Revolution</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean Ms. Fey is still being held hostage? And who's this "mastermind"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Paul Atishon-Wimperson was nothing more than a puppet. His benefactor was the one pulling the strings. But I have no idea who they are.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So all we know is it's the person he was trying to give the orb to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. He was just following orders. Whoever it is, it seems they really want to get their hands on the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, Ms. Fey's abduction is the work of this so-called "benefactor," too?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right again. Whoever they are, they're in Khura'in... ...along with Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder who they could be.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Wright, this Maya -- the spirit medium you've been talking about... She wouldn't happen to be that bun-haired young lady you defended back in Khura'in?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's her. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I see... I think I know what's going on here.  I've got good news for you, Wright. Maya is somewhere safe. That much I'm sure of.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Heh heh heh. So that's who the little snot's patron is. It's all starting to make sense. That fool has no idea I'm here in the States with you all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, you mind filling us in?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">..........................................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! ...No caller ID. I wonder who's calling?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">*beep*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hello?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">Mr. Phoenix Wright, yes? Let me start by thanking you... ...for taking such good care of my subordinate.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Who is this?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">I believe you know me as Mr. Atishon's... "benefactor."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like they're using a voice changer or something to disguise themself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where's Maya?! Is she safe?!</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...I had my ears on today's proceedings. What a shock it was to hear that the key to solving the orb's riddle is a spirit medium. I admit, I did not see that coming.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait, did they plant a listening device in here somehow?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phone">Nevertheless, don't think for a minute that it will guarantee Maya Fey's safety. She is not the only medium within my reach, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You harm a hair on Maya's head and you'll have to answer to me!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Wright, give it here a sec.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hey, there. How's it going, stranger?</line>
<line speaker="Phone">...Who is this?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Why, it's your friendly neighborhood dragon. I just happen to be in the U.S. on a little trip. ...Minister of Justice Inga Karkhuul Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-Inga?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya's kidnapper...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Is Khura'in's... Minister of Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Dh-Dhurke?! Is that you, ya dirty turncoat?! How in the--! What in blazes is going on here?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, you know, just popped over to the States for a little R&amp;R. But enough about me, Inga. That was a poor excuse for a bluff you pulled just now. We both know your threats are as empty as your head. You can't lay a hand on Maya Fey, and I do mean that literally.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Ugh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is he talking about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You can kiss your chances of getting the orb goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">...Heh heh heh. Maya Fey ain't my only... how shall I say... insurance, you know, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">I've got someone dear to you right in the palm of my hand, see? Now that one, well... You can imagine what kinds of things I could do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">! ............</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh heh. Glad you're seeing things my way. Meet me at Amara's Tomb tomorrow, 3 PM sharp. And you better come alone, got it? If all goes well, the orb is all you'll need to get Maya Fey back.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dh-Dhurke, what's going on?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You heard him. I have to get back to Khura'in at once.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Why?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No time to explain.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But are you even going to make it? What if there are no seats left on the next flight? Plus, you're a wanted man. They're not just going to let you get on a plane.</line>
<line speaker="???">Let me worry about that, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ch-Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Taking care of the hostage situation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, now that you mention it... ...Pearl did say that she saw you around in Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had him look into a few things while I was on my way back from Khura'in. ...Including Maya's situation, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I was astonished to hear she was still in Khura'in earlier... ...but it explained why I found no connection between her and Mr. Atishon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry to interrupt, but going back to the plane situation...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I've taken the liberty of chartering one for us. It's ready to take off at any time. And I will do what's necessary to hide the fact that Dhurke Sahdmadhi is onboard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wow. <thought>Must be nice to be chief prosecutor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, we have no time to lose. We must head for Khura'in at once.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm going, too! After all, you're bound to need my help!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No fair! I wanna go, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This isn't a vacation, Trucy. Besides, I'll need you to hold down the fort.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I should also only bring what's necessary.</thought> ...Sorry Trucy, but would you mind holding on to this stuff for me?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Fine. But you'd better bring me back something besides just more evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Excellent. Now, let us make haste... to Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that's how our sudden trip to the Kingdom of Khura'in began. I never imagined I'd return to the country of my youth under such circumstances, though... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was a long flight. It's already 2:30 in the afternoon. Talk about cutting it close. ........... <thought>The Kingdom of Khura'in... This is no time to reminisce, but... ...I gotta say, this place sure brings back memories.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hurry up, Apollo! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right behind you!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Amara's Tomb is located in the courtyard of Ga'ran Palace. We should have just enough time to get there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sure, no sweat!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I'll contact the royal family and the local police, and inform them of our arrival.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo. I'm sure this place brings back memories, but could you reminisce later? Time's running out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right. We have to find Ms. Fey before it's too late.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know you probably want to reminisce and all, but there's no time for that right now!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right. We've got to get to Amara's Tomb with Ms. Fey is being held captive!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Don't go showing me stuff for no reason! We have to find Ms. Fey before it's too late!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*{huff, puff* *huff, puff* I wasn't made for all the running and climbing and near-drowning I've done this week.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's 2:45... Only 15 minutes left.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">See that cylindrical building rising in the distance? That's Amara's Tomb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Amara... Wasn't that the previous queen? The one who was assassinated?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. And I'm the one they pinned it on</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It will take a few minutes to get to the tomb from here.</line>
<line speaker="???">So, you have returned... Barbed Head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I've seen her before on the news. If I remember correctly, this is the crown princess Rayfa Padma Khura'in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What are you people doing here? This is the Royal Residence! Commoners are not allowed entry without permission.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A prosecutor from the States... ...should've already called and requested permission for us to enter. As to why we're here, Your Benevolence... Have you seen Minister Inga?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">If you seek my father, I just saw him heading toward Amara's Tomb.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Was he with anyone? You know, like some shady-looking underlings or something?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">No, he was alone. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looks like she has no idea about Ms. Fey's abduction.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You hear that? I think we have company.</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Bow down before her glooooooory!!! Her Eminence Queen Ga'ran, grand priestess of Khura'in approooooooooaches!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? ...Ga'ran? Ahhh! I-It's--!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Q-Queen Ga'ran!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">............... Guards... Surround Amara's Tomb at once!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Emineeeeeeeence! Ur di'hara Ga'ran!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's she doing? Is she going to help us?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Excuse me, Your Eminence...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">So, our "Barbed Head" lawyer returns. May we presume you are here for Maya Fey, the spirit medium who has been abducted?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, you may!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Allow us to apologize for the criminal actions of our husband.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... no need to apologize for him!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Honestly, Inga... Abducting a guest in our country? How could you?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Father... abducted someone?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Eminence, what about those soldiers over there?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">They are the Ga'ran Royal Guard, soldiers who serve the crown and no other.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Royal guard?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">They are an elite force selected from only the most loyal and outstanding of our subjects.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And why have you ordered them to surround the tomb?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">The police will not come if it is my husband who is committing the crime. We shall have to storm the tomb and take Minister Inga into custody ourselves!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaat?! Y-You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ga'ran! No! His hostage is in there!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Dhurke! How dare you set foot in the palace! Have you come to turn yourself in?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Listen, we need to call a truce for now!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Ga'ran Royal Guard! Seize this traitor of the crown!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">As you wiiiiiiish, Your Eminence! Resist and you diiiiiie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="???">Dhurke:</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...A hostage exchange? And why would he choose to do such a thing with you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We can talk about that later. Right now, I need to get in there before it's too late. If I can't resolve this in twenty minutes, you can storm the palace. Now then... if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Dhurke, wait! ... *sigh* Guards, allow the insurgent Dhurke Sahdmadhi to pass.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head, you have some explaining to do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... Well, while we're waiting here... ...Apollo, why don't you explain the situation?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaat?! M-Me?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Leave nothing out, Horn Head, or I'll dehorn you where you stand!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Horn Head? She doesn't waste any time coming up with nicknames. And what's with the attitude? Her father is the one who abducted Ms. Fey!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is no time to be looking around. Not until Dhurke gets back.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do my ears deceive me, or did I hear talk about my father abducting someone?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um, you heard right. He abducted Maya Fey, and...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-Insolent fool!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Pardon my rudeness!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">A gentle soul such as my father could not possibly have committed such a crime!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Gentle"? You think he's gentle? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm afraid it's true, Your Benevolence. He's holed up in that tomb as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Really? I find this difficult to believe. Why would he do such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, Your Benevolence? You saw your father heading toward the tomb?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I did. I was over on that veranda, deep in thought... ...when I saw him hurrying toward the tomb. I'd say it was about 10 minutes ago. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why was he rushing? Maybe he was worried he'd be late?</thought> Did you see anyone else heading for the tomb?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I saw no one else after he entered.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So Minister Inga and Ms. Fey are the only ones in there besides Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows? But I wouldn't be surprised if he had a minion or two with him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke... I sure hope he's all right.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Horn Head! Stop wasting time and explain what's going on here! And make it quick, or I'll yank those horns right off your head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nngh... How about we keep our hands to ourselves and I'll explain everything...? <thought>Guess I'd better start talking...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Where do you think you are going?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, right. We're supposed to wait for Dhurke to return.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's only been five minutes? <thought>Argh, it feels like an eternity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Patience, Apollo, patience.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's been almost twenty minutes. What's taking Dhurke so long?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...The appointed time has come. Our royal guard shall now storm in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, can't you wait just a little longer?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">No, we cannot. Every second we wait puts the hostage's life in even more danger. Therefore, we see no alternative but to order our guards to storm in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But that'll put Ms. Fey's life in danger, too!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Guards! Storm the tomb and seize Minister Inga, along with the insurgent Dhurke Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Emineeeeeeeence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! Dhurke's under arrest, too?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Naturally. That traitorous snake assassinated my predecessor, Queen Amara. Now go! Seize them both!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Raaaaaaaaah! We're going in! Follow me, men! For Her Eminenece! Ur dihara Ga'raaaaaaaan!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>I hope no one gets hurt.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Ah! Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! Your Eminineeeeeeeence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the--? Why are they running back out?!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">What is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">S-Something terrible has happened! Dhurke...! Th-Th-The minister...! H-H-He's dead!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">What's this?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WH-WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, quick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm right behind you!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">No one enters without our--! ...Hmph! Come, let us see what has transpired!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Emineeeeeeeence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Where's Dhurke?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, over there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke! Wh-Wh-What... What have you done?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">..........Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">L-Look!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">So it is... Minister Inga who has fallen? ...! Guards! Seize this murderous man at once!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Emineeeeeeeence! Surrender or peeeeeeerish, rebel scum!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">N-No, wait! Aaaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke! <thought>They're taking him away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oww! <thought>Dhurke just threw something at me.</thought> Wait, this is the... <thought>Is he telling me to keep it safe?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">......Nick? ...Is that you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-Maya! Are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Dh-Dhurke, he... he saved me. ...I feel... exhausted. I can't keep my eyes... open...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Minister Inga -- the man behind Ms. Fey's abduction -- had been killed. And Dhurke was arrested for his murder. So it was that the abduction of Maya Fey came to a sudden and unexpected resolution. With this, the curtain fell on the minister, but things were far from over.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! What happened?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......I can't say for sure. But from what I can tell, it seems Dhurke has killed Minister Inga.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaaaaaaaaaat?! You think he did it to save Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Most likely... But who knows? I'm really confused right now...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">M-My father... He's...? This cannot be! I must see for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Your Benevolence! We cannot allow you to pass!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Fools! Stand aside!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Forgive us! But we have direct orders from Her Eminence, Queen Ga'ran!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Uuuuuuuuuuuh! Father... Oh, Father...! Dhuuuuuurke! You will pay for this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo, let's go regroup somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... <thought>Dhurke... It wasn't really you that did it... right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Are you okay, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Y-Yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth's speaking with the local police... ...so let's sit tight until he returns.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...O-Okay. ...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I know you must be in a state of shock right now, but I need you to stay with us, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's right. I can't go to pieces now!</thought> Thanks, Mr. Wright. I'll be fine!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, Mr. Justice... I'm afraid I have some bad news. It looks like things will only get more complicated from here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Edgeworth... What's happening with Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As I understand it, he has been officially charged with the murder of Minister Inga.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-He has?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">However, I did manage to get us permission to investigate the crime scene. And I expect we'll be allowed to visit Mr. Sahdmadhi shortly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Thank you. <thought>I'm sure glad Prosecutor Edgeworth is here with us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Also, it just so happens that Detective Skye is here in Khura'in... ...so I have asked her to assist us with our investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! What's she doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Prosecutor Sahdmadhi has grown quite fond of her. He's been ferrying her around all over the place. A few days here, a few days there... They've almost become a team of sorts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Despite what Nahyuta says... ...it seems he thinks highly of Ema's skills.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So what now, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think I'll go pay Dhurke a visit at the Detention Center.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I... want to go check in on Maya at the hospital. What about you, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well... If there's footwork to be done, I'd better stick with Apollo and give him a hand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Very well. Then I will accompany Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, we'll go our separate ways for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right. If anything comes up, you have my cell number.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you know your way around here, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's been over ten years since I left... but I'll try not to get us hopelessly lost.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright stayed there the entire time he was here, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would he stay at a temple instead of a hotel?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He says it helped to cut costs. Long stays at a hotel really add up, you know. But he had to sleep on the floor with a load of strangers. There weren't any showers, either.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that's worse than staying at a youth hostel for backpackers.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is said to be a sacred spring, and a pathway for souls to follow. The people of Khura'in believe the spring draws souls to the temple... ...and by the truth gained in the Hall of Justice beyond, they are memorialized. It seems that legal trials and funeral rites are inseparable in this country.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There sure are a lot of temples around here. In fact, it looks like most of the buildings around here are related to Khura'inism.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Queen Ga'ran sure has a lot of personal attendants.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. The Ga'ran Royal Guard... They're like her own private army.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">More like an elite fan club made up of carefully selected soldiers who adore her. That's how I see it anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's... a pretty blunt way of putting it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dhurke Sahdmadhi -- the charismatic leader of the Defiant Dragons -- arrested. This is going to deal a major blow to the rebels.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. I can already see Datz having a heart attack when he finds out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Speaking of Datz, he was on the plane with us... ...but I haven't seen him since we landed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke said he wanted Datz to go to him before he caused any more trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Yeah, he strikes me as a troublemaker.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I just hope he doesn't do anything crazy, like trying to break Dhurke out of jail.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I thought that attorney badges were the same around the world. But I just realized this type is only used back home.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You've had your badge for a while now, and you're JUST noticing that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, I'm still getting used to things after all the time I spent in Europe. But as they say, when in Rome!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what are we even talking about anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The orb... It was a real surprise to find out that it's hollow on the inside, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, and an even bigger surprise to find that the founder's face was hidden within.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But now that the orb's secret has been revealed... ...how are you supposed to restore it to its original state?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well, it was probably wax or something that melted to reveal the figure inside, so... ...if we turned it upside down and heated it up again, it should go back to the way it was.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ohhh, I get it! That's one clever little contraption.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I've been thinking about that photo. Your father was quite the manly man, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. I sense a compliment in there somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? Where'd you get that idea?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... N-Never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Never mind what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... Er, nice weather we're having today.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......... Aww... Is there something you wanted to hear me say, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">L-Look! Just forget I said anything, okay?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo! Here to see your old man, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke. Are they done interrogating you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nope, the fun hasn't even started. I imagine they'll really take me over the coals though.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't even want to think about how harsh their interrogation method will be.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah, but that's nothing compared to what they'll do if they find him guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">They've branded me a terrorist who killed the previous queen, and now the justice minister. If found guilty of these crimes, I'll be facing a very public execution.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Public execution...?! <thought>This is worse than I thought!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Come on, son. Turn that frown upside down! You'll jinx us. As soon as I get out of here, I'll take you to this tasty hash house I know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........I'd like that. <thought>I really need to find out what happened. Time to switch to work mode.</thought> Dhurke, can you tell me what happened? ...Oh, and there's also something I want you to take a look at.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Don't do it, Athena. Don't ring that bell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ack! Wh-Who, me...?! Perish the thought. I mean, would I ever do something so childish?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right, all right! Put your bracelet away already. Talk about unfair!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That guard's standing so still, and with such great posture... I wonder if he spends his days just watching the dust dance in the sunlight. Wait a second. Don't you do that in court sometimes, Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eep! You mean you noticed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't think you can take it easy just because I'm the lead lawyer on this one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, what happened in there? You didn't really kill Minister Inga, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, the thing is... ...I really don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I remember seeing the mural of the founder right as I entered the tomb... ...but I got all dizzy immediately after that. The next thing I knew, I was standing there with a bloody knife in my hand... ...and covered in Inga's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you don't remember meeting with him?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No. The last thing I remember after entering the tomb is feeling really dizzy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's no way he can explain what happened if he can't remember anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Hmm. I suppose there's no getting out of this one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we can't give up yet!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! I was just messing with you, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, stop. It's not funny.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sheesh. Nothing seems to faze him. Not even being arrested for murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This is going to be one tough case, Apollo. Not only have I been charged with Inga's murder... ...but I've also been charged with Amara's assassination from twenty-three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're on trial for two charges?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ga'ran is practically licking her chops just thinking about my public execution. Guess it means we can't afford to lose our heads, huh. Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I don't know how you can laugh at a time like this.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...So, son, I take it you'll be defending me at my trial?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Of course. You can count on me.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's my boy! Looks like your nerves are as steely as those vocal chords of yours! After all, you've got the Defense Culpability Ace to contend with, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, right... So if you're found guilty... ...then I'll be charged with the same double homicide, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't tell me you forgot about that...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'll-- I'll be fine. I-I just have to make sure we win this one.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You sure? Because you don't sound very fine.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Um, Apollo? What was that about an assassination twenty-three years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About that incident twenty-three years ago... That was when the previous queen, Amara, was assassinated, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. Someone set her private residence on fire. She lost her life in the ensuing blaze.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you were arrested for the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why would they arrest you, Mr. Sahdmadhi? Weren't you just a lawyer back then? What relation could you have had with the queen?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Um, about that... Amara was... well... she was my wife. I may not look the part, but I was once husband to a queen. In short, I was royalty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? No waaaaaay! Are you saying you won the heart of the reigning queen?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! C'mon, you're talking to a guy who hones his prowess against witnesses on the stand. Even a queen is no match for this dragon's glare!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Wow, you're really something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So was a verdict ever reached, Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I acted as my own attorney and won. ...Until I was accused of fabricating evidence, that is. Then it all went south.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Now where have I heard a story like that before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What happened after that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I, uh... I made a run for it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You ran?! But why?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I didn't kill Amara, and I didn't fabricate any evidence. But if I had stuck around for a retrial, I'd have been found guilty for sure. I couldn't allow that to happen; Amara's true killer would never face justice if I did. So I left my law practice behind and went underground.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But that was twenty-three years ago. ...Are you telling me that after all these years... ...you still haven't discovered the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah... The fact that it was arson means that the crime scene was reduced to ashes. There is little in the way of evidence left. It's just been brick wall after brick wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess that means it's all up to me to figure it out, huh. Along with Minister Inga's murder, of course. ...I think I'm going to be sick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Come on, son. Don't look so down. With you on the case, it'll work out somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I hope he's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Say, son, do you remember my office?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sure. <thought> I remember that messy, dimly lit room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The file I've amassed on Amara's assassination is kept there. I think it might help you on this case. Do you remember how to get there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Let me think... I recall going in through a manhole...</thought> How can I not, Dhurke. i hated how I always got so dirty getting there. And that stench... <thought>That old case is important, too, but I should probably focus on the minister's murder first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm proud of you, son. You've really become a fine lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, at least it means I'm qualified to defend you.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...To think the day would come where you'd come to my defense. I'm one lucky man. Now I can die in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, slow down! I'm going to prove you innocent, so...!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! Just pulling your leg, son!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Even when he's in the slammer, Dhurke is Dhurke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I see you got it safely out of the tomb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why did you throw it at me like that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I want you to listen carefully, son. The orb must not fall into Ga'ran's hands... not ever.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought Minister Inga was the one who was after it. He was the one who lent it to Professor Buff to study, after all. So haven't you exposed his crime now?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I have, but... ...there's more connected to this relic than meets the eye... Much more. And whatever it is, I can't help feeling that it could turn this entire kingdom upside down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You said something like that before. <thought>Looks like Dhurke's intuition is at it again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ga'ran will do anything to retrieve this... ...so guard it well, son -- at least until tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's the only remaining photo of your father. Take good care of it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I will. ...I'm just surprised to see it after all these years.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I had a tough time tracking it down and retrieving it. It was taken by some European tourists who just happened to be watching your father. I had one of my men go to Europe to look them up and ask whether we could have it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You went through all that trouble?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...I did. So don't go losing it or anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I said I'd take good care of it, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm afraid your time is up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! N-Nahyuta.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It's time for the prisoner's interrogation. So begone, you putrid-headed, criminal-abetting lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! Don't tell me... you're the prosecuting attorney?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! But that would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Is there a problem here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You bet there is. He's your father!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...And your point is...? My relation to the accused is irrelevant. The fact remains, I am a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, that's not what I... <thought>I don't think I'm getting through to him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Nahyuta. Long time no see, son. How've you been?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Look... I hear you've been serving Ga'ran -- rather faithfully, in fact. Whatever happened to our dream of taking her down and changing this country, son?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........The past is the past.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What do you mean? Why are you doing this?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........It's simple. People change. The Nahyuta you knew exists no more.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Listen, son, I don't know what made you change like this... ...but you're still my boy, even if you prosecute my case. The rest of the Defiant Dragons and I eagerly await your return. Whenever you're ready, we'll welcome you back with open arms.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">........Ngh! .........As I said, I've moved on. Now, let us waste no more time; for flowers do not blossom simply from talk of the past.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Nahyuta... Why do I get the feeling there's something he wants to say, but can't?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Guard, move the accused to the interrogation room.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Yes, sir! This way, you rebel scum!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ow! Watch it! Not so rough, will you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Nahyuta. Is he seriously going to prosecute his own father?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this is the tomb of Amara, the previous queen of Khura'in. It's really lavish. I guess you could say it's fit for a queen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is the faceless woman in that mural over there Amara?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, that's the Holy Mother. She's the one who brought spirit channeling to Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, right. The woman in the orb.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, it's you two. Getting right down to business, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hi, Ema. We heard you'd give us a hand if we needed it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yep. Mr. Edgeworth asked me to help where I could. So, it's been quite a while since you've been back in Khura'in, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, more than ten years, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, you sure didn't waste any time. I mean, you're already mixed up in a murder. You're as big a trouble magnet as Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Please don't say that. My luck's already bad enough as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ema, I hear Prosecutor Sahdmadhi has requested your services again. He seems to have really taken a liking to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You mean His Ephemeral Holiness? MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH. I don't mind that he approves of me and my abilities. It's just, his people skills need some serious work. But when he manages a smile and compliments my work, it's hard to say no. Plus, working on investigations overseas is a priceless experience. But flying back and forth between here and home every few days with no days off... That's been tough, and the lack of sleep has been brutal on my skin. To make matters worse, the defendant in this case is someone I know. I mean, how could this get any worse?! MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like they've got one complicated prosecutor-detective relationship going on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We better get Ema's okay before we start snooping around.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, have you determined the cause of death?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Blood loss from a stab wound. A single stab in the back was enough to cause the victim to bleed to death. The estimated time of death is 3 PM, which is when Dhurke came onto the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Any suspects besides Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No. He, Maya, and the minister were the only ones here. And Maya had been tied up until she was freed by the queen's royal guard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could someone have been hiding somewhere in here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not likely. I was told this tomb was searched from top to bottom right after the murder. And during that time, the royal guard set up a perimeter to prevent anyone from escaping.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In other words, the crime scene was completely sealed off?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It would appear so.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... No way for a third party to escape without being spotted, so... <thought>Great. It's another one of those convoluted locked-room mysteries.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About the victim, Minister Inga... He was the kingdom's Minister of Justice, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. Inga Karkhuul Khura'in was the second most powerful figure in Khura'in. Plus, he was married to the queen.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Seems strange that someone of his status would abduct someone.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently, he only told a few of his most loyal subordinates about his plan. That way, there was little chance of the police or even the queen finding out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What was Inga hoping to gain by getting his hands on the orb?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That I don't know. But I'm working on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I wonder if it really was for what Paul Atishon-Wimperson said...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I must deliver it to my benefactor at all costs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do they want that relic for anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. It's something to do with an old legend. My patron seeks the great power said to be granted to whoever solves its secret.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A great power that is said to be bestowed on whoever solves the orb's secret. In Khura'in, only those who can channel spirits are said to be fit to rule. Was that why Inga wanted such power? Did he want to be king?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is the tomb of the previous queen?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, Queen Amara was laid to rest here. She lost her life in an arsonist's blaze. What a tragic end. I heard this tomb sits on the actual site of her residence before it was burned down. They built it on the same spot so her soul could rest in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this is where the fire happened, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why do you think Minister Inga was holding Ms. Fey captive here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's the perfect spot, if you think about it. It's close to his private quarters, which made it easy to keep an eye on his prisoner. And the courtyard is only open to the royal family, so he had little fear of prying eyes. Plus, the tomb is normally locked, and only the royal family is allowed access.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So that's why he picked this place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How long had Ms. Fey been held captive?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">About six days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?! That long?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It appears that she was severely weakened by her prolonged confinement. She passed out as soon as she was freed, and is now on an IV drip at the hospital. She's been asleep ever since.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is Amara's sarcophagus. Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The sarcophagus is surrounded by a curtain. I bet someone could've hidden behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">True, but that's one of the many places the royal guard checked after storming in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, they were really thorough.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes, well, apparently, one of their members loves mystery novels. He peered into every nook and cranny with an almost frightening amount of gusto. And when he was done, he said: "Very interesting. It's like one of those locked-room mysteries."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like he's in the wrong line of work.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, it's covered in blood.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With a blood spatter this large , it must've gotten all over the killer, too. Come to think of it... There was blood on Dhurke's clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The circumstantial evidence points to Dhurke being the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's what I'd conclude if I were a cop, too. <thought>Why are things always so bleak for me...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, these curtains open, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...That's one big sarcophagus.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They say the mummy of Amara, the former queen, rests inside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A mummy, huh? ...Rats, it's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hey, don't touch that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean we can't search inside it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Not a chance. Besides, it's not something anyone'd try opening, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if the real killer's hiding inside?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey! Anyone in there?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">D-Don't do that! You're going to get us cursed!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">C-C-Cursed?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The queen likely bears a grudge toward the living after such a violent, painful death. So no one dares touch the sarcophagus for fear of incurring her wrath.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Oh no, Apollo. What am I going to do?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't look at me.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...In any case, the sarcophagus is temperature controlled. It's kept really cold to preserve the mummy. So even if someone did decide to hide inside it, they would eventually freeze to death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see... <thought>Still, if they bundled up, I bet a person could hide in there for a little while.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like the Holy Mother was painted here to watch over Amara's sarcophagus.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So it's like, this tomb is protected by the founder? That must be so reassuring to those she left behind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Only one problem: they didn't paint the eyes she needs to do said watching.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come to think of it, she doesn't have a mouth to smile down on the tomb with, either. It's actually kind of creepy. I wonder if being watched over by something like that gives the queen nightmares.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey, hey. Keep that up, and the founder just might come and "watch over" you, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, one of the statues is broken.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but it's kind of hard to see from here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's check it out when we get a little closer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One of the statues is broken. Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This thing's more splinter than statue now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The bullet from the victim's gun did a real number on it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It seems like something you'd get cursed for, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">In Minister Inga's case, I'd say getting your ticket punched is curse enough.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, but don't curses extend to the afterlife?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You need to stop taking what Nahyuta says so seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I'm perfectly capable of thinking for myself!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a magatama... I think. Did it come from the broken statue?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, Apollo, there's another one. But the other statues only have one each.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right. Maybe this statue was special or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, there's a bullet here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It's from the pistol the victim was carrying. My guess is he tried to shoot his attacker, but missed, and the bullet ended up here. We've already determined the rifling marks to be a match to his gun.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Rifling marks? Aren't those...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh ho! Shall I explain? The science behind it is absolutely fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, no, we're good.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmph, lawyers... Think they're so smart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You do realize we can hear you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? There's something shiny down there. It's a pendant...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">There's blood on it. I wonder who it belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All we know is it's not the victims. No one in the royal family recognized it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ema, did you lift any fingerprints from it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I did, but... ...I wasn't able to get a clean one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's too bad.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">But the blood turned out to be the victim's.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That means it must have fallen here in the course of the murder. <thought>It might be Dhurke's. I should ask him about it later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Guess this is where Inga collapsed when he died. Better take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They've already taken the body away. It's kind of sad how familiar I've become with body outlines.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I have a photo of the body if you're interested. He was stabbed right in the back; the poor guy was practically skewered.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's he wearing on his arms?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Those are the Cuffs of Justice. Seems to be a tradition here for the Minister of Justice to wear those forearm cuffs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They look like they're made of a thick fabric, so I guess they aren't for protection.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe they're for keeping his sleeves out of the way when handling documents.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, that's probably their original purpose. But over the years, the reason for wearing them was probably forgotten. So now, they're just one of many traditional things that people do without knowing why.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh, I get it. Kind of like the way you roll up your sleeves, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Or your psychology, if we're going there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I happen to know why I started, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These white lines indicate where the minister's body fell.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, didn't Ema give us a photo of the crime scene before they took the body away?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like he was stabbed in the back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Those things on his arms... They're called the "Cuffs of Justice," right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, they're supposedly a traditional part of the minister's outfit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this is the murder weapon. Ema, did you find any prints on it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yep, and they were super clear. They belong to one Dhurke Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not good. Were there any others?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There was one more print from another individual... ...but it was too smudged to identify. It's probably an old print from someone else who had handled the knife.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... <thought>Yet another piece of unhelpful info to add to our ever-growing pile... *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apparently, Dhurke's prints were found on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's not very helpful, is it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if this is Inga's cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It should be. His fingerprints are all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you know if he talked with anyone recently?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">There were a few calls logged between him and his underlings. They're all members of the secret police, who were directly under the minister's control.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You mean like spies?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think that's quite it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the minister was armed, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Mm-hm. That's a four-shot pistol. He had it for self-defense, apparently. But it won't be firing anything any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He was carrying a broken gun around for show?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, we recovered a bullet here. Which means the gun probably broke as the minister fired its last round. Thing is... the gun's chambers are all empty. Yet, that one bullet is the only bullet we could find.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That is strange. Where did the other three go?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Maybe Dhurke ate them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We can ask the next time we see him. Just be ready for his predictably "shocking" answer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Inga's pistol... He used to carry it for self-defense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apparently, he fired all four rounds.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but only one slug was recovered in this tomb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's like a small army of monks, all neatly lined up. It looks like they're facing the sarcophagus in prayer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you look carefully, each one has a slightly different expression.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if they used real people as models.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Some are frowning, some are smiling... Hm? There's one that looks like he's trying his hardest not to burst out laughing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Really? Hmm, I wonder why.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's like those times when things are so intense, you can't help but laugh. You know, like at funerals and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They went through all the trouble of depicting that? Talk about going overboard...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's full of ash. My guess would be this is an incense burner.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hey, look, Apollo. There's something in the ashes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Let's see what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's full of ash. They must burn incense in here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, I was wondering, Apollo... Did the ash come from the incense sticks that were burned in this? Or do people put their incense in after there was already she in here to hold them up?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't be silly, Athena. The answer's simple. The ash is the product of prayers from countless visitors who came here. It's not a chicken-or-the-egg kind of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, that's an interesting take on it. It's so much more poetic than mine!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that... a gemstone? Wonder what it's doing here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Heh heh heh, I've got this one covered, Apollo. Would you like to hear my brilliant theory?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess it wouldn't do any harm.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You know how people make wishes by throwing coins into a fountain, right? Well--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, on second thought, I'm good.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaat?! Y-You sure you don't need to hear my theory? I was just about to get to the good part!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's just ask Ema. That'll be much quicker. Excuse me, Ema? What's this gemstone doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, that... It's not a gem, it's a button -- albeit a very expensive one -- from the victim's jacket. Must've fallen off and gotten in there somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">See? Every puzzle has an answer, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, I thought my idea was pretty good... Wait... What's with this soot? See here, on the gemstone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the grape juice Inga was drinking. He was probably nervous before his meeting with Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So he drank grape juice? I'm not seeing the logic here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright told me all about it when he was hospitalized a few years ago. He said grape juice has something in it that helps you relax.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? ...Um, are you sure he was talking about regular, plain old grape juice? Because it sounds like he was talking about the fermented variety.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, he couldn't have meant that. I mean, we're talking about a medical facility. They wouldn't have allowed something like that in.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">R-Right... Let's just leave it at that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a painting up there, but I can't see it very well from here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A baby on a lotus blossom? That's one strange painting.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Apparently, that's part of a mural depicting the life and times of Queen Amara. You know, like a storyboard or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that baby's supposed to be Amara?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This one depicts Amara preaching to the faithful.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's hard to put into words, but I've never seen anything like it. Let's see, the next one is... I-Is that... Dhurke? Why does he have horns?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My best guess is... ...it depicts the first time Amara and Dhurke met.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So he's supposed to be some kind of demon who's seducing her?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, he WAS successful since they got married after that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The mural continues on the opposite wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like the spirit of some country's sultan or something. And she seems to be conveying something to his retainers.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Sh-She's on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This must be Amara's assassination as allegedly carried out by Dhurke. They really made him look evil.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...This is the weirdest one of all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that supposed to be Dhurke facing his punishment in the afterlife? Anyway... Hm? I guess that's the last one.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess we're supposed to see this as a happy ending.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, except nobody came out of this story happy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Fey was apparently tied to this chair. Let's take a closer look. We should try to cover every angle possible here. Slide the Touch Screen... ... or use the Circle Pad <thought>Circle Pad</thought> to look around carefully in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Poor Ms. Fey. She must've been tied up to this chair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can just imagine how much her backside must've hurt after sitting here for so long.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would've been torture for you, I bet. I mean, you don't know how to sit still.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If by that you mean I like to stay active, then I have to agree with you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, there's a bloodstain on one of the chair legs. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really?! Hey, you're right. I completely missed that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's move the chair so we can check under it. ...There's more blood under the chair leg.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm... I wonder what it's doing there. I have some luminol here. Why don't you do some testing around it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look! The bloodstain leads all the way to the sarcophagus!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ema, is this Minister Inga's blood?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hold on one second... .........Huh? That's strange. I didn't get a match.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then...whose blood is it? Dhurke and Ms. Fey weren't wounded as far as we know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And the blood's been wiped up by someone for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, that's strange, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a bloodstain on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's already been mostly wiped up, but the stain leads all the way to the sarcophagus. I wonder whose blood it is.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet you didn't know, but I happen to be a bit of an escape artist myself. Trucy showed me how to do her rope escape trick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-huh. And why would you bother learning something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Because we're always getting into trouble when working cases with Mr. Wright. So I thought it might come in handy someday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess you're right about that. Ms. Fey could've definitely used that knowledge.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right! So now, you just sit right here and we'll get started.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What in the world gave you the idea I wanted to learn?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone could have hid behind these curtains.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Here, I'll go give it a try! Well, can you tell I'm hiding here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I can't tell at all. That's it! That's the perfect hiding place!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it, Apollo! We solved the case!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry to burst your bubble, but... ...the royal guard searched the tomb high and low right after they stormed in. And they said no one else was in here besides Minister Inga, Dhurke, and Ms. Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well. Back to the drawing board, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">My brilliant deduction -- destroyed in three sentences.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Your attorney's badge? Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, that normally gets a better reaction from you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm tired of collecting your fingerprints. It's kind of lost its luster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but who knows? There could be other people's prints on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh, that's true! Hand it over, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............Hmph. The only prints I found were yours.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh, it's all dusty now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, you must need my forensic expertise! Just leave it to me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... Actually, I was wondering if you see anything strange about this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Oh. ....................................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why isn't she saying anything?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, do you mind if we start looking around?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sure, I've already got the okay. Knock yourselves out. Oh, and here. It's a diagram the police drew of the tomb. I thought I'd give you a copy to help your investigation along.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, and let me know if you need my forensic expertise. Don't you dare keep all the fun to yourselves, you hear?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't need to worry about that. <thought>Besides, I'd hardly classify this as "fun".</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... For starters, we're dealing with a locked-room murder. But instead of the tomb being locked, it was being cordoned off by the royal guard. And after the murder, no one was found to be hiding inside. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. In addition... ...we also know that Dhurke's fingerprints are all over the murder weapon. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">The curtain around the sarcophagus was drenched in the victim's blood on one side. The blood must've also gotten on the killer when they stabbed the minister from behind. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke had blood on him when the crime was first discovered. Unfortunately, he doesn't remember what happened. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Athena">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is not good.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So, what we know so far is... ...things couldn't be worse for our case. And that's still and understatement somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, it's looking pretty grim.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, uh! If you two are done here, I'll have to ask you to leave. Go on, scoot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something wrong, Ema? Why are you trying to give us the boot?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...It's just easier if you're not here when His Ephemeral Holiness arrives. ...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Speak of the devil.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">P-Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... </line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Detective Skye... It seems you've spoken at length with these two lawyers. I do hope you've also kept an eye on them.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Y-Yes, of course! Like a hawk! They didn't touch a single thing! Ha, a-ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Give a lawyer an inch, and they'll take a mile. Never forget that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's that look of distrust again.</thought> ...Hey, Nahyuta. Do you really believe that Dhurke's guilty?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And are you seriously going to prosecute this case? I mean, he's your father. You were once part of the Defiant Dragons, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey! Nahyuta! Wait! I said wait! Come on, Athena, after him!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? ...Oh, uh, right behind you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta, would you stop already?!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........What do you want?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's about Dhurke. Would you please hear me out?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I fail to see why I should. Now, if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........Very well. Speak. But make it quick. There is much I must do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Why does everything have to be so difficult with you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Somebody got a little carried away decorating this place. There's a golden lion keeping watch at the entrance.</thought> ...That frog looks like it's cowering under the lion's glare.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? 'Cause to me, it looks like the frog is glaring at the lion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come on, Athena. How does that make any sense?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? I just call 'em as I see 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess we'll have to agree to disagree.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The palace of Queen Ga'ran is built to impress. Its white walls and gold ornamentation lend it an imposing air.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It makes Minister Inga's residence look downright humble by comparison.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It shows the difference in their tastes... and which one wears the pants, so to speak</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The previous queen, Amara, was laid to rest in her own private tomb. Pretty impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They say it cost $800 million to build, and took 400 workers five years to complete. Special memorial rites were also conducted at various points of its construction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's quite an undertaking.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It was built with donations from her devoted subjects and royalty of neighboring countries. It ended up giving a huge boost to the national economy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, Queen Amara must've been one charismatic lady...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, look at those flowers! They give the whole house such a cute vibe! I wonder if this is where Princess Rayfa lives.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I doubt it. She doesn't look like the type to decorate with cute flowers. I mean, I may not know her well, but she seems awfully serious and snobby. I bet she uses nothing but roses and peonies  stuffy old people flowers, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">......Apollo. I guess it's too much to ask that you not judge a book by its cover, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are these... Inga's footprints? They appear to be heading toward the tomb.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Didn't Princess Rayfa mention something about that? You know, something about him rushing over to the tomb before we arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder if he had accidentally dozed off before the exchange or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Vibrant lotus flowers floating on still waters... Butterflies dancing about... It's almost supernatural in its beauty.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And at the center of it all rises the tomb where Amara's soul slumbers.  It makes you wonder if that bridge there is a getaway to the hereafter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... Especially after both Dhurke and Inga crossed that bridge earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This overturned urn has spilled water everywhere. Everything around it is soaking wet.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">D-Don't look at me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Rightly or wrongly, I'm guessing Athena's the type who gets blamed for a lot of things. And the more people accuse her, the more defensive she becomes. Even to the point of preemptively denying any wrongdoing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I said, it wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I never said it was.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I know you'll be prosecuting Dhurke's case, but... ...aren't there any other prosecutors in this country? Why does it have to be you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Her Eminence, Queen Ga'ran, personally requested that I serve as prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sh-She did? That WOULD make it hard to say no.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Her Eminence thinks highly of my prosecution skills.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Still, she didn't have to ask you to handle a case against your own father. Be honest. You really don't want to do this, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Ahh. You speak of love and sentiment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, I guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I do not deny such human emotions. But... the law is the law. And placing personal feelings above it is beyond reprieve. ...Do you disagree?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well... No, I don't disagree, but...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Civilizations only exist due to  the confines of the law. Without them, love and sentiment would lack the fertile they need to flourish. Do you disagree?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, but...</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The law must be obeyed. This truth sits above all else, including personal feelings. Therefore, whether or not I am the son of the accused is of no consequence. It is that simple, or would you say otherwise?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnnngh... B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Come on, Apollo! Tell him how wrong he is!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B...But don't you... you know... wish it wasn't that way...?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It appears I've wasted my breath on you.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And the winner is... Prosecutor Sahdmadhi!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Hmph. Still spewing empty words devoid of meaning or consequence, I see... ...you putrid red pepper.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh! ........ <thought>I know I'm right... But did he have to be so eloquent about his point? It;s like he's trying to cover something up with his pretty words.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I'd cut back on the debates with him if I were you. Just stick to questions, like the one you wanted to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta, I wanted to ask you about the hostage situation. Inga said he had someone dear to Dhurke in the palm of his hand. And he was using that person, along with his hostage, as leverage in obtaining the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...! That's news to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's what Inga said.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You can kiss your chances of getting the orb goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Inga">...Heh heh heh. Maya Fey ain't my only... how shall I say... insurance, you know, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">I've got someone dear to you right in the palm of my hand, see? Now that one, well... You can imagine what kinds of things I could do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Inga">I've got someone dear to you right in the palm of my hand, see? Now that one, well... You can imagine what kinds of things I could do, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">! ............</line>
<line speaker="Inga">Heh heh. Glad you're seeing things my way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I got the impression Dhurke had no choice but to follow Inga's demands after he heard that. So who do you suppose this special person is?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........I wouldn't know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! <thought>My bracelet's reacting!</thought> Hey, Nahyuta, about what you just said--</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I'm wise to your tricks, you putrid pepper. That bracelet reacts to the anxieties around you by squeezing your wrist. But now that I know how it works, I can make it tighten around your wrist any time I wish. Consider this a warning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh... <thought>I don't know how he did it, but this renders my bracelet useless.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Such devilry is powerless in the face of the Holy Mother's blessings.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like your special power won't work against Prosecutor Sahdmadhi, Apollo. We'll have to try something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh, you're right. We'll just have to ask Dhurke about this.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Why is that badge before me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Remember how we used to talk about what we wanted to be back when we were kids? I wanted to be a lawyer, and you, a prosecutor. You said you wanted to prosecute bad guys to make sure they got punished.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Yes, passing judgment upon evil... That is my calling. And it is why I have taken this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you saying Dhurke is evil?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">He who goes against what is righteous and holy... ...I shall reap his soul with all my power, whoever he may be, for that is my role.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Then I'll just have to defend his soul with all MY power, Nahyuta.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Alas... Another soul has departed this world, and must now be guided to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You would even hold last rites for a kidnapper like Minister Inga?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Criminals, too, must be given funerary rites. Deny that, and their soul will turn malevolent, bringing woe upon the living. That is why all who pass on must receive a proper requiem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Makes sense. I mean, if I were murdered, I'd probably be pretty keen on revenge, too.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">The putrid-minded lawyer seeks information from me? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come on, throw me a bone here.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I think not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, aren't we stingy?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...You intend to go through with a trial you have no hope of winning. Grow up, Mr. Justice. We are no longer children, you and I.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not the one who needs to grow up, Nahyuta. In case you didn't hear, I won my last case against none other than Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You tell him, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is he mad? I can never tell with him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...This trial is different. Your foolishness will only earn you a death sentence for aiding and abetting a criminal. And those who die as criminals... ...are doomed to be reborn in the next life as something lower than a bug or vegetable. You would be lucky to return to this realm as a patch of mold.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-Mold? That's pretty harsh.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">If you wish to avert such a fate, abandon this folly before it is too late.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I don't care if I end up as a dollop of blue cheese dressing in my next life! I'm going to defend Dhurke in court!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........You fool. Know this... I intend to prosecute the accused with all my might -- no matter what you say or do. Consider yourself forewarned. ...Now, if you will excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Prosecutor Sahdmadhi knows his father will be publicly executed if he's found guilty. Yet he won't show even an ounce of mercy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............... <thought>...Nahyuta. Is this the real you? Have you really changed? Do you really plan on sending Dhurke to his death? Do you even hear me? Don't Dhurke and I matter to you anymore?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya passed out right after we found her in the tomb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...I feel... exhausted. I can't keep my eyes... open...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's been out cold ever since. We haven't been able to get a word out of her. The doctor says it's just exhaustion, but I can't help but worry...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">What is it, Wright? Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah. Just thinking is all. I'm glad you're here, Edgeworth. We wouldn't have gotten the permissions we have without you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Well, I didn't come all the way to Khura'in to be useless. Speaking of the investigation, I received a few things from Detective Skye. These should prove to be useful to us as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't thank you enough, Edgeworth. <thought>Honestly, I'd have been so lost without him these past few days.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You there! The "Barbed Head" lawyer, Phoenix Wriiiiiight!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? .........You're... from the Ga'ran Royal Guard, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">I am Lah'kee, royal guard member and Her Eminence's shoooooulder rubber!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's... very specific... And what does the royal shoulder rubber want with me? Wait, come to think of it, my shoulders ARE a bit stiff--</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Don't be absuuurd!!! I am here for one purpose ooonly!!! I am to bring you before Her Eminence... ...Queen Ga'ran, grand priestess of Khura'in!! Will you complyyy?!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The queen? What could she want with me? <thought>And why does he have to shout like that&#160;?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... I can't fathom why Queen Ga'ran would summon you... ...but I advise you to accept Her Eminence's gracious invitation. .........Royal shoulder rubber Lahkee, was it? May I join Mr. Wright in his audience with the queen?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">The name's Lah'kee! L-A-H apostrophe K-E-E!!! And...! All praise the omnipotent Queen Ga'raaan!!! For she has already foreseen and approved your request, Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth!!! You are both to come with meeeee!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You mean to say that Queen Ga'ran sees our every move?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes indeeeed! Her Eminence's spiritual power is immeeeeeeense!!! She can even see what's going on thoooousands of miiiiiiiiles away!!!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Wright. I fear I'll lose my hearing next if we don't hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... Me, too... Why would the queen herself summon me personally? What could she possibly be up to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There weren't any hotels available, so this is our home for tonight. It's a bed to sleep in and a roof over our heads.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sorry to disappoint, but... there aren't any beds here. We'll have to sleep on the floor next to a bunch of strangers.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What? ...Tell me there's a shower at the very least.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The kitchen sink works just fine, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Of all the-- Wright, you will work to bring this case to a swift resolution. The sooner the better.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I suppose it will do.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The water's so clear, it's like a window into the soul.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I wouldn't stare too hard into it, Wright. Or you may find all your bluffs staring right back at you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No pool-gazing in front of a client. Got it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There appears to be many temples in this area.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, there are always a lot of monks and worshippers praying around here. And then there's tourists like us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's unfortunate that we have more pressing matters to attend to. Then again, sightseeing with you of all people isn't exactly at the top of my list.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As if you have the luxury to be so picky, Edgeworth.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So you'd been here all this time. I wondered where you had gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't tell me you missed me, Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As if. The courts have been so peaceful without you around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You make it sound like I leave legal devastation in my wake.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Heh... Well, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, Wright, what do you intend to do now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was thinking... I want to help Apollo win this case. So why don't we try to gather whatever information we can?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You're quite the considerate boss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I kinda forced him to take care of the office in my absence, so... ...it's the least I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Still at it, I see. I guess borders mean little in the face of your incurable habit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I heard you used to present evidence left and right during your investigations, too.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That was a long time ago. ...Besides, who did you hear that from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I have my sources.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Oh? Well, tell your "source" that I look forward to his next salary review.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It's ironic that the man tasked with upholding the law should end up breaking it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, it's not like we don't have our fair share of that back home.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, that is a thing of the past. The worst offenders have already been removed.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that you mention it, wasn't Gaspen Payne expelled from the prosecutor's office?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, he was a particularly troublesome individual. I was shocked to see him resurface here in Khura'in, and with considerable sway, no less. I just hope he doesn't end up making a mess of things here as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ga'ran Palace, the heart of the kingdom's government and religion.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, the two are inseparably intertwined here in Khura'in. The religious beliefs of its people touch every aspect of their lives, including legal affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. Like how they commune with spirits in court. I suppose Khura'inism is the glue that binds their faith, law, and politics together. It may seem strange to foreigners like us, but for them, it's perfectly natural.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What a beautiful place this is. But I'd be enjoying this a whole lot more if we weren't investigating a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Commoners aren't normally allowed access to the royal residence, you know. Under ordinary circumstances, it would be impossible to take in such a spectacular view. Though murder is certainly a unique reason to be offered such a rare opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This place is decorated with all sorts of colorful flowers. And that view from the veranda looks like it would be amazing. If I had to guess, I'd say Rayfa must live here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Amara's Tomb -- the scene of Inga's murder. Poor Maya was held captive in there.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To think she was actually being held here in Khura'in. If only we had found out sooner.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...No point dwelling on that now. All we can do is to keep moving forward. </line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">There are footprints coming from this residence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Too bad they just kinda end. I wonder who made them and where they went.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This overturned urn spilled its water all over the place. It was already knocked over when we got here earlier this afternoon, so... ...we can rule out Athena at least.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Wright. What does it say about you if your first suspect is your own subordinate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What a gaudy building. Looks like something you'd appreciate, Edgworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...For the record, Wright, I have absolutely no interest in such ostentatious things.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Says the man who rides around in a red sports car, wearing that frilly cravat thing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo and Athena are already working this area. Edgeworth and I should try someplace else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">This bell must be for summoning the guard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I bet one of your detectives would come running if you rang it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's find out, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-They're not seriously going to show up, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, the guard's asleep. And here I thought he was stoically doing his duty. Impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Ah, the "Barbed Head" lawyer has arrived. We bid you welcome. And you, as well, Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Th-Thank you. <thought>This place is still as magnificent as last time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">We have heard much about you, Barbed One. It seems your bluffs and tomfoolery tend to leave our court devastated in their wake.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh... Is that what people have been saying about me?</line>
<line speaker="Edgworth">...Wright! Where are your manners?! Your Eminence. I am both humbled and delighted to be in your presence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, umm... Your Eminence... Um, glad to be here. Looks like you're doing well.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...Heh. It is all right. There is no need to keep your head bowed all day.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Eminence.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa's not looking too good. I guess even she can't just bounce back from her father's murder...</thought> ...So what can I do for you, Your Eminence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Perfect. Because I have a few questions of my own.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one swanky throne. I wouldn't mind taking a seat there myself.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The jester and the crown. I imagine it'd make quite the interesting picture.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know Edgeworth... I hate to say this, but you're absolutely right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the Ga'ran Royal Guard. The one who came for us earlier said that he's the royal shoulder rubber. ...Um, excuse me. But are each of you charged with your own specific task?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">I'm the royal teeeeeaaaa server!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">I'm the royal taaaaaaster!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">I'm the royal bed maaaaaaaker!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">I'm the royal fitness traaaaiiiiine--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All right, all right... I'm sorry I asked.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">At this rate, one has to wonder if there is no task left unassigned by Her Eminence.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">We fear we do not fully comprehend what has transpired. So it is that we summoned you here to further elucidate the situation. Is it true that our husband Inga had been seeking the Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's right. He wanted to trade a hostage for it. That's why he abducted Maya Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Insolent fool!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oww!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That is a lie! A lie, I say! Father would have never done such a thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But he did abduct Maya. That much is--</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I will not stand here and listen to this nonsense! You will pay for this, you... you...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ow-Ow-Oww! P-Please, Your Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">That is quite enough, Rayfa. We understand your feelings, but we fear he speaks the truth. For we believe we know why your father would do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">We believe he was seeking the orb as a means of obtaining spiritual power. And with it, he intended to usurp the throne.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........M-Mother...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, Your Eminence?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Inga was planning a coup, for he was dissatisfied with the current administration... ...and his secret police was the primary instrument of his treason.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The secret police... They came up during the high priest's murder trial, too. An elite force under the direct command of the Minister of Justice -- in this case, Inga. The man who was hunting down rebels as Lady Kee'ra was a member of that group.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Indeed. Inga turned that once proud force into his own private army. And he intended on using them to launch a coup and assassinate us.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So Your Eminence had no control over them?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">As much as it shames us to admit it, Khura'in is not the unified realm it would appear to be. We are truly sorry you have had to witness the dirty underbelly of our kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">H...How could Father...?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">But know that Inga could not have become king simply through our assassination. For in Khura'in, only those who possess spiritual power may sit on the throne.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... That explains why Minister Inga was seeking the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Barbed One, do you recall the man known as Pees'lubn Andistan'dhin?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What about him?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">He, too, was involved in Inga's machinations. Inga had bought his loyalty, ordered the man to steal the orb, and covered up the theft.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And then, he sent the orb to the U.S. for Dr. Buff to study... It's all coming together...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">The capture of the infamous villain Dhurke Sahdmadhi... It may prove to be the crowning achievement of our reign. Now, perhaps, the kingdom may return to the peace it once knew. Oh, what a joyous day.</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Hail to Her Eminence, Queen Ga'ran, Grand Priestess of Khura'in! Her Eminence's spiritual power invoked a blessing straight from the Holy Mother!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I could see how her cronies would be elated at the prospect. But the queen herself seems almost giddy for someone whose husband was just murdered.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Father...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa, on the other hand, doesn't appear to be taking it so well.</thought> About that incident that occurred twenty-three years ago... The one in which Dhurke was accused of assassinating Queen Amara.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Yes, he set fire to her private residence, burning my dear sister alive.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Murder by arson...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">ONly a demon would be capable of such a heinous crime.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But that event also set the stage for you to become queen...</thought> What did you do before you were crowned queen, Your Eminence?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">As part of our training to be queen, we served in many different governmental positions. The longest of which was as the previous Minister of Justice. It was in that position that we were best able to support our elder sister, Queen Amara.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Interesting... That's her husband's position, or at least it was.</thought> And when you ascended to the throne, you passed the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"...those who would support criminals will be deemed just as guilty." What prompted you to pass something like the Defense Culpability Act, Your Eminence?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...The assassination of our dear sister Amara. When the infamous villain Dhurke Sahdmadhi was apprehended... ...he announced that he would act as his own lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's right... Dhurke used to be a lawyer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Dhurke had been an extraordinarily talented lawyer, and highly esteemed by the people. But he falsified evidence in an attempt to win his own case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">But when the truth of his fabrications and the assassination of the queen came to light... ...the people were devastated. And trust in the legal system plummeted.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........Now why does that sound so familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I wonder, aha-hah-hah...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">In Khura'in, the Hall of Justice is a sacred space where victims receive their last rites. Should the people lose their faith in it, the kingdom would be shaken to its very core. That is why the Defense Culpability Act had to be passed. It was the only way to keep our legal system from tumbling into the abyss.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So that's how you sought to eliminate the use of perjury and phony evidence, huh. But that law is what made lawyers go extinct in your kingdom. Now there's no one left to defend those who have been accused.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.........We see how you could take issue with such a reality. However, we have not banned the act of lawyering itself. Those who are confident that they can prove their client's innocence... ...are always welcome to mount a vigorous defense, as you yourself have shown.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-Well, I guess so, but... Without lawyers, there's the possibility of false charges being filed and prosecuted.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">So long as our prosecutors continue to run nothing but perfect trials... ...there needn't be fear of such nefarious dealings. Do you disagree?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Perfect prosecutors and their perfect trials, huh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Let's not get started down THIS path...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Furthermore, here in Khura'in, we have the Divination Sance. And so it is we no longer need lawyers, for the dead do not lie.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, in the short time I've been here, I've beaten back false charges twice. And I've found that cases built on the memories of the dead are less than perfect. So yes, I do take issue with the Defense Culpability Act, to say the least.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...Ho ho ho. Such relentless rhetoric. Your reputation precedes you, Barbed One. It feels as if we ourselves were being cross-examined.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Oh, no, that wasn't my intention.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...It is true that some feel that the Defense Culpability Act is a necessary evil at best. But it is a small sacrifice upon which the peace of our kingdom has been forged.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If you consider executing innocent lawyers a small sacrifice, then sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">The fact is that following its passage... ...the crime rate here in Khura'in dropped markedly. Therefore, we have no regrets concerning the enactment of the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really? None at all?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, why don't we leave it at that? This isn't a court of law, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">About the Founder's Orb that was to be exchanged for the hostage... It went missing after the murder. Would you happen to know anything about that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's missing? I'm sure Dhurke had it when he went into the tomb. If it wasn't there, I have no idea where it could be, Your Eminence.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...In that case, then perhaps Dhurke has hidden it somewhere. ...Incidentally... there is the matter of that horned youth you were with.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, you must mean Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">From his odd hairstyle, may we assume him to be a relative? Perhaps, your younger brother?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, no! You've got it all wrong. He's Dhurke's son. Well, more like foster son -- they're not actually related by blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Dhurke's...? .........Royal guard!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Your Eminence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? <thought>What's she whispering in that one guy's ear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.........Thank you for your time. The two of you may go now.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, Your Eminence. We'll be on our way.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay, now what? Apollo and Athena have the murder scene investigation covered, so... ...maybe we should go speak with the locals over at the bazaar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, please take a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...That reminds us of when Dhurke was still practicing law. So, we see that lawyers in your country also present evidence... ...simply to gauge the other party's reaction when all else has failed. Do not presume to use such simplistic methods upon us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wh-What... Was that a lion?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that? Caught me by surprise, too, when I first heard it. It's the cry of a local bird known as a warbaa'd.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">A bird? That sounds like that?</line>
<line speaker="Warbaa'd">RAWWWRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Sounds more like a beast than a bird, if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a form of mimicry. You know, to help protect them against predators and stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Yes, well... Can't say I've heard one quite like that before.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, it's more than unusual -- it's endangered. It's extremely rare to encounter one in the wild these days.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...If it's so rare, then what's one doing out here in the middle of the bazaar?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You got me. Maybe it's got something to do with it being their national bird.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaahh! <thought>Was that a gunshot?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Har har har har har! Startle ya, PW?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What was that, Datz?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The Defiant Dragons' newest weapon. I call these puppies... Dragon Snot Snaps!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, huh... And you need those... why?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Because our hard work is starting to pay off! Thanks to our TV signal hijacking and stuff, more and more people are joining our cause. But on account o' that, the regime's been cracking down on us real tough-like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, there's been a lot going on lately.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You can say that again. I mean, what with the high priest's fake-murder-slash-suicide. People are calling the "DCA Tragedy," and it's causing a real public uproar.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hopefully this means Tahrust's death won't be in vain after all.</thought> ...So how exactly is a handful of firecrackers going to be of help to you guys anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Simple. First, I supply 'em to our fellow rebels. Then we use 'em as a diversion when we need to shake Ga'ran's goons.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Like this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa! W-Will you cut that out?! I'm not with the regime, and I'm not chasing you!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har har! Haaaar har har har har! Your reaction! That was priceless, PW!</line>
<line speaker="Warbaa'd">RAWWWRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har har! Guess I startled that warbaa'd, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's a miracle no one's trying to arrest him while he's too busy laughing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">You there.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You are one of those insurgents, are you not?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yikes! ...<cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Eek!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaand he's gone. Those firecrackers are more useful than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence. What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I... I wanted to speak with you. .........About what my mother said... I do not believe a word of it. My father could not have been planning a coup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, I can understand why you'd feel like that, but...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It was a setup! Someone must have been plotting against him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, and how do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I just do. Because the Holy Mother guides me. And as the royal priestess, I must uncover the truth for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Maybe this is just how Rayfa expresses her sense of duty.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You're investigating this matter, are you not? Then rejoice, for I shall accompany you, and bestow upon you the royal priestess's wisdom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha, a-ha ha. That's the best news I've heard all day, Your Benevolence. <thought>No one would dare get in our way with Rayfa by our side.</thought> We humbly accept your offer, don't we, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">As you wish, Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Excellent. Then let us begin with my father's private quarters. We should be able to find some clues there. I shall expose this false charge for what it is, if it is the last thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Could it be? Is the reason she's so defensive about Inga because she's a daddy's girl?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head! Let us not waste any time! My father's private quarters are located within the royal residence. Now, follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! She's sure in a hurry.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, the minister's private quarters may hold evidence related to his murder as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, maybe we can kill two birds with one stone. <thought>Rayfa's awfully fired up. I just hope she'll be ready for the truth we find. After all, it's hard to believe that Inga was not in full control of the whole affair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I never thought the day would come when we'd be investigating a case side by side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? 'Cause I never thought the day would come when you'd get sentimental on me.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nghrk! Come on, Wright! Time's a wasting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, exactly which one of us was wasting time here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, if we could figure out which of these buildings houses Inga's private quarters... That's where we'll find Rayfa.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now that's what I call and extravagant exterior. Is this where Inga's private quarters are?</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Watch your step, Wright. That urn's been knocked over, spilling water everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the ground's soaked. I wonder who did this?</line>
<line speaker="???">.........*sob*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? ...I think someone's in there.</line>
<line speaker="???">*sob* Father... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is that... Princess Rayfa?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">There were still so many things I wished to tell you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...She always puts on such a brave face.</thought> <thought>But hearing her crying all alone... I...</thought> <thought>I can't help but think of Trucy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">*sob* Father... ...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, Princess Rayfa? Are you in there?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah! J-Just a moment! I'll be right out! .........I see you are finally here. Well, let us commence our investigation, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Um, Your Benevolence? Maybe you should rest for a minute first.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...! You were eavesdropping on me! Weren't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, no! I mean, yes... Sorry. I couldn't help overhearing...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........Grrrr.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-It wasn't like I was spying on you or anything!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...You stupid... stupid... Barbed Head!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeowch!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...You could've feigned ignorance. It's as if your brain-to-mouth filter shuts off the moment you step out of the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... I'm not THAT bad, Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Anyway, what took you so long? I thought you would never get here. You have a lot of nerve, keeping the crown princess waiting.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, um... sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This was my father's residence. I have already unlocked it, so you can go right in. Oh, and... Be careful. Some dingbat dog in the courtyard and spilled water over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dingbat dog?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's right. The yappy mutt spilled a whole urn's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder how it got into this area. Do you know what it looked like?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. I have better things to do than to memorize what some stray dog looks like. Anyway, it is not worth talking about. Let's search my father's room, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I really hope she's all right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The Minister of Justice used to live here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the decor looks like something he'd choose.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What a mess. You can definitely tell a guy used to live in this room. I guess Inga and I had at least that much in common.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Bah, this staff keeps getting in the way. Nayna! .................. ...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Where's Nayna? Normally... ...she comes running whenever Rayfa calls.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...That's right. Nayna is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nayna is... what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh, well. You, Barbed Head! Come, hold this staff for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-Why me?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Just take it! It's too heavy, and I am tired of holding it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sigh How does Nayna put up with this day in and day out?</thought> Um... I'll just set it over here for now.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are some muddy shoeprints here. <thought>Come to think of it... There was some spilled water by the entrance. Somebody must've stepped in it before coming in here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">They're already dry. That means they're at least several hours old.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then someone must have been in here today in the early afternoon... ...for our servants clean this room each day. Here in Khura'in we have a saying: "Leave not today's untidiness to the morrow."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Mine is: "Why clean up today what you can leave for tomorrow?"</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's this? ..."Je suis L'Belle!"? Never thought I'd see THIS brand again...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears to be a sample of some sort of spray-on hair color.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Color: Jet Black"... I wonder if Inga was going grey. Here, Edgeworth. Maybe you can use it.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I like my natural hair color just fine, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">His desk is crammed full of documents!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... They appear to be paperwork for executions.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-But for this many cases?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Indeed. Something is rotten in the Kingdom of Khura'in. Hm? This one dates back to five years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something tells me he simply kept putting them off because he hated doing paperwork.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's one luxurious and comfy-looking bed. I've slept on nothing but hard floors since coming to Khura'in. Can't wait to sleep in a nice, soft bed again.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Then take it. It's yours, if you wish. ......We'll have to clean this room out, anyway, now that my father's gone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But don't you want to keep these things as a memento of your father? Besides... I don't need his spirit haunting me late at night.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........Do you suppose if I slept on it, I could see my father once more?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Princess Rayfa... <thought>I honestly don't know how to answer that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow... That's one gaudy sculpture.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My father sculpted it himself from a block of solid gold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why does it not surprise me that he was also a narcissist?</thought> Ha ha ha. It's pretty detailed. He even included that personal stamp of his. Hey, the stamp's a little loose. Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Look. There's a secret safe inside!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Oh, my! To think such a thing was here all this time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Rats. Looks like we'll need the combination to get in.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">To have a secret safe in his own bedroom... It seems the minister was a rather cagey man.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's take a look inside. Who knows what we might find.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can't open this without the combination, but I doubt Princess Rayfa would know it...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Well, if we can't open it, we can't open it. For now, let's continue our investigation, and come back to this dilemma later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a syringe and a vial...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Those were for my father's back pain. He said it really helped when the pain was particularly unbearable.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was that bad, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">He must've been injecting some sort of painkiller directly into his back, then.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, my father said his back pain could knock him off his feet.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know the feeling. I've experienced some pretty severe back pain of my own...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well, we can't have you throwing your back out in court, so why don't you take a vial?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, uh, no thanks. I hear your body builds up a tolerance to that sort of thing.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I thought you didn't want them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm going straight to a chiropractor as soon as I get home.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This notepad must've belonged to Inga. Let's see... That's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">These appear to be notes detailing people's most prominent characteristics.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, there's even some stuff about me in here. Why would he bother doing this?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... I am afraid even I can't answer that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Whatever the reason, it's giving me a case of the heebie-jeebies.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmm... It's as though he was taking down descriptions of people over the phone... That's what it reminds me of, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">What a brilliant deduction! One fitting of a chief prosecutor such as yourself. I commend you.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Heh, that's high praise coming from you, Your Benevolence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Edgeworth's right. They do look like dictation notes, but... I don't know... I mean, why bother describing Nayna, who he must've seen every day?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the notepad with those descriptions of various people in it. I wonder what Inga was using it for.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head... I, the Royal Priestess of Khura'in, shall share my thoughts on the abduction.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You will?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">......Listen carefully, for such opportunities do not come often.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yes, of course. We'd be grateful to hear anything you'd like to share.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...My father was very likely seeking to obtain the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But it was not for the purposes of a coup d'tat. It was all... for my sake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">For your sake? </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">The Founder's Orb is capable of bestowing great spiritual power. My father truly believed that. And he wanted that power to be mine. I haven't finished my training, and I still can't channel spiritsQ! He was doing it for me! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......Right, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Well? Do you understand why he did it now?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............I do, but... ...it doesn't change the fact that Minister Inga was a kidnapper.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I guess you don't believe he is, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ooooooh! New information is sure to surface upon further investigation. S-Suffice to say , he did this all for me. End of story!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">(Was he really trying to obtain the orb for Rayfa? Somehow, I doubt it. Speaking of powers... ...I wonder if Rayfa will be performing the Divination Sance tomorrow. I should probably ask her about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, I noticed Nayna isn't with you today.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........I know not where she has gone. I have not spoken with her since this morning. I assume she must be quite busy today. I did catch a glimpse of her a little after two o'clock. I tried calling out to her... ...but she went off somewhere again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A little after two? That's about an hour before the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Indeed. Of all the times for this to happen... She normally comes to me the moment I call her name.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I know it's hard to believe, but even nannies have lives, you know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your inability to find her after the murder is slightly alarming. I wonder if her absence is related to today's incidents somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Do you think she was unwittingly caught up in them?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who knows... At the very least I don't think she was at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nayna... I hope she is all right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa seems really worried for Nayna.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I take it you'll be conducting tomorrow's Divination Sance?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Who else, if not I?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good point. <thought>The thing is... ...Divination Sances are all about what victims experienced in their final moments. So, tomorrow... ...Rayfa will experience her own father's death, exactly as it happened. That's more than anyone should ever have to deal with.</thought> ...Do you really have to go through with the Sance tomorrow? There's really no one else? What about just calling the whole thing off?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............It's not as if... ...It's not as if I'm doing this because I want to.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Ah! N-Never mind. I misspoke! The Divination Sance is a very important duty of the Royal Priestess. And it is one I intend to fulfill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's that word: duty</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">...Your Benevolence. As crown princess, you are destined to rule this kingdom one day. That means there will be many things that you alone must determine. Things like how to keep your people happy, and what is true and what is false... And most importantly, what role you must play therein.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.................. I wonder if I am even up to the task.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Performing the Divination Sance IS very important for a priestess... ...but duty or not, it's a heavy burden for someone so young. Even worse, she'll be forced to watch her father's murder. Will it be a weight too heavy for her to bear?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, has Nayna served you long?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, she has been at my beck and call for as long as I can remember. I have heard she even cared for me as an infant, right down to changing my diapers.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your diapers? It almost sounds like she could be your mother.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Indeed. But that is a simple fact of life when your mother is busy being queen. Nayna takes care of my every need. She is my teacher in all things, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Rayfa's pool of knowledge seems rather lopsided in some respects. Could that be the result of Nayna's teachings?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nayna... Could it be that my trusted attendant has come to dislike me? Now that I think about it, perhaps I've been acting rather spoiled as of late.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'm sure she'll be back.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Yes, I suppose Nayna would never truly abandon me. Upon her return, I will do something nice for her. Perhaps she'd like a shoulder massage.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And yet, I can't shake the feeling that Nayna's connected to this case in some way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Remove that vile badge from my sight! If you insist on tormenting me, I will take matters into my own hands!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, don't bite it!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............ Hmm, it's much harder than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...What did you think it's made of?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...! ............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........Father.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoops, s-sorry! Didn't mean to hurt you like that.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph! Do not underestimate me! I am the royal priestess, and as such I will experience my father's death tomorrow. So hand it over! A photo of a corpse... will not... phase...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You Benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wright, you fool! Put that picture away!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Nngh. There is no need to worry. I simply lost my footing, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now I'm REALLY worried about tomorrow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">My father's back used to cause him considerable pain. I would give him massages from time to time. He seemed to truly enjoy them.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm, I didn't peg you as the dutiful daughter type.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">But never again... will I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence... Um... I could stand in for your father if you'd like--</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">............Rrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Youch! M-My back! I think you broke something!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph. That's what I call the royal treatment.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">These are notes my father took on the characteristics of those around him. I wonder what he wrote about me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let's see... Pink raiment... Tattoos on face... Ch-Childishly cute?!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That last one's rather subjective, isn't it...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence, I wanted to ask you about this.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nayna! Nayna! Where are you?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, I thought you said she wasn't around...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Oh, yes, of course......... Well, you're sadly mistaken if you think questioning Nayna will clear things up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>But I'm trying to question you, not Nayna.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Barbed Head. First you make me wait, and now you're simply going to leave?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess I should stay put for a while.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">None whatsoever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It looks like a four-digit combo lock, so maybe it's a date. But it's probably not anything that would be easy to guess.</thought> Well, let's try some dates and see what happens. I wonder what date Inga would use as a combination?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about the date the Defense Culpability Act was enacted? Do you know when that was, Your Benevolence? </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nayna! Nayna!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Your Benevolence... *whisper, whisper*...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Yes, of course... I believe the date would be: June 14!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Really, Edgeworth? Is whispering in the ears of elites the secret to your success?</thought> All right, let's give 0-6-1-4 a try. Nope, that's not it. Time to try something else.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How about your parents' anniversary?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmm... I have not the faintest idea of when it is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, I guess you wouldn't, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...It's December 11.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How in the world do you know THAT fact, Edgeworth?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Hmph, I don't. I simply deduced it using elementary school-level logic. Though I doubt you'd grasp how I arrived at my conclusion, so I'll save my breath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's no way you didn't use some kind of superpower to come up with that...</thought> Anyway, here goes... 1-2-1-1. ...No good. It won't open. Let's try another number, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When's your birthday, Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Hmph, you are wasting your time. It could not possibly be my birthday.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aw, come on. It's worth a shot.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...Fine. It's December 24.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Christmas Eve? Well, let's give it a try. 1-2-2-4... Ahhh! ...I-It... It opened!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">It did?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. And it looks like the bottom safe was a fake.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Something meant to mislead would-be thieves, no doubt. Still, it was rendered quite ineffective by his use of such an easily-guessed combination.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-Why, Father...? Why my birthdate...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, let's see what's in here. Hm? This looks like a letter or something. Let's see... "Dear Father... I wanted to wish you a happy birthday. You're always so kind, and I love you very much. I hope you live to be a hundred years old! Love, Rayfa." ...............</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I-I wrote this to my father when I was eight years old. F-Father... Why would you hold on to... something so childish and stupid...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........There are some other papers in here. Hmm... Ah! This... This is the plan for the coup d'tat!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Wh-What?! Give me that! .........I... I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems Justice Minister Inga was plotting the assassination of the queen.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">This... This can't be true. Father would never harm Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Rayfa. This has to come as a terrible shock.</thought> ...What's this? There's a photo in here, too. Hmm... It's of a woman and a baby. I wonder who they are. ...On the far left, there's a law book with the mark of the Defiant Dragons branded on it.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........Wait! Th-Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...How... How can this be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">P-Princess Rayfa!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's looking incredibly pale.</thought> Your Benevolence. Are you all right?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........All right? How can I be all right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........All that I have believed... It was all lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm afraid I don't follow. <thought>What the heck's she talking about?</thought> Um... Can I ask who the woman is in this picture?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...H-How should I know?! .........It seems I didn't know ANYTHING that was going on!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Doesn't look like I'm going to get much more out of her while she's like this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">.........Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I must ask my mother... about the secret she is hiding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, what secret...?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">...I must go. Goodbye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! ...What was that all about? It's like her mind was off somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It appears this photo really upset her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder who the lady in this picture is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Stop! Shah'do! Come back here!</line>
<line speaker="???">Ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, that sounds like... Ahlbi and Shah'do.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">That's odd. Commoners aren't normally allowed in this area. I wonder what's afoot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I better not touch anything without Rayfa's permission. Who knows what she might say... or do if she finds out.</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff ruff ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nghoooooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahhh! Edgewooooorth!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">.........I hope one of you has a good explanation for this.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ahhhhhh! I'm SO sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hi, Ahlbi...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">No, Shah'do! Bad dog! Leave the man's frilly thingamajig alone!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Grrrrrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">If you would kindly detach your dog from my cravat.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">R-Right away, sir! Just hold still, and...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">And...?</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Grrrrrr...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Hrrrrrgh! Hrrrrrrrrrrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Nghoooh! Stop pulling like that! You'll only stretch the fabric!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Come on, Shah'do...! Let go of his... carava-chamacallit!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Hmm... This isn't working. I'll just have to pull harder, then... One, two...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Wait! What are you--?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">THREEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE! RRRRRRRNNNNNNNNGH! .........Come OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOON!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">NNNNGHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH! AAAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIRRRRRRRRRRRRRRR! I NEED AAAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIIIIIIIRRRRRRRRRRR! *huff... huff... huff...* Were you trying to kill me?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I'm really sorry, mister. My dog has a habit of attacking frilly things like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe for his sake, he should stick to more traditional targets, like cars, or his tail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">What's worse, he snuck in here again today and stole some weird-looking hat. I don't know what to do anymore. Bad dog! You're a very bad dog!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'da">*whine*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a second... I've seen that hat before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, could I see that hat again?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait... Isn't this... Isn't this Nayna's hat? But I thought she'd disappeared.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Shah'do swiped it from someone.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Ahlbi? How exactly did Shah'do get this?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain! It all started while we were on a walk through the bazaar today. When, suddenly, Datz popped out of a manhole!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Whoa!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The fangs of the Defiant Dragons... ...Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaah... ...Datz Are'bal is here! .........Say, you wanna join our cause, kid? </line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Naturally, I was super startled by that weirdo's sudden appearance.</line>
<line speaker="Warbaa'd">RAWWWWWWRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Back! Dog of the Ga'ran regime! </line>
<line speaker="Datz">Defiant Dragon secret weapon: Dragon Snot Snaps! ACHOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">WHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOA! Oof!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har! Aw man, the look on your face! That was classic!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">The sudden bang of the firecracker spooked Shah'do, and he ran off into the crowds.</line>
<line speaker="Shah'do">Ruff ruff ruff ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ahhhhhh! Shah'do, come back here!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har! That'll teach ya, Ga'ran's lapdog!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">You there! What do you think you're doing?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Ack! Not good!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">That's when a policeman came running over and hauled Datz away. That happened right around 2 PM, if I remember correctly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I'm not even going to pretend I know what Datz was trying to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I chased right after Shah'do, and... ...when I finally caught up to him here in the palace courtyard, he had this in his mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">2 PM, hmm? That's about an hour before the minister's death. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nayna supposedly went missing after the murder... ...but this would place her here at the palace at around 2.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Actually! I just remembered I saw something pretty amazing around that time, too! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something amazing?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, Ahlbi, what was it you saw that was so amazing?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I saw Her Eminence Queen Ga'ran channeling a spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is it really that big of a deal to see her channeling someone?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">You bet it is! Commoners are never allowed to behold the sacred rite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Can you tell me more?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Of course! I'm always happy to explain! Um... I believe it was around 2:10 PM today. I got lost on the palace grounds while looking for Shah'do.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ooh... What is this place? It gives me the creeps. Where could Shah'do have gone?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">In my search, I took a peek into a small room and... ...that's when I saw Queen Ga'ran! She was channeling a spirit for a neighboring kingdom's king! I saw her transform right before my eyes! I was so excited, I had to take a picture of it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You... You took a picture?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I know I shouldn't have... ...but I just couldn't help myself!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Between this and the treasure room, Ahlbi's not exactly the picture of self-restraint...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You could've been arrested again, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Yeah, I know... ........................ Anyway, here's a copy of the picture. Just don't tell anyone I was the one who took it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I worry about his future sometimes.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come to think of it... ...how did you and Shah'do get into the royal residence anyway? it's not open to commoners, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Allow me to explain!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">There's a way to get into the palace from the bazaar. It's a bit of a tight squeeze, though. Shah'do can easily fit, but anyone bigger than me is out of luck.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You don't say...</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Yeah, part of the palace wall is damaged, and there's a hole I can just make it through.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Heh heh heh. Betcha didn't know they have some really tasty food here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Then this isn't your first time in here, huh. ...Trespassing is illegal, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">N-No, it's not like that! I didn't mean any harm. It's just... I want to help change this kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Well, after Ms. Fey's trial, I started thinking. Like maybe... Maybe there was something I could do to help the revolution, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Maya's trial, huh. That tragedy only happened because of how twisted Khura'in's legal system has become.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">How utterly foolish to cast away one's life for such a reason! There must have been other ways to cover up the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Tahrust">Yet, had I done so, my wife would rush to my defense. And when the case went to trial... ...she would suffer the same fate as I under the Defense Culpability Act. I could not have lived with myself had she been convicted because of that fiendish man!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Th-This... cannot be... All I have done under the laws of our kingdom... It has all been...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The DC Act led to the false charges against Maya and the high priest's suicide. But that trial also caused the public to start questioning the current state of things. And it seems even Ahlbi has some pretty strong feelings on the matter.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">I knew there had to be something I could do to help! That's when I remembered the hole in the palace wall, and started thinking... ...maybe I could sneak in and take a picture of one of the royals up to no good. I just want to do my part!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">The spirit of revolution seems to be catching on, even with one so young. Wright, the momentum is steadily building, and the tipping point is fast approaching. It's just a matter of when.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. And the public's perception of the Defiant Dragons seems to be changing, too. But Ahlbi... You can't go trespassing like that. Even if it's for a good cause, it's not right.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Okay. I won't do it again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, is that really all you have to confess? You haven't been up to any other mischief? And when I say "you," I mean Shah'do.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Huh?! Oh, um... I-I... I don't know what you're talking about. Aheh... heh heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nice try, Ahlbi, but the proof is literally right in front of us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, that's an attorney's badge from your homeland, right?! I've studied all about it. Allow me to explain! There's a reason why the badge is shaped like a sunflower. You know how sunflowers always turn to face the sun -- the source of their well-being? Well, lawyers are like that -- they will chase after anything that will make them money!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...I guess people hate lawyers in your country, too, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... Where did you get your information from again?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">A proud sermon Chief Prosecutor Payne gave in the middle of the bazaar the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... Lawyers already have a bad enough time here without his lies.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you know about this, Ahlbi? </line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">.........S-Sorry. I don't know anything about that. I'm the worst tour guide ever.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No, no, it's my fault for randomly whipping it out and asking you about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Don't worry. I'll study hard, so I'll be ready to answer all your questions next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh, now I feel like a jerk.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ahlbi, you wouldn't happen to know how this urn got knocked over, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because Her Benevolence told me something rather interesting.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Be careful. Some dingbat dog got in the courtyard and spilled water over there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A dingbat dog?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">That's right. The yappy mutt spilled a whole urn's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The "dingbat dog" she mentioned wouldn't happen to be Shah'do, would it?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">...Ooh...! ......... I guess the dog's out of the bag. Sorry I lied. But I was worried I'd get in trouble. I know I shouldn't lie to a lawyer like that. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, it's not good to lie to anyone like that. So let's try to only tell the truth. Okay, Ahlbi?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">Oh, Mr. Wright! I almost forgot. I saw a couple of Americans a moment ago. They had really weird haircuts, so I thought they might be friends of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...R-Really, now... Um...</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">It seems your little friend thinks all us Americans have strange hairstyles. I suppose we have you to thank for that, Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......... So, what exactly did their hair look like?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">There was a guy with two crops of hair sticking out of his forehead like antennae. Then there was this lady with a long bunch of hair that looked like a big, orange spider leg.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, that sounds like Apollo and Athena. What were they doing?</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">They were racing through the bazaar... ... with the Ga'ran Royal Guard in hot pursuit!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait, whaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Why were they being pursued...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure, but I have my suspicions. I just hope they're all right.</line>
<line speaker="Ahlbi">S-Sorry for not mentioning it before. It just kind of slipped my mind, heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*huff, puff, huff, puff* Those... Those guys... sure are... persistent!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*huff, puff, huff, puff* Yeah. They even wore ME out, and that doesn't happen often.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why are they after us, anyway?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ah, Apollo! It's the royal guards again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Argh! Q-Quick, hide!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Hey! Where'd Horn Head and Spidey Hair gooooooo?!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Spidey Hair? They're not talking about me, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Is that a trick question...?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">We know you're hiding somewhere around heeeeeeeeeee!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo, that weird-looking bird over there... Did it just...?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah, it did. It's called a warbaa'd and... You know what? I'll tell you all about it later when we're not being chased by masked men!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Come out, come out, wherever you aaaaare!!! ...Hand over the Founder's Orb, if you know what's good for yooooouuuuuu!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It figures they're after the orb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't want to know what they'll do to us if we were captured. If they grill us in those obnoxious, loud voices... ...I'd cave after the first hour and confess to whatever they wanted, truth or no!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Come out now, you foreign deeeeevils!!! This has gone faaaaaar enough!!! You must not keep Her Eminence waiting any looooooonger!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-We've gotta get out of here! There must be a safe place to hide somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe we could hide here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No way! They'd find us in no time!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Stay where you aaaare!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Th-They're closing in on us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've gotta find a place to hide!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! We shouldn't be standing around talking like this! Who knows what they'll do to us if they catch us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right. Let's find somewhere safe to hide!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo! Do you really HAVE to show that to me right this second?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry. It's just... something I do now when I'm stuck... Anyway, your shouting isn't helping, either.</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">That voice! It's Spidey Hair!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeek! ...Hiii-yaaaaaa!!!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sh-She sent him flying!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">L-Let's find somewhere else to hide before the other guards get here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, a manhole. ...Ahhh! That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Say, son, do you remember my office?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sure. <thought>I remember that messy, dimly lit room.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The file I've amassed on Amara's assassination is kept there. I think it might help you on this case. Do you remember how to get there?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena! I know where we can hide! Follow me!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh?! Where are we going?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hrrrrrrrnngh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Wait. You're not seriously thinking about going down there? It smells like rotten eggs. And are those rats I hear?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've got no choice! I can get us somewhere safe, but this is the only way in. Quick, before it's too late!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. It's going to take forever to get this stench out of my hair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Looks like we lost them. That was close. .................. <thought>Dhurke's office... How long has it been since I last set foot in here?</thought> At least we're safe now, but...</line>
<line speaker="Athena"><thought>Why is Athena all huddled over in the corner like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">AJ! What the heck are ya doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ga'ran's royal guards are after us.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har! Once a rebel, always a rebel. Don't worry. The regime doesn't know about this place, so ya can relax now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good. But since when am I part of the rebellion? I don't recall signing up.</line>
<line speaker="???">Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We say you two go into that manhole.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">You narrowly escaped the guards' notice.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was like watching a pair of ostriches burying their heads in the sand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess that was a closer shave than I had thought...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Anyway, you're safe and sound now, and that's what really counts. Oh, I also have some evidence for you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">So, what is this dubious hovel we've found ourselves in, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the Defiant Dragons' safe house... also known as the former Sahdmadhi Law Offices.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">I see... Well. Though it might just be happenstance... ...here I am -- a chief prosecutor -- hiding out in a rebel base.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, please don't report this place to the local police, Prosecutor Edgeworth... <thought>Might as well take a look around while we're waiting for the heat to die down out there.</thought> Come on, Athena. Stop moping over there and help me check this place out.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*shudder* Please tell me there's a shower here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a sink in the kitchen. And if you're lucky, maybe even some soap.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........I'm sorry I even asked.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a scary-looking knife sticking out of the queen's picture. If anyone saw this, they'd think the Defiant Dragons were a violent group.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, that? That was actually me trying to kill a fly. I threw that knife at it and whiffed, and the thing ended up stuck right between her eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean this wasn't on purpose?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, what's with the altar?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">It's where we pay our respects to the victims of the Defense Culpability Act. The DC Act is a heinous law that puts innocent people to death!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A law that's supposed to protect the people sends them to their graves instead... Talk about insane.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait... Don't tell me we have to go back through the manhole to get out of here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The only reason this safe house is still safe is because the front door's been boarded up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Fine, then I'll just have to live here till the revolution begins!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What if I told you rats come out at night?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I bet the revolution never thought it'd get a new ally this way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hm? Who's the kid... Wait a second! That's YOU, Apollo! I'd recognize those horns anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that really the only way ANYBODY recognizes me?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee hee. You were so cute! ...And who's THAT fine-looking young man?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Nahyuta, back when he used to smile.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Wow. His smile is absolutely angelic.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sure brings back memories! That was taken the day we all went out fishing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What was Prosecutor Sahdmadhi like when he was younger?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">He was kinda quiet, but passionate when it came to his convictions. When he finally made prosecutor, he was all fired up to change Khura'in for the better. But now he's nothing more than Ga'ran's lackey!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">(Seems like Datz has a lot to say about Nahyuta. I'll ask him about his thoughts later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These pictures sure bring back memories. Nahyuta is cheerfully smiling in this one. That quiet smile he gives in court now seems almost fake by comparison.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeewww... Is that a newt? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come on, Athena. Can't you tell a gecko when you see one?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the difference?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Geckos like to live in houses, while newts prefer to be outside near water. They're totally different creatures.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, how do you know this one wasn't caught outside near some water? It could very well be a gecko.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I'm pretty sure it's a newt.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so then you agree it's a newt, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! <thought>I fell right into her trap!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're both wrong. It's just a plain old lizard.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm surprised to see so many appliances here. There's even a TV. </line>
<line speaker="Datz">Speaking of which, we gave the people of Khura'in quite a shock... ...when "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm" was last on TV.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean that show where actors play the parts of Dhurke and Rayfa? You hijacked that in the middle of its broadcast, right?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. All their writers do each week is try to ruin the Defiant Dragons' good name. So we decided to hit 'em where it hurts! Har har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must've been real shocking, especially for the kids who'd waited all week to see it. I mean, the show's main villain was actually hijacking the very show he's in!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dhurke's jacket... You should try it on, Apollo. It might actually suit you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">There's also a spare eye patch here. Why not try that on, too?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Pffft. ...*snicker* Hee hee hee! S-Sorry, sorry. Just picturing you in all that... Ha ha ha ha! It's just too funny!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oww... My pride...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sahdmadhi Law Offices... That's the sign Dhurke used to display out front. Hey, Datz. I heard the office used [sic]do quite a bit of business. </line>
<line speaker="Datz">That it did. Dhurke was a famous lawyer with countless courtroom victories, after all. He was the Dauntless Dragon who turned trials upside down... ...snatching victory from the jaws of defeat! His fame as a lawyer spread far and wide across Khura'in back in the day. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I hope the day comes when he can proudly display this sign again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's with all the spider webs, Datz? Don't you ever clean the place?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Not the webs! We have what ya call a symbiotic relationship. They catch the bugs that get in here, and I don't clean 'em up!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know... that actually makes a lot of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is Dhurke's old law book.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, there's a mark on the cover. It looks like it was branded with a hot iron.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I think it was done in protest against the Defense Culpability Act. There's an entry on the DC Act right here. See?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, so this is the infamous anti-lawyer law you guys are always talking about...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what's in this file. Oh, it's full of newspaper clippings. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It seems to be a collection of documents and information on Amara's assassination. <thought>So this is what Dhurke was talking about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We already know most of the stuff here on top. Let's see what else there is. Wow, where did he get all this? Umm... Anything important here...? Hmm, what about this... "Apollo's roving musician father got caught up in this incident and lost his life." ...Whaaat?! Th-This is about your father, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like it. But I was never told much more than what's written here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Really? How come? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke always skated around the subject. Maybe he thought I was still too young. Plus, I always thought of Dhurke as my dad, so I never really brought it up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Oh, I see. Still... I feel kind of sorry for your real dad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>My real dad... I was never really interested in learning about him. But after seeing his picture, I can't help but feel a little curious. I wonder if Datz could tell me anything about him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo, this file looks like it might be useful. But there are so many pages, I can't tell what's important. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We ne4ed someone to help organize all of this. <thought>And I think I know just the person to ask.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This file has a ton of information on Amara's assassination. We should go over the important parts later.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Datz, you guys are still using this office, I see. </line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. 'Cept now it's the official HQ of the Defiant Dragons. But as Dhurke said, and I quote... "We must keep it for the day when Khura'in needs lawyers once more."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Restoring the legal system to its rightful form through popular uprising... You can tell how much Khurke believes in his cause.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, and AJ. Dhurke said something else that might interest ya. He said he hopes you'll come back and take over this office someday. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T-Take over?! Me?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Those were his words. He may've been half joking though.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Dhurke! Guess what I heard from PW! AJ's become a lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Yeah, I've been meaning to tell you. </line>
<line speaker="Datz">Must've been because of you, Dhurke!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm not so sure about that. I imagine he's already forgotten about me.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Whaddaya talking about? I bet he can't wait to follow in your footsteps.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah, ha ha ha. Nothing would make me happier. Maybe one day he'll return to Khura'in and take over this office. ...Heh. It's just a pipe dream, though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Dhurke really said that?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Dhurke was never a hands-on kinda dad... ...but not a day went by that he wasn't thinking of ya. That much I'm sure of.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Doesn't get more paternal than that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Dhurke... And to think, I really did spend my days trying to forget you. I'm looking forward to a nice, long talk once you're free.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, wasn't Nahyuta once part of the Defiant Dragons?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. Yuty was a rising star in the resistance! He vowed to fight for the cause through the legal system. Said he's become a prosecutor, and give Inga and Ga'ran the smackdown they deserved!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But now he's...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah... a puppet of the Ga'ran regime. Not only that, but now he's gonna prosecute his own dad. It doesn't add up!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder what happened to him.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Me, too. But if I had to guess... ...I'd say Ga'ran has some serious leverage over him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leverage? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Wish I knew. But it seems like Dhurke knows. I tried to press him about it, but he wouldn't say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it, Dhurke did say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta... is suffering...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. He knows the rightful state of Khura'in's legal system... ...but something forced him to bend to Ga'ran's will, and it's tearing him apart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If that's the case... ...I bet Nahyuta doesn't really want to go through with Dhurke's prosecution.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you know what my biological father was like?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Dhurke once told me about him. He was a modern minstrel, walking the world and making music in his travels.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">This file also has some information on your real dad. It says he died in the blaze at Queen Amara's residence twenty-three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's right. Dhurke had invited him over. Dhurke's the kinda guy who can become fast friends with just about anyone. And it seems your pops was like that, too, AJ. They hit it off at a bar... ...and the next thing ya know, Dhurke's asked him over to play some tunes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And then the place went up in flames...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah. Dhurke had just stepped out for a sec when the fire broke out. .........Apollo. You were there, too, but you were still just a baby.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I remember hearing about that when I was little.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, it was a crying shame. Your pops just happened to take you along that day. So you were there with him when the fire broke out. But Dhurke risked his life to save you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's like Dhurke's done nothing but save me all my life...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">All your pops's stuff got burned up. Including anything that could've helped us identify him. All we knew about him at first was his stage name, "Jangly Justice" or something like that. Dhurke did everything he could just to dig up what little we know now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, what about my mother? Do you know anything about her?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">All we know is she was traveling with your pops. But that day, she was off doing something on her own.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, she probably didn't even know my father had been with Dhurke, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But she must've been desperate to find you and your father once you'd gone missing.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">No doubt. But the queen's assassination threw the kingdom into chaos. The police were so overwhelmed, they were probably hardly of any help to her. We searched and searched till our legs gave out, too, but we never found her. And with your father's stuff all burned up, we had zero leads -- not even a photo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that's how I became an orphan...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah... Who knows? Maybe your mom read about the details of the fire in the newspaper. And maybe she figured you'd died along with your pops.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, I had no idea you'd been through all that, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, I wanted to ask you about this picture.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That's the picture of your pops that Dhurke found. And he had a heck of a time tracking it down. He said he searched all over for it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why...? Why would he go through all that trouble?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Datz, please tell us everything you know about Apollo's dad!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The Mark of the Dragon... That's the symbol of our group, the Defiant Dragons.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke has the same mark tattooed on the palm of his hand, right?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. And I've got one, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Where?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">On my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, you mean metaphorically. Like you're ready to die at any time for the cause or something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You got that right. Dead or alive, I'll always be a Defiant Dragon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, about this file... Can you help me figure out whihc pages are the most relevant?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yup, sure can. I got the whole thing memorized. See this page? It's definitely worth a look.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, that's right! Prosecutor Sahdmadhi was part of the royal family, wasn't he!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. But he was expelled after that whole thing with Dhurke happened. He must've gone through hell once he entered the legal world though.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Because of the whole "the sins of the father are visited upon his children" thing?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. In the eyes of the people, Dhurke is not only a traitor to his kingdom... ...he's also the terrorist who assassinated the previous queen. So, as his son, Yuty no doubt got the cold shoulder at every turn.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That must've been really hard on him.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, the ties between father and son aren't something you could break, even if you tried. No matter where he went, he was probably labeled the son of a criminal. But despite it all, he made a name for himself through blood, sweat, and tears. I mean, just look at him now. He's a star prosecutor working cases around the globe. He's become a hero! The pride and joy of Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now that's the Nahyuta I know -- super smart and never willing to give in. He must've studied and fought like his life depended on it to get to where he is today.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Ahhhhhh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Do you know something about this?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Nope. Just felt like shouting is all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He had me going there for a sec...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Your poor son -- imprisoned for a crime he didn't commit... Let's petition the government for his release and a declaration of innocence!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm? Who's that?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hey there, Mrs. Inmee. Hard at work, I see. </line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">Yes, I have my own battle that I must wage. After all, there are many who suffer under the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Rebel">Mrs. Inmee! Please don't forget about our case, too!</line>
<line speaker="Beh'leeb">I won't! I will look into it as soon as I am able.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, Datz? What's Mrs. Inmee doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">She's lending an ear to all those suffering under the regime's wrongful accusations. A lady whose husband's been imprisoned, parents whose son's been falsely charged... She's helping all those types of people.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So she's trying to help the revolution along... ...in her own special way.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yep. And thanks to her, more and more folks are coming over to our side! All the people who've been unhappy with the regime have been waiting for just this chance! And they're starting to speak out in support of us!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The people are responding... and a grassroots movement is growing... Dhurke's dream of revolution may finally come true.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">What should we do about the Founder's Orb? We'll probably run into the royal guards again the moment we leave this place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we can't stay here forever, so we'll have to think of something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I've got it. Why don't you hold on to it, Datz? It should be safe here, right?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">You can count on me! I'll get it back to you in time for tomorrow's trial at the Hall of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What now, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we've got a handle on what happened twenty-three years ago. Maybe we should pay Dhurke a visit. There's something I want to show him. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'll join you. I want to talk to him before tomorrow's trial.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">Maybe I should wait here, then. We'll attract undue attention if we go in too large of a group.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a yak. They used to serve as a beast of burden here.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">They're actually kind of cute up-close. Hello there, big fella! Or are you a girl...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, if you stick your face that close to it, it's liable to--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeewwww, gross! ..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Need some tissues?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-I could use a handful of wet naps, if you've got 'em...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's this bird doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wouldn't get too close to it if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="???">RAWWWWWWRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Athena, meet the warbaa'd. Its cry resembles a lion's roar to scare off predators.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow... that's one gutsy little bird. But I bet it's not really all that tough.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about we just leave the bird alone?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So many street stalls... And they all have stuff you can't find back home.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">We should spend some time shopping here when this case is over. I'd like to buy Trucy a souvenir or something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a poster here... "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's a special-effects-driven action-here show that's become a huge hit here in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe it's a cultural thing, but she totally looks like a villain to me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Khura'in's national delicacy, magatah'man -- or "soul buns," if that makes it easier. Apparently, they're so delicious, they'll send your soul straight to the Twilight Realm.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Delicious"? More like "deadly."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, in one of the commercials, an old man literally drops dead after taking a bite. And at the very end, there's a warning that goes, "Enjoy at your own risk."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like I said: deadly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is the manhole that leads to Dhurke's office-turned-safe house. It's the only way in or out. And for obvious reasons, there's no doorbell or welcome mat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The souvenir stands sure are popular with the tourists. I should check them out later.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tehm'pul Temple is just up ahead. When I was a kid, I used to race Nahyuta and my friends to the top.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The victim was the Minister of Justice, the second most powerful person here in Khura'in. In Wright Anything Agency terms... ...I guess that would be you, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. Thanks, but... ...everyone knows it's Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Yeah, you're probably right. On second thought, she might actually be number one. I mean, even Mr. Wright is no match for her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Remind me not to forget to buy her a souvenir.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I can't believe Dhurke's been fighting the good fight for over twenty years. Fighting for the truth and the repeal of the Defense Culpability Act...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. And being branded a traitor for it. That's got to be extremely hard on him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whatever happens, we can't let them find him guilty! We have to help him achieve his life's dream!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........What? Are you just going to show that to me without a word?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess she doesn't have anything to say about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Well?! Are you going to at least say SOMETHING?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Edgeworth and I already searched this room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, okay. <thought>I wonder if anything interesting turned up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Je suis L'Belle! SAMPLE"... Now THERE'S a brand I know well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Yeah... Me, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see what it says on the back. "The hair care sensation celebrities have been RAVING about!" "Guaranteed to make you WANT to proclaim, 'Je suis L'Belle!' to the world!" "This product is NOT FOR SALE. EVER. Even if you come to really like it, PEASANT."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I REALLY still don't get his sales strategy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We already investigated that, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hey there, son. Came to see your old man again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hi, Dhurke. Guess they're done questioning you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah... You'd think Nahyuta might've cut his old man a little slack, but no. He really laid into me. Seems they're really keen on recovering the Founder's Orb. When I wouldn't tell them where it was, he confiscated what few possessions I had left.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Wait, Dhurke's not wearing his attorney's badge. They even took THAT from him? *sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He confiscated all my prized jailbreaking tools.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did you expect? I mean, no prosecutor in their right mind would let a prisoner keep stuff like that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did he take your attorney's badge, too?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No. I thought it strange, but... ...just when it looked like he was going to take it from me, he changed his mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder why.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Indeed. I find it hard to understand anything he does these days.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Khura'inese attorney's badge... You've worn it all these years -- even though all the lawyers are gone.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, because the Dragon's Eye is the embodiment of my creed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>To show the world that "a dragon never yields," huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, Dhurke? Why do you still wear your badge? You're not a lawyer anymore, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This badge is my heart and soul, son. I'll never stop trying to realize my dream -- not until my very last breath.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">"A dragon never yields," right?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Exactly. ...Nahyuta, Apollo, I vow to restore Khura'in's legal system to its rightful state one day. I want to pass on to you a world where you can live free from the fear of tyranny.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He was always saying stuff like that to the two of us. Nahyuta... Is the reason why you didn't take Dhurke's badge... ...because you still remember those talks, too? I really hope that's what it is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Son, would you keep my badge for me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure?! I can't take something so important to you.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's exactly why I want you to hold on to it, Apollo. I'm placing my fate in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........All right. I'll make sure it stays safe.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Inga Karkhuul Khura'in... He was an entirely insufferable, unlikable fellow, but I never thought he'd wind up dead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you like him?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He was the most hawkish one in the Ga'ran regime. He established the secret police to arrest us rebels without due process. Those they managed to capture were immediately executed. My compatriots in the Defiant Dragons came to call him "The Executioner."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"The Executioner"? Pretty ironic, considering how he ended up.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He's probably in Hell now, being tormented by those he wrongfully put to death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I found this in the tomb. Look familiar?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Ah! Th-That's...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Where did you find it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Down between the monk statues in the tomb. Is it yours, Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Oh, um, it's... it's something I bought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">? <thought>Why's he suddenly acting all awkward?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hmm... I wonder when I lost it. let's have it. It's very important to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">O-Of course... <thought>I'll just make a note about it for future reference.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Careful with that. Don't go showing it around town. You'll be branded a rebel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But I'm not a rebel.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't be ridiculous. You're a member of the Defiant Dragons simply by being my son. Or did you think that dragon tattoo on your rear end was just for show?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Whaaat?! You have a tattoo on your butt, Apollo?! Let me see!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Relax, Athena. He's just jerking our chains again.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I prepared that myself. Use it well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm surprised you were able to gather this much information.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It wasn't easy. After all, all of the evidence from the assassination was lost in the fire. And the newly-installed Ga'ran regime was in full control of the media. Every lead I tried to follow led to a dead end.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then how am I supposed to solve this case?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...You'll figure something out once tomorrow's trial is underway. After all, no one's looked into this assassination since my last trial.</line>
<line speaker="Apolo"><thought>I hope I can turn things around enough to snatch victory from the jaws of defeat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ah, my attorney's badge. You don't see those around here anymore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not exactly something you can wear publicly, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah... And if you did, people would jeer and throw things at you. I've had tomatoes, cabbages -- even eggs thrown at me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That sounds awful. But at least they didn't throw rocks.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...True. Plus, if you were good at catching things, you'd have the start of a good meal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's true. An hour's walk can yield all you need for a nice, big hot pot! Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Dhurke... I'm sorry I never knew how bad things were when you were raising us.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Is that for me, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I was just wondering if you knew anything about it.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What? You came to visit me and you didn't even bring a present?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll take that as a "no."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. I'll give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did the minister mean when he said... ...he had someone dear to you in the palm of his hand? Who was he talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hm? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta seemed to know, but he wouldn't tell me anything.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">W-Well, I've no idea, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you obediently followed his every word after he said that... ...so it seems to me the minister was in close proximity to someone you really care about.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, um...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone you really care about that isn't Nahyuta...? Wait, don't tell me--! Is there a new lady in your life, Dhurke?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Wh-What?! No! Don't be ridiculous, son!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.................. The love of my life was Amara. But she's gone now and there will never be another.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ah! My bracelet! Wait, does this mean...? Dhurke... Have you REALLY not met somebody new?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The love of my life was Amara. But she's gone now and there will never be another.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. You can't fool me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">D-Don't be ridiculous! I'm just getting tense because of your intrusive questions! Anyone would react the same way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">(Hmm, I guess that's not it... Still, my bracelet reacted... ...so I know he must be hiding something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. You can't fool me. You tensed up when you said, "But she's gone now." And you unconsciously moved your arm... ...causing something to press up against your jacket.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ahhhhh! ...H-How did you do that?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, so that's it! You're hiding a woman's photo up your sleeve. You don't have to keep secrets like that from me, Dhurke. You're an eligible bachelor now. But you'll... introduce her to me at some point, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I keep telling you, there's no other woman!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine, then let's see it. What are you hiding up your sleeve?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...It's just this. Satisfied?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? But that's the pendant we found in Amara's Tomb...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">See? I wasn't trying to hide anything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Then why did he tense up?</thought> Dhurke, let me take a look at that.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Hey, what's this button for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! I-It's...! It's a picture of Khurke and some lady! And she's really young-looking, too!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mon Dieu! Are you into younger women, Dhurke?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Heh heh. Dhurke, you old dog, you. You got yourself a younger lover.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Will you stop with this nonsense! This is Amara before she died. If you look closer, you'll see that I was younger, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Aww. That's no fun.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wait a second. Haven't we seen this woman before?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........Now that you mention it...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Isn't this woman the same as the one in the pendant's photo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Have you had your eyes checked lately, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm wrong, not blind! Maybe I should compare the pendant's photo against the evidence again.</thought> Dhurke, I know I've seen the woman in the pendant's photo before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The woman in the pendant is also the one in this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">A-Apollo, where did you get this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">From the safe in Inga's room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo. If this is Queen Amara, it had to have been taken at least twenty-three years ago. But that's just not possible.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I just noticed the same thing. Here's why this photo couldn't be twenty-three years old!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look closer. Doesn't that part look, you know, kinda modern?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I don't know about that. Maybe you just don't know what's considered new and hip these days, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This photo is at least twenty-three years old. I don't know how you could say otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's where you're wrong, Dhurke. <thought>There's something in this photo that couldn't have existed back then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at the law book. It has the mark of the Defiant Dragons branded on it. But that mark didn't exist until after you started your revolutionary activities, Dhurke. So, this photo must've been taken AFTER Ga'ran came into power. ...And that didn't happen until AFTER Amara was assassinated.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So then, how could Amara even be in this photo? ...............Wait a second. That would mean that Amara is... ...still alive?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrgh! ............Looks like you found me out, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... So it's actually true?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke! What do you mean, Amara's still alive?! I thought she'd been assassinated.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........So did I. But it seems she made it out alive, only to be held captive by the Ga'ran regime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why would they do that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">When I fled from the law and went underground twenty-three years ago... ...I heard some shocking news from a Defiant Dragons spy. There were rumors of Queen Amara being sighted in the palace.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And those rumors turned out to be true?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. I snuck into the palace to see for myself. She was confined within the grounds, but otherwise, she was as fit as a fiddle.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">S-So then, the sarcophagus in the tomb... It's empty?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. That entire tomb is one big charade. Ga'ran had it built to stage Amara's death.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So we're not going to be cursed by her vengeful spirit? That's a relief.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">She was being held under virtual house arrest. So I freed her, and we made a run for it. This photo was taken back then.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Look at how they're both grinning from ear to ear.</thought> .........Hm? <thought>There's a fingerprint on the metal part. I guess Dhurke must've left it by accident.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ooh, Mr. Sahdmadhi! I wanna hear ALL about how you ran away with Queen Amara!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm surprised Amara agreed to run away with you. I mean, Ga'ran must've told her that you tried to kill her.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I tried to convince her that I wasn't the one who set the blaze.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And she believed you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">She said, and I quote, "I shall accompany you so I may ascertain the truth myself." Heh, she always was a tough one to read.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet she was thrilled you came to her rescue, Mr. Sahdmadhi. To be set free by your beloved... It's like something out of a fairy tale.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah, well... There was no "happily ever after" once Ga'ran's people caught up with us. They took Amara away to who-knows-where. I snuck back into the palace and searched high and low for her, but to no avail. They probably moved her to some remote mountain prison or the like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, does Nahyuta know about this?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He knows she's his true mother. I told him as much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... Is that why Nahyuta is following Ga'ran's orders?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Most likely.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So then, do you think that deep down, he doesn't really want to prosecute you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, he's not one to show his feelings. And lately, I've had no idea what he's thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo. We need to grill the queen about Amara when we have the chance.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Um. I was wondering about something. The little baby the lady's holding... Is that Prosecutor Sahdmadhi?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not necessarily. It could just as well be me. After all, we're only one year apart.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know. I mean, the kid in the picture is too cute to be you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Let's settle this by asking Dhurke himself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Amara... I hope she's doing well.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've been wondering, Dhurke... How could a commoner win the heart of a queen anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Hm? Wait, don't tell me... Have you fallen for Princess Rayfa, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo. I had no idea you liked your women so young.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I don't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's barely in her teens. That's just not right, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Listen to me! I never said anything about her!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aww, it's all right son. In a few more years, the age difference won't matter so much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Would you guys just stop already?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, about the cute little kid in this photo... Is that me?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Huh? What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Athena">See? I told you it was Prosecutor Sahdmadhi.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hm? .........Oh, I see. Well, either way, it's not you, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then... ...if it's Nahyuta, it was taken when he was about a year old, right? And that would mean... ...you ran away with Amara around 22 or 23 years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hm? .........You're pretty good with numbers, son! Impressive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? <thought>What kind of answer is that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Before you go, son, there is something else I need to tell you. Something important.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is it, Dhurke? I've never seen you act so serious before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So what's this "something important" you have to tell me?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">........................ Listen son. Even if you manage to prove me innocent tomorrow... ............... ...I... I don't have long to live.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? ............... Wh-What are you talking about? </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What I mean is, I can already hear the Twilight Realm calling my name. There is no escaping death now that it has its sights set on me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! ............I-Is this another one of your jokes?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I wish it was.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha... Ha ha ha. You can't fool me, Dhurke. <thought>Hm? That's strange. Why isn't my bracelet reacting?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Are you sick?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I-It's something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're not joking?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........I'm afraid not, son. Sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Isn't there a cure? Or at least some sort of treatment?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Unfortunately not. Not for what I've got.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you need some kind of surgery, I'll work hard until I can pay for it! So... Please...!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........It's too late. There's nothing more to be done now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But you always say, "A dragon never yields." So why are you giving up now?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Apollo, I'm sorry. I really am.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............I don't understand. Why is this happening, Dhurke? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">..................Listen, Apollo. I've got a favor to ask of you. Would you keep quiet about this? I don't want my fellow Dragons to find out. They'd lose all hope if they knew I was dying. Would you do that for me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............Of course. <thought>Why is this happening now? Just when I was finally starting to feel like you really are my... I thought that this time, we'd finally... But now...</thought> ...Damn it... Why...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Listen, son. I don't have much longer to live... ...but I'll never let them execute me. Not before I finish what I need to do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I know, Dhurke. There's no way I'm going to let them prove you guilty. <thought>Before he goes, I'm going to turn back time by righting the wrongs that have been done. I'm going to restore Dhurke's freedom... ...and return a real smile to Nahyuta's face! I'm going to win this case. I just have to!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Son. I have one more... big secret.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? There's something else you've been hiding from me?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm afraid I can't tell you what it is. I'd be betraying a certain someone if I did.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Forgive me. You'll just have to find out for yourself. That's the only way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't understand, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">..................... Apollo. In court tomorrow... ...you may find yourself faced with a truth that is difficult to accept. But I know you. And I know you can handle the truth, no matter what it turns out to be. I know that because I believe in you. You're my son, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. <thought>What is he talking about? Wait... He's not going to reveal that he actually IS the killer, is he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like we've run out of things to discuss. Apollo? ...Are you okay?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm fine.</line>
<line speaker="???">FREE HIM NOW...!!! RELEASE DHURKE...!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's going on out there?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sounds like the party's getting started without me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It's coming from the temple. Let's go, Apollo, and take a look!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whoa! What IS all this?!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Ow-ow-oww! Let go, will ya?!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">W-What are they--</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Huh? Well, look at that! The people are coming to take their courts back!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Don't hold back, men! Arrest them all!</line>
<line speaker="Rebel">Dhurke belongs to the people! Give him back! </line>
<line speaker="Rebel">Yeaaaaah! Where are you holding him?!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Quiet down, you!</line>
<line speaker="Child">Th-They have my big sister, too! But she didn't do anything wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Ouch! YOUCH! Stop pulling my hair!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Release my son! Release him now...!!!</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Aaaagh! Stop that! No biting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This... is really something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it looks like Datz and Mrs. Inmee are leading the charge.</line>
<line speaker="???">...You unenlightened fools. Do you honestly think this will change anything?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yuty! ...Why do you keep serving that witch Ga'ran?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! <thought>It's...</thought> Hey, Nahyuta!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">! You again?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">It would appear that the insurgents are fanning the flames of the rebellion. ...But I never thought it would grow so large. However, they will all be under arrest shortly. Reinforcements are almost here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They'll be arrested? Just for protesting?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">They are aiding and abetting a criminal by seeking his release. Her Eminence, Queen Ga'ran, has ordered they be arrested and judged en masse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But weren't you once a member of the Defiant Dragons, too? How can you go along with this?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I am simply following the orders that Her Eminence has handed down.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it can't be as simple as that. Listen, Nahyuta. There's something I want to talk to you about. Hey! You're not getting away this time! We need to talk.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........*sigh* I see there is no reasoning with you. Very well, then. Speak.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look at all these people! They've got the whole temple surrounded.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And it looks like Datz is fanning the flames. The police are going to really have their hands full with this many protesters.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This whole thing is like a powder keg waiting to go off. We should keep our distance for now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta, do you really have to serve as prosecutor on Dhurke's case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I mean, prosecuting your own flesh and blood... It's just not right.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Again with this drivel? Your ethical standards are not the be-all, end-all of the world around you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not getting into another debate with him.</thought> .........Nahyuta, did you know that Dhurke is sick?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He apparently doesn't have that much longer to live. If found guilty, he probably wouldn't even make it until his execution day.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Knowing this, are you still prepared to send an already dying man to his grave?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Enough with the zen monk act, Nahyuta. Tell me how you really feel.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........Mr. Justice. Each person is born with a role to fulfill. And I... must fulfill mine.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As for why you've been at Ga'ran's every beck and call... ...I think I might have the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta. You know the truth about your mother, don't you? About how the former queen is still alive and being held somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">So Dhurke told you, did he... Yes, it's true. My mother was spirited away to some remote corner of this kingdom... ...to keep her safe from harm.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Safe from harm? But Dhurke said the Ga'ran regime is holding her captive.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">No, they are keeping her safe.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you don't know where Amara is being held?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">I only know that it is some secluded hideaway where visitors are not allowed. I have heard she leads a simple life, akin to that of monastic disciples.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sure sounds like she's being held captive to me.</thought> Listen, Nahyuta... Aren't you really doing the queen's bidding... ...because she's holding Amara captive?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And this whole thing with Dhurke... You know he didn't really kill Inga, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke doesn't have much longer to live, so I want to help him however I can. This time, it's our turn...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sniffle* *hiccup* *hiccup*</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You... You could've been killed... But you risked your life... to save us... Why...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What a silly question. What father wouldn't risk his life to save his own children? Nahyuta, Apollo... Don't you ever hesitate to call when you need me. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's our turn to help Dhurke however we can.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.................................... .........What you speak of... is futile.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">.........Let it go, and move on. The guilty verdict... The hopelessness... You must resign yourself to it all. Clinging to false hope now will only serve to magnify your future despair. So let it go... and move on...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Nahyuta. <thought>Are you really going to just roll over on this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...I've no more time for idle chatter. I must prepare for tomorrow's trial. Now, if you'll excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">That's...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The rebels' "Mark of the Dragon." It symbolizes a person's opposition to the Defense Culpability Act.</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You seek to argue with me about the legal system? ...If so, you're wasting your breath. Lawyers and prosecutors do not lay down the law; they merely follow it. The laws decreed by our sovereign are absolute. There is no room for debate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So "let it go, and move on," right? Why is that your only answer to everything?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I picked up on that, too. Looks like Dhurke really won't be the only one who will need my help tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I think it's about time to pay Queen Ga'ran another visit... ...and ask her about her sister Amara.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I didn't know Dhurke was sick. What's wrong with him? I mean, he looked fine to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I really don't know. The Dhurke I remember would go out hunting in the middle of winter... ...while everyone around him was dropping like flies with the flu and whatnot.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">........................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Come on everyone, cheer up! The worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo, you don't have to put on a brave face for--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I'm fine! Besides, Dhurke will have his day in court. I won't let this get me down.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So you don't know Queen Amara at all, Apollo? I thought that since you used to live with Dhurke, that maybe you had met her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke escaped with Amara twenty-three or so years ago, so I was still just an infant. Even if I had met her, I wouldn't have remembered it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess not. But that means you may have been cared for by a queen. And if you had been, then... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-Then what?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You would've turned out... I don't know... better?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hm? The royal guard isn't around.</line>
<line speaker="???">That is utter... utter... hooey! You cannot continue to deceive the people like that!</line>
<line speaker="???">...Rayfa. Justice is much more than simply speaking the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that Princess Rayfa and Queen Ga'ran over there?</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Y-You deceived me, too, Mother! How can I ever believe a word you say again?! You... You... nincompoop! .........Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Benevolence... ...I, uh, couldn't help but overhear...</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">Nnnnnnnnnnnngh... You impudent--!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oww!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you okay, Mr. Wright? I can't believe she actually punched you...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Yeah, I'm used to it by now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's the matter with the princess?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It sounded like she was arguing with her mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Maybe it has something to do with this picture. Rayfa said she had to ask her mother about some secret or another as soon as she saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then... ...does that mean that Princess Rayfa knows what really happened? That Amara wasn't assassinated, and is still very much alive?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would seem so. And she doesn't seem to be taking Ga'ran's lies very well. But that's no surprise, considering how much Rayfa reveres her mother.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That would definitely cause her a great deal of anguish and sadness.</line>
<line speaker="???">Eavesdropping, are we? How very rude.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um, nice to meet you, Your Eminence. We're actually here to speak with you, if you could spare a moment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo? What are you doing? This is the queen's audience chamber. You can't snoop around in here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Sorry! <thought>I wonder what it'd be like to sit there with Athena and Mr. Wright groveling at my feet... No! Stop! I can't let myself think about that sort of thing!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Eminence, Dhurke told me about Amara. About how she's still alive, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...We know not of what you speak.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">After Dhurke learned Amara was still alive, he rescued her, and they ran off together. But she was captured and remains captive in a secret location to this day. As for Nahyuta doing your bidding, it's only because Amara's life's in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Ho ho ho. What an active imagination you have.</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Ha ha ha ha ha ha! A lawyer AND a comedian! How droll!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh-Whoa. Where'd THEY come from? Anyway! If she's going to play dumb, I'll just have to jog her memory with some evidence!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, you admit that Amara's still alive?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.........Yes. She is under our protection in a safe location.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I think you mean "being held prisoner."</thought> ...And where is she being kept?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Ho ho ho. Now why would we tell the son of a traitor that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess she has a point there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Now, heed our warning, Horned Devil. It would not be wise to inform the people that Amara yet lives. It would only serve to plunge public order into chaos.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have no intention of doing that. <thought>Besides, there are real terrorists out there who might try to kill her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...Good. Now, there was something we have been meaning to ask you. Do you know what has become of the Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">The Founders Orb went missing after Dhurke took it into the tomb. As his son, we thought you might know something of its current whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I knew it. I suppose I should thank you for that free running tour of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...That was the royal guards' own doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nice try, lady. But now you're definitely not getting the orb, ever.</thought> Why do you want the orb so badly, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Because... it would be most dangerous in the wrong hands. It must be recovered.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is the legend true? Can the orb really impart spiritual power? Are you worried that someone could overthrow you with it?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">The Holy Mother's power is without equal. Should Her Holiness once again return to our world... ...she could conceivably bestow great power upon the one who unlocked the orb's secret.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess it makes sense, considering spirit channeling is a fact of life here.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...So we ask you, Horned Devil. Did you receive the Founder's Orb from Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Does it look like I did?</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...So you like to play games, do you? ...Royal guard!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Eminence!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Search this devil, and his belongings!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">At once, Your Eminence! Don't move!!! You're only making this haaaaaarder on yourseeelf!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes! Hey, cut it out! Argh! What the--?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek! Apollo! Don't strip here!</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Stop resisting!!! Just submit to our strip search alreeeeeady!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, wait! Hey! Cut it out! Aaaaaaaaaaaaagh! .................. <thought>Rest in pieces, my poor, tattered dignity.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">There's no sign of the Founder's Orb, Your Eminence!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.........So, you have hidden it somewhere. Heh. No matter. We shall recover it one way or another once you are found guilty of abetting the accused.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Dhurke was right. She really is bent on getting the orb.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">What have we here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's the attorney's badge used by lawyers like me back home.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, an effect you caused by enacting the Defense Culpability Act.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">His own ill will was visited upon him. So it is within the cycle of karma. Others might call it divine retribution -- the punishment of the gods.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't seem particularly sad, even though it was your own husband.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">We were betrayed by the man we had called husband. Moreover, we are the Grand Priestess, summoner of spirits from the Twilight Realm. For us, death is not the end, for we can still speak with those who have passed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess being a spirit-channeling queen gives you a different take on life and death.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Eminence, I ask that you take a look at this photo.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Why, that's--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a photo of Amara. And here you can see a law book bearing the mark of the Defiant Dragons. I believe you know what that means.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">.................. ..........Very well. Royal guard, stand down.</line>
<line speaker="Royal Guard">Yes, Your Eminence! Your wish is our command!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">It seems there is no need to perpetuate this charade any longer. We shall speak... of all we know.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">To burn such a mark upon a sacred text of the law... He will surely be visited by what he has wrought. And to think he once called himself a man of the law.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think it's just his way of objecting to the DC Act.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Yet that act is but an objection to his falsified evidence. How appalling that even now he recognizes no responsibility and knows no shame.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, I was wondering if...</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">We have no intention of bestowing any information upon you or any other lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess someone doesn't like to play nice with others.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like the princess is back. </line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">I took a stroll to try to calm myself, but... I still find this situation unacceptable. The people must be informed about Queen Amara!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! <thought>So she DOES know about that!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Rayfa, you do not yet possess a clear grasp of how a government and its people interact. There will always be secrets that must be kept from the ignorant masses.</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa">You have little faith in our people, Mother. But it is the Royal Priestess's duty to always speak the truth. And as such I cannot remain silent! I will not!</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">Hah. The truth, you say? Your mind has been poisoned by the Barbed One.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was an honor and a pleasure, Your Eminence.</line>
<line speaker="Ga'ran">...We must speak with our child. It is a mother's duty to discipline her child, after all. Now, if you would excuse us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Discipline? Coming from her, I don't like the sound of that at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Apollo, let's head back to the safe house for now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good idea. We need to go over what we've found and collect our thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...Ah, you're back.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Thank you for holding down the fort, Chief Prosecutor Edgeworth. Sorry it took so long. Hope you weren't too bored.</line>
<line speaker="Edgeworth">...I watched "The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm" while you were gone. And my verdict is... it's an outrage! Especially its theme song. Even worse, the people here believe it's an original, Khura'inese show. Can you believe it! I've already spoke about it at length with Mr. Are'bal here, and he...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not sure what he's babbling about, but at least it seems he wasn't bored.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Moving along to things that actually matter... We've gathered about all the information and evidence we can concerning this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think it's time we go over everything we've learned so far.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo. We probably shouldn't search the place while Datz is gone. Besides, we need to go over the case for tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What's with you recently? It's like you want to spend every free minute we have snooping.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But don't you get the urge to look at everything you can sometimes, too?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The orb trial... Maya's abduction... And the murder of the mastermind behind it all, Justice Minister Inga... It's a lot to consider. Think you have all the facts straight in your head?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yep, I've got it covered, Mr. Wright. It's the truth about what really went down that's going to be the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, it's like the more we learn about this case, the less we understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I agree. There's a deep darkness enveloping this case. I'm almost afraid of what we will find once we lift that black veil. Suffice to say, the real killer is certainly waiting underneath.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The real killer, huh... Now that's the million dollar question.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who killed Inga, and why? Think Apollo. Who would you say had a motive to commit this crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I, for one, am drawing a complete blank.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I want to know how the killer slipped into the tomb, killed Inga, and slipped back out... ...without ever being seen. That's a bona fide locked-room mystery right there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we've collected plenty of evidence and statements. I just hope the rest comes out in court. It'll be a thinner tightrope than usual, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This case has one big fly in the ointment. In order to prove Dhurke completely innocent... ...we'll also have to exonerate him of the crime committed twenty-three years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Amara's supposed assassination...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right. We know Amara's still alive... ...but Dhurke could still be charged with plotting to kill her.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He couldn't discover the truth-- even after over two decades of investigating. So our biggest hurdle is going to be the complete lack of evidence. The fire made sure of that.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, have you ever won a case without any evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, that's one thing I've never done before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A trial unprecedented even in the decorated annals of the Wright Anything Agency... <thought>Still, I can't help but wonder... Was there really no evidence left behind?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You flash that badge like a pro now. And with such confidence, too. I can really feel it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sure. Take Trucy's case, or that civil trial yesterday. You really came into your own during both of them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eheh... Heh heh heh. <thought>I can feel my cheeks betraying me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You'd better not be thinking of starting your own firm, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? No, of course not. <thought>I'm probably not ready for that, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Amara... She's still alive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But she's basically being held prisoner somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This puts Dhurke at a distinct disadvantage. ...Not to mention us, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And Nahyuta is under Ga'ran's thumb because of all this as well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yep. It's a problem all right, and it's not like we can just go and rescue Amara. There must be something we can do...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'll just have to pin our hopes on Dhurke's revolution!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, basically, the fates of Amara and Nahyuta... ...depend entirely on our ability to beat the charges against Dhruke tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What would you do if the Defense Culpability Act was established back home?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What would I do? That's a good question.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you worried about, Apollo? You'd always have a job as Trucy's assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh-huh... And what about you, Athena? Couldn't you become a therapist?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I don't know if I could do it for a living...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd probably go back to playing piano.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey! What are those looks for?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just because you don't know something, doesn't mean that I do, Apollo. That's an important lesson for you to learn.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>In other words, this didn't ring any bells.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Beat the charges or die... What kind of crazy, upside-down legal system is this, anyway?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Don't worry. I can't ask someone as young as you to risk your life, Athena. So tomorrow, it'll just be me and Apollo on the courtroom floor. But you can support us by watching from the gallery.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! No... I wanna help! I'm part of the agency, too, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sorry, but this is a direct order from your boss. Plus, there's Prosecutor Blackquill to think of. He said he's use me for sword practice if I put you in harm's way.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Nrrgh... Simon... Well, at least promise me this, you two. Promise me you'll make it back alive!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha... Ha ha... Make it back alive... huh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with that face, Apollo? You'll never inspire confidence in your client like that. And it'll play right into the prosecution's hands. Remember, "the worst of times are when lawyers have to force their biggest smiles."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right! Even when it seems hopeless, or when there's not a shred of evidence to be found... ... we can never let it show on our faces... right? <thought>But will I actually be able to do that tomorrow? When push comes to shove, will I be able to force my biggest smile?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
</xml>