<xml>
<title>Turnabout Corner</title>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh... Mr. Wright's not here today?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He said his old foot injury was acting up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Old injury...!? He was all smiles yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yes, he smiled when he said we'd be fine "as long as you're there, Trucy".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes... Fine... We'll be fine. Here comes Justice!!! I started my voice training at 5 this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oooh! Do some now! I want to see! ...Er, hear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, OK. ...Ahem. My name is Apollo Justice, and I'm fine!!!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...... That sounds more like a self-mantra than voice training.</line>
<line speaker="???">...I'm fine! I'm fine! You know what I'm saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! G-Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yo, 'sup. Hit me with the guilty verdict, G! See if I care. You just hang loose and let things go with the flow. You know what I'm saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh, not really.</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">Wocky! Don't be running your mouth like that in here!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">See, that's the difference between me and you, old man. I ain't afraid of no cops. Real G's can't keep it real till they spend some hard time in the pen.</line>
<line speaker="Big Wins">You have absolutely no idea what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sounds like they've both been voice training too, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>My worst fears realized... The trial's starting and I still haven't had a real talk with my client!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Wocky Kitaki.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ready to rock 'n' roll, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ah! It's him! The pri--guy from yesterday! He's a prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...It's Mr. Gavin's brother!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Long time no see... Prosecutor Gavin. Were you taking a leave of absence?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You know that little band I started in my free time? Thing is, we got real popular. Hard to say "nein" to your fans when three of your singles go platinum, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. To be honest, I was a little concerned. I feared that you might still be distraught over that one trial...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Not to worry, Herr Judge. I wouldn't miss this day in court for the world. It's worth even more than VIP passes to one of my concerts, ja? How could I pass up a chance to see the true strength... ...of the little boy who bested my brother?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was worth canceling a show or two.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Understood. You may give your opening statements to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Before that, I was thinking... Is the air in this courtroom not a bit... serious?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It IS a court of law.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That's no way to get the crowd jumping, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They're not supposed to jump! This is a courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung, baby! Today, we play it my way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that... noise?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Sometimes you have to get on up in order to get down... to prosecuting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is crazy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The victim... Pal Meraktis, director of the Meraktis Clinic. The scene... People Park. He was found pulling a noodle stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What in the world was a doctor doing pulling a noodle stand?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, I believe... ...you will only find that out by asking the defendant, right here, right now. Because it's an undeniable truth that he shot the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean, undeniable?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">If you are to glare at anyone, Herr Justice, glare at the punk in the defendant's chair. His crime was witnessed quite clearly, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Please admit this witness to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Nein! Not yet! First, there is a little matter to be cleaned up...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could you talk without the accompaniment?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I swear I could see the guitar for a second!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is it, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The "motive", Herr Judge. Why did the little punk do it? Why did he kill the director of the Meraktis Clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not so fast! The defendant doesn't have to explain that!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? But what if the defendant specifically requests to do so? As he did this morning? I want to "give a shout out to all my homeys!" I believe he said.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Whaaaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What is right!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">They always say that, on stage, you should hit the crowd with speed and ferocity! Sounds like he got you good, huh, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this is highly unusual. But... The court will now hear from the defendant concerning his motive in the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... You, son, are the defendant... Wocky, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I ain't your son, old man! You step to a Kitaki, you best be prepared to step strong!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You "step" to a public official, you'd best be prepared to step into jail.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You got to hand it to him, Wocky sure has guts!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's not his guts I'm worried about...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well then, the court will now hear testimony on the defendant's motive... ...from the defendant himself!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I'll tell you one thing, that doctor was a quacker!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're saying you were one of the victim's patients...!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Lotta stuff goes down when you're keeping it real on the street. Tru dat. I tell you one thing, that doc was wack!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, the defense may begin the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't believe this is the first time I'm hearing about all of this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I'll tell you one thing, that doctor was a quacker!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First of all, the word you're looking for is "quack". And isn't that a little harsh? He's your family doctor...</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Who asked you, pointy-locks!? Just who do you think you are?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Uh... your lawyer?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Look, I ain't trying to hear that. He was a quacker, plain and simple.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Someone had to show him what's what!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "someone" you mean...? Was there anyone with a score to settle with this doctor? ...Besides you, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You better ask somebody else, homes. What do I care? I made up my own mind and did what had to be done. Straight gangsta-style!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But... why were you so mad at this doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Yo, sit back and listen while I drop it, J-man.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I was in his clinic 'bout half a year ago. He messed up my op something bad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you were a patient at the Meraktis Clinic half a year ago? For what reason?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">I had what you might call a "mark of honor".</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Can you explain precisely what was wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">We had a little run-in with the Rivales Family. That's when I pulled a jack move... ...and ran into an ambush. G busted a cap right in me.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">According to my sources... you "couldn't stand the stress of waiting... ...and ran in 15 minutes before the appointed time." ...By yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Hey, I was more than a match for those guys!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you were carried to the Meraktis Clinic from there?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Apparently, he was shot in the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Shot in the heart and he's still alive!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can catch bullets between my teeth! But I never learned how to catch them with my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">The bullet stopped just short of my thumper, you know what I'm saying? I woulda been golden if it weren't for that wack doc! Can't even take out a stupid bullet!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...So, as you say, the surgery was a failure.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That ain't all of it, homes!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">And then he just lets me go, without a word. See ya later, bye!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean, he just let you go without a word?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">What do you think it means!? It's wack, that's what!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm not sure what that means, but it sounds bad...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It sounds as though Herr Doktor wished to hide his mistake... This is why he let the defendant go.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">He's a liar, straight up! He's a badder G than me!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">So I gotta go in, get another doc to patch me up again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, this bullet is still...?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You know it! I can still feel it... Right there in my chest, pressin' up against my heart!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Your words are like a bullet shot straight into my heart." ...or something to that effect? Incidentally, that's from one of our hit singles.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, that sounds like a straightforward case of malpractice!</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Word, J-man. Weren't no accident, that's fo' shizzle.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That was the day I done figured it out. No O.G.'s gonna let that pass!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You figured it out that day? So you had no idea until then?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">For half a year, I didn't notice a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaaat!? You had a bullet in your chest and you didn't know!?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Heh! Takes more than a bullet to bring me down, homes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How many bullets does it take!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That's why I went to his pad that night, know what I'm saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You "went to his pad"...? Did you have an appointment to meet with the victim? In the park, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">You out of your mind!? Who makes an appointment to get the drop on someone!? I came ready to fight my way into that clinic of his. Shortest way to the clinic from my place is through that park, know what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...He's right. That does seem to be the shortest path.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">There I was, cold walking through the park... ...when he comes popping up out of nowhere, right before my eyes! I figured someone up on high was looking out for me, know what I'm saying?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Unngh... This sounds bad right from the get-go.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, there won't be any get-go if we don't get some more information!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right. First, gather the facts. Time enough for despair later!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Man, putting him down was like doing the world a favor!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wocky! ...Please consult your lawyer before saying things like that...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Chin up, Apollo! Back straight!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, why did this mistake only come to light that day?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">It was found during the Family health check-up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The F-Family check-up?</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">That was the wackest thing of all! All us G's lining up, taking eye exams 'n' all that.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Better to die young than fade away, bizzzoy!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A relief to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">Eh? Wh-What's a relief!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh? Did your father not tell you? That bullet you carry so close to your heart... if not attended to immediately... ...It could kill you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaat!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yes, Herr Doktor Meraktis had knowledge concerning this ticking "time bomb" in you. Knowledge... that could have saved your life.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">No way! Th-That's wacked!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There is proof. Your check-up report.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...How ironic that you would kill the one man capable of helping you. You're almost as careless as he was! ...Ah ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Wocky">......</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Well, now that the place is hopping... Let's get this gig started!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Started...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">We've had enough of a warm-up act, ja? Time to hear from the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Wocky sure is quiet all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm a little uneasy myself. <thought>Is this Gavin's strategy...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">So. You will tell us your name and occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">My name... is Wesley Stickler. By "occupation" I take it you refer to some labor that "profits" society at large, and supports a livelihood under which definition I must confess to being "unemployed" however, we must acknowledge the meaning of "identity" which is commonly attached to this notion of "occupation", and once we have accepted this reality, we see that our confusion is not Gestalt, per se, but derives instead from the "vagueness" inherent in all representations of thoug--</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">By which he means to say that he is a student. A junior at Ivy University if I'm not mistaken?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yes, in the Department of Science and Engineering. Filled with curiosity for all things, I spend my days in pursuit of truth, honing my...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Stickler, please direct said curiosity to the case at hand today.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Stickler. Please testify to the court about what you saw on the night of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">You ask, quite simplistically, "what I saw". However, we must understand that homo sapiens possess two eyes, each of these designed to receive and interpret data, sending images in the form of signals to the...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">That night, I passed through the park on my way home from shopping... when I saw them!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Was there anyone else in the park at that time?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I can say with 100% accuracy that there was not.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The pistol our witness refers to... is this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court accepts this into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! Don't point that thing to me!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry! I can handle myself around guns. Magic guns, at least. The ones that pigeons come out of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Very reassuring.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Mr. Justice, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... Trucy? Why are you staring like that at the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That man... I can't help but feel I've seen him somewhere before.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">That night, I passed through the park on my way home from shopping... when I saw them!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the way home from shopping, you say? Why go through the park?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ah, a fascinating inquiry. Revealing me culpable of being insufficiently verbose! Let us consider the time saved by passing through the park on the way home from the store: In that time I am capable of solving two GMAT problem sets. On average, it requires me 3 minutes, 24 seconds to complete one such set. Ergo the time to complete two is, on average, 6 minutes 48 seconds. However! In the case that the questions are in the verbal category, admittedly not m...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's enough! Enough. I get the idea.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! The court hopes to finish cross-examination sometime this month.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Please. I've a recording booked after this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And I've got a show to perform.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Gee, sorry you're all so busy!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">One man, pulling a stand. Another man, facing him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Were these men talking, by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ah, now that you mention it, they were, though I cannot claim I heard them clearly. Only fragments... such as, "You lied to me!" Oh, and... "I'm gonna give you a taste of your own medicine, pal."</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah ha ha ha! It's just as our defendant claims! I believe he wished to "teach" the victim what it felt like to take a bullet in the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that's true, then this is a vital piece of testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like he heard them clearly enough to me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Might I be allowed to amend my testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wh... What now!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">To be precise, he did not say "pal" but "man". Yes, that was the way of it. I swear it on my diploma!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's the difference!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And this other man, who was he?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I saw them quite clearly. The man facing the victim was the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How can you be so sure it was the defendant!? The crime took place at night! It would have been too dark!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...Perhaps I was remiss in not mentioning this earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">You see, in class, I always sit in the very backmost seat. Do you know why?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Who cares!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Because I do not wish anyone to copy my perfect notes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...And this relates to your testimony how?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I mention this to illustrate my predisposition to that which is "perfect". It was dark, you say? Yet there are lights in the park. If I say the defendant was in the park that night, then he was in the park that night. It is a hard, immutable fact.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He sure is confident...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He seems to be telling the truth, too. *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">In his hand he held... yes, a pistol! It was pointed at the man pulling the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure the pistol you saw is the same as the one just submitted as evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Am I "sure"? Surely... you jest! ...Or so a common witness would be tempted to say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yet I am no common witness. I see not only events as they are, but the logical structure governing these events! First, we must consider the fact that it was night in the park, which indeed restricted my field of vision due to insufficient levels of illumination. Now if we consider that the pistol, let us call it "Object A", was indeed shrouded in darkness it becomes difficult to say with certainty that Object A was indeed Object A.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think he means he couldn't see it that clearly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>My badge for a normal witness...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yet the fact that a pistol was fired before my eyes is indisputable. I can still see it when I close my eyes. The defendant raised his weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">A shot! The bullet hit the man pulling the stand from the front, square in the forehead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you absolutely certain only one shot was fired?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yes. Of course it was one shot. Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ah ha! A contradiction! Finally!</thought> Mr. Stickler. According to the Court Record, the pistol was fired twice. A clear contradiction!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Good eyes, Herr Justice. You're cool. Real cool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh? Y-You really think so?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Yet, there is no reason why this other shot had to have been fired that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Meaning...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This pistol came from the Kitaki Family mansion, ja? I think it's not unreasonable to assume the pistol had been fired once before that night. During, perhaps... another altercation?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... He's got a point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Judging from his smug expression... ...I'd say Prosecutor Gavin had that answer ready before you even spotted the problem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He seems pretty confident in his testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">We always make the biggest mistakes when we're our most confident! He's got a weak point somewhere, Apollo! Find it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Right! Better give that testimony another listen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whew... If that's all of it, I think I have a chance.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Is that you... relaxing, I see, Herr Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, er... Ahem! <cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Once is quite enough, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Pace yourself! This trial's not over yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! Eh, right! Ahem, um, look at this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The... autopsy report? Is there a problem with the autopsy report?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, right, a problem... Problem... problem... Yes!!! The problem is the location of the entry wound!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The location...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You testified that the killer shot the victim "square in the forehead", did you not?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ah, I have already determined your "angle" of inquiry. ...Allow me to explain. It</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Was your objection to these, er, krypton particle things?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">This is the big time, and you are obsessed with something so small? You disappoint me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-N-No! I'm obsessed with something big! I mean, there's a bigger, less nitpicky problem here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do tell...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just look at the autopsy report! The location of the entry wound was... ...the right temple!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">T-Temple...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler, you said quite clearly that the victim was shot "square in the forehead"! That's a contradiction! ...Isn't it? <thought>It is, right? Finally!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Herr Justice... Oh, Herr Justice...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Your tactics are outdated. Trying to shake the witness by objecting to trifles? Surely you haven't forgotten the fatal wound your master suffered seven years ago? Phoenix Wright... was it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! Look, I know the wound was in the wrong place according to this testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Nyurk...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Hey, Herr Forehead...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>F... "Forehead"!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let us imagine you are walking through the park. You see two men facing each other. One with a pistol trained on the other. ...What would you do, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I... I guess... I would try to stop them. I'd probably shout, "Stop!"</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And you, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">M-Me? Well... I'd probably scream, "Eeeeeek!"</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And you, Herr Stickler? What did you shout, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack...! <thought>If the victim turned his head at the last moment...*gulp*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...Ah yes. Thank you for jogging my memory.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It sounds like an addendum to the testimony is required.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">As soon as the killer raised his pistol, I took action.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... So you attempted to stop the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Indeed. ...With composure.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, maybe the criminal wouldn't have fired if he hadn't shouted like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That doesn't really matter now, unfortunately.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let us consider this new testimony, shall we? ...Observe the diagram, if you would. The witness... Mr. Stickler, was it? Stood here. He shouted, "Oh stop! Please!" or something of this nature. And the victim responded by looking in the witness's direction! If the killer were to have fired at just that moment... As we can see, the bullet would have struck the right temple, as in the report.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That does seem to be the case.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Witness the power of a Junior in Ivy University's Department of Science!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice, you may cross-examine the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">As soon as the killer raised his pistol, I took action.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you saw a raised pistol... Weren't you frightened?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It can be said we students of Ivy University know no fear. The moment I saw that pistol, my inner sense of justice compelled me to take action!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That was certainly brave of you. You might have gotten shot!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Eh!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">You certainly were lucky. If I were in the killer's shoes, I certainly wouldn't have left a witness behind.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">......!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He actually looks like he had no idea he was in danger.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">R-Regardless, I attempted to halt the bloodshed!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">"Cease this at once, you two!" I cried... with composure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure both men were able to hear your voice?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">They were, of course. My high, exquisite voice echoed through the park.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">And the victim responded to that clarion call...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Quite.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">The victim turned in the direction of my voice... and a shot rang out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you hear the gunshot at the same time as the victim turned?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Indeed. I would say "about" the same time, to be precise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And the victim didn't ask you for help?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It can be said that he didn't have time to ask. He didn't even have time to take a single step.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm totally sure that the killer fired because Mr. Stickler startled him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't say that too loud, Trucy, please...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Whereupon our cowardly killer, the defendant, appeared to have become frightened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you describe the killer's actions more clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">He seemed quite surprised, especially considering that it was he who did the deed! As we can see, human psychology is a tangled web, indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">He simply couldn't believe what he had done. He shot, he panicked. A common tale, but true.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Unfortunately, before I could take further action...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Tossing the pistol aside, he fled from the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't try to apprehend the criminal?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It all happened so fast, I'm afraid I hadn't the time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Doesn't something about that strike you as odd, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The killer was in a hurry, right? He fired the pistol, and tossed it right away...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">According to the testimony, that's what happened, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">In that case, I'd expect to find something that we didn't find!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Find "something"? Find what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait a second!</line>
<line speaker="Sticker">Tsk, tsk, another misleading request. Yet you're so beholden to your own mode of "discourse" you can't see how it affects you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... come again?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wait a "second", you say? A "second"? Are we intended to wait just that, a single second, one sixtieth of a minute? That's hardly enough time to draw a breath, let alone make a statement in court! Now, had you asked for a longer period of time, say, 3 minutes, 35 seconds, th--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Am I to understand you are objecting to the length of a second?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes! I mean, no! Here, just look at the pistol! It doesn't have a single fingerprint on it!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ah, a common ploy, made all the more common, I fear, by the prevalence of television. Criminals these days are loathe to leave fingerprints.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait! But you said the killer tossed the gun and ran!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! He didn't have time to wipe the gun for prints!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, the little girl sticking it to the university student. There's a song in there...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not little!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">A ha ha ha... Then let's think like adults, shall we, Fräulein?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What if the killer... the defendant, was wearing gloves?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">... Gotta admit, I didn't think of that, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Could the killer have been wearing gloves...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If he was wearing gloves, there wouldn't be prints...</thought> ... <thought>C'mon Justice, you've gotta come up with something...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is there something you want to tell the court, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">His silence speaks louder than words, Herr Judge. He can think of nothing... nein?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I g-guess he could have been wearing gloves. <thought>...I guess.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then let's continue with the testimony. If you would.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...My pleasure, Your Honor. A small pleasure, but still.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I liked that contradiction. Kinda sad to see it go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not as sad as I feel. What do we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">At least the testimony's getting a little clearer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's right! Maybe I can find something to use in this new testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The record of the murder weapon is very clear about one thing: The fingerprints were "wiped" which means some trace of prints remained! Which contradicts your testimony! If everything happened as you say it did, he wouldn't have had time to wipe the pistol!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...That may be. But it does not change what I saw. The killer... the defendant... He threw down the murderous weapon from his hand and fled.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">And this pistol was found at the scene of the crime. Strongly suggesting that this was the weapon he disposed of!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">That sounds solid to me. Well, Herr Forehead? Any of your precious "objections"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What gives, Apollo!? Let's see that voice training go to work!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, I've only recently realized something. No matter how much you train your voice, it doesn't matter if you have nothing to say.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean, "nothing to say"!? Isn't it obvious from what the witness just said?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Isn't what obvious?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">When he re-stated what he saw just now, he said he saw Wocky drop a "murderous weapon". But that's not the same as being 100% sure of what Wocky threw away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's just confused because a pistol was found at the scene! Poor Mr. Stickler... It must be hard to be so perfect, and yet so wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">W-Well! It can be said that I'm quite offended! While it is, indeed, true that once, in my youth, I wrote a love letter in my own blood that was seized by the teacher and posted on the blackboard for all to see, and for this the appellation "poor" might as well be prefixed to my name, yet as for the issue at ha--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What we can say for certain is that the witness saw the killer throw "something"... Does the defense have anything to say about this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, if what he threw wasn't a pistol...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Then it had to be something else!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">At least one person on the defense team seems to be thinking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... I'll wipe that smile off your pretty face, Gavin!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you can inform the court as to the nature of this "something else"? What did the killer throw away before fleeing the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What the witness really saw... was this! Or... something like it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That didn't even warrant a wise-crack, did it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps you'd like to try that again, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that... a sword? I saw one of those on the late night movie last night!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great, a sleep-deprived judge...</thought> This knife was found at the scene of the crime... with the defendant's prints on it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">His prints!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This single piece of evidence proves two important things: One, that what the defendant threw down wasn't a pistol. Two, that the defendant wasn't wearing gloves!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, Herr Forehead? You're forgetting two other things you've just proven.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">One, that the man the witness saw was the defendant, Mr. Wocky Kitaki. Two, that the defendant was holding a knife, with the intent of harming the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grr... Never underestimate a Gavin is the lesson here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is of the opinion that our witness is fond of making assumptions. In that light, I believe it would behoove us to hear about what really occurred... ...with less assuming, please!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It is always the same with you people. "Mark left the house on foot, and five minutes later, his brother left after him. How long would it take for Mark's brother to catch up to him... ...assuming that Mark never had to stop for a traffic light!" "Assuming"... Yes, that's what I said. "Assuming"! As if that were a probable situation at all! Yet here you are "assuming" that my "assumption" is no better!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahem. What this court "assumes"... ...is that the witness will testify as to what happened after the shot was fired!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I could not prevent the killer from leaving the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you chase the killer?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">He was, as you say, a killer. Of course, I could have run him down, yet what would he have done when cornered? Sadly, it takes more than an aptitude for solving quadratic equations to know that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did the testimony earlier not prove the defendant's presence at the scene? And do we not also now know that there was no one else there? ...It seems clear that we have our killer. Does it not?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does it not, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better find a way to take this testimony down quick!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I could not prevent the killer from leaving the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which way did the killer run?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">By that time, it was clear the killer had noticed me. Naturally, he ran in the opposite direction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That would mean he ran in the opposite direction from the Kitaki mansion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung! Don't even think about pointing out that he was going away from his home. All he had to do was loop back once he was out of sight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... How did he know that's where I was going...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! I can't find a single problem with that testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Had enough at last, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe it's time to back off a bit...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe there isn't anything left to unravel in this testimony after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some of us have glamorous careers we'd like to get back to this month, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...They don't have enough to put Wocky away yet. Should I back off for now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Nor could I simply leave the scene in good conscience.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were certainly composed for someone who had just witnessed a killing.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">If one is to devote one's life to the pursuit of science... ...one must never flinch at the sight of a little blood. Nor be so moved by a chemical discovery that one drops one's flask upon the lab room floor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oooh, cool answer. Very cool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... So nothing strange about how he acted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Trucy looks like she has something to say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! I can't find a single problem with that testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Had enough at last, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe it's time to back off a bit...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe there isn't anything left to unravel in this testimony after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some of us have glamorous careers we'd like to get back to this month, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...They don't have enough to put Wocky away yet. Should I back off for now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ergo! I used my cell phone to call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wasn't your first thought to call an ambulance?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It can be said that I have dabbled in medicine... The injury I witnessed, namely a single shot to the head, tends to result in death. Ergo, there was no need for me to call an ambulance! Oh... a perfect syllogism... A proof in three parts! Exquisite! Simply exquisite!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...He actually looks like he's going to cry.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! I can't find a single problem with that testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Had enough at last, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe it's time to back off a bit...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe there isn't anything left to unravel in this testimony after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some of us have glamorous careers we'd like to get back to this month, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...They don't have enough to put Wocky away yet. Should I back off for now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Until the police arrived at the scene 10 minutes later, I saw no one else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell us in detail about these 10 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I stood in a state of heightened awareness. Anything could happen at any moment. Anyone could appear from any direction! ...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is... that all?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">No one came. Nothing happened at all. I saw it all, which is to say... I saw nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was late at night. It's not odd to think there would be few people around in the park.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he just stood there, watching? Hmm... Not much to go on there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>... Trucy, if you've got something to say, by all means, say it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh! I can't find a single problem with that testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Had enough at last, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe it's time to back off a bit...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Maybe there isn't anything left to unravel in this testimony after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Some of us have glamorous careers we'd like to get back to this month, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...They don't have enough to put Wocky away yet. Should I back off for now?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense still has some questions that demand answers, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Your opinion, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, let him play attorney until he's satisfied, I say. I will amuse myself by composing my next smash hit in my head...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may continue with the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This witness is way too self-assured! There's got to be a weakness somewhere in this testimony!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnk...! <thought>Argh! There's nothing fishy about that testimony at all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">It appears there are no objections to the witness's current testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">There are any number of ways to explain the lack of prints on the pistol, I assure you. Perhaps the killer really was wearing gloves which wiped the previous user's prints off. Then, after the deed was done, this fell out of his pocket as he was throwing the gun away. A mistake befitting of a small-time punk, in my opinion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No... Nooooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems we've come to the end of the line here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>No... that can't be all!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How unfortunate. It seems that you weren't cut out to stand on the same stage as me. Were you, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this brings the cross-examination to a close. This court will now declare a verdict for the defendant, Wocky Kitaki.</line>
<line speaker="???">Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T-Trucy!?</line>
<line speaker="???">Nobody move!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What's the meaning of this? Who are you!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...</line>
<line speaker="???">There'll be no verdict in this court... Not yet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... Are you... one of the Kitakis!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Kitakis!? You mean the notorious gangsters!?</line>
<line speaker="???">If you don't want to see me give the pretty little girl a new smile, do as I say! Adjourn the court for twenty minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaat!? Th-This court will not bow to pressure from the likes of...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I see little point in further aggravating this gentleman.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Urk! Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="???">Recess, twenty minutes. Or I promise you, you'll regret it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait! <thought>How'd he disappear so fast!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Come to the defendant lobby, Apollo!!!...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I suppose I have no choice but to adjourn for a twenty minute recess! Bailiff! Catch that mysterious man!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! Trucy!?</line>
<line speaker="???">...You move quick, Apollo. Good show, good show!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">T... Trucy! You're OK! I-I thought... *sniff* *sob* *bawl*</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">D-Don't cry, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grr... Those good-for-nothing gangsters! There are some things you just don't do! I'm pressing charges!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait! Just calm down, Apollo! Or else...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Aaaaaugh! Wh-Wh-What the heck is that!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Surprised? This is one of my best tricks! The Amazing Mr. Hat!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">You look mahvelous, dahling!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's a big hit on stage at the Wonder Bar!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">Yes. I am a big hit. Ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, what do you think? Do ya like it!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean you... Trucy! There are some things you just don't do! I... I'm pressing charges!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Now is not the time to be threatening me! It's you who's being threatened here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Remember what you said to Wocky's father yesterday? You promised you'd save his son!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">B-But that testimony was rock solid! What are you suggesting I do?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, once the judge declares a verdict, it's all over. If I can use my talent to stop that from happening, I will!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy, no more staged abductions, please...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm not talking about magic, Apollo! I know when the witness isn't confident... I can perceive what he's feeling! It might not mean anything, but it's all we've got...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can see... what he's "feeling"?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Think back, Apollo. Think back to the times when there was a contradiction in his testimony! All the times!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All the times there was a contradiction...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I think I remember them, sure...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Actually, I don't remember them exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good thing I do!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">There were two times when he made statements he wasn't confident in. And each time, there was a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">In his hand he held.. yes, a pistol! It was pointed at the man pulling the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Tossing the pistol aside, he fled from the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He said the man tossed aside a pistol... But it turned out he wasn't sure, and sure enough, there was a contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's true, but how does that help us?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Didn't you notice anything? Whenever he made a statement he wasn't confident in... ...he displayed a certain habit!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">In his hand he held... yes, a pistol! It was pointed at the man pulling the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Did you see it? The very moment he said the word "pistol"... ...his fingers got all tense, and he fiddled with the corner of a page in his book!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How'm I supposed to see that!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I could see it. How else do you think Daddy went seven years without losing a game of poker?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wha--!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I always sat next to Daddy during big matches. I could see what his opponents were feeling!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean that's how Mr. Wright won all those games?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's not cheating, officially. I wasn't looking at their hands or anything. And I wasn't there all the time, either. Daddy's quite good at poker, after all. But not good enough to go undefeated that long!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great, so he cheated. But what does that do for us? <thought>I don't believe this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You have to listen to his testimony one more time! No... scratch that! You have to watch his testimony! Perceive the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Watch" a testimony? "Perceive" the truth? The only thing I'm perceiving is that I'm going to lose.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Not true!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy said so. He said you have the power, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright said that? <thought>Watch the testimony... Perceive his true feelings... Is she serious!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Time's up! Sorry I can't think of any other way out of this one, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What was that she said before the trial started?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh... Mr. Wright's not here today?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He said his old foot injury was acting up. Yes, he smiled when he said we'd be fine "as long as you're there, Trucy".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is this what he meant by us being "fine"...? Well... methods aside, she did avoid one guilty verdict already today. Time to show this court what I'm made of! Get ready for Justice!</thought> ...Let's do it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know, I'm starting to think I can do this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I knew you could do it all along! Oh, one more thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Try to cover for Mr. Hat as best you can!</line>
<line speaker="Mr. Hat">I just flew in from the coast, and boy are my arms tired!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... <thought>*sigh*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now back in session.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right! We're fine!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...... Ahem. I'd like to say to the young lady standing next to you, Mr. Justice...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, you mean me?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Don't you have anything to report? Anything... concerning the mysterious phantom in the silk top hat?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Right! Him! Don't worry about him. I settled that.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You "settled" that...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Erm, yes, it was an... out of court settlement! Right.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Perhaps Fräulein would have us believe it was nothing more than a passing dream... ...a fantastic illusion, now you see it, now you don't. Am I right?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I think he's on to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wish he would stop being so... so cool.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Let us dispense with these niceties and get straight to the matter. What are your plans for our gifted witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right... The defense would like to request another cross-examination! B-Because... Because I forgot to ask something.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There was no issue with the witness's previous testimony. I will grant your request, however. But this court will not permit stalling for time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Understood, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't forget, Apollo! When he isn't sure about something, he has a habit of fiddling with his book!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I could not prevent the killer from leaving the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not sure I'm qualified to "watch" testimonies after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Focus, Apollo! Find his weak spot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Focus... If only it were that easy! My ears hear what he says, my eyes see his expression. Do I have to do something more? What other senses do I have!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>W-What's this...? My bracelet...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's going on? My bracelet feels different somehow...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I think Daddy was right! You can see it, can't you, Apollo? You're almost there! Find the weak spot in his testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know this sounds crazy... But my bracelet is trying to tell me something!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I could not prevent the killer from leaving the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which way did the killer run?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">By that time, it was clear the killer had noticed me. Naturally, he ran in the opposite direction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That would mean he ran in the opposite direction from the Kitaki mansion...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Achtung! Don't even think about pointing out that he was going away from his home. All he had to do was loop back once he was out of sight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... How did he know that's where I was going...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Nor could I simply leave the scene in good conscience.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were certainly composed for someone who had just witnessed a killing.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">If one is to devote one's life to the pursuit of science... ...one must never flinch at the sight of a little blood. Nor be so moved by a chemical discovery that one drops one's flask upon the lab room floor.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oooh, cool answer. Very cool.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... So nothing strange about how he acted...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ergo! I used my cell phone to call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Until the police arrived at the scene 10 minutes later, I saw no one else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you tell us in detail about these 10 minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I stood in a state of heightened awareness. Anything could happen at any moment. Anyone could appear from any direction! ...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is... that all?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">No one came. Nothing happened at all. I saw it all, which is to say... I saw nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It was late at night. It's not odd to think there would be few people around in the park.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So he just stood there, watching? Hmm... Not much to go on there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't forget, Apollo. You have to focus to perceive the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'm not sure I entirely understand this just yet. But I have "perceived" one thing... My bracelet is reacting to his testimony... this has to be the key!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you called immediately after witnessing the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">The police undoubtedly have a record of the call. Why not check with them?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, Apollo! This has to be it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you mean his habit?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't forget, Apollo! When he isn't sure about something, he has a habit of fiddling with his book!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The only time he even had the book open was here... Which means this is the place to look for this "habit"!</thought> I... don't know how I know, but I know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Know what?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's my bracelet, it's different, somehow. I can feel it reacting to something about the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Your... bracelet?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure I get this "focus" stuff you were talking about, Trucy. But... I have a feeling that trusting my bracelet is the way to go. <thought>OK, I just need to touch my bracelet as it reacts to the testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's going on!? <thought>I can see the witness's face, his expression so clearly! I-It's filling my mind! I can see nothing else, hear nothing else!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy! What's happening to me!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This is what I meant by "focusing".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Focusing...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">In this state, you can see everything, Apollo! Everything the witness does!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-That's great, but this is kind of freaking me out!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just look for Mr. Stickler's twitch -- his habit. You remember it, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure! When he says something he's not sure of, he fiddles with a page of his book.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You got it! Right now, you're looking at the witness's face. ...And your eyes are sort of bugging out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'll bet they are.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">First, move your focus of attention down to Mr. Stickler's hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">His hand...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You know what to look for now, but you have to be looking at the right place.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She's right. I can only see his face like this... Time to try changing my viewpoint!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Perfect! Now you're really ready!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ready... for what?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ready to perceive the truth behind the twitch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Perceive...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Try listening to the witness talk as you focus. Then watch for his habit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... You mean when he fiddles with the page!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's right! That's your signal to look closer, to perceive! Find his weak spot and I guarantee we'll be able to give him the Royal Flush!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Spoken like a true poker head's daughter.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm a magician, thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So I have to pay attention to his words... and his fingers!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't worry if you miss it, you can always try again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right! Look out nervous twitch, here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gotcha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A-Apollo! That's not it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh... I guess I'm kind of lost here.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Remember his habit: He fiddles with the pages of his book! The word he's saying right when you see his fingers twitch is the key!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>OK, so I have to watch for his fingers to move. Got it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And don't worry about getting it perfect your first time. You can always try again!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>I... I saw it! Just now... I could see it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Justice? Do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">A-all this b-banging of desks! I-It's quite bad for my circulation, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler... Allow me to ask you a simple question. Why did you fiddle with the page of your book just now? ...The very moment you mentioned your cell phone!?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wh-Wh-What are you talking about!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm curious now about this cell phone of yours... Mind if I ask a few questions? <thought>Hmm... What to ask, What to ask...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler... Tell me your phone number!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Urk!? Wh-Why? Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Why not? You have something against making friends?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...What does this witness's cell phone number have to do with the case?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Absolutely nothing! This is a... an invasion of my privacy!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Seeing you grimace like that makes me wonder about your cell phone, too. The witness will present his cell phone number to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Waaaugh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy... Do you have your cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sure do!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Try dialing the number that he gives us.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You want me to call Mr. Stickler's phone?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This... is all highly irregular.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">H-Hey! My pocket's ringing! Wait! This is the phone from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look... a cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone dropped it beneath this tire! If the car moved, it would be crushed for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I wonder if it belongs to the doctor here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How strange, Mr. Stickler.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you explain why your cell phone is sitting here in my assistant's hand!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler, please show me your cell phone!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Urk!? Wh-Why? Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Show me, and you'll find out.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">W-Well I can't! I don't have it, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't have it...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Mr. Stickler. Is this your cell phone?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yeeeeow! Wh-Where did you get that!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's the phone from yesterday!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look... a cell phone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Someone dropped it beneath this tire! If the car moved, it would be crushed for sure!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... I wonder if it belongs to the doctor here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How strange, Mr. Stickler.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can you explain why your cell phone is sitting here in my hand at this very moment?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was wondering... Can you tell me what model of cell phone you own?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Urk!? Wh-Why? Whatever for?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why not tell him? It's not some matter of national security, I'm sure. Nor does it have anything to do with this case! Take it to the lobby, gentlemen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, our current market is flooded with generic-brand cell phones. Please ask questions with a little regard for market trends, please.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Who would have guessed the judge was up on his cell phone industry trends?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who would have guessed I'd get chewed out for asking a simple question...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait a minute! What is the meaning of this!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This cell phone was found yesterday... ...in the Meraktis Clinic garage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Meraktis... Why, that's where the victim lived!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yeeeeeerrgh! Th-That's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler, you lied to the court, didn't you? If your cell phone is here, how could you have called the police!?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Weeeeeeeeeeeeeouk!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It... It's true. I didn't have my cell phone that night. That is why it can be said that I called the police from a public pay phone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A pay phone! So you didn't call on your cell phone after all...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just where was this pay phone located, Mr. Stickler!?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Well, to indicate it with a startlingly high degree of accuracy... ...it was right around here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's... quite a ways from the park. But... But why did you lie?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There can be only one reason. He didn't want the court to know he had lost his cell phone. Because it was found... ...in the victim's garage!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wh-Wh-What are you saying!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler... You broke into the Meraktis Clinic garage on the night of the murder! This cell phone tells all!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">B-But that's ridiculous! That makes it sound like... Like I snuck into this fellow's garage to commit some crime! As though I were trying to kill him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Dr. Meraktis was killed that night.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">W-Well y-yes, but no! This line of reasoning has to be against the rules! Yes, it's true! I lost my cell phone! But you can't prove that I lost it that night!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Mr. Justice? If that cell phone was dropped the night of the murder... ...it does raise considerable suspicions as to a connection with the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now's your chance, Apollo! Connect Mr. Stickler to the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, he's already connected enough. I just have to prove it. <thought>Well... Do I have a piece of evidence that can do the job? Can I prove the cell phone was dropped on the night of the murder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course I have evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ooh, I like your swagger, Herr Forehead. Hit it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will see this evidence. Mr. Justice, "hit it", as they say!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Evidence... If only I had some evidence, it'd make this whole thing a lot easier.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Care to explain the lack of confidence smeared across your face, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Oh, Herr Forehead... I think it should be clear by now. "No evidence" means "no case".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! I guess this is it, then. Time to go for broke!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence that proves the cell phone was dropped on the night of the murder is:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Well, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">No comment, Herr Judge.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No dice, Mr. Justice. Penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! Remember where we found that cell phone! If it had fallen on the ground before that night...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's right! The cell phone would have been crushed!</thought> Your Honor! One more chance, please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, keep this up and you'll run yourself out of a life's worth of chances!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's... a side-view mirror?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As it so happens... Dr. Meraktis's car was in an accident... ...that took place the night of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">An accident!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An accident. It happened a little after 9 PM, just outside People Park... our murder scene. Dr. Meraktis's car hit a pedestrian!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Wh-What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">From the absence of a mirror, it's clear that the car was parked after the accident. Which means it was parked there after 9 PM on the night of the murder. If your cell phone had been dropped before the car was parked in that garage... ...then it would have been crushed. After all, it was lying on the ground, right under the wheel!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Urk...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ergo, Mr. Stickler! The only time you could have dropped this in that garage... ...was after 9 PM the night of the murder in the park!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Weeeeeeeeoooorrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler! You know what this means? You did break into the victim's garage that night.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This is most unexpected! Mr. Justice... Are you naming the witness as a suspect in the murder of Pal Meraktis!?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">N-No, stop! This is too much! This can't be happening! P-P-P-P-Prosecutor! Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">I suppose it is worth saying this: No connection has been found between Wesley Stickler and Pal Meraktis. That is, other than this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe our next testimony will be most... revelatory. Is the witness prepared?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Y-Y-Yes, Your Honor!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know that face... That's the face of guilt!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">That night... Yes! I went to the supermarket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes... but your cell phone was lying in a garage.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ah, yes, well, as you can see my model of cell phone has a defect... It is given to rolling! It's quite a pain when I drop it alongside the road, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Looks like a normal cell phone to me. In any case, Mr. Justice, the cross-examination, please.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's funny... My bracelet didn't react at all during that testimony.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">His nervous habit must not be acting up... I didn't sense anything either, actually. Looks like you're on your own this time around!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Right, no problem... I hope. Here comes Justice!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">That night... Yes! I went to the supermarket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you went shopping. Which means... ...you were holding a grocery bag when you witnessed the murder taking place?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Eh!? W-Well, yes, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Incidentally, the prosecution has received no report of this domestic detail.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Stickler? Can you explain yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">No! I mean, yes! I did go shopping, really. I walked around the supermarket, trying out the free samples... It's... a deeply spiritual time for me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sure the store clerks would disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Do you think sampling free food counts as a religion?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">In any case! That night... ...I sampled to my heart's content, and was on my way back home, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I must have dropped my cell phone on my way back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's when you passed in front of the Meraktis Clinic?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Why... yes. That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That was a pretty suspicious pause there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler, do you think you could be a bit more specific? Please show us the exact route you took on the night of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">O-Of course. The supermarket is here, along the main road. My way home from there takes me past the Meraktis Clinic. This is probably when I dropped my cell phone. Yet, woe is I, I walked on, unaware of my loss! ...And walked right into that fateful park.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">And when I was walking through the park, I happened to witness the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Which entrance did you enter the park from?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Well, to be exact... One might say that I went in from the entrance closest to the Meraktis Clinic.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">The same entrance our victim used.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did you notice anything when you entered? Wheel marks from a noodle stand, for instance?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...I have no recollection of such a thing, no. Yet, though I might have missed the tracks, I could not miss what happened next! I can a keen observer... of the obvious, you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...I saw the killer, the victim, the stand... all as clear as day!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This part of the testimony is the key. I know it! Should I press him about the killer, the victim, or the noodle stand?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you sure you remember the killer clearly?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">How many times must I repeat myself!? It was him, that unscrupulous, fox-like fellow in the defendant's chair! He was looking even more unscrupulous at the time, no less.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... He does look a bit like one of those trickster foxes in legends of yore.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess the victim's identity is already old territory... Time to ask something new.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could see the victim quite clearly, too?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Oh, clear as clear can be, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see. So... Um... How'd he look?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">How? How do you mean, "how"? Be specific.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, I mean, in general.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will refrain from straining to come up with questions. Find the question that lies in your heart and ask that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor. <thought>Great, a judge who moonlights as a self-help guru...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you happen to remember the noodle stand?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Quite well, yes! For a student of the sciences, keen observation and healthy curiosity are vital! I remember everything! I could even read the sign! I believe it said... Er... "NOODLE". ......... Yes, that was it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">For remembering something "quite well" it sure took you a while to tell us. And thank you for telling us that a noodle stand sells noodles. Very enlightening. Well, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... What about that sign? Could that be important?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How could the sign matter at all? We know it's a noodle stand!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, please continue with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the sign on the noodle stand said "NOODLE"...? It appears the defense has just obtained a vital piece of testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this noodle stand's broth really that delicious? I'll have to go sample the wares one of these days. I think that's worth adding to the testimony as well.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...Hmph! Whatever sort of noodles that stand sells, it can't match up to Ivy U.'s cafeteria! Some apply to the school merely for a taste of our Smart Noodles!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wouldn't mind a taste of that myself...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"Why, I even remember the sign on the stand the victim was pulling! It said "NOODLE"!"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler, you've proven to be a most skilled witness.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Skilled? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thank you for your powers of recollection. Your testimony just now was quite vital.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Something going on up in your noodle, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If my gut feeling here is right... I've just stumbled across a major contradiction!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Why, I even remember the sign on the stand the victim was pulling! It said "NOODLE"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the sign said "NOODLE"? You're absolutely sure?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Let me be frank: Yes. In fact, the word "unsure" isn't even in my dictionary! Nor the word "uncertain" or...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He was wasting time looking that stuff up!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">"NOODLE", eh? I like that. It tells you what you're getting, no nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It tells me a lot more than that, actually!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why are you smiling like that, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It was him! I saw the defendant at the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are you absolutely sure it was the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Stop asking me the same questions over and over! This isn't some kind of make-up test!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's a "make-up test", Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing a good student like you has to worry about. <thought>Time to find his weak spot and press it till he breaks!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">His habit isn't acting up... which means he isn't lying.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... I was kind of relying on my bracelet to get me through this one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But he's pretty unsettled! The odds are really high that you can get something out of him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That gleam in your eyes... You're a gambler's daughter through and through.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm a magician, thank you very much!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you're absolutely sure the sign read "NOODLE"?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Why, just last week, my professor offered me this praise: "At least you have good eyesight, Stickler. I'll give you that." ...It read, without a doubt, "NOODLE".</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">What? Why are you looking at me like that? Is that... pity I see in your eyes!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's take a look at our map, shall we? So, you're claiming that when you saw the sign, you were standing... Here, was it? ...Although, it would've been a bit hard to read the sign from this spot.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Y-You think so?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Stickler. I'd like you to please take another look at the stand. ...and to carefully read what the sign says. See? That sign actually states the name of the stand's owner. ..."ELDOON'S".</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">E... El... Eld... Inconceivable! I'm certain it was definitely "NOODLE" for sure! Positive!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm afraid your professor was wrong about that eyesight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wouldn't be so quick to jump to that conclusion. <thought>The sign he saw changes everything!</thought> The witness says the sign said "NOODLE"...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The answer is quite simple. The witness saw the sign wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That would seem to be the case, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! The only thing that changes is the witness's eyesight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Eh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">OK, so you've proven the witness has bad eyesight, and is overconfident. But that just proves he's a bad witness! It doesn't solve the case!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">How rude! I've not made a single mistake, I assure you! I am a student of science! Errors are not tolerated in my field, I'll have you know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What if Mr. Stickler is right to be so confident...? And if he is right about the sign... what does that mean for the entire case!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What would you say if I told you... ...that there is one spot from which the sign would be read the way Mr. Stickler claims?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice! Show us this spot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness actually viewed the stand from this location!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... That's a river.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, "Oh". As in, I "oh" you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk.. Sorry, Your Honor... Mind if I try again?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell us, if you would, where was the witness standing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Though it pains me to point out the obvious... I see you leave me with no choice. It was the victim, Herr Doktor Meraktis who was pulling the stand, ja?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Ja.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, hopefully this penalty will inspire you to take this case more seriously.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Your Honor... One more time, please...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell us, if you would, where was the witness standing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... Any thoughts, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What, it's my turn to chastise the upstart, is it? Herr Forehead... Recall what you just told the court! The sign on the stand reads "ELDOON'S", ja? How would the witness standing where you have indicated change anything!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...... Um... I picked the wrong place.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your honesty becomes you, Mr. Justice. However, your mistake does not.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Your Honor... Do I get another chance?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Tell us, once again, where was the witness standing?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness was standing... Here! On the opposite side!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">H-How do you know that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When viewed from the south... ...the sign on the stand reads "ELDOON'S", as we know. ...However! Observe the other side of the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh! This side says "NOODLE"!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly! The name of the stand is split between the front and back signs! Mr. Stickler, you lied to the court! You witnessed the crime from the northern side of the park, not the south!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yeeeow! Y-You got me!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...So what.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-So what!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">What does it matter if he saw the killing from the north or the south side? It makes no difference at all!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">H-He's right! Travel far enough to the south, and you will end up going north! Viewed on a global scale, directions are utterly without meaning!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Actually, maybe he's right. What does it change?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It changes everything, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Remember his testimony from before... Though to be honest, I'm a little scared of where this is leading... The killer and the victim are facing each other here. Then, at the moment the killer raises his weapon... ...Mr. Stickler shouts! At which point, the victim turns his head to look... ...and the killer fires his pistol. That's why the bullet hit him in the right temple. No contradictions, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... But if Mr. Stickler was standing on the north side of the park... ...that reverses the whole scenario!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Completely! If Mr. Stickler shouts from where he is now... ...and the victim looks in his direction... ...the bullet would have to hit his left temple!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Aaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">In other words, someone standing at point "K"... ...couldn't shoot the victim in his right temple. It's impossible!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So, now that we know that Mr. Stickler was standing on the northern side... ...the wound location takes on an entirely different meaning!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Indeed... You are absolutely correct, Fräulein.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh... What meaning!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">The entry wound was on the right side of the victim's head, correct? Well, the right side of the victim's head... is north.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">North... Ah!!! But that's where the witness, Wesley Stickler was standing!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Correct. So, if he was standing to the north... ...then the only person here who could have shot the victim in the right temple... ...was Mr. Stickler himself!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yeeeeeeeeeeeeooooooowwwrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow... The apple didn't fall far from the tree! She's flipped this whole case on its head while I was still figuring it out!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Klavier"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Clarify one point for me if you would, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What now?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Are you truly accusing this college student... ...of murder?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>Well, I can't say he exactly looks innocent... But... something still doesn't feel right. I just can't picture him as the real killer!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">No, please! Looks aside, I'm really a nice guy! All my friends say so!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's hear what the defense has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What are you going to do now, Justice!? Should I really accuse Mr. Stickler!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I accuse Mr. Stickler of murder!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Are you quite sure, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes. Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">"Accuse of murder"... Only three words, but a very, very long sentence. ...You have evidence worthy of such a bold accusation, I hope?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">... Um, maybe I'd better think this over some more.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...A wise decision.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No accusations, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">......</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">......... Well. I'm glad that's sorted out.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! You sure you're doing the right thing!? They'll end up convicting Wocky if you let Mr. Stickler off the hook!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! You think? Uh, w-wait, Your Honor! Let me rethink that...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If you must...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I don't think Wesley Stickler is a killer. But he's not innocent, either! His unusual silence tells me that much...</thought> ...Mr. Stickler! You seem unusually quiet... Tell us why, now!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">... Th-The word "confession" isn't in my dictionary!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Tsk, tsk, tsk, Herr Forehead. I'm afraid it falls to you to elucidate Herr Stickler's silence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, you did say you were accusing the witness just now... ...for a crime other than murder. Your reason? The court's all ears.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Gah! I know he's guilty of something... but what crime other than murder is there? Do I have evidence that shows his involvement in some other crime...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your evidence? The court's all eyes, Mr. Justice. Show us evidence that points to the witness's involvement in a crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Something tells me this isn't one of those good silences.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Something else to say, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... One more chance? Please?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...By all means. But your effort wasn't wasted. Look, a brand-new penalty. Now, please reveal your thoughts to the court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence... is this!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? Is that... women's underwear!?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey! Those are mine!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">D-Don't look at me like thaaaaaaat!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! ...Mr. Stickler. While I can't say this comes as a shock...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I-It's not what it seems! By Pythagorilla's Theorem, I swear it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the night of the murder, just past 9 PM... A young girl catches a panty-snatcher red-handed! Bravely, she gives chase, but the snatcher flees... ...and hides himself in no other place than the Meraktis Clinic garage!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Incidentally... ...these panties were found in the exhaust pipe of the car there. Presumably, he was trying to hide the evidence of his crime. Ergo! While you may not be a murderer... ...you are guilty of panty-snatching in the first degree!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Please! Here me out! It's not what it looks like!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order! Order!!! Mr. Stickler. You should be ashamed!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">It's... not... what... it... seeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee... ...eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee... ...eeeeeeeeeeeeeems... *gasp*</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, are we to understand that you were silent not because you were guilty of murder... ...but because you lacked the courage to admit your theft of this girl's undergarments?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Ahem. Perhaps you are not aware that my school's name was originally written "IV"! "I" stands for "Intelligent", "V" stands for "Valiant"! See!?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Your point?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I'm not done! Now, I'm a major in the Science Department... ...and what does science teach if not curiosity!? Yes, we of the Ivy U. Science Department are valiantly curious! No challenge is too daunting, and what greater challenge to science than a mystery!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">C'mon! You're talking about a girl's panties here!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">No! You do not understand! A mystery is the unknown, and the unknown is unacceptable! And, my friends, when it comes to mysteries, those panties are the promised land! From the moment I first laid eyes on them, I was compelled to investigate... for science! A full-sized car tire was only the first mystery those panties revealed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A... tire?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yes! I saw her do it! She pulled a tire out of those panties! But that's not all! First, there was the tire, then a stewpot, and a frozen chicken! One mystery after another! It was... It was magic!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, I remember now! He's one of the regulars in the audience at the Wonder Bar!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's talking about my Magic Panties trick!</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I just don't understand... A broom... from a pair of panties? It mocks the very laws of physics...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A broom... and a frozen chicken, Trucy? What ever happened to doves and bunny rabbits?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Stickler! You stole this girl's panties to understand a magic trick?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">You say "panties" but they are so much more than that! For me, they are an object for serious study!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...I wonder... There has been a recent rash of panty-snatchings in the area... ...Were they all you?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I... I am sorry. But I did it for science! Each time I spied a pair of panties flapping in the breeze, I thought maybe! Maybe this would be the pair that would elucidate the mystery... Even that night as she chased me through the streets, I wept tears of joy! Perhaps this is the night that I will seize the truth that lies within those panties! Yet woe was I! For once again the lacy heart-patterned truth slipped through my fingers a--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Still, that leaves one thing unexplained.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Ah, you refer to our witness's other lie, yes? The witness claimed he saw the crime from the south, but was in fact, in the north.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Would anyone care to explain why he lied about that?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">...</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Be my guest, Herr Forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Me!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Did I not hear you correctly? Did you not say you "do not accuse the witness of murder"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...!</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Why, then, did the witness lie about his location at the time of the shooting? ...Or have you no idea?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo... There's something about the way the diagram is arranged right now... When you think about it, right near where Mr. Stickler was standing... Isn't there a...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Justice? What say you? Do you have any evidence to show why the witness lied about his location?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Judge">... I fail to see how this evidence relates to our witness's fabrication...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">As do I! But I'm sure it does! Somehow! Somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...It appears the fabrication was yours, Mr. Justice. Penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Somebody help...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're welcome to show us another piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence that shows why he lied... is this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What!? More panties!?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">How many panties are you carrying in your pocket, Herr Forehead?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These are the last!! Honest!! These were found in a trash can at the park. Looking at the diagram... ...we can see that the trash can was right next to where the witness stood.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Stickler... You didn't...</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Alas! I'm a failure as a scientist! I can't unravel the mysteries of the universe! I can't even unravel a pair of panties!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So... these panties are you handiwork as well...?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Th... That night, I had been chased, hounded into the Meraktis Clinic garage... Weeping in frustration, I was forced to abandon my prize! Don't you see how I felt!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Believe me, I'd rather not.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I hid in the garage for a short while... Then, abandoning the panties, I made for home. To avoid the office where the girl works, I went towards the south entrance... ...when I saw them hanging there on a clothesline by a giant mansion... ...A giant pair of panties!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Apparently he didn't know those bloomers belonged to the mob...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I had them, safe in my pocket, ready to take home... ...when I stumbled upon a murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The murder of Dr. Meraktis.</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">I reported what I had seen, but as I waited for the police to arrive... I got scared. What if they searched me!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's when you disposed of the bloomers?</line>
<line speaker="Stickler">Yes... it was a severe blow to the progress of science, but one that had to be born.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A fascinating, if disturbing tale.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I believe this brings today's proceedings to a close. And I'm more than pleased to dismiss this witness for the remainder of the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">One last thing, if I might.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Prosecutor Gavin?</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">Regardless of where we ended today, some vital points were made. Namely, that the defendant, Wocky Kitaki, was at the scene of the crime. And... he was pointing a weapon at the victim. ...One more thing. Wocky Kitaki has a clear motive.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, the defendant Wocky Kitaki is still the prime suspect in this case. The only suspect, in fact. Assuming there was no one else on the scene at the time. Yet, a mystery remains... The location of the wound in the victim's right temple has yet to be explained. The court requests further investigation from both the defense and prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Klavier">...Ja, baby.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No problem!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. This brings the trial for the day to a close. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! What do you think about the witness's statement?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh... I'm not sure I follow you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It clearly, er, contradicts the... um... I thought...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...You don't sound very sure, Mr. Justice. Objection overruled.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This evidence clearly reveals a contradiction in that statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">How exactly are the evidence and the statement just now related?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">They aren't, are they...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not at all. Mr. Justice, please think the facts over before making accusations.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't think that won me any points with the judge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! That statement contradicts the evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...? It does? I don't see anything contradictory...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um... You sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Objection overruled. Try to think before you make accusations, Mr. Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ack! That didn't go so well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Wocky Kitaki...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defendant will surrender himself to the court's care... ...to undergo a regular trial at the High Court within a month's time. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>