
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Revolution</title>
<line speaker="Defiant Dragons Henchman Actor">Heeheeheehahaha!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa Actress">Aaah! Why me?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke Actor">Mwahahahaha! It's time for a revolution!</line>
<line speaker="Rayfa Actress">No! Let go of me!</line>
<line speaker="Plumed Punisher Actor">That's far enough!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke Actor">Who's there?!</line>
<line speaker="Plumed Punisher Actor">It is I-- The Plumed Punisher: Warrior of Neo Twilight Realm!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Good people of Khura'in, we can't allow things to go on like this. The Defense Culpability Act has done nothing but produce countless victims of wrongful convictions. The time to act is now. For we, the Defiant Dragons, have obtained the ultimate weapon: the Founder's Orb! And to the Ga'ran regime: Make no mistake about it-- I will personally dethrone you! A dragon never yields. Nor will he rest until his revolution is complete.</line>
<line speaker="TV">...And this concludes our report on the recent television hijacking in Khura'in. But really, who could have anticipated a surprising turn of events?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Did you hear that, Polly? Someone hijacked the airwaves over there! It's like something out of a movie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Um, yeah. Dhurke... What are you up to this time?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait a second... Do you know the TV hijacker or something, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......You could say that... but it was a long time ago.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...And WHY do you know someone like that? I mean, they're calling him an "insurgent."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... about that...</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey now. Is that any way to talk about the man who raised you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hey there, Apollo! Long time no see! How've you been, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I-It's--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's that guy that was on TV!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! Guilty as charged! Surprised to see me, Apollo? I just beamed in from Khura'in, and boy are my arms tired!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Th-Th-This can't be happening! ...I must be dreaming... or hallucinating... or both...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, you're not, Apollo! It's that TV hijacker-slash-insurgent in the flesh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">........ <thought>I'm so confused.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Um! Mr. Hijacker! Sir! I have SO many questions, I don't even know where to begin! But let's start with that bit about "the man who raised you."</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Wait, don't tell me you haven't told anyone about me, son? It's okay to brag about it. Tell everyone your old man's me, the rebel Dhurke! I mean, my face is all over TV these days! I'm practically a celebrity, hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Trucy, what do you say we close up early today?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What?! Why?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Aw, come on, son. No need for the cold shoulder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>*sigh* I know I'm going to regret this, but...</thought> What do you want, Dhurke? You just show up here without warning after all this time... What gives?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I came all this way to see you, son! Come, rejoice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Riiight... Why don't you tell me the real reason you're here.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">W-Well... Okay, so maybe there's a little something I need your help with, too, but... The fact is I came here to see you. That's the honest truth.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I think we've established that. <thought>It figures... I haven't seen him in ten plus years and he's already asking for a favor. He really is a rebel in the purest sense -- he just does whatever he pleases.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">C'mon, Polly! I need details. Inquiring minds want to know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, okay. Hold your horses. First, I've got a few questions of my own.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hm? Why, this is Apollo's journal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! What's it doing at the office?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's magic!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Let's see what he wrote...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, don't!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Huh... There's nothing in here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">This calls for a special spell! Presto diario!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Why, there's writing appearing right before my very eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Like I said, it's magic! Now go ahead, read to your heart's content!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow! ...Er, I mean, give me that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's Charley the houseplant.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You know, my hideout used to have a houseplant, too. We called it "Apollo."</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I bet it was a cactus!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">How'd you guess?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Because Polly's hair's just as spiny!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, leave my hair out of this.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">And he has a prickly attitude, to boot!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I better quit while I'm ahead.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">More magic props... Oh! I've seen a ring like this before! I used to be quite good with these.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Why don't you show us?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, if you insist! I'll show you the act of daring-do I used to perform to supplement my income. First, I have to light the ring on fire, then I'll jump through it...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a fire hoop, this is a kid's toy, Dhurke...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, it has sentimental value for Daddy, you see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but this office could use a little help with its bottom line. What if we sold it?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Apollo! ...You'd better give me a cut of the proceeds when you do.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Money before memories, eh? This office's finances really must be in dire straits then.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This is one of those contraptions for cutting people into pieces!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How did you know that, Mr. Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, it just so happens I've been in one of these myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You have?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. Once, when I was being held prisoner by Minister Inga's secret police... ...they tried to torture me into revealing one of my compatriot's hideouts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's a torture device, this is a magic prop, Dhurke...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, you have my respect as a magician for your death-defying spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What's with this bright red jacket? Who would wear such a garish thing?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe one of our clients forgot it here.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'd love to get a look at the man who'd dare wear something like this!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Me, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I know I don't wear it much, but... she has to know it's mine, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Pleased to meet you, little lady. My name is Dhurke Sahdmadhi. I'm a... well... a rebel by trade.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">A rebel? But on TV, they were calling you an insurgent. So which is it? Personally, I vote for a rebel with a cause -- a real "head"-ache for anyone in your way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Trucy...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">That's too bad. You seem like you'd be a fun, cool guy to hang with!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...This little lady's a real catch, son. I'm talking bride material, if you get my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh! Stop it! You're embarrassing me... Dad.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! She's a plucky one, all right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someone pluck me out of my misery...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now, about that "man who raised you" business...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What did Mr. Dhurke mean when he said that he's "the man who raised you," Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The truth is, I grew up in the Kingdom of Khura'in. Did I, uh... never mention that?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, so you grew up in... Khura'in?! Wait, are you saying... ...you're not from around here, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's just I was raised in Khura'in when I was really little.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Still, that's a shocker. It's like I hardly know anything about you! How come you never told me?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Apollo. You really haven't said a word about your past, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, that I was raised by a wanted criminal? It's like a bad joke.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It does sound rather melodramatic. I doubt anyone would even believe you. So you two haven't seen each other in a while, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You could say that. I'd wager it's been at least ten years.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow... That's a really long time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well, I figured he'd forgotten about me.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Not a chance! It's just, well... Starting a revolution takes time, and keeping it going even more so... And being a wanted man, I couldn't just hop a plane to come say hello.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I get it. It's fine. <thought>Though, truth be told... ...it's weird having Dhurke show up acting all paternal. I'd even almost forgotten about Khura'in... No, that's not true. I probably tried to forget about it on purpose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Now then, Mr. Dhurke, what is it we can help you with?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I need to get my hand on the Founder's Orb, the most sacred treasure of Khura'in. That's where you come in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, but didn't you say you already have it in that broadcast of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! Don't go believing everything you see on TV, little lady. No one's seen hide nor hair of the Founder's Orb for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No way!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-So that was just a bluff...? What are you going to do if you DON'T find it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I don't know. Guess that just means we HAVE to find it, son. 'Cause I can't really back down now, can I? Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Different year, same old Dhurke. It's all coming back to me now.</thought> Hold on. I think I read something about this in the newspaper a while back. Something about you stealing a sacred treasure from a temple's treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's a load of crock. We didn't lay a finger on the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, Baseless allegations, all of it. Our enemy has really found a way to keep us all on our toes.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh! So it's like a setup!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's the long and short of it. However, my compatriot has been hot on the orb's trail. And just the other day, his hard work finally paid off. We now know the Founder's Orb is in... Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kurain Village?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. I hear there are spirit mediums there. They even have direct relations with Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Spirit mediums... Right...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Some doctor of archeology there supposedly has the orb. His name is Archie Buff. My Defiant Dragon compatriot has already made contact with him. Apparently, someone asked the doctor to study the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So whoever asked him to do that is the real thief?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Most likely.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you think this guy will just hand the orb over to you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">My compatriot, Datz, says Dr. Buff has already promised to do so. It seems he knew it was stolen, and wanted to do the right thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Datz... I remember running around him when I was a kid.</thought> <thought>So he's here, too, huh.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo, I want you to be present as my lawyer when I take possession of the orb. Would you do that for me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I haven't seen you in years, and you waltz in here asking for a favor? You have a lot of nerve, you know--</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Of course we'll help! Right, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait, Trucy...!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, come on. It's not like you have any work anyway. Besides, we're talking about rebels and legendary treasure here. It'll be fun!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>*sigh* Why is she always into the things I'm not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Fine, but I'll charge my standard fee. Now tell me about the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If I remember correctly, the founder is always depicted as a faceless spirit medium.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What do you mean "faceless"?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Images of the founder, the Holy Mother of Khura'in, never show her face. To depict it is to commit the greatest taboo in Khura'inism.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The greatest taboo, huh? (I wonder why? I mean, what could she have looked like to make them hide her face like that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">As for the Founder's Orb, it was discovered during an excavation eight years ago... ...and has an interesting legend that goes along with it. It's said that there's a riddle to the orb, and that any who can solve it... ...will receive immense spiritual power from the founder herself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like one big fairy tale to me.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">In any case... ...it's just what us Defiant Dragons need to get our revolution started. With it, we can gain the spiritual power, and thus, the legal authority to rule Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, suppose I believe this legend. Then, anyone could become king or queen? And THAT'S why you think it'll help you overthrow the Gar'an regime?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Only the rulers of Khura'in have ever laid eyes on the orb, Apollo. A legendary treasure that bestows immense spiritual power... Doesn't that sound like something you'd want to see with your own two eyes?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...That does sound just a tiny bit intriguing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's my attorney's badge.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I can relate. I used to want to show mine off, too. But don't ever show it to anyone in Khura'in. They'll run you right out of town the moment they find out you're a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder how it went for Mr. Wright. Knowing him, he probably flashed his left and right...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The Founder's Orb... They say the Holy Mother will return when the riddle of the orb is solved. And she will bestow great spiritual power upon whoever accomplishes that feat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wonder if I could channel spirits if I had such power.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Brings back memories... He was a fine young man. So cheerful and fun to be around. His big, booming singing voice would captivate everyone in the tavern. But looks-wise, he was like a grownup version of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, that still doesn't give me a sense of what my real father was like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not right now.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ah, I almost forgot. I brought you a present. Eat up, son!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sushi?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I figured you probably couldn't afford three square meals a day, so...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yay! I was just thinking it was time for lunch!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You dig in, too, little lady. After all, we're practically family, right?! Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Thanks, Dad! Ooh, that tuna looks good! *chomp* *nom nom nom*</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This salmon sushi's got my name on it! *chomp* *chew chew chew* Aren't you hungry, son? This is some of the best sushi you'll ever have!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........I'm... I'm good.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">O-Oh, well... Okay then. ...Actually, I have one more present for you. Here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">A picture of your father. It's been twenty-three years since he passed away.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! This... This is my father?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">His name was Jove Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jove...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I haven't talked to you about your real father in some time, but as you know... ...he was a musician -- a wandering minstrel, if you will -- and a talented one at that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ Why... Why are you giving this to me now?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I thought it was sad you didn't know what your old man looked like. I searched high and low to find that one picture.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What's wrong, Apollo? Don't you want it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't know. I mean, it's not like I ever met the guy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, I went through all the trouble of finding it, so go on, take it! And don't ever let it go, you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, now that our bellies are full, what do you say we hit the road?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One second. Hey, Trucy, any idea where Athena is?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">She left early this morning to pick up Daddy from the airport.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I almost forgot. Mr. Wright is coming back today.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah... but I wonder why he cut his trip short like that. Anyway, shouldn't they have been back by now?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Knowing Athena, she probably got lost. Well, there's no point sitting around here waiting. Let's get going.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I can't wait to see that super mysterious treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">To Kurain Village, then! The Founder's Orb awaits!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So this is Kurain, the mystical village of spirit channeling... ... and where ancient traditions come alive. Looks like a really peaceful place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ahh, I love the air here! Nothing beats the mountains, huh, Apollo?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it... We used to live way up in the mountains, too, just like this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sure brings back memories. Those were the days. The three of us living happily in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...I still can't wrap my mind around it all, you know. That Mr. Dhurke is not only Polly's daddy, but Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's as well. And the way you two talked about it like it was nothing the whole bus ride here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess it IS a lot to take in...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">So tell me, Mr. Dhurke, what was Apollo like as a kid?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, he was full of piss and vinegar, he was. A real rascal! He and Nahyuta used to run around in the open fields, naked as jaybirds. I've even got pictures of him posing in his birthday suit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, whoa, Dhurke!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No way! Prosecutor Sahdmadhi used to be like that, too?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The two of ‘em would end up with leeches on their butts and cry like babies, hah-ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke! Don't you think you've said enough?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aw, you're no fun.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! I wanted to hear more about the misadventures of Polly!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hey, what are you people doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You know this lady, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, this is Ema Skye. She's a detective.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Technically speaking, I'm a forensics expert, but I'll let it slide. ...Anyway, I can't say I'm surprised to see you here. You always seem to pop up whenever there's trouble afoot. Still, what are the odds of running into you here in the boonies?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">By "trouble," you mean you're investigating a case?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Does it look like I'm here to sightsee? .........Wait, don't tell me... You're not here to see Dr. Buff, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? How'd you know that? We're actually on our way to meet with him right now.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Figures... Well, follow me. I'll show you the way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Really?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't look a gift horse in the mouth, son. Just follow the nice lady.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A phone booth and a bus stop made of wood. They both look really old. You hardly ever see phone booths in the city anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo... what's this glass box for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess you hardly see them in Khura'in, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a big boulder towering into the sky over there. According to the sign, it's called the "Kurain Boulder." It also says that a spirit dwells within it. Hmm... A rock with a spirit in it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's called animism – the belief that spirits dwell within inanimate objects. They've probably enshrined this boulder as a sacred object. Their tradition of worshiping such objects is similar to our tradition in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Interesting... <thought>Who knew Dhurke could make sense every once in a while?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Seeing those mountains really takes me back. I remember when we used to live high in the mountains to escape from the government.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you don't live there anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nope. I needed a more convenient place to lead the revolution from. But that old mountain hut is still there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Man, I miss that hut...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What, are you getting homesick, Apollo? You can come on back to Khura'in anytime, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, no, I'm fine. Besides, I've got a lot on my plate here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A thatched roof... First time I've ever seen one in real life.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It looks just like the traditional thatched roofs they use in Japan. All we need now are some samurai with topknots, a few ninjas, and a cuddly mascot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When was the last time you were in Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Mass transit and electronic communications... This country's infrastructure is really advanced compared to Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why don't you see the sights once you have the orb?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well... I guess I could use a break. How about you show me around?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, um, I'll probably be busy with work, so, uh...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...I-I see.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What are you talking about, Polly? Your only work right now is cleaning the office.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The Founder's Orb should be with the doctor right now. What do you say we go take a gander?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What if he doesn't have it? What if you came all the way from Khura'in for nothing?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'll cross that bridge if and when I come to it. Besides... even if I leave empty-handed, at least I got to see you, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, ha ha. Thanks?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">N-No, no – I really mean it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is Dr. Buff's study...</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wow, look at all those books! The shelves go from floor to ceiling! It's like a library in here!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, and lots of artifacts, too. A true archeologist's paradise. Look, son! There are so many relics, they're spilling onto the floor! What a delightfully amusing room!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All I see is a mess. <thought>And what's with that white outline...?</thought> ...Um, Ema, where's the doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well the thing is... he died last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It seems an avalanche of books knocked him off his bookshelf ladder. We're labeling it an accidental death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! Please tell me you're joking...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">As if I'd come all the way out here for a few laughs, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah. I guess not.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">A scholar killed by his own books...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh man. What do we do now? I mean, how can he transfer ownership of the orb to you if he's dead?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, that is a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, can you please tell us exactly what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the doctor died in an accident?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I received a call this morning saying Dr. Buff had been found dead under a pile of books.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This morning? <thought>Talk about bad timing...</thought> You mentioned that he had fallen off a ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Right. We believe he fell from the top of that big ladder there. Apparently, he triggered an avalanche of books while fumbling to reach one. And that sent him headlong on a fatal fall onto the hard floor.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">How sad... Killed by his own books. But at least he was doing something he loved.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">For a scholar, I suppose it's kind of like a soldier killed in the line of duty. You could say he died an honorable death.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, who was the first one to discover the body?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">About that... Whoever it was, it seems they wanted to remain anonymous.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It happens now and then. Some people would rather not get involved with the police.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I can relate to that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, being a wanted man and all.</thought> What now, Dhurke? A dead man can't exactly hand over the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We'll just have to find it. It must be around here somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just to fill you in, Ema, we're actually here to get something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pops here had an agreement with the doctor. The doctor was supposed to hand over a sacred relic known as the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">"P-Pops"...?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Oh, I see. That could be a problem, considering he's dead. Do you have a plan B?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I have an agreement in writing. My compatriot Datz should have it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, there shouldn't be any problems, then. So, who IS this gentleman you're escorting?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right, I haven't introduced you [sic] yet. This is Dhurke. He's from the Kingdom of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">All the way from Khura'in, huh? So, what do you do there?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I used to practice law, but I'm taking a break from all that. I'm focused now on making Khura'in a better place through... volunteer work. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">Volunteer work, huh? How interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Well, it's not technically a lie.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, how do you two know each other?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... He's sorta my foster father.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Come again?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah! And he's Prosecutor Sahdmadhi's real father, too!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Whaaat?! You mean you... and Prosecutor Sahdmadhi... ............I'm so sorry. It seems you've had quite a life.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Guess she's put a few things together.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually, Dhurke, you look kind of... familiar. Have we met before?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Um, not that I recall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Great... She must've seen that news report on TV.</thought> <thought>It will really complicate things if she figures out he's a wanted man.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are lots of guys who look like him. Sure you're not mistaking him for someone else?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Are there, really? I mean, a middle-aged man with long hair and an eye patch? You don't see that every day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, I'm sure you're just imagining things.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So what does that sacred relic you're searching for look like? I mean, there's lots of stuff in here that's old and relic-y.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Indeed. Unfortunately, I've no idea what it actually looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, how are we supposed to find it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That, I do not know, either. We'll just have to go through each candidate one by one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great plan of attack there, Dhurke. Well, Ema, do you mind if we give this room a once-over?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...I guess not. But in exchange, you're going to help me in my investigation. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sure. It can't hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Ooh, I can't wait to get started! It'll be like hunting for buried treasure!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What do you think you're doing? You can't just poke around without my permission.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>Guess I should ask her what's going on first.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is where Dr. Buff died.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Poor man... He fell right on his head, and probably died almost instantly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I see some blood on the book there, but what's that dark stain?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It appears to be coffee. It's still damp, so it must have gotten on there recently, perhaps even last night.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's a mighty big window he's next to -- big enough for someone to see inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Exactly. That's how the local resident who reported his death found him to begin with. The doctor's body was visible from outside the window. And a passerby called in earlier this morning to report what they'd found.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you mean this case is still only a few hours old?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That explains why your investigation is just getting underway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So this is where Dr. Buff died.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah, the police received a call this morning so their investigation is still just getting started.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a pair of glasses on this little pyramid here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They belonged to the doctor. Scientifically speaking, they appear to be your ordinary run-of-the-mill glasses.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess they don't pique her interest, scientifically speaking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This PC is password protected. Trucy, you think your magic can do something about this?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... I don't think it can override a password. Now, a locked desk... That I can get into. Like yours back at the office, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes... I'd better watch what I put in there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What? Do you put weird stuff in your desk? Stuff you don't want anyone to see?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Jeez, are you a mind reader, too? </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No, but unlocking your thoughts is a cinch!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor fell from the top of that ladder.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hmm... From that height, a fall onto a hard surface would probably kill anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know why anyone would want to climb that high in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Guess you can say he climbed it all the way to heaven...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a two-tone raincoat. </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's still a bit damp. I think someone might've worn it recently.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are a few pairs of shoes here. I guess there must be an entrance on this floor, too. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah, there's a backdoor over that way. But it's usually locked from what I can tell. The visitor's entrance is up that spiral staircase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That's the way we came in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There are animal drawings on the floor. They look like those famous geoglyph things.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">They remind me of the chalk outlines detectives draw around bodies. And the doctor's has [sic] just joined them. Now that's what I call dedication to one's field. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't think it was on purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What a huge window. I bet you could see the entire study from the outside. </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">How could he concentrate in here? I'd feel so exposed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well... He does have a bookshelf positioned for some privacy around his desk.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There's some sort of machinery inside this clay figure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, it's moving!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">D-Do I even want to know what that thing is for?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look, it's one of the doctor's notebooks.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Maybe there's something about the orb in there. It's a photo of the treasure box! The one from Tehm'pul Temple's treasure room. These must be his research notes on the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that on the right page? It looks like a poem or something.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Let's see... Oh, it's the song that's performed during the Dance of Devotion. It's been sung during Khura'inese rites of offering since ancient times.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I think I've heard of that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a song everyone in Khura'in knows? Not much of a way to keep it secret.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's called "hiding secrets in plain sight," Polly. Us magicians know all about that.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Huh. That's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Dr. Buff's notes contain the second half of the song. Only the first half is sung during the Dance of Devotion. Most people haven't even heard the second half.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The second half? As in the part that begins, "Offer thy prayers"?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm impressed. That's some thorough research he was conducting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this a bird?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It looks like an airplane to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, there couldn't have been any planes back when this was made.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, but it has wings and both horizontal and vertical stabilizers. That makes it an airplane.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's definitely a bird.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Open your eyes, son... As a lawyer, your job is to see the true nature of things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>I still say it's a bird.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a brown stain on this scroll. Hm? Why does it smell like... gravy?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Why would there be a gravy stain on it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who knows? But it looks like it's meant to be there.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Maybe the artist was trying to inspire a "gravy" new trend: food splatter art.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That pun wounded me "gravy-ly," Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A coffeemaker and a bunch of coffee cups... He must've taken his coffee breaks here. Oh, and there's a filter with old coffee grounds in here. *sigh* Guess I'd better clean this up.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What are you doing there, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah!  <thought>What AM I doing, cleaning this office?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't tell me they have you on coffee duty back at your office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, no... It's just, if I don't keep the place clean, no one will.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a golden statue. Looks pretty old, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder how he got his hands on something like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Ami"... Hmm... Why's someone's name written on here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Maybe it's so if it ever got lost, someone could return it to its owner. You know, like how school kids put their names on things.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but this is just an urn. And the name is written so big.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I wrote my name on my magic panties. It says W-R-I-G-H-T in super big letters!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The less said about this, the better.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a spiral staircase... And it's connected to a hallway up there. Why'd they have to place the second floor so high up?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait... You're not afraid of heights, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Oh, Polly's hilarious around high places. He gets all wobbly, like a baby deer taking its first steps. And his face turns as green as a watermelon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not nice to make fun of people's phobias, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Come to think of it, the visitor's entrance is on the second floor. What an odd layout for a house...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hey... this spirit medium looks like the Holy Mother of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, her face was left blank, but the rest is clearly detailed and well-crafted.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Did you know some researchers claim that the Holy Mother had three eyes? And that her third eye was able to divine the truth, just like the gods above. It is said to be on her forehead.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like you said, you shouldn't believe everything you hear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's one big suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's locked. Is it the doctor's?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No, someone left it here last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the doctor might've had a visitor? But how can you tell?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That sticker there. You only see those on airport luggage. Which means, its owner is likely from overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Is there any way to figure out who it belongs to?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not unless we can open it to see what's inside.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Guess not...</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh heh heh. Ah-ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's because you're not me: Ema Skye, forensics expert extraordinaire! Try as you might, you won't find the word "impossible" in my forensics handbook!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I-Is she okay, son? It's like she became an entirely different person.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, that's just what happens when her forensics switch gets flipped.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">With this, identifying the suitcase's owner will be easy as pie!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is that fingerprint powder?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's right. And there's no better time than the present to use it! Here we go! You remember how to do this, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I apply the powder to where I think some prints might be, and blow any excess off?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Exactly. Well, have at it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... Now where would I expect to find prints on a suitcase?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Doesn't look like there are any prints here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">This one isn't clear enough for a match.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Where else could someone leave prints behind?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Think, son. How might someone handle a suitcase? Start by considering what you do with them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, besides being wheeled or carried, they can be opened and closed. So, I should look for prints that would be left at those times.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'll need to use more powder than that to get a clear print.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey Ema, I've got a pretty clear print here.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Okay, now let me know who you think it could belong to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm, who could it be? It would have to be someone who would've paid Dr. Buff a visit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">We didn't get a match.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Any other ideas, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Well, we can probably assume the print belongs to the suitcase's owner. <thought>But who could that be? It would have to be someone who would've visited the doctor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">We have a match!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz... Come to think of it, he did stop by to see the doctor, didn't he? To conclude the orb transfer agreement.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">So he's the one who forgot his suitcase here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where do you suppose he is now?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Haven't heard from him in a while, and he's not answering his phone.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Wait, you don't think he left his phone inside his suitcase, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I wouldn't put it past that knucklehead.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Actually, I think we may have run into him earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A suspicious man had been reported in the area, but when one of my officers approached to question him, he took off like a shot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sorry about that. Khura'inese people aren't all like him... I swear.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, he's probably still in the village somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe he knows something about the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Your attorney's badge? Huh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, that normally gets a better reaction from you.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">I'm tired of collecting your fingerprints. It's kind of lost its luster.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but who knows? There could be other people's prints on it.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Ooh, that's true! Hand it over, buddy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">............Hmph. The only prints I found were yours.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Blue:  <thought>Argh, it's all dusty now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Scientifically speaking, ancient relics are highly fascinating.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because of all the tests I can run. CT scans, electron microscopy, chemical analysis... The list goes on and on! If you ever do find one, you'd better bring it to me straight away!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Can I count on getting it back intact?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">We'll see. Scientific advances don't come without sacrifices, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>...I know someone who WON'T be seeing the orb anytime soon.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Maybe it was Dr. Buff's wish to die under a pile of his beloved books. I know I could die happily under a big pile of forensic equipment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I'll pass on dying under a big pile of evidence from my past cases. It's all murder weapons and photos of dead bodies.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">So, what? Are you saying you don't love your job?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You sure like to shove things in people's faces, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about you? You're always dusting around for prints. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">That's my job!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's not like I'm presenting evidence for the fun of it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Really? Because it sure seems like you enjoy it, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right back at you, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It seems the orb isn't here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That means Datz might be our only lead at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Detective Skye said he might still be here in the village. We should try to find him.</line>
<line speaker="???">Good day to you, citizens of Kurain Village! My name is Paul Atishon, and I want your vote!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow, that's REALLY loud.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Look, something's coming this way.</line>
<line speaker="???">Paul Atishon, savior of Kurain, has come to– Ahhh! It's you people!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo? What is that strange conveyance coming this way?</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Right, left, right, left, HALT!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It's one of those... what-do-you-call-'ems? Palanquins...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">So, you finally left Dr. Buff's house! What were you doing there? ...What a bunch of shady-looking characters.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And you aren't?</thought> So I take it you knew the doctor?</line>
<line speaker="???">Heh, what a foolish question. I've memorized the names and faces of the entire electorate here in Kurain. After all, I am the man who's destined to be kind of this fine nation someday.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ignorant fools. I am THE Paul Atishon. I am a soon-to-be eminent politician– a man whose name will go down in history. You should be ashamed that you've never heard of me before.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Is he really that famous of a politician, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not that I know of.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I'm running for a seat on the local council right now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess even Jerk Q. Public has to start somewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">But my election is a sure thing, I'm told. After all, my grandfather was a famous politician with untold influence. In short, I'm the chosen one, the chosen one, the golden boy, the powerhouse of politics!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...And rider-of-his-grandfather's-coattails.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. Are you blinded by my majesty? Go ahead! Bask in the resplendent glory that is me, the chosen one!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Sure...</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">A pleasant day to you, good people of Kurain! I am Paul Atishon! It's time to reclaim the glory of Kurain, together! A convenience store on every corner, a karaoke bar in every home! A vote for Paul Atishon is a vote for a happier, hopey-er Kurain Village!</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">Turn off that infernal racket, you fool! You're a stain on your grandfather's good name!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Thank you, good sir! Your support is appreciated, as always!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I guess he's one of those people who only hears what they want to hear.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...In other words, he's a model politician.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Now where was I? Oh right, you were in the doctor's house. Just what in the world were you doing in there? Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this what you ride around in when you're campaigning?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. It's perfect for the narrow roads and steep hills here in this village. It has a top speed of 5 miles per hour, but it suffers from serious reliability issues. Namely, these imbeciles tire out too quickly.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">*cough* *huff, puff* We'll try harder next time, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Poor guys... They're exhausted and covered in sweat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">The Atishon family has been in politics for generations, even back in the old country.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">My grandfather, Abe Atishon, was a prominent member of Congress. And he was born right here in Kurain. There isn't a person here who hasn't heard of him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>All I asked about was his palanquin.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">You must've heard of the Atishons. I'm even reviving our old country campaigning style.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, um... politics aren't really my thing. Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I don't recall ever reading about them at school.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh... Young people today. You people really need to pay more attention to politics.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">So, what business did you people have at Dr. Buff's house?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was going to transfer ownership of the Founder's Orb to us. It's a sacred relic from the Kingdom of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">The Founder's Orb? So you tried to get your hands on it, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what do you know about the orb?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh. I know that it's mine, that's what.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How do you figure that?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Because I know it's not the Founder's Orb. Its real name is the Crystal of Ami Fey. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The Crystal of Ami Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. It's been passed down for generations in the Atishon family. Until it was stolen, that is. But just when I had zeroed in on the culprit, the doctor hid it away and then kicked the bucket.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're saying Dr. Buff stole your family heirloom? <thought>That's not what Dhurke said. Strange...</thought> But I've been told the doctor himself said that he had the "Founder's Orb."</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It's all that weird foreigner's doing! He filled the doctor's head with nonsense! Nonsense like the Crystal of Ami Fey being the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"Weird foreigner"? <thought>Could he mean...?</thought> Is this the foreigner you're talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Atishon:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, wouldn't that be nice. <thought>Because I certainly wouldn't vote for you. It seems this isn't the person he's talking about. But I can't imagine the doctor had contact with that many foreigners way out here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes, that's him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I thought so. <thought>Now we really have to find Datz.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Do you know where this man is now?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I imagine he's at the Detention Center by now. I called the authorities after I found him hiding in my dog's doghouse.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That buffoon...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, at least we know where he is now.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Let's head over to the Detention Center and see what he knows about the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">So, you really are after my crystal. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, we're looking for the Founder's Orb, and we have an agreement to prove it.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Well, just so you know, you're not going to lay a finger on it. It's mine. And I intend to give it to my benefactor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your... benefactor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you're just going to give your family heirloom away to this person?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. It's a purely political decision.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And in exchange, your patron will get the people of Kurain to vote for you?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. Eminent politicians are skilled at leveraging all of their connections.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Isn't it illegal to buy votes?</thought> Well, good luck with that, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh, you just wait. Paul Atishon will reign supreme someday.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Actually, I'm a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. You're so shallow. Relying on your badge to impress people... What would you be without it? I petty men like you have no sense of self. Real men make their own mark in this world.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Says the man who's riding on his grandfather's coattails.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you think about this?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Paul Atishon is the "squeaky-clean candidate." So if you're going to bribe me, try to be a little more subtle about it, would you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I wasn't trying to bribe you.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">"Don't accept any bribes unless they come in unmarked bills." This is but a fraction of the political wisdom my grandfather shared with me. Better luck next time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>After a spin cycle or two with those bills, I bet I'D be "squeaky-clean," too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">About that Paul Atishon fellow... He's aiming to be a councilman and beyond, as his famous grandfather once was, right? No doubt some would vote for him on the merits of his grandfather's achievements. I see a grim future for Kurain Village if someone like that is able to climb the ranks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wouldn't worry about it. Who in their right mind would vote for him with the way he's campaigning?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">So the more aggressively he campaigns, the less people will want to vote for him? That makes me want to get out there and help him fail.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We turned the doctor's study upside down, but never found the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah, I didn't expect this to be so hard.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Well, I think it's fun. It's like a big old treasure hunt!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That orb is the key to Khura'in's future, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Yeah, and our office's future, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She does realize it's not up for sale, right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Ah, the old show-'em-and-see-what-they-say tactic. I used to try that whenever I had nothing else to say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who says I have nothing else to say?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's written all over your face.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Like you have anything to add right now.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">.........</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">.........Hey.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yipes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's he doing under the desk...?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Foul cogs of the corrupt regime! I've got nothing to say to you!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Datz, it's me, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh! Dhurke! You're a sight for sore eyes! I knew you'd come save me!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, this is another fine mess you've gotten yourself into.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har! My bad, my bad! ‘Least the grub here's pretty good compared to that prison back home! Ya get three squares plus a place to sleep! Why don't ya join me, Dhurke?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No thanks. They'd just send me back to Khura'in where I'd face immediate execution.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, I guess that wouldn't be such a good idea.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looks like he's still the same, too.</thought> ...Long time no see, Datz.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Huh? Hey, ya look... kinda familiar... A-A-A-Apollo?! Is it really you, m'boy?! A-to-the-J, all grown up and whatnot! How've ya been?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine. And you, Datz? You look good, besides the incarceration and all.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Pffffff! Haaaaar har har har har! Those horns, AJ!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Horns?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">They've grown up with ya, just like a stag's antlers! I can't take it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* You really haven't changed a bit. Anyway, there's something we needed to talk to you about.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sure, pull up a chair. I've got all the time in the world. The slammer's like my second home. It's really not so bad once ya get used to it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">He's rather laid back for someone in police custody.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, was what the doctor had really the Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Absolutely positively! The doc was sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Really? Because someone from the village is calling the Crystal of Ami Fey. He also claims you were filling the doctor's head with lies.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">That ain't true! The doc said he was sure it was the real deal. All his fancy research confirmed it was the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then that Paul Atishon character was lying? Imagine that, a politician who lies...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">I bet he wants the orb all to himself!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hmm... I wonder who's telling the truth?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Well, take a look at this! It proves the doc believed he had the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Let me see that. "I agree to hand over the Founder's Orb to the Defiant Dragons if I will come to no harm." Signed, Dr. Archie Buff.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">See, I got it all down in writing!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">But Datz, why does it say, "if I will come to no harm" at the end here?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Sounds like he was scared of you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, did you threaten the doctor in any way?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">No, ya got it all wrong! It was the doc's friend! HE told the old man us rebels were dangerous. It's his fault the doc thought I might hurt him!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like the work of that politician. He's really made a mess of things.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What have you done now, Datz?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Nothing! I'm innocent, I tell ya! It all started when this dog-faced cop tried to question me! He looked so funny, I started laughing at him. That's when they came after me. But it was hilarious, I tell ya! I mean, a human police dog? How funny is that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... So what happened after that?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">They caught me hiding in a doghouse. Dang pooch ratted me out! I guess that's what I get for laughing at one of his doggy comrades.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like the dogs got the last laugh.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Datz, weren't you cleared of those jailbreak charges? And your capture by Lady Kee'ra deemed unlawful?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah, but... The cops here don't seem to like me anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are the charges this time?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Unauthorized entry, or something like that. They think I'm an illegal alien! And I can't prove otherwise ‘cause I lost my passport!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Is there any way they'd let you go?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Not without my passport... If only I had it! Dhurke, AJ! You gotta find my passport!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...All right, we'll find it. <thought>One more thing to add to our to-do list. Now, where might Datz's passport be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I hate the feeling of being constantly watched.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Indeed. Considering my current situation, the less I'm seen, the better.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's not like there's an international arrest warrant out for you.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">True, but I seem to have made quite an international splash with that hijacking stunt. I had to sign a ton of autographs and take a load of selfies before I got to your office.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Maybe they thought the hijacking was part of some movie's promotion.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's completely uninterested in us.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That suits me fine. It will only complicate things if I'm recognized.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... You're known as some sort of scary terrorist who fled from Khura'in. Though, in reality, no one would believe you're the real Dhurke of legend anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, why are you holding that mic?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I get this strange urge to speak whenever there's a microphone before me. We, the Defiant Dragons, shall–!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, stop! Stop...!!!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Why, AJ! You've become a fine lawyer in your own right!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nah, I still have a lot to learn.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Aw, c'mon, don't be so hard on yourself. If I ever went to trial, I'd definitely want you on my side!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Knowing you, you'd probably skip town before the trial even started.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">The doc agreed in writing to hand the orb over to me, but he kept stalling, like he didn't  trust me or something.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That scary mug of yours no doubt frightened him.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Look who's talking!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Honestly, I think you're both about equally scary looking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch... Both Dhurke and Datz look like they've been stabbed right in the ego.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh, is that for me!?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I was just showing it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Anything I could use here in the slammer is more than welcome!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, Datz, the guard is giving you some serious side eye.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Oh! About the orb's whereabouts... Maybe the doc's kid knows something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor has a kid?</line>
<line speaker="Dat">Yeah... A bit of a shut-in, though. The poor thing's own bedroom has become like a self-imposed prison.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A shut-in? Sounds like it will be a challenge just to get a conversation going.</line>
<line speaker="Guard">Time for your questioning. Follow me.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">It must be lunchtime. Today is fried chicken, if I'm not mistaken!</line>
<line speaker="Guard">You'll get your lunch IF you behave yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Dhurke, AJ. I'll see ya guys around!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Our only lead now is Dr. Buff's kid. But luring a shut-in out is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Not going to be easy. I know.</line>
<line speaker="???">Oh, it's you again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He was?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What was Daddy doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good question.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He said he was looking for something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did he say anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Let me think... Something abuot how his ride never showed up at the airport. Yes, that was it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess Athena really did get lost...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Trucy">But what's Daddy doing all the way out here in the first place? He can't be looking for us since no one told him we'd be here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, if you're here to take another look around, be my guest. I have other work to do, so if you'll excuse me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. Thanks, Ema.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">First and foremost, we'd better find Datz's passport. We should also have a word with Dr. Buff's child.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, is it just me... or is there something new in here?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Oh, you mean that thing? Yeah, we should take a closer look at it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's not forget about Datz's passport. It should be around here somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz's suitcase... Maybe his passport's in there.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Annggh! It's no good. It's locked tight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We should've asked him for the key.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this? A model helicopter?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't you know anything, Apollo? It's a drone! They're all the rage right now. I bet it belongs to the doctor's kid.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We need to ask them about the orb's whereabouts.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but luring out a shut-in isn't going to be easy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing new here. Let's go look somewhere else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What are we going to do about Datz's passport? It's probably right there inside his suitcase, but we can't get it open.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Why don't I take it over to Datz so he can unlock it? That way, you guys can continue looking for the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good thinking, Trucy!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Okay, here I go! ...Huh? What the...? Hrrgh...! This thing weighs a ton!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let me try. ............Jeez, how can a suitcase be so heavy? Is it filled with bricks or something?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Knowing Datz, he probably packed his dumbbells in there. It's certainly much too heavy to lug all the way to the detention center. Here, let me take a crack at that lock.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What, are you going to pick it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There you go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was fast.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha! A lock like that is child's play to me. Especially after all the wrongly imprisoned compatriots I've busted out over the years.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You've sure seen a lot of action for an ex-lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aaand here we go. Datz's passport.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'll take it over to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks, Trucy.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">No problem! Now you guys enjoy some quality father-son treasure hunting time, okay? See you later!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There she goes. I wish she wouldn't make such a big deal out of our little "family" situation.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Father-son time, eh? Hmm... Been ages since we've had a father-son talk, huh, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well over a decade.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">So, Apollo, um... how've you been?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh... Fine. I'm fine, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Is that so? Fine, you say? Well, fine is fine by me! Good to hear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, okay. ..................</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>Umm... So what do we talk about now...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Hm? Get down! Hit the dirt, son!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? What the--? AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! .........Unngh......Oof... .........</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Speak to me, son! Say something!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Ooh... Th-that smarts...</line>
<line speaker="???">Youuuu maggots! Whattaya think yer doin', invading Buff airspace?! It'll be a scorching day in Siberia before you get past me, ya yellow-bellied yahoos!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa! ...It can talk?! What kind of drone is this, anyw... ...AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAYYYYYY!</line>
<line speaker="???">Drone, nothin'! That's Sergeant Buff to you, soldier! You got that, you lowly grunts?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oww... what the who now...?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Buff? Sounds like the doctor's son is behind the controls.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's controlling this thing?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo, let's play along for now. At least until we can get the information we need out of him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">G-Got it. Um... Sergeant Buff?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Sergeant Buff, sir! You forgot to say, "sir"! Ain't you never seen a war movie before?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Let me try that again. Sergeant Buff, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Better. Much better. Now, state your name, unit, and rank, soldier!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um, I'm Apollo Justice. I serve at the Wright Anything Agency. And my rank is, um... fledgling lawyer? ...Sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Affirmative, Private Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">P-Private?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Listen up, diaper baby! Your commanding officer's orders are absolute! Disobedience means a one-way trip to the firing squad! Do I make myself clear?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... sir! Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Good, good, we might make a man out of you yet, private! Now for you, Cyclops!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Huh? ...Oh, you want my name, unit, and rank, too? Um, I'm Dhurke Sahdmadhi. I comand the rebel group the Defiant Dragons, and my rank is... um... leader, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Excellent! Welcome aboard, Komandir Dhurke! Wait a second! What's with that ridiculous mop you call a head? Soldiers should be clean cut!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">S-Sorry, but this is my signature look. I'm not going to-- WHOOOOOOOOOA! Fine, fine! I'll get a haircut before we ship out!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Listen up, you! It's kill-or-be-killed out on that battlefield. No place for leave-in conditioners. All you've got is your life, and you're lucky to have that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's oddly obsessed with field survival for someone who never goes outdoors...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This is going to be harder than I thought, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Don't let me catch you stepping out of line again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Guess I'd better play along and ask what he wants.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge, sir, do you ever read these books?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Why, of course! Soldiers must have extensive knowledge, as well as fighting prowess. I'm learning all I can each and every day in preparation for the big battle!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The big battle?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Um, you know... for when I go back to school. I'll need to be up to date on every subject. Stuff like... y'know, the latest comics and Hollywood gossip...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I see... <thought>What about reading, writing and arithmetic?</thought> Well, I'm rooting for you, Sarge!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Th-Thanks. I'll try my best.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This computer could provide some useful information. Drat. It's password protected. Dhurke, you're good at getting into places you're not supposed to.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't look at me. I don't know the first thing about computers.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ha ha ha ha ha! Leave it to me! A modern day warrior must be well-versed in technology... and have a mean, mean pride! After all, he who controls information, controls the battlefield!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Aaaaand I'm in!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Looks like modern day warriors have mean, mean keyboard skills, too.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Okay, let's see what we can find.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, what's this...? An e-mail message? Now this is interesting. It's a research report to whoever asked the doctor to study the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Here, I put the data on this! Take it and use it well, soldier!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor's computer. It contains an e-mail detailing the progress of his research.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I wonder who he prepared the report for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Are these the doctor's?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yes, those are Papa's reading glasses. He said he'd been having trouble reading lately. But those glasses seemed to help.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Reading glasses, eh? I'll just hold on to these.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. Don't tell me you're having trouble reading, too?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Perish the thought! ...I-I just don't want to leave any stone unturned.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a raincoat... Hm...? It's a bit wet, and there's fresh mud on it... That must mean someone wore it recently.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Indeed. Maybe even as recently as last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge, did it rain here last night?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Negative. There wasn't a cloud in the sky.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Then how did this raincoat get all muddy and wet?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">When I saw it last evening, it looked pretty clean and dry to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That means it got like this later at night.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Good eye, son. This may very well turn out to be a vital clue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's this thing's problem...?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">It's an OOPArt -- an our-of-place artifact. Papa won it in an online auction.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">An online auction?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yes, he said it's an alien weapon that destroyed an entire ancient civilization.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Where do I even start with an explanation like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This urn with "Ami" painted on it looks really old. But I don't think it's going to provide any info we need.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is your room upstairs, Sarge?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yes, it's the one at the end of the hall.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What do you say you come out, so we can enjoy a snack together?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I promise we won't bite!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...............If you insist... ...then I'm not going to talk to you anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No, wait!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, you'd better apologize quick.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...I'm sorry for pushing.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">V-Very well. As long as you don't do it again, I'll let it slide this one time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's Datz's suitcase. It's full of survival gear and questionable souvenirs. But we already got his passport, so we can leave it be for now.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a shoe cubby. Hmm, these shoes look like they belong to Sarge and his dad. ...Ah, these boots here are a little damp!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And it looks like there's something inside this one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe Doctor Buff wore them last night.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">They might lead us to where he hid the orb. Let's take a closer look.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a question mark on the bottom of this boot.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa had those custom-made for his archeological fieldwork. He had the soul of an adventurer.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This boot had the "sole" of an adventurer, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Something's giving off a soft glow inside this boot. But it's too dark in there to see what it is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We might get a better look inside if we undid these straps.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like some kind of glowing moss.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It could've come from wherever the doctor went last night. Must've gotten in with some of that mud.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It might be worth looking into... ...if it'll help us pinpoint where the doctor hid the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, are you controlling that drone from your room, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Affirmative! But I can see everything you do from here, so... Teeen-HUT, soldier! Wipe that stupid look off your face! I'm going to whip you sheltered peaceniks into shape!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With what? Your "charming" personality?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Look, it's got a camera and speakers, too.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">And that's not all, Komandir! With these arms, I can cook and clean, too! Speaking of which... Private Justice! You're on latrine duty! Snap to it, on the double!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...*sigh*... As if I don't see enough of the toilet back at the office.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That thing's pretty handy. Us Defiant Dragons could use one of those.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Yes, it is a fine piece of hardware, isn't it? I modified it especially for siege defense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Siege defense...? You mean how you won't leave your room? AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Holing up in a stronghold to defend against an enemy is an age-old military tactic! A timeless strategy still applicable in modern warfare! I hope you're not trying to mock the wisdom of my forefathers!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I... I meant no offense. It was just an observation.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">So the greenhorn who ain't even discharged a firearm's got something to say, does he?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry, sorry! It won't happen again, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Darn tootin'. Now, state your intentions, soldier.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We had an agreement with your father. He had promised to hand over the Founder's Orb to us.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What?! Papa promised you that?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He did. But he died before he could tell us where it's hidden. Now we have no idea where it is.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">.................. ...Oh. *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">P-Papa... Why...? Why'd you have to die?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It was an unfortunate accident. And I'm sorry for your loss.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If it helps at all, I know how you feel, Sergeant Bu-- AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! What'd I do nowww?!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Y-You insignificant maggot! What would an unseasoned rookie like you know about how I feel?! First I lost Mama... and now I've lost Papa!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You lost your mother, too?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">She's been gone for some time now. I'm... I'm all alone now. All alone... *sniffle*</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Sergeant Buff, would you tell us a little more about what happened to your mother?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Mama passed away about six months ago. We were still living in our apartment in the city. Back then, I had yet to engage in my siege defense strategy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>In other words, something caused him to withdraw from the world.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...It was arson. It happened so suddenly... and before we knew it, our apartment was a sea of flames. Mama and I were trapped inside. But help never came. So Mama cradled me in her arms... ...kicked out a window... and jumped!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She did what?!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">She was like a walkin', talkin' medal of valor, my Mama was. She delivered me safely to terra firma with a perfectly executed PLF. It's a five-point landing technique used by paratroopers to land safely on the ground.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>She sounds like a superhero or something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">But from that height, she suffered massive injuries in order to protect me. She... She died so that I could live! AHHHHHHHHHHHH! MAMAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I... I don't know what to say...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And the person who started the fire?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">He was immediately apprehended. They say he was standing outside laughing while the building burned.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">At least justice was served. I hope that brought you some solace.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I've lost both my parents now. You can't possibly know how I feel! *sniffle* *sob* Mama... Papa...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Poor kid. It's hard losing both your parents at such a young age. He must really feel alone now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo... I imagine you know what he's going through.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I do?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The road to recovery begins by talking to someone who's suffered the same hardship. I know you have something that shows you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge, sir. Do you have any idea where the orb might be?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">It was here in Papa's study until last night. But he said he was going to go hide it somewhere. He meantioned something about a shady character being after it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Where do you think he could've hidden it?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Hmm... Somewhere in the village, I'd guess. He said he'd found a suitable hiding place for it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, it was here last night. That is, until he went out to hide it somewhere in the village. The only question is where?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Maybe he left some clue here in his study. Let's search the place again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We should also find out more about Dr. Buff. It might steer us toward the hiding place.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Sarge, what was your father like?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa was as king as Mama was courageous. His whole reason for moving to the countryside was for me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I initiated my siege defense strategy after Mama died. Papawas so worried about me, he moved us here to the countryside. He thought the fresh air, blue skies, and natural surroundings might alter my tactics.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What a fine father.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">He even quit his position at the university to move here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He did?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">He did. He gave up his beloved research position just for me! "A parent must be prepared to sacrifice everything for his child." That's what Papa said!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Well, I'm feeling about two inches tall right now.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">There's no one in the world I respected more than him. But that just makes his passing all the more devastating. *sniffle, sniffle* Papa, may you continue your beloved research up there with the angels!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What insubordination!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">ARRRRRRAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Petty trinkets have no place in Buff's army, soldier! Now drop and give me twenty!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sheesh... At least let me show the evidence before you shoot it down...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, sergeant, sir. Would you please take a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What do we have here?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a photo of my father. I wasn't even a year old when he died... in a fire.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And like your mother, he died in an arsonist's blaze. But in his final moments, he managed to save his infant son.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">P-Private Justice, you've suffered a loss just like mine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I have... and that's why I know how you feel.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">B-But... you still have your mother, don't you?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I lost her, too.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She disappeared after the fire. I don't know if she's still alive or dead. Heck, I don't even know what she looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Wow...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sergeant Buff, his experience is very much like your own. If anyone can understand the sadness in your heart, it's him.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Rrrr... Nnngh... .............................. ATTEEEEEENSHUN!!! I salute you, Comrade Justice! You are no longer a private in the Buff Army! Henceforth, you will be a corporal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Corporal?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Congratulations on your promotion, Corporal Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I'm just glad that seemed to cheer him up a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Now, comrade, let's toast to your new stripes! And call me Sarge! Don't be shy! We're a band of brothers now! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Now's our chance, corporal! Ask him about the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Dhurke's getting waaaaay too much of a kick out of this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Corporal Justice... you shoulder a bitter past.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You've been through quite a lot yourself, Sarge.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Corporal, if I may... um...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Well... um... it doesn't have to be that often, but... W-W-Would you mind coming over from time to time?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You want me to visit you?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">O-Only if you want to, of course!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sure. I'll come by, and I'll even bring along my coworkers, Sarge.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">R-Really?! Yaaaaaay! Our band of  brothers continues to grow in rank! Ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Nice work, son. Glad to see you haven't changed one bit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's that supposed to mean?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's my attorney's badge, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">You mean like a medal?! What act of valor earned you such an honor?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I rescued my clients from those who would brand them as guilty, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">A heroic act, indeed!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thank you for your kind words, sir! <thought>This whole "sir" thing is getting real old, real quick.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Why...? Why did Papa have to fall in battle?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's putting on a brave face, but he's still just a child.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">In honor of Papa's heroic sacrifice...  let us march on, comrade! To victory!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?! I-I mean, sir! Yes, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Are you two seriously bent on waging war against that bookcase?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It looks like you can do everything by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Indeed! I can even cook and build things whenever I want!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So there's really no reason for you to leave your room, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yes, but there is still one gaping hole in my siege defense. ...Going to the bathroom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When nature calls, it's best not to fight it.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yes, all great tacticians will say never wage a battle you have no hope of winning.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Let me ask you something, Corporal Justice! How does that aid you on the battlefield?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, well, if you count the courtroom as a battlefield, it's a fairly useful weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Good answer! A military man must know his weapons inside and out! Keep up the good work, corporal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sir, yes, sir! <thought>I guess that's all he has to say about that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's go over what we've learned so far. Wherever it was that Dr. Buff went, he needed a raincoat. And it was somewhere where this glowing moss grows. Any ideas where that might be, Sarge?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Negative, comrade. I hate to say my intel's a little thin on this one. I've been occupied with my siege defense strategy ever since we moved to the village.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, son, it seems we have no other choice. We'll have to ask the locals if they know of a place like that.</line>
<line speaker="May 16Kurain VillageApollo">Ugh. It feels like somebody's watching me, and it's really creeping me out. Oh, it's just Paul Atishon's campaign posters. When did he put these up? <thought>Whatever. I've got more important things to be paying attention to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What great weather! It really lifts the spirits. I know! After our little treasure hunt, what do you say we go hunting, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hunting? We used to do that a lot...didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Just look at that mountain. I bet there are some feisty wild boars up there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I...think I'll pass...but thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, so hunting's a no-go. Um, well...I guess that wild boar stew will have to wait, then. .........Hm? Apollo, something seems different from the last time we were here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Uh... You mean the posters?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No, not those.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's he talking about...? Guess I should take a look around myself.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That poor child... How is he going to survive all on his own?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, it's not like he can go out grocery shopping on his own. We should drop off some food later.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No, that would only make it worse. We should be encouraging him to come out on his own. Once his food runs out, he'll have to leave the house if he wants to eat.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Talk about your old-school siege tactics. Sounds more like you want to starve him out...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">............</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Talk about an awkward silence. I have no idea what to say.</thought> ............ <thought>Yeah... I've got nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aw, come on, son! Don't tell me you've got nothing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When did Paul Atishon have a chance to put up all these election posters?</line>
<line speaker="Old Man">That fool keeps stickin' 'em on our houses! He's a disgrace to his distinguished heritage!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He's doing this without permission?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A thatched roof... First time I've ever seen one in real life.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It looks just like the traditional thatched roofs they use In Japan. All we need now are some samurai with topknots, a few ninjas, and a cuddly mascot.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">When was the last time you were in Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>A phone booth and a bus stop made of wood. They both look really old. You hardly ever see phone booths in the city anymore.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo... what's this glass box for?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>I guess you hardly see them in Khura'in, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Seeing those mountains really takes me back. I remember when we used to live high in the mountains to escape from the government.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, you don't live there anymore?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nope. I needed a more convenient place to lead the revolution from. But that old mountain hut is still there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>Man, I miss that hut...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What, are you getting homesick, Apollo? You can come on back to Khura'in anytime, you know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, no, I'm fine. Besides, I've got a lot on my plate here...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a big boulder towering into the sky over there. According to the sign, it's called the "Kurain Boulder." It also says that a spirit dwells within it. Hmm... A rock with a spirit in it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's called animism -- the belief that spirits dwell within inanimate objects. They've probably enshrined this boulder as a sacred object. Their tradition of worshipping such objects is similar to our tradition in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-Interesting...  <thought>Who knew Dhurke could make sense every once in a while?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do we have here? It looks like an unfinished picture... like something a little kid might paint.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hmm, you're right. But I can't quite tell what it's of.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think it's supposed to be nighttime, but what's that thing on the left?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Um... A monster, or some kind of alien, perhaps? In any case, it's a pretty poor excuse for a drawing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, what did you expect from a little kid?</line>
<line speaker="???">A... little kid...&#160;?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Oh, it's you, Pearl!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why, Mr. Apollo, is that you? What a pleasant surprise! It's been quite some time. How have you been?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Fine, thanks. You're looking good too, Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aren't you going to introduce me, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. This is Pearl Fey. She's a spirit medium here in Kurain Village. Pearl, this is Dhurke, my umm... client.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hello, sir. Pleased to meet you. If there is anything I can do to help, please let me know.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nice to meet you, too. And what a polite little girl you are!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Um, actually... I'm a high-schooler.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Whoops! Sorry about that! So, you're a spirit medium? Does that mean you can channel spirits, then?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. I'm still in training, though. But I'm well-versed in the art of spirit channeling.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well now, isn't that something! I mean, back in my country, our little princess hasn't channeled a single spirit yet! Pretty impressive, young lady!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, but compared to Mystic Maya, there is so much more I must learn!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mystic Maya? Oh, right, Maya Fey... Mr. Wright's former courtroom assistant. He told me all about her. She's a spirit medium, too, if memory serves.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, she's an amazing medium. And soon, she'll be the next lead of the Fey clan, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Mediums and spirit channeling... I've heard all about it from Mr. Wright. He said that mediums will even physically become the person they're channeling. I wonder if even little Pearl would turn into a hulking giant if she hand to channel one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I hope you don't mind me asking, but what brings you all the way out here, Mr. Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, just a small matter to take care of.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Wait, would it happen to be the matter Mr. Edgeworth is looking into?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Prosecutor Edgeworth? What's he doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, so it's a different matter, then? Because I just saw him a moment ago. He appeared to be searching for something.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? Hmm... <thought>Mr. Edgeworth is a friend of Mr. Wright's, and the district's chief prosecutor. Why would HE be here in Kurain? Well, no point obsessing over it.</thought> Come to think of it, you live here in Kurain Village, don't you, Pearl?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, I was born and raised here.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This is perfect, Apollo. Let's ask the young lady if she knows where the doctor might have gone last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I was thinking the exact same thing. <thought>Maybe I should show her what we found in the doctor's study.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Hee hee. Seeing you present your badge like that... ...reminds me of when I used to investigate cases alongside Mr. Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You used to help Mr. Wright all the time, I hear.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That I did! Doing so helped me expand mu horizons beyond this tiny little village. So please, Mr. Apollo! If there's anything I can help you with, you just let me know!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I will. <thought>What I'd really like is her help with cleaning the office again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pearl, do you have any idea where this moss might grow?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That looks like... Mitama Moss. It grows on Mt. Mitama, and gives off a soft glow in the dark.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mt. Mitama?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">See that mountain over there? That's Mt. Mitama.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And how would one get there?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You can take a bus from that bus stop over there. ...Um, may I ask why you're so interested in that moss?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Dr. Buff was supposed to give us something. But it seems he hid it somewhere last night.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">H-He did? Maybe that's why he, um...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pearl? Do you know something that might help us?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um, well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like I'd better find out what she knows.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, um... Sorry, I wish I could help, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, don't worry about it! I'm sorry I wasted your time like that.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Um... At least let me offer you some tea. I mean, you must be tired from all your investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, no, you don't have to do that. We'll be just fine, thank you. <thought>She's so polite, it's hard NOT to feel rude around her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What a peaceful place. Ahh... Nothing beats mountain air.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Many of the villagers have left for the city, but I just love it here. Blue skies, lush forests, star-filled skies at night, and fireflies in the summer. Plus, the big, beautiful, blue ocean is just beyond that mountain!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The ocean?! What do you say we go for a swim, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, um... I think I'll pass. <thought>Besides, I can't swim.</thought> ...Um, Pearl? Kurain Village is like, "the home of spirit mediums," right?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, and I'm a part of a long line of mediums.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've never seen a channeling before, but... ...is it possible to channel the spirit of anyone who's passed away?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">No, not just anyone. You must know their face and true name.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? You can channel a spirit just by knowing their face and name? That's an amazing ability.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">It is, but it can only be learned by those with a gift occurring in certain bloodlines... ...and years of intense training. At present, Mystic Maya and I are the only ones in our village who can channel spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Looks like spirit mediums are highly valued here, much like they are back in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I heard there used to be many more of us a long time ago...:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well, you guys aren't exactly close to any shopping malls or nightclubs out here. But what about you? Are you NOT interested in things like that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">W-Who, me? Well, I... I wouldn't mind a new outfit or two, and, well... Oh, never mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's okay, Pearl. You are at that age, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh! We met this weirdo earlier named Paul Atishon. Do you know anything about him?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes, he's been campaigning a lot around here lately. And the noise he's been making has become quite a problem. People are especially upset that he's campaigning at all hours of the night and day.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hmm, well... The local police should arrest him for disturbing the peace.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Unfortunately, there's little they can do because the Atishon family is so powerful.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Well, isn't HE the proverbial pampered provincial prince.</thought> He seems pretty intent on winning here in Kurain. Is there some special reason why?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm not sure, but I have an idea. The spirit mediums of Kurain once held considerable sway in the political world. Judging by his slogan, maybe that's what he's after.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Great, so he's just another politician seeking powerful connections...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The ability to commune with the dead gives comfort to those anxious about the future. Tiny Khura'in has preserved its independence by the queen's power of spirit channeling. It must play a similar role in this village.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Yes. Even today, many here revere those with spirit medium blood flowing in their veins.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So basically, as Paul Atishon's benefactor goes, so goes the whole village? <thought>Who is this benefactor? Who could hold this much sway over Kurain Village?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pearl... Do you have any idea where Dr. Buff might've gone last night?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Umm... Well...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Uhh, about that... ...All I know is Dr. Buff was somewhere on Mt. Mitama.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...! <thought>My bracelet...! It's reacting! Which means that Pearl is hiding something from me.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Anyone would feel uneasy being stared at like that!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? But I...!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'd be unnerved, too. I mean, your eyes are practically popping out of your head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I get it. I'll tone it down a little. <thought>Guess I was wrong.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pearl, you seem anxious around the topic of Mt. Mitama. I could tell because you'd rub your thumb over a splotch of dried paint as you said it.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh! U-Um, well...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That nighttime painting is yours, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">.........! ...This is so embarrassing. As you saw, I'm not a very good artist. But that picture has nothing to do with Dr. Buff!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not so sure about that. In fact, I'm going to guess that while you were out here painting last night... ...you actually saw the good doctor heading out to Mt. Mitama from the bus stop.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">N-No! I-I didn't see anything like that! I swear!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No, I'm positive you saw the doctor. After all, he's right here in your picture.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Really? That doesn't look like him to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I guess it IS pretty abstract.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh... Is it really that hard to make out? Er, what I mean is, it has nothing to do with Dr. Buff! After all, I never even saw him that night!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Y-You think that's the doctor? I may not be a very good artist, but at least I know how to draw a person!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, if this isn't a person, then what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Er... Th-That's a... a rain spirit!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, and what's a rain spirit doing at a bus stop?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Oh, umm, rain spirits have places to go, too!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">........ <thought>This is getting ridiculous.</thought> Sorry, Pearl, but you're not a very good liar. That is Dr. Buff, and this piece of evidence proves it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Pearl:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No no, it's... <thought>...totally like that, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">That isn't a person! It's a rain spirit, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, Pearl, that isn't a rain spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is the raincoat we found in the doctor's study. It's still wet and muddy, so we know that someone wore it last night. Now, let's see how this pattern is the same as the "rain spirit" in your picture?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You didn't see a rain spirit last night. You saw Dr. Buff wearing this raincoat!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I'm sorry I didn't tell you before, Mr. Apollo, but I did see the doctor last night.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's all right. Just, please, tell me everything you know.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">...Of course. I was painting out here last night... when the doctor came up to the bus stop. He was wearing a raincoat, even though it wasn't raining, and a helmet with a light on it. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like he was well-prepared for something.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">I know. That's why I asked him if he was going off exploring again. He looked startled, like he hadn't noticed me there. And then, he suddenly said... "Please don't tell anyone you saw me here."</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Why would he want to silence you like that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Something must've happened to spook him. And he didn't want anyone to know where he was going to hide the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But where could he have been going dressed like that?</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">My best guess is a cave somewhere on Mt. Mitama. I heard there's a cave there where mediums of the Kurain tradition went to train long ago. Legend has it, there are some sort of mystical ruins in there. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mystical ruins? Sounds like the exact sort of place an archeologist might go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we should get going now, but thanks for all your help, Pearl.</line>
<line speaker="Pearl">You're welcome, Mr. Apollo. Take care.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What do you say we go find that cave, son? I sense that the orb might finally be within our grasp.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This treasure hunt is shaping up to be the real deal.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah hah hah. Really gets the blood pumping, doesn't it?! Well, what are we waiting for? Let's go!</line>
<line speaker="May 16Mt. Mitama - Cave EntranceApollo">Whew, I'm all out of breath.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aw, come on, that was nothing. And you're so much younger than me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I, uh... *huff* *puff* ...don't normally get this much exercise... *cough* *sputter*</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Need a break?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, I'm fine. *huff* *puff*</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">This must be where the doctor was last night. Let's take a look inside.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ I can't see a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Relax. Your eyes will adjust eventually. Now, follow me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I really think we need a flashlight, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Should've brought one along then, son.</line>
<line speaker="???">...Here, use mine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks! Wait, were you holding out on me?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Um... who are you talking to, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You...? Whoa! <thought>Someone just pushed me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo? What the--?! Apollo! Ah... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oww...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Are you all right, son?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... Looks like someone got the drop on us.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Quite literally.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But who--? I mean, we could've died from that fall!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I don't know... Hmm... But I don't think we'll be getting out the way we came in. Looks like we're in a pretty deep cave. Nothing to do but press on, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How can you even see in here?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Come on, let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Hey, wait! <thought>One false step and we're dead... What in the world should we do...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How about we wait for help to come?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And how are we to call for said help, hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With my phone, obviously. I'll just-- Argh...! Of course we're in a dead zone... *sigh*</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Guess that's that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just great...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's try climbing back up.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Can you even see the wall in front of you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...No...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, I can tell you it's far too steep.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You never know until you try! Here goes nothing! Hrrrgh... Annngh...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Your loud voice may move mountains... ...but you've barely moved an inch, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Argh!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I guess we keep going. There must've been some path for Dr. Buff to follow when he came to hide the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Right. By the way, it looks like our attacker left us with this useful parting gift.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">From lawyer to spelunker... How do I always get myself into these situations...? We're never going to make it out alive, I hope you know.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't tell me you're scared, son. We're just getting started. The greatest treasures are only ever found at the point of a blade, or the edge of a cliff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, sure... If I'd known I'd wind up at the bottom of some dark, damp cave... ...I would've never taken your request, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Save your breath, Apollo. Just keep putting one foot ahead of the other.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There'd really better be a way out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We'll find one before you know it. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*huff* *puff*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... This cave goes deeper than I thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, don't tell me there really is no way out...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Where there's a will, there's a way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ever the optimist, aren't you... <thought>Maybe we should cut our losses while we still can...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I seriously think we're going to get completely turned around if we go any further, Dhurke. I mean, we don't even know if there's a way out up ahead.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">But we DO know we can't climb up that wall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I still know the way back from here. Don't worry, son. We can always go back there any time we want.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-If you say so. <thought>Famous last words if I've ever heard some...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not taking another step, Dhurke!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Come on, now... Be reasonable...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No! I'm done, and that's final.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I remember when you used to throw tantrums like this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Well, I'm not a child anymore!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There, there! It's okay. Daddy'll buy anything you want once we get home, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I'd better quit while I still have some manhood left to salvage... But it doesn't seem like Dhurke's about to quit any time soon. Even still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Even if we were to turn back, we wouldn't make it up that wall of solid rock. So, I guess we keep going.</thought> ............*sigh* How did I get stuck wandering around in a dark cave again? It's definitely not in my job description.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Heh heh. Listen, son. Only the truly accomplished have the luxury of being so choosy. When I was just starting out, I did everything from street performing to yak milking.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And... that helped you become an accomplished attorney, how?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It didn't. But when you need to make a living, you'll take on any job just to survive. ...Say, how IS your career going, by the way?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's been a harrowing adventure so far, to say the least. My first trial really put me through the wringer. And my next case had me investigating a pair of stolen panties. And just when I was hitting my stride, this one prosecutor branded me as "Herr Forehead." Oh, and there's this other, ridiculous prosecutor who wields a samurai sword.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Sounds like you've, um... seen quite a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You're telling me.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Listen, Apollo... I'm, uh, I'm sorry I didn't contact you for so long.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............It's fine, Dhurke. What happened, happened.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Hm? Careful, the ground doesn't feel as solid here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Yikes! The cave floor's collapsing!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Argh! Not agaaaain!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHH!</line>
<line speaker="May 16??????">Hey, Apollo. Can you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Unngh.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I was shocked, too. These ruins look really old.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's not exactly something you'd expect to find in the middle of a cave system, that's for sure. Maybe the doctor hid the orb here? I mean, those look like footprints over there.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Son, I think our little adventure is about to pay dividends! Time to find that orb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I wonder what this place was for before it was... well, ruins.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm guessing it was a place for spirit mediums to perform their rites. But earthquakes and the changing landscape eventually buried it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you're right, that would mean that it hasn't been used in ages.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's a plastic bottle doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There's seaweed stuck to it, which means it probably came from the ocean. Hmm... It's possible this cavern is connected to the sea somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Driftwood? How'd that get in here?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">By drifting on in, I'd assume. The only question is, from where?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that's the hole we fell through. Doesn't look like we'll be going back that way. We're lucky we survived the fall from way up there.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Indeed. If that hole hadn't been above the lake, we'd be history. You passed out the moment you hit the water.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, well, water's not really my thing.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hmm, this cavern is solid rock all around. Looks like we either go back through that hole...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. Why am I always between a rock and a hard place?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's a big stone altar. One false move, and some god might come and smite us.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, come on. It's not all doom and gloom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I dare you to look at our surroundings and say that again, Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! You've got me there, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"> <thought>Dear gods, please smite me now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This lake looks really deep. I can't even see the bottom.  <thought>A bottomless lake in the depths of a mountain cave system. My blood runs cold at the thought of falling in there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The water... It's salty. This lake may very well lead to the ocean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Didn't Pearl mention something about the ocean? ...Like how it's on the other side of the mountain? Can't imagine she meant it literally.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">These have gotta be the doctor's footprints. They match the bottoms of the boots we saw in his study.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">So he made it all the way down here. Hmm... The water's washed and most of them away, but his footprints are everywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? 'Cause these are the only sets I see.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He must've been looking for something. ...Ah. Those prints... They're coming out of that lake.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, you're right. But that would mean Dr. Buff came walking out of the water.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This box looks pretty new. I'm guessing... the doctor's the one who brought it down here.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's no good. It's locked tight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's no way to open it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Doesn't look like it. There isn't even a keyhole. Which means... there must be a trick to opening it. We'll have to figure it out if we want to see what's inside.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Let's sum up what we know so far. The orb is almost definitely inside this box contraption that we can't open. As for this cave, there doesn't seem to be any way out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnrgh... We're THIS close to the orb...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Aww, come now, son. Don't be like that. It's just a bit of bad luck. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A bit? Murphy called. He wants his law back.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What doesn't kill you, makes you stronger, right? Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How can he laugh at a time like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We're stuck here for now, so we might as well try to open this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's see what we're dealing with.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a big button here. ...Huh. Nothing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This thing is covered with pictures. And, hey! Each section also rotates!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Take a look at this, son. See the picture of a dragon battling a tiger? And this green and purple one... ...is of a Khura'inese butterfly and a mitamah.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I wonder if they're clues for figuring out how to open this box.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Let's see... There's the dragon and tiger fight, a Khura'inese butterfly with a mitamah...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...And a number of pictures, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke, I was thinking... Maybe we should check the evidence we've collected so far. I think we have something that just might help us open it.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You read my mind, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think this will help us open the puzzle box.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? <thought>Guess that wasn't it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There's a dragon and tiger fighting, and a Khura'inese butterfly with a mitamah. We've gotta have something related to those things, don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dr. Buff's research notes mention the Song of Ceremony. Maybe its lyrics and the pictures on the box correspond somehow. </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I think you're on to something, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, let's give it a shot. Each dial has six pictures and there are four dials in all. The box should open once the pictures are arranged in the right order. Funky puzzle box... here comes Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It won't open.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Maybe the pictures aren't in the right order. The case should open if the pictures are arranged properly, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. I should carefully consider which part of the song corresponds to which picture.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It opened! So this is the Founder's Orb...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">We did it, son! The orb is finally ours!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">At last, the Founder's Orb is ours! And it's all thanks to you, son! Well done! Then again, I'd expect nothing less from my boy!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, uh, ha ha. It's no big deal.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't sell yourself short! You may think it's nothing, but your insights and reasoning led us here. And I'd say that's truly impressive!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know about that, ha ha ha.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">All those battles you fought in the courtroom have shaped you into the man you are today. And I couldn't be prouder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...W-Will you cut it out, already? <thought>...Before I turn into a sun-ripened tomato.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">With this orb, I can finally deliver a fatal blow to the Ga'ran regime. Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, how exactly do you plan on using it? You're not going to try to become a spirit medium, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't be ridiculous. I don't need supernatural powers like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, are you going to use it as a bargaining chip with Queen Ga'ran? Like demanding she abolishes the Defense Culpability Act?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, the thought had crossed my mind, but the main thing is returning this to the Kingdom of Khura'in. After all, as a sacred relic of Khura'inism, that is where it belongs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? That's all you wanted to do?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Mm-hm. Because my true objective has always been to find out who asked Dr. Buff to study it and why.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm not sure I follow.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The official story is that the orb was stolen from the Tehm'pul Temple treasure room.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I heard about that on the news. They also said your group was behind the theft.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's not good... We're probably on an international most-wanted list now. ...Let me ask you something, Apollo: Who do YOU think really stole the orb?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm, I really haven't a clue.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, I think it was one of the royals.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? Someone from the royal family?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yeah, and I've got a pretty good idea which one it was.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He knows who it is?</thought> Care to share your hunch?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">All I'll say at this point is this: Security is pretty tight, but the royals have unfettered access to the treasure room. Plus, they seem to be turning a blind eye to the orb's loss.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But why would a member of the royal family do that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...That, I haven't figured out yet. But whatever the reason, it can't be good. I mean, a Khura'inese royal stealing a national treasure of such religious significance? And then pinning the crime on us, the Defiant Dragons?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds like a conspiracy or something.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I agree. And if the truth were to come to light, it would be a scandal of epic proportions. To allow a foreign national to study a treasure so sacred that it's off limits to the public... It would be seen as an utter sacrilege to those who truly revere the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So if this were to go public, support for the Ga'ran regime would weaken.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">But that's not all. This is just a hunch, but I believe there's something even bigger here. Something that would explain why the orb was being studied in the first place. Something that would shake the Kingdom of Khura'in to its very core. And I'm going to find out what.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>.........He's probably right. His intuition is usually spot on.</thought> Dhurke, why are you so bent on revolution, anyway? Is it to reform the legal system in Khura'in?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">There's that. But I'm  also doing this for my children... I want to save Nahyuta.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...This is for your ears only. It's the other reason why this revolution needs to succeed.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta... I never thought that our reunion would take place in a courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, so you've run into each other already.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but it was like he was a different person. He used to be such a kind, cheerful kid -- always smiling and stuff. But now... He tried to convict Trucy for a crime she didn't even commit. Plus, he kept telling me I had a "putrid mind" and to "let it go, and move on."</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Has it really gotten that bad? It must be Ga'ran's influence. He wasn't like that when he first stepped into the courtroom. Back then, he still had a keen sense of justice.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's what he swore to do... but that was also five years ago. He'd been the shining star of the Defiant Dragons, and our greatest hope.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, Nahyuta was a Dragon?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He was. But these days, he's more like Ga'ran's lapdog.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Talk about a complete about-face. Why would he do that?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Something must have happened to him. Something that sparked a radical change. Still... I don't think he truly believes in the new path he's taken. It's not conviction that fills his heart; it's resignation and despair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...The only thing I know for sure is... Nahyuta is suffering... and he is suffering in silence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nahyuta... is suffering...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. He knows the rightful state of Khura'in's legal system, but something forces him to bend to Ga'ran's will, and it's tearing him apart.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But it's been five years. Do you really think he even still wants to reform the legal system?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...As long as he carries what I've taught him in his heart, I do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">"A dragon never yields." ...That's what you always told us.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That I did. It's a belief I've held since back when I was lawyer. The dragon stands at the pinnacle of the natural world. Nothing and no one can bend its will.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's why we lawyers must pursue the truth like an unyielding dragon, right? We must fight for truth to the bitter end, no matter what it takes... <thought>Dhurke and Mr. Wright... they have that much in common.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's why I've held onto this badge, even though there are no more lawyers in Khura'in. I believe that one day, our legal system will return to its former glory. And this badge here is a testament to that belief.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hmm... I wonder if Nahyuta still believes in what you taught us?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">He does. That much I'm sure of.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I know that belief is etched deep in his heart. ...I'd bet my life on it. After all, he is my flesh and blood!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">............ <thought>This unshakable faith and confidence... It's what draws people to him, whether they like it or not. ...Even people like me.</thought> You know, I remember back when we were kids, Nahyuta used to say with great pride, "I have the blood of the dragon within me."</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, and that's why I want to free him. Free him from the poisonous clutches of the Ga'ran regime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So that's your other reason for starting a revolution...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. I need to smack some sense into that boy of mine. I mean, what else are fathers for? Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I... I wouldn't know.)</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That was one fancy puzzle box.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The fact that he chose to use such an elaborate box makes me think that Dr. Buff must've had a rather playful side to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I can almost imagine him saying, "Go ahead. Open it if you can."</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">The orb is ours at last!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm just glad we were able to make what you said in your broadcast a reality.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Me, too. I didn't want to admit it before, but I was starting to have second thoughts about making such a big, bold move. I kept thinking, "What would happen if we failed to get the orb?"</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Just another example of how a bluff can be the starting point in the quest for the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And what a hard-won truth it was. But I couldn't have done it without you, son.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Now that we have the orb, on to the next problem -- getting out of here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we're not going back the way we came. That's for sure. That hole we fell through is way too high to climb back up to. </line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Actually, I have an idea. That lake water tastes salty, which means it must connect to the ocean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">W-Wait a second. You're not suggesting we SWIM our way out of here...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">That's exactly what I'm suggesting.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But we have no idea how deep that lake goes. It's pitch black down there.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Not a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How is that not a problem? I mean, how do you even know if there's really a passage to the ocean?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Well, one of us has to try, and I'm the better swimmer. Time's a wastin'! I'll be back before you know it, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke! ... He's gone. I sure hope he knows what he's doing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>It's been twenty minutes. I hope he's okay.</thought> What's going on? Uh-oh. Th-The water...! It's rising! And fast! Aaaaaaaaaaaaah! <thought>N-Need... air...</thought> *cough* *sputter* *cough* *cough* ...Ahhh! I don't know how to swim! If I don't grab onto something that floats...! .................. *cough* *sputter* *cough* *cough* ...This is bad! I-I better think of something -- quick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hey, maybe I can use this like an oxygen tank! ...Wait what am I thinking?! I need to stay calm and be more rational about this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've got it! As long as I hold onto this, I should be able to stay afloat!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This is not good. The water's almost up to the top of the altar. It won't be long before it reaches the roof of the cave.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The puzzle box is still at the base of the altar. It must've been designed to stay put, even at high tide. Wait, that's it! Dr. Buff must've gotten in here from some ocean-side entrance at low tide. That's why his footprints were leading OUT of the lake. So it really DOES connect to the ocean. Not that that helps. I'd drown before I made it out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nnrrgh... It's no use! The hole's still too high up! I'll have to find another way -- and quick -- before I drown!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The water won't stop rising! Aaaah! I-I'm getting swept away! Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhh! Please...! STOPPPP!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If only that bottle were a little bigger, it'd store that much more air... No, it wouldn't make that much of a difference... I need to stop with these harebrained ideas, and come up with a real way to escape!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The water's almost to the top now. At this rate, I'll run out of breathing room! I'm a goner if I don't find a way out quick!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The water's just high enough for me to reach the hole! I'm saved! All I have to do is go back the way we came! The water might even lift me all the way back up, over that wall of rock! Here goes!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Huh? The hole! It's full of rubble. The tunnel collapsing above must've filled it in after we fell through it. Nngh... This... This can't be happening! No, I can't give up now. I refuse to die here! Th-The water...! I can't--! *cough* *sputter* I can't... I can't... breathe... .................. <thought>Is this... the end?</thought> .................. <thought>Dhurke... I wonder if he made it out.</thought> .................. <thought>So this is what it feels like to drown. I would've eaten that sushi if I'd known it would be my last meal. ... I feel like I've been through this before. ...Ah, now I remember. It was back when all three of us were living in that shack in the mountains. Nahyuta and I were playing by the riverside when we got swept up in the rapids.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAHHH!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">AAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I thought we were goners, but then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nahyuta! Apollo! Hold on! I'm coming!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...*sniffle*...*sniffle*...*sniffle*... Wahhhhh!!!</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">Waaahhhh!!!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! That was a close one! Thought I'd lost you two!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I'm sorry, Dhuuuuuuurke!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">All right, that's enough now. Didn't I teach you that boys don't cry?</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">...Thank you, Father.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sniffle* *hiccup* *hiccup*</line>
<line speaker="Nahyuta">You... You could've been killed... But you risked your life... to save us... Why...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">What a silly question. What father wouldn't risk his life to save his own children? Nahyuta, Apollo... Don't you ever hesitate to call when you need me. Understand?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Hey Dhurke? This isn't forever, right? You'll bring me back from America someday, right?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Of course... I'll come pick you up as soon as things settle down here. Promise.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay! You promised!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. I waited and waited. For the day you'd come and take me home. But you never came. That's why I tried to forget about you and my life back in Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="???">A... ...lo... A... pol... lo...! Apollo! Can you hear me?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*cough* *sputter* *cough* .........D-Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Still can't swim, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You... You came back? But why?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I said I'd come for you, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... But you can't hold me and swim...! We're both going to...!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Stop talking. You'll bite your tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Whoa whoa whoa! <thought>We're being pulled under! What's going on?! Why is this happeniiiiing?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*cough* ...Uuuuugh. Wh-Where...?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ahh, you finally came to, son.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Get your fill of seawater? Good thing your name's not Neptune, huh! Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">D-Dhurke...</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Har har har har har har! You're telling me! Check it out, snot's coming out of his nose!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">What a miraculous escape! Not even some of the escape-artist greats could pull that off!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Wh-What on earth happened?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sorry it took me so long, son. I made it to the ocean, but I figured you still couldn't swim. So I found a local fisherman and had him take us out near the undersea cavern. He tied a rope to me, and I came and grabbed you. Then he yanked me back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so that's what pulled us under with such force.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Don't forget about me! I assisted in your escape act, too, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I've helped compatriots escape from all sorts of places -- mountain jails, island prisons... But an undersea cavern? Now that was a first!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Dhurke... He risked his life for me.</thought> .........Dhurke. I'm only alive because of you. ...Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Oh, uh... Y-You're welcome. I, uh... just did what any father would do for his son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>.........He saved my life yet again.</thought> *growl* ...Um...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! I guess seawater doesn't make for much of a meal!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">It's 'cause Polly didn't have any sushi!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, yeah. I haven't eaten anything since this morning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">...Oh, that's right! Hey, AJ! Dhurke had me buy this for ya.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Thought you might be hungry. Ready to have some this time around?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Yeah. Thanks! *chomp* *nom nom nom* Oh wow, this is delicious!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! Glad you approve! I'd better get some before you eat them all! *chomp* *chew chew chew*</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just like old times. Dhurke used to slice up the fish he caught, and we'd all eat fresh sashimi together. He used to talk about all the vitamins and minerals packed in the raw fish.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">*chomp* *munch munch munch* Hey, by the way! Lemme see that orb, AJ!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Hoa, so that's what it looks like!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">You found the legendary treasure! Nice work, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Thanks. ...Guess you could say, mission accomplished!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">With the orb, our revolution can take a big step forward. Let's celebrate the eve of our revolution! We'll all get dressed up and feast till dawn!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Yeah! Now you're talkin'! Time to party!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>After all that? I just want to go to bed. Sure wish Nahyuta was here. Maybe one day, we'll enjoy times like these together again. ...The revolution. If it can bring back those happy days, you can sign me up for--</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry to interrupt your little party, but I'm here for my crystal.</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Right, left, right, left, HALT!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! It's him again!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. Well done. Then again, I always knew you could do it. After all, we politicians must be excellent judges of character. Still, I'm impressed you both made it out of there alive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...W-Wait a second. YOU'RE the one who shoved us into that pit?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It sounds so bad when you say it like that. All I did was give you a little nudge in the right direction.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...So... it was you... ............................................................... You no good, son of a--!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...EEP! D-Don't look at me like that! The Crystal of Ami Fey is mine! Now, hand it over!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Over my dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">EEK! Detective! Help!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yeah yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema? What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">He filed a police report. He claims you're trying to steal his family heirloom.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Th-That's him! The one with the long hair! Arrest him this instant! He's the thief that made off with the Atishon family's most precious heirloom!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, I suppose I should ask you to come in for questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Down at the police station? I... think I'll pass. After all, Mr. Atishon seems bent on having me arrested on theft charges.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This is not good! If Dhurke gets arrested, he'll be sent back to Khura'in to face execution!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Sorry, but now that I know you have the crystal, or orb as you call it, I must insist. Will you please come with me, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Is that so? Can you prove it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Of course. This should sufficiently prove that the orb now belongs to Dhurke.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Umm... All this proves is you're completely our of your mind.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oops... <thought>I guess that wasn't it.</thought> But the doctor definitely transferred it over to us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at this agreement.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What do we have here? Let's see... "I agree to hand over the Founder's Orb to the Defiant Dragons if I will come to no harm." Hmm... It appears to be a perfectly legal agreement.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Not so fast! That's not the Founder's Orb! It's the Crystal of Ami Fey, which means their agreement is null and void!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Hmm, this is going nowhere fast.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You can say that again.</line>
<line speaker="???">Then it will just have to go to trial. Right, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-M-Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What's with you two? You look like you just saw a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Oh yeah. Ema mentioned she had seen him around.</thought> ...Um  what're you doing in Kurain Village, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atishon has retained me as his lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you're his... lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, why are you serving as Mr. Atishon's lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Because he hired me. He needed my help in getting a family heirloom back from Dr. Buff. And it seems he correctly foresaw that something like this might happen.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It's because those shifty insurgents were harassing poor Dr. Buff. So I knew I might need a lawyer if things went south. I figured with a celebrated lawyer like Phoenix Wright, I couldn't go wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Is this what you came back from Khura'in for, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It was just good timing. My work over there just happened to wrap up, so here I am. Plus... Mr. Atishon is a very important client.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>They know each other? But I've never heard Mr. Wright mention his name before.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright, are you sure this is Mr. Atishon's family heirloom?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That's my client's assertion. He says it's the Crystal of Ami Fey. Apparently, it's the crystal she once used when channeling spirits.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Who's Ami Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She brought Khura'inese channeling to Japan, and her descendants brought it here. Her true origins are still rather murky, but what's clear is she is the founder of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so she's like the one they call the founder in Khura'in -- the Holy Mother.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'd think you would have more pressing things to ask me about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yeah... <thought>I'd better ask what I can while I can.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Apollo, I don't plan to betray my client's confidence. I may not know all the facts yet, but I do know we won't be handing the crystal over to you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Are you saying...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.................. I'm really sorry it's come to this, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright? I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Let me spell it out then. If you continue to claim that the crystal belongs to your client, then I will be seeing you in court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Wh-What's gotten into you, Daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nothing. This is strictly business.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. Two lawyers from the same firm facing off? What are the odds! Lucky for me, I believe I have the "right" man for the job! What ever are you going to do? Remember, he IS your boss.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ngrrrgh... <thought>How did it come to this?!</thought> M-Mr. Wright! Please! Don't do this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo, there's no point arguing about it here when it's now clear we're headed to court. That's where we'll find out who the crystal really belongs to.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't believe it. Am I really going to face Mr. Wright in court?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy! Apollo! No! We can't have our agency's talent competing against each other!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's too late, Trucy. The die has been cast. We each have to fight for our clients' best interests.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, what's it going to be, Apollo. Are we going to have to take this to trial?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I have to battle Mr. Wright in court? THE legendary Phoenix Wright? No matter how many trials of his I've watched, no matter how dire the situation, he's always pulled out a win in the end. Can I do it? Can I really take on the man whose footsteps I've been following in...? I owe it to Dhurke to at least try. I... What should I do?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I can't do this. I mean, how can I go up against a man like him? I couldn't possibly win! ...But do I really want to give up without a fight? If I do, I'll be forever walking in his shadow! Plus, I'd be letting Dhurke down! And I can't let that happen!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's no turning back now.</thought> If it's a trial you want, Mr. Wright, I'm more than happy to oblige! I'm ready to fight for my client even if it means facing off against you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.................................... .................. ...All right. I won't be pulling any punches, either, Apollo. The kid gloves are officially off. May the best attorney win.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You got it!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Whoa whoa whoa! First Daddy, now you! Polly! You're not seriously...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Sorry, Trucy. But I have to do this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..................Apollo... All right, then, I'd better go prepare for tomorrow. See you in court.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Daddy, no! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">A Fine mess I've gotten you into, son. I mean, of all the lawyers we could've faced, it had to be him? He's practically a celebrity in Khura'in now. They're calling him the Fighting Phoenix.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I-I'll be fine! <thought>After all, I've come a long way, too! Who knows? I could even end up winning. There's always a chance...... right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">You know, this may be a blessing in disguise. If the trial proves what we found is indeed the Founder's Orb, then whoever asked Dr. Buff to study it may be revealed, too. This is our chance to finally pull them out of the shadows!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...The first step of your revolution, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes. The revolution to restore Khura'in to its former glory, and save Nahyuta's soul!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dhurke... I swear to fight as hard as I can in court to make that a reality. We're going to win this one. You'll see.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I know you can do it... son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>It doesn't matter that I'll be going up against Mr. Wright. I have to win this for Dhurke and for Nahyuta. His salvation, along with all of Khura'in, depends on it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nothing particularly interesting here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We've already searched here, but it never hurts to take another look around.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, this is harder than I imagined. I thought all we had to do was arrange the pictures according to the song.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It's times like these you have to think outside the puzzle-box. Sometimes the truth can only be found when you look at things from a different angle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A different angle? <thought>Come to think of it, one of the pictures from the song is missing. Does this mean the pictures don't line up exactly one-to-one?</thought></line>
</xml>