
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Reclaimed</title>
<line speaker="Athena">Good morning, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good morning. Chipper as ever this morning, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm just thankful we actually get to have a trial for Orla. As a matter of fact, I just ran a few laps around the courthouse to get extra pumped!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And I just splashed my face with some water to get the sleep out of my eyes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, I also cued the Swashbuckler video so we can watch it any time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. It just might help our case. By the way, you have some serious dark circles. Did you stay up late watching this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! M-Me? No, I, uh, just woke up early, that's all. ...Guess I need to cover them up. I get ragged on enough as it is by Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Speaking of being pumped, I'm pretty fired up for this trial, too. It's been a while.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee. That explains why your hair is spikier than usual. I mean, look at it! It's all super pokey and prickly and stuff. It's amazing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...That was a compliment... right?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Pearl">Good luck, Mr. Nick! I'll be cheering you on from the gallery.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Pearls. It's been so long, I'm actually a little nervous.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Good morning, Mr. Lawyer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh, Mr. Rimes! You came to watch the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah. Sasha is back at the aquarium with the orca... ...so I thought I'd better come here to watch for her.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, don't you worry! We're going to win for Orla! Isn't that right, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right. One unprecedented trial, coming right up!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Court is now in session for the trial of Orla Shipley.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defense is ready, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ Must we waste words on this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Prosecutor Simon Blackquill... Known as the "Twisted Samurai," he's a prosecutor who's also a convicted felon. They say he never conducts a trial without his loyal hawk Taka by his side.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Mr. Wright, it's been quite a while since I've seen you like that. The lawyer image suits you. You look younger somehow. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Your Honor. And you look as young as ever yourself. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ha ha ha. Well, I have to keep up with you folks, after all. By the way, has the defendant arrived in court yet?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Surely you jest, Your Baldness. Did you not receive the memo? The defendant, Ora Shipley, is an orca at Shipshape Aquarium. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-An orcaaaaaaaaaaaaa?! Arrangements for this trial were made only yesterday, so I didn't have time to review. But an orca as a defendant? It's patently absurd!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph......... Direct your comments to the defense. He's the absurd fellow who insisted on defending the orca in court in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Absurd or not, I will carry out my duty to defend my client. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your duty to defend your "crying ant"? Don't you mean your "crying orca," Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If we are to proceed, we must treat the orca as we would any other defendant. Every soul -- be it of man or beast -- is of equal value. The question is whether that soul is painted in black or white. Take Taka for example. He is as human in spirit as you or I. </line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The real question is, am I in for more pain... as always?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Orca or not, I suppose the defendant is still a defendant. And I vow to render my verdict fairly and impartially! *ahem* Now then, Prosecutor Blackquill, your opening statement, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I suppose I can hardly leave it to someone who knew nothing of the defendant... Very well. Listen carefully. The orca murdered the owner of Shipshape Aquarium in the aquarium's orca pool. The orca apparently toyed with the victim mercilessly as he died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A sadistic orca... What a chilling thought. And where exactly is this defendant now?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Inside this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-A cell phone, Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Time marches on, Your Baldness -- with or without us. I borrowed this TV phone from the aquarium, which will allow us to interact with the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A "TV phone"? Very well. The court accepts it into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We will be able to view the defendant in question on this large monitor. Fool Bright, prepare for transmission.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! You've got it, Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We will proceed with the defendant on telecast.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So that is the orca that stands accused, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Aw. She's waving her flipper at us. Maybe she's cheering us on?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla, wish Phoenix and Athena luck!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, it's quite cute, isn't it? And this adorable creature is suspected of killing a man...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Orla's really pouring on the charm, huh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">She is far from "cute." She is a violent, reckless animal. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">That's right! The name's Bobby Fulbright, and I'll take over the explaining from here. Now, if I could direct your attention to this diagram of the crime scene. Following the report of an orca attack, we the police raced on over to Shipshape Aquarium. There, we found a guest who says she saw the orca and the victim from the visitor's corridor. As the witness was watching, the orca suddenly went crazy and attacked the victim. The orca was the only one there; therefore, no one else could have committed the crime. It's not quite finished, but I have a portion of the autopsy report here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't imagine the terror of being attacked underwater by such a large creature...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But attack it did. Prepare yourself for the grisly details, Your Baldness. The prosecution moves to introduce our witness. ...Fool Bright.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">You got it, Prosecutor Blackquill! In justice we trust! One brave lady whose fine sense of justice compelled her to speak, coming right up!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">How dare you make me wait? Don't you know I'm a busy woman?! I could have written an entire book for all the time I spent in that lobby!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... Prosecutor Blackquill?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Well?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I am Norma DePlume, and I'm a nonfiction writer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Am I the only one who isn't telepathic here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like she can read into people's words just as well as I can read into people's hearts.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not everything needs to be a competition, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What?! Norma DePlume?! The great nonfiction writer, Ms. Norma DePlume herself?! I've read all of your works and enjoyed them immensely. Your million seller, "The Great Grief of the Great Thief," is one of my favorites.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh, are you a fan, Your Honor? I could give you my autograph, if you'd like.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wait a second... I could swear you looked much different in the photos in your book......</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, I use ones from ten years ago in my books so that paparazzi won't harass me.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">The judge seems to be shocked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The visual disconnect must really be doing a number on His Honor's head...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Could we get started, please? If I find you to be lacking as a judge... ...you will see your debut in my books!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Such harsh comments...! You really MUST be the real Norma DePlume.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Who knew Ms. DePlume was so famous?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Enough jabbering. Tell the court what you saw, and keep it brief.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I would thank you to not order me around. I am perfectly willing to tell everyone what I witnessed. It was the moment of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well, then. Please proceed with your testimony. </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I went to Shipshape Aquarium to see the killer whale.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The adorable defendant really did all that?! Hmm... It must be much more vicious than it looks...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, deliver your judgment so I may carry out the sentence. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Must you drag this out with your tomfoolery?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">A fellow inmate told me just this morning... "If you want something signed, all you need is the document and a witness."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Let me guess. They were convicted for contract fraud, right?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ All we need in this case is the evidence and a witness to convict. It's as simple as that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I guessed right.</thought> Sorry, but as Ms. Cykes said... ...the defense has every right to cross-examine. Isn't that correct, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, of course. You may proceed with your cross-examination, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">.........I shall relish the sight of you thrashing around in vain.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I went to Shipshape Aquarium to see the killer whale.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Well, it IS the featured attraction of the aquarium, after all. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Why waste energy on such tripe? There is but one attraction in Shipshape Aquarium that is worth anyone's time... ...and that is the penguins. Isn't that right, Taka, my friend?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All righty then. I guess Prosecutor Blackquill is for the birds.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess I should jot that down. Note to self: Prosecutor Blackquill is on Team Rifle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so you went to see the orca in its tank?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">As I was watching the killer whale from the visitor's corridor, it suddenly went crazy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes. It took a look at me, and then, all at once, it started going berserk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Did you do anything to make her angry?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I did nothing more than simply glare at it from the visitor's corridor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She glared at Orla?</thought> And that's what caused her to go berserk?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">In any case, the killer whale began behaving wildly in front of my very eyes. And then...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I saw the killer whale bite the victim to death with its huge mouth and deadly teeth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That is exactly what I'm saying! Oh, it was simply dreadful! It was as frightening as losing one's manuscript just before a deadline!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I suppose for a writer, that would be pretty terrifying...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I witnessed the killer whale's horrific act, and I knew I had to do something, so...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Attempting to remain calm, I reported the incident to the police immediately.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I was afraid if I told aquarium staff, they might try to cover it up. Of course, I immediately told aquarium security after my call to the police. I believe I deserve praise for my swift decision-making skills under pressure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ms. DePlume is the most assertive witness I've ever seen.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We'd better do our best to look like big-shot lawyers if we want to match her intensity!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume, I praise your swift decision-making skills under pressure!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was more "kiss up" than "big shot"...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I suppose it was unrealistic to expect "big shot" from Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. How fitting for a small fry to praise a big shot.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>How about cutting this small fry some slack, you big meanies?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The important thing here is, did she really see the "moment of the murder"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're raring to go, aren't you, Mr. Wright? I see it in your eyes... and in your heart!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ha ha ha. I guess I really am a lawyer at heart.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It would seem that you are mistaken, Ms. DePlume.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I beg your pardon?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The autopsy report does indeed say, "Death thought to be result of orca attack"... ...but the actual cause of death is "contusion from head trauma," not "being bitten"!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">What?! B-But...! But... I'm sure the victim was bitten!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe that can be true. The security footage doesn't show anything of the kind.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Well, what did you expect when he wouldn't play nice and share?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But, unfortunately for you... ...the footage you saw was only one small part.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yesterday, after I decided to take this case to trial, I re-reviewed all of the evidence. Taka, the evidence I gave to you for safekeeping.</line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Guess that hawk is higher up on the pecking order than Fulbright in Blackquill's book.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Let's view the footage. Wh-What's this?! The orca is biting the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-No waaaaaay!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to say that this appears to be very damning evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No... I can't believe Orla really bit him!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">And there is more... Look at this. This photograph was taken while the body was being examined.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... There seems to be a strange bruise on the victim's right wrist.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes! They do appear to suggest that she did, in fact, bite the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I told you so! And then the killer whale swam up toward the surface with the victim in its mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then what explanation is there for what the witness saw?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-My goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Nrgh...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">M-Mr. Wright! The hearts of the people in the gallery are suddenly filled with fear -- fear of Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the defendant bit the victim after she had killed him... But if that's the case, then we must still figure out how the defendant killed the victim. Prosecutor Blackquill, do you have a sound theory to give to this court?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">But Orla is black AND white! ...Her body, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Athena, please try not to provoke Prosecutor Blackquill.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The witness also observed the actual moment of the murder. Think back, Word Mistress. Think back to what you observed before the orca bit the victim.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...Ah, I see what you're driving at. So that was the true moment of the murder, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Now, explain it in a way that even these simpletons can understand.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">There you go again, ordering me around! Stop that this instant! But whatever... I don't mind telling my story. I saw the killer whale before it toyed with the body as well. I saw it the moment it killed the victim by head-butting him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-Orla killed the victim by head-butting him?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That's right. It rammed the victim over and over again.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Recall that the autopsy report stated that there were bruises all over his body. Recall as well, how persistent the defendant can be when she's attacking her prey.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">And we all just saw the killer whale head-butting the victim in the footage, don't forget.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... That footage backs up Ms. DePlume's testimony... But there's also something very important it does NOT show...!</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Now do you see what a menace this killer whale is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh! ...Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I want to look away... but I can't...</thought>. Even if it was the victim, you couldn't have seen him from where you were, could you?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">............What? O-Oh. Well... I suppose not...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume, did you actually witness the victim getting head-butted by the defendant?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Ah, let's see... Oh, I remember now! As I recall, a rock in the shape of a skull was obstructing my view.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So are you admitting that you couldn't see the victim?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes... Yes, I suppose I am. However! Immediately after the head-butting, the victim came floating up! He came up from behind the skull-shaped rock, and his body was all limp. What else could I think except that the killer whale was head-butting the victim?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">H-How dare you speak so rudely to me?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">There's no need for hysterics. Clear your mind and recall how you reached your conclusion. Though you couldn't see what the orca was attacking, you didn't need to, did you? Because you knew she was behaving exactly as she had only one year prior.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>One year ago...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That's right! Yes, that's it! That's how I knew the killer whale was head-butting the victim! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but could someone explain exactly what happened a year ago?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you must know, a very similar incident occurred only last year, in which... ...the defendant murdered her trainer. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-Whaaaaaaat?! The orca murdered her trainer, you say?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Is this really true?! <thought>This is not looking good for us!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It's all in this book. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">That book... "The Killer Killer Whale"...! That's Ms. DePlume's latest work! I was just thinking of picking that up.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Last year, the defendant killed her trainer in the middle of a show. The orca head-butted and bit the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The same thing she's accused of in this case!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Woman">That orca killed two people?!</line>
<line speaker="Man">That thing is a menace! Guilty! Guilty, I say!</line>
<line speaker="Man">I never want to go to the beach again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We were doing so well, but now... Now everyone in the room has a bad impression of Orla. I don't want to think she did it... ...but it's hard to keep on believing in somebody who can't even tell me her side...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Phoenix! Athena! You gotta believe in Orla! There's no way she killed anybody! You gotta save her! Please, I'm begging you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sasha... <thought>What am I doing, doubting my client like this? This is the time to be strong!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I believe in Orla! And I'm ready to fight for our clients! I'll take everybody in this courtroom on if I have to!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't you worry, Sasha. We won't give up on Orla. We'll defend her to the very end!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Thank you! Thank you, both of you!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fweet, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We are Orla's lawyers. Who else but us can save her?! We can't give up on her now!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... For an instant there, you were afraid of the orca, weren't you, Wright-dono. When you saw the photograph of the victim from a year ago, you turned paler than me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! <thought>He saw right through me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It's obvious you have neither the guts nor the determination to defend the orca.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true that Orla can't speak, and I don't know her thoughts... ...but there's a certain someone who believes in Orla with all her heart. I respect the trust she has in Orla, so I'm willing to believe in Orla, too.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. And what do you know about orcas? Nothing, that's what. So, allow me to fill you in. Do you have any idea why orcas are also called "killer whales"? Because they are cunning and merciless predators that hunt and kill even true whales.</line>
<line speaker="Judges">So "killer whales" really are "killers"! What terrifying creatures indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I can't bear to hear any more of such rubbish as "trusting a killer." Can you, Your Baldness?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No matter what you say, I will continue to believe. I don't give up that easily, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Dullard. You don't know when to give up, do you? Very well. I shall give you a chance to prove just how determined you are. Witness, spare no quarter and lay the full truth on them.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Oh ho ho! But of course! That is what I do, after all. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill, what will you have the witness testify about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I shall have her testify about what she saw, and what she heard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What she heard...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ms. DePlume, please tell the court what you saw and what you heard. </line>
<line speaker="DePlume">The killer whale's behavior was exactly the same as a year ago. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So the orca displayed the same behavior as during the incident a year ago...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">That's right! Those weren't just simple cries. It was singing! As I approached the pool, the killer whale suddenly started singing! It kept head-butting while it sang the Swashbuckler Spectacular song! That's right. It was singing the same song it sang in the aquarium's stage show back then. It was singing while it was head-butting! Oh, it was perfectly horrible! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... I don't see a single obvious inconsistency in this testimony. It's clear I won't be able to take her apart her statements with evidence alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! Now would be a good time for me to put my skills to work! It's time to show what analytical psychology can really do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You seem pretty confident. Let me guess. You noticed a contradiction between the testimony and her emotions?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You bet I did! And once we expose it, we just might be able to crack her. No, scratch that. Make it, "we'll definitely be able to"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then let's give your knowledge of analytical psychology a try!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it, Boss! A complete analysis of Ms. DePlume's heart, coming right up!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">The killer whale's behavior was exactly the same as a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">As I approached the pool...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...the killer whale suddenly started singing.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I was calm when I saw it start to head-butt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">But when the pirate hat and victim came floating up, I let out a scream!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you see any emotions that seem odd or out of place? Pay attention to not only which emotions you see, but how strong they are, too. An emotion might suddenly get stronger, for example, or you might see it grow weaker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. Let me listen to her testimony again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume, Orla really frightened you with her head-butting, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Don't be absurd! I certainly was NOT frightened by the likes of any killer whale!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It must've been something else that scared her, then, Boss.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">However... I do remember being very afraid for some reason while it was doing that. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">It sounds like maybe you saw something we haven't discussed yet. Take your time and try to remember what it was... What did you see?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is practically turning into a counseling session.</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">............ I... saw something...? ...Oh! Aaaaaaaaaaaagh! I-I remember now!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay, good! Now, if you could please tell the court what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I saw... I saw... I saw... bright red blood! The killer whale's ramming caused the victim to bleed. There was a great cloud of blood!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Yes, that's it! That's why I was so sure! That's when I knew that killer whale had killed a person for a second time!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! That was a very compelling statement indeed. Looking at this again, there does appear to be something that could be a cloud of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So her terror was a reaction to blood, was it? That would certainly explain what happened yesterday...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this bloodstained coin.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Eeeeeeeeeeeeek! C-Cease and desist, at once! Wh-What kind of man shows a lady blood?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>She doesn't have to get so worked up...</thought></line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I was badly injured during an interview once. Ever since then, I've been terrified of blood. The very sight of it dreadfully upsets my delicate sensibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is a bad turn... If Ms. DePlume saw blood... ...then does that mean Orla really did attack the victim...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It would appear that orcas are even more vicious than I am. So, how does it feel to be thoroughly rammed by your own cross-examination, Wright-dono?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wh-What do we do now, Boss?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Argh... That testimony was not at all what I expected to hear...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait a minute... There's still some discord left in Ms. DePlume's heart. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? You mean there's more?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, but there's no telling what it is. It could be something even more damaging...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... Is there even anything left of our case to damage...? Well, whatever it is, we have to face it head-on.</thought> Athena, you believe in Orla, right? If so, there's no reason for us to shy away from the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Yeah, you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I know we can handle the truth, whatever it is, so let's delve a little deeper!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You've got it, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">The killer whale's behavior was exactly the same as a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">As I approached the pool...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">...the killer whale suddenly started singing.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">After it started head-butting, I saw that awful blood and was terrified.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">But when the pirate hat and victim came floating up, I let out a scream!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you see any emotions that seem odd or out of place? Pay attention to not only which emotions you see, but how strong they are, too. An emotion might suddenly get stronger, for example, or you might see it grow weaker.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay. Let me listen to her testimony again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Huh? Her fear appears to lessen here at this statement.</thought> Ms. DePlume, weren't you afraid when you saw the victim with blood coming out of him?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">My, that's a very good question. I was shaken after witnessing a murder, yes, but then... the blood seemed to disappear...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Disappear? And why do you suppose that was?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Simple! It was because of the pirate hat! After the killer whale put the hat on, the cloud of blood disappeared!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">How should I know?! I'm just telling you what I remember, blue boy!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait a minute... From whom was this blood that Ms. DePlume saw actually coming from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you see an injury anywhere on that individual?! And when exactly was this individual supposed to have entered the pool?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't think you're ready to play in the deep end just yet, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I-I'll be right back with some floaties, Your Honor... <thought>Hold on... "Entered the pool"...? What if this individual didn't "enter" the pool, but was already "in" the pool...? Who else was in the pool besides the victim?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Consider this. Maybe the one who was bleeding wasn't the victim.</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I beg your pardon? What kind of ridiculous nonsense is that? There was no one else in that pool beside the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I wouldn't say there was no one else. It IS an orca pool, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What?! Then where is this alleged injury on the defendant?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure. But if simply wearing the pirate hat made the blood "disappear"... ...then the blood must've been coming from somewhere on Orla's head!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca's head? What are you prattling on about now?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Please think about it again, Ms. DePlume! Think back to what you really saw!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Errr... I... That is... Th-The one who was bleeding was not the victim, but the killer whale...? Ngh... I remember now! There wasn't any blood coming from the victim after all!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We did it! Analytical psychology got us what we needed from her!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was a huge help, Athena. <thought>It was also pretty dicey for a while, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! This is a surprise! The blood the witness saw was the defendant's, not the victim's!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That is correct. And since there was no blood coming from the victim... ...there's only one thing we can conclude. That what Ms. DePlume witnessed was not the "moment of the murder," as she claims!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Meaning...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I grant that what the witness saw was not the victim's blood, but it proves nothing. After all, being rammed doesn't always result in a wound that bleeds, does it? Death from internal hemorrhaging is also a possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...! <thought>He has a point there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">If you wish to challenge me to a duel, you'll need a sharper blade than that, Wright-dono. I demand evidence that proves the witness did not see the moment of the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack! <thought>There must be something. Think, Phoenix! If I'm correct, then the victim's death occurred...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the victim was alive when Orla started her head-butting... ...then that would basically make Orla the one who killed him. But since I don't think she did it, then we must be wrong about when it took place.</thought>         </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>If the victim was already dead when Orla started her head-butting... ...then that would mean he died sometime before Ms. DePlume was watching her. The events Ms. DePlume witnessed took place at around 10:10 AM. I must have something that can tell us about what happened before 10:10 AM!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Huh? I'm not sure that's really related to what Ms. DePlume did or didn't witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............But you're not sure, right...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">No, we can be quite sure it's unrelated.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, quite.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ouch. I guess we can be...</thought>         </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We've only seen the footage from 10:09 to 10:10 AM. Which means... there's still footage going further back that we need to check!</thought> Your Honor, I request that ALL of the security footage be played for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All of the footage?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume witnessed the cloud of blood at around 10:10 AM. But I believe the victim was already dead by that time. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">So your assertion is that the murder took place before Ms. DePlume arrived?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. The security camera footage starts at 10:00 AM when the aquarium opened. And I believe there is vital evidence in the ten minutes before!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ You are quite the gambling man, Wright-dono. Are you honestly willing to risk everything on those mere ten minutes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I've bet on slimmer chances before, but when he puts it that way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh-oh. I can't back down now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, if the defense is that confident in its importance... Prosecutor Blackquill, the security footage.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Fool Bright.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Roger! I have the rest of the security footage right here!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please play it for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Please, PLEASE have something for me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">This is what it looked like at 10:10 AM. The witness can be seen here. All right. I'll just back the footage up to the beginning now!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It appears Ms. DePlume hasn't arrived yet at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now to see if I can find something from before this point in time!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">............</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............ Is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Yep! That's all the footage there is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, Mr. Wright? Did you see what you were looking for?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-We got nothin'...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ Well, Wright-dono? Those were the ten minutes you placed your bet on. Did you see anything of significance?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Did I see anything important? I'd better think about this carefully...</thought> In the footage, we see...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is the important thing the footage shows!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Different things are important to different people. "Importance" is a subjective thing!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, just as my decision to assign a penalty is a "subjective thing."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk. <thought>Wait a minute... What if something that SHOULD be in the footage isn't there...?</thought> P-Please wait, Your Honor! Um... That footage...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We can see nothing of importance in that footage.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Just as I thought. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Ha ha ha! You're right about that! That section was completely meaningless! It doesn't show a thing. That's why I didn't submit it as evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Huh? What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In this ten minutes of footage, something important that SHOULD be there isn't there! Detective Fulbright, this footage should have been submitted as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">What? Are you questioning the way I carry out my duty to justice?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Explain yourself, please! What is this important thing that you say should be in the footage, but isn't?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There is no problem, which is exactly why it is a problem, right?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While I admire your enthusiasm, please don't think you can wing it on enthusiasm alone. I would further like to suggest that your attitude is a problem, Mr. Wright. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...My apologies, Your Honor. <thought>If the victim was alive, there's something we should see in the footage...</thought> I still content that there is something important that is not in this footage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">If that is your contention, please back it up with evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The important thing we should see in the footage is the victim himself, Jack Shipley. I don't know about you, but I didn't see him get in the pool in that footage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Aaaaagh! That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If the victim is not shown entering the pool in this footage... ...it means that he must have been there by the skull rock during those ten minutes. But no human being can hold their breath underwater for that long. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">W-Wait a minute... Are you saying...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When the security camera started up at 10 AM, the victim was already dead!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Order! Order in the court! If that's the case, then when was the victim murdered?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't know, Your Honor, but we now know it had to have been sometime before 10 AM. Therefore, this footage can no longer be called decisive evidence against my client!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. But there is no one else who could have killed the victim. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not necessarily. The defense believes that the true culprit may have been human. And we have evidence to back up our theory as well!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you, now? I would be very interested in seeing this evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The defense's trump card -- that thing we found during our investigation yesterday... I wouldn't go so far as to call it "decisive," but... ...now's the time to play it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. Please submit your evidence. What evidence shows that the crime may have been committed by a human?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What are you doing?! That's not the right piece at all, Boss!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's what I was just thinking myself, judging by the judge's expression...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! You will refrain from presenting evidence you're not sure about just to feel me out!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... I must still be rusty, but this time, I'll present our real trump card!</thought>        </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Let's try again, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? A coin...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, a fake coin used in the aquarium's pirate show. We found it beside the pool. This coin is quite possibly the real murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This tiny little coin... is the murder weapon? Mr. Wright! If this is another one of your bluffs...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. As they say, the bolder the presentation, the less confident the solicitor. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This is no bluff, and this isn't the only coin. There are 300 of these coins all together, weighing a total of about seven pounds. This one just happens to have blood on it. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Did you have the blood analyzed to see whose it is?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not yet... ...but there were coins scattered all around the body, and the victim had a head wound. Taking these things into account, I believe it has to be the victim's blood. So, to put it together, we have about seven pounds of coins by the side of the pool... ...one of them with a bloodstain on it. I think the answer is pretty clear here. Your Honor! The defense proposes that the victim was killed beside the pool! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">The side of the pool?! But if the murder took place there, it would be difficult to say the orca did it...</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I realize you are trying to defend your client, but that theory is preposterous! How could 300 coins possibly be made to hit someone all at once?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It'd be pretty easy if they were in a bag or something of that nature.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And so where is this bag the coins were in?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unfortunately, Your Honor, we recovered nothing of the sort from the scene. It's possible the culprit took it with them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They took it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true culprit used the coins as a blunt instrument to commit murder. They then threw the body into the pool before the security cameras started up. And then they left, taking the bag the coins were in with them. They got rid of the evidence that points to a human culprit to pin the blame on Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was brilliant, Mr. Wright! You found a way to introduce the possibility of a human perpetrator!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, somehow... <thought>Let's hope my luck holds out... Hmm... I wonder why Prosecutor Blackquill hasn't said anything...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The possibility of a perpetrator other than the defendant has now been suggested. But if we hold this possibility to be true, then what did Ms. DePlume witness?</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Th-That's right! I saw the killer whale attack the victim! Just like it did a year ago, singing a song!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... I guess there still is that... Even with somebody else as the culprit, Orla's behavior still seem [sic] pretty bizarre. I wonder why did she [sic] was doing the same things she did a year ago?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But are they REALLY that bizarre...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">To explain the inexplicable, all we have to do is turn our thinking around.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Turn our thinking around, huh? Sounds good to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Time to give the ol' "turn my thinking around" method a try! Instead of trying to figure out WHY Orla did the same things she did a year ago... ...I should consider the results that were produced by her behavior this time around. Orla sang a song, did some head-butts, and bit the victim. If the real culprit wanted to shift the suspicion onto Orla... ...then they would've needed to give people a reason to think Orla did it in the first place!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright, as her lawyer, how do you explain your client's actions?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I believe we should think of it in this way, Your Honor: What kind of effect did Orla's actions have on the case?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well. Then why don't you explain it for the court. How did the defendant's actions affect the case?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant's actions may have killed the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So your assertion is that... the defendant is guilty...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh! What?! No...! I retract my statement, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may retract your statement, but you will first contract a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Instead of trying to figure out WHY Orla did the same things she did a year ago... ...I should consider what the result was of her doing the same things as a year ago. That's what I have to focus on now!</thought> Your Honor! Please let me try again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please explain to the court...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant's actions may have gotten rid of evidence! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And what evidence might that be, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Vital evidence that would prove who the true culprit is! ...At least, that is what I hope.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I am not asking about your hopes and dreams, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Instead of trying to figure out WHY Orla did the same things she did a year ago... ...I should consider what the result was of her doing the same things as a year ago. That's what I have to focus on now!</thought> Your Honor! Please let me try again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Please explain to the court...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume focused her attention on the orca pool because she heard the song. The orca's act of singing a song created a witness. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Created a witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Isn't it possible... ...that fabricating a witness was the real culprit's true intention? After all, Ms. DePlume witnessed two things: She saw Orla head-butt something over and over, and she saw the orca bite the victim. Those two actions of Orla's might have been... ...the true culprit's plot to make the witness think the orca was attacking the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you saying... that the defendant was being manipulated by the true perpetrator?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. And that would explain Orla's actions perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But the defendant is an orca. Is it even possible to manipulate her?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, there is a way to manipulate Orla's behavior, with this!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Sure, maybe it could be, if one knew how!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I wish someone would manipulate YOU into presenting relevant evidence, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">M-My apologies, Your Honor... <thought>Hmm... I know I have something that can be used to control Orla's behavior...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Wright, is it really possible to manipulate Orla's behavior?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this... a whistle?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. Trainers at the aquarium use whistles to issues commands to Orla. But in truth, anyone can do it, provided they know the right signals.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, that must be how they get Orla to do tricks for their pirate shows.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The true culprit hid the body in a spot that couldn't be seen from the visitor's corridor. Then, when Ms. DePlume appeared, they gave Orla the commands! In other words, Orla was manipulated by the culprit to perform a series of "tricks"!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">Wh-Whaaat...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And, as for you, Ms. DePlume... ...you were manipulated by the true culprit to play the part of the witness!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">I-I, Norma DePlume, was set up...?! I, Norma DePlume, writer extraordinaire, was used...? N-No... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Ms. DePlume...! Please do something about your attire!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh... That was one wardrobe malfunction I did NOT want to see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-It would appear we need to shift our suspicion toward someone other than Orla. Prosecutor Blackquill, please have the bloodstained coin analyzed. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. You waste your breath.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess even Prosecutor Blackquill can't refute the possibility of a human suspect.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You did it, Boss! If the crime happened beside the pool, there's no way an orca could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Now, if only we could find the bag the coins were in...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... In light of the new discovery, it would appear that the orca couldn't have done it. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly, Your Honor. If the blood on the coin proves to be that of the victim... ...we can unequivocally overturn Orla's accusation.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">ACK! <thought>M-My hair! My beautiful hair!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Yesterday, a new inmate was brought into the prison. He said, "The moment you relax is when you're most vulnerable."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And what did this man go in for?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...He is merely a sneaky thief who enjoys a spot of fishing now and again. But Wright-dono here would be easier to hook than any fish... </line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That hawk sure does love the judge's head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's this? That coin from before and... some sort of bag?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A b-bag...? <thought>I don't think I'm gonna like this...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">This is the coin bag the 300 coins were in. I believe you were looking for this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-How did you get that?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I never said we didn't find it at the crime scene. The bag had blood on it, so naturally, I had it sent to the crime lab.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And... does the blood belong to the victim?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It does indeed, as does the blood on the coin.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I knew it! So the blood on the coin DID belong to the victim!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The bag was open and the coins had all spilled out. But the bag alone wasn't proof enough to say that it was used as the murder weapon. ...However, thanks to the defense and their coin, I am more than satisfied that it was.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill! Are you conceding that the true culprit committed the murder with the bag of coins?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I shall concede that the victim was put into the pool after his death. However, even with the bag... ...it doesn't change the fact it was the orca that killed the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! How can you still suspect Orla?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You said that the true culprit manipulated Orla's behavior. But Orla isn't the kind of orca that would let someone control her. If anything, Orla used the victim's behavior against him to murder him!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! But--</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A-Are you arguing that the orca manipulated a human being?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... To prove it, I have summoned another witness. Marlon Rimes, take the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>M-Marlon Rimes?! Is a witness...?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Well, don't just stand there. State your name. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............I told ya I didn't wanna be a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I thought one witness would be quite enough to prove the defendant's guilt... ...but apparently Wright-dono won't be satisfied until every stone is turned.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, son of a... All right, fine! If I gotta talk, then let's get this over with!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Rimes doesn't seem like a willing witness.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I wonder what Prosecutor Blackquill is going to have him testify about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Um... So could we have your name and occupation for the record, witness?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ Ahoy! Yo! Yo! Yo ho hooooo! People of da law! Time to testify! Chillin' with my crew at the Shipshape. Orcas, penguins, and da seascape. Cleanin' n' feedin', there ain't no end. But dem bratty kid's tours, I shall transcend. Noob animal keeper, from the house of Rimes! I'm da master keeper, Marlon with the rhymes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my... I'm afraid I couldn't understand a word you said! Is that that "flip-flop" music young people nowadays like?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So close, Your Honor, so close... and yet so far.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Please proceed with your testimony, witness. Without the flip-flop.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Okay, fine. But I don't wanna do this, I tell ya. I feel like I'm sellin' Sasha out.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">At about 10:10 AM, I was in the staff room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... So that gives us a little more info about the area around the orca pool.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The defendant made the stuff fall down...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Overturned crates and assorted props were scattered all over the pool room floor. There is no doubt that it was the orca that caused the mess. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">But could she really have done that from within the pool?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. As I said, the orca is the only one that could've perform [sic] such a feat. The pool and its room were tidied the night before, including its various odds and ends. But when our rhyming marlin checked on the scene, over 400 pounds of props had fallen. To move it all in one go would challenge even the brawny prisoner in the cell next to mine.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...What is he? The jail gossip?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">So, how did 400 pounds of items fall all at once? I'll tell you how. The orca pulled on the cloth that was underneath them. A weight that would be all but impossible for a human to move... ...was child's play to an orca. During a friendly game of volleyball, the defendant made the crates fall... ...and the bag of coins that was among the items fell on the victim's head and killed him! The orca then toyed with the victim's body underwater, which is what Ms. DePlume saw. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">That orca sometimes makes a loud noise to summon her trainer. But I'm still a newbie, so I don't have a security card to get into the pool room yet. So even if she tries to summon somebody, there isn't much I can do about it. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. So the witness couldn't enter the crime scene...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Whether the orca was actually playing volleyball or not is not the issue. Traces of the orca's saliva were found on the cloth that was underneath the crates. The important point is that the orca is the only one that could have moved the items!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Argh! I have to discredit that statement somehow! If I don't, it'd mean that Orla was the culprit, even if the victim died beside the pool!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">At about 10:10 AM, I was in the staff room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">What?! Y-Yes, I'm sure! I'm pretty good with time. I've never been late to work once. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... If he's sure about the time, then there's something wrong with that statement. I'd better take another look through the Court Record...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Please continue with your testimony, Mr. Rimes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I heard a loud noise from the pool room, so I went to the door to look in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">That's right. The orca pool room and the staff room are pretty close to each other. Anyway, I heard the noise, so I went to the door of the pool room. But I don't have a security card, so all I could do was look through the door crack.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What kind of noise did you hear?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Want me to describe it? Awww yiiiiis! Yo word up Courtroom Numbah Fouuuuurrr! Da crash, boom, bowing to relativity! Everything fallin' with sweet simplicity! This testimony yo, it ain't got no fallacies! Things fallin' n' breakin', was pure insanity! ...Kinda like that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay... But why the need to rap it...?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I didn't really get all of that, but, in any case, I gather it was a very loud noise... Very well. Please describe what you saw at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I couldn't see the captain or the orca, but I saw a bunch of coins scattered around.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I was just lookin' through the door crack. I guess all that stuff was blockin' my view. I did notice a whole bunch of coins scattered all over the place, though... But, at the time, I had no idea the captain was dead.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Killed by gold coins. Ironic, isn't it? Perhaps the orca wanted to be paid for her labor, paid in coins raining from the skies.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Coins raining from the skies? He makes it sound... almost poetic. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But the hard truth is that those coins were actually the murder weapon...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">We all deserve to be paid for our work, do we not? I shall have a fine meal tonight... </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If you find our client guilty, that is. Mr. Rimes, do you have a theory on how the things got knocked down?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Of course I do.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">The orca knows there's a certain spot people stand to play volleyball with her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">If you stand on the mark on the floor, the orca spikes the ball at you. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Taka is good at flying straight at his target as well. And I see plenty of targets right here in this room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Everyone's so busy protecting their head, they forgot about the trial...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Including you. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Tell them what the defendant caused to happen. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Well, the orca knows people stand in a certain spot for volleyball...</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I think maybe she knocked down the stuff that was piled up there and hit the captain.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I don't wanna believe it, myself, but that orca's pretty smart... It'd be easy for her to pull the cloth the stuff was on while she was playin' volleyball. Orcas are really strong. One good pull and all those things would come crashin' down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess maybe an orca could be strong enough to make that much stuff fall...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I've never seen an orca play tug of war, myself. But the fact is, this one did. The traces of the orca's saliva found on the cloth prove it. How long do you plan to walk tightrope on those shaky theories of yours?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Wait until you see me do acrobatics! Moments like these are what I became a lawyer again for!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know why, but Mr. Rimes is lying. I'm afraid I have to expose that secret he and Pearls were keeping to resolve this...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you were in the staff room, but is that really true?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Of course it's true. Why would I lie about a thing like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, have you ever seen this calendar before?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Hey! That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I see you recognize it.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah, that's the Rifle calendar. It's a big hit at the Shipshape Aquarium gift shop. Thank you for shoppin' at Shipshape! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Rimes! Please refrain from scattering fish around the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Not to worry, Your Baldness. Taka will have them cleaned up in no time.</line>
<line speaker="Taka">*Screech!*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...I guess that bird comes in handy now and then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, Mr. Wright. We have all seen your cute souvenir. Now, if you wouldn't mind...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, no, Your Honor! This isn't my calendar. It was originally the witness's, but it came into the possession of a certain young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes and this young lady first met each other in the food prep room. After a mishap, their calendars got switched around. They ran into each other at about 10:10 AM in the food prep room. So clearly, the witness was not in the staff room. In other words, there's no way he could have heard the noise in the pool room upstairs!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What's this? This is the first I'm hearing about any calendar! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That's because Mr. Rimes and Pearls were keeping it a secret.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">You lied to ME?! This transgression will not go unpunished!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Mr. Rimes, you didn't hear the noise of the equipment falling after all, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">...Okay. I admit it. I didn't hear the noise in the orca pool room myself. But somebody told me about it. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Who told you about it?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............It was... uh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Unless you tell the truth, Mr. Rimes, I can't save Orla. And I'm sure you know how sad that would make Ms. Buckler.</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ ............I heard about it... from Sasha.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! From Ms. Buckler?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">B-But that doesn't make sense!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What is going on here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... Now it's the trainer's own words that drive the orca into a corner. How do you like being bitten by your own client, Wright-dono?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Ugh! I certainly didn't see this coming!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">What perfect timing. There was something I wanted to ask Ms. Buckler about the orca. The prosecution calls the trainer, Ms. Sasha Buckler, to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I suppose it would be a good idea to hear what the orca's trainer has to say.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't know what Sasha is going to say... ...but I'll just have to meet it head-on, whatever it is!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">We will take a twenty minute recess while the witness is summoned.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright... are you going to cross-examine Sasha?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I'll have to ask her about the noise from the stuff falling down. </line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Rimes, why did you lie?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I... I didn't want Sasha to have to appear in court. I thought if anybody had to testify, I should be the one to do it for her. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">But why would you go to all those lengths...?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">............ Did you see the entry for the twentieth on that calendar?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The note about meeting the captain at the orca pool?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Yeah. I found that calendar in the nap room. I think it's probably Sasha's.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What?! Then that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it does look like more of a woman's calendar than a man's...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Rimes">I didn't want suspicion to fall on Sasha... Mr. Wright... I gotta go back to the aquarium to look after the orca in Sasha's place. I'll be rootin' for ya on the other end of that TV phone. Please take care of Sasha...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Okay! We can't let Prosecutor Blackquill get the best of us! Time to refocus!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. After all, we're the only ones who can save Orla.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now reconvene. Prosecutor Blackquill, please call the witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Again, you waste your breath. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Me name be Sasha! And I be one of Cap'n Orla's Swashbucklers! I come to rescue me bucko from the false charges put on her by Dread Pirate Nostache!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............"Nostache"...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess "Nostache" refers to Prosecutor Blackquill this time.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Well, it can't be the judge. He HAS a mustache... and a full beard.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Now then, Cap'n Judge... shall we begin the pirate court?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"C-Cap'n Judge"...! Hmm... I rather like that. It makes me feel like a salty old sea dog.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">And scene! How was that for a self-intro?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............The court is not a show. State your full name and occupation. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I'm Sasha Buckler. I work at Shipshape Aquarium. I perform in our Swashbuckler Spectacular pirate show alongside Orla, as her trainer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well! You seem like a completely different person now. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You r-EEL-y think so? Thanks! I was in my pirate show persona just then! Prosecutor Blackquill said I could introduce myself any way I like.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'd bet money he didn't think you were going to do it like THAT...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what will this witness testify about?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca manipulated the victim into playing volleyball and then knocked the items down. The witness will report about hearing the noise that caused the victim's death. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Now wait just a minute! Sure, Orla uses the ball to break props sometimes... She even spiked the ball at the giant octopus's leg yesterday when I was cleaning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...So Orla was the one who broke that leg, huh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">But she couldn't have knocked down that huge stack of equipment with her little ball!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. I thought you were paying attention to the trial over the telecast... ...but you apparently know nothing of what we have been discussing. The orca knocked down the equipment by pulling on the cloth that was underneath it. No one said anything about the orca knocking it down with a ball!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Whaaaaaat?! I-Is THAT what we're talking about?! Ngh... I came in here to give Prosecutor Nostache a good keelhauling... ...but I'm the one getting the cat-o'-nine-tails! Ooh, he's as vicious as a tiger shark!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ms. Buckler! Just focus on your testimony and you'll be all right! Don't worry. We'll take care of that tiger shark for you!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Thank you, Athena! Okay, I can do this! My testimony will be fin-omenal!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, Ms. Buckler. Please proceed with your testimony. </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I admit I heard Orla summoning me with a loud noise.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Her story doesn't seem to be much different from Marlon Rimes's testimony. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Or does it...? The circumstances are different. The actual order of Orla's actions depend on the order the witness heard the two noises. If she heard the scream first, the prosecution's claims don't stand up!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Blackquill:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Sh-She doesn't...?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I was distracted at the time... so I don't really recall which one I heard first... I was lost in thought until the guard brought me back to myself... Sorry I'm no help. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">As long as the order remains unclear, I shall not alter the prosecution's claims. After killing the victim with the bag of coins, the orca toyed with the body in the water.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I have to turn things around here somehow! Unless I can prove the sound Sasha heard was NOT the sound of the victim's murder... ...Blackquill's claim that Orla pulled down the equipment to kill the victim will stand. If I want to save Orla, I have to find a contradiction, no matter how small!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Your cross-examination, please, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I admit I heard Orla summoning me with a loud noise.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Orla knows the sound of her cries doesn't carry far enough. So sometimes she summons people by making a loud noise. Heh heh. That Orla is smarter than the average whale, I tell you!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph. Taka would not be bested in a battle of wits.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Mirror, mirror, on the wall. Who's the smartest one of all? Widget!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Am I expected to enter Trucy into this "my kid is better than yours"-apalooza...?</thought> And did you heed the summons of this very intelligent Orla immediately?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I couldn't right away, although I was concerned about her, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler"> But the aquarium guest's scream I heard over the walkie-talkie was more urgent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. I heard her through the walkie-talkie of a guard making his rounds. "Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagh!" I can still hear it in my head. It was so loud, I thought it was a sea lion. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. DePlume sort of reminds me of a sea lion, actually. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I know, right? Ooh, I should call her "sea lion lady" and see how she likes it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess Athena is still upset about being called "yellow girl."</thought>      </line>
<line speaker="Judge">What did you do after hearing the visitor's scream?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I talked to Norma DePlume first and then went to the pool room with the security guard.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah. Apparently, that obnoxious writer lady said she didn't trust me by myself. That's why, after talking to her, the guard and I went to the pool room together. Why the wench be so suspicious?! Arrrrr! I demand a swordfish duel! That's what I felt like saying to her, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">............I'm afraid I don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was a line from the show when Orla and Sasha quarrel with each other! Didn't you do your Swashbuckler Spectacular homework, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why am I getting scolded, Mr. Wright?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And why am I getting scolded here, Your Honor...? Ms. Buckler, please tell me what happened after you headed to the pool room.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">All right. When the guard and I got there, we saw that...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The equipment was everywhere, and... the captain was lying in the middle of it all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">I don't remember much, to be honest... I was in total shock from seeing the captain like that. If you ask me something specific, I might be able to remember, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Specific questions, huh? Okay, let's see. What should I ask her about?</thought>      </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me more about the things that were scattered around?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">They were equipment and props for the new show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The new show?  </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah. We were supposed to debut a brand-new Swashbuckler Spectacular yesterday. We already defeated the giant octopus and Nostache, after all. We were going to have a new nemesis, Redstache. He's on the flyer.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh! That's the flyer Rifle was distributing! "Who will obtain the gold coins hidden in the skull rock?!" Ooh, I wish it could be me!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Leave it to you, Athena, to know all about it! Orla's even got some new tricks for the new show.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So all the stuff that fell down was for the new show, is that it? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">That's right. A bunch of props in crates and other equipment, stacked up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, for the record, I'd like that information added to the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Ms. Buckler, please append what you just said to your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Sure thing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Could you tell me more about the state you found the victim in?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It's so hard to even think about right now...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sasha is deeply traumatized by the victim's death...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I shouldn't push her on it, then. <thought>Poor Sasha... She must've really adored him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Buckler">The props for the new show were everywhere, and... the captain was in the middle of it all. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">A blow-up dolphin and anchor, Redstache's costume, the bag of coins... Stuff like that. The captain was wearing his usual costume, and the new props were all there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What [sic] a minute... Something about that doesn't seem right... Is there a problem with Sasha's testimony?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess there isn't any particular problem. I'd better get on with the cross-exam.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Do you think Orla really did make that stuff fall down? </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I think we probably need more information before we can know what really happened. Let's be careful not to let a single inconsistency slip by us.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You say you the captain was wearing his "usual costume," but is that completely accurate? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Come on, Phoenix! What are you nitpicking my testimony for?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If we look at the body, we see that there's a discrepancy between that and your statement. You stated that the victim was wearing his usual costume. But you'll notice that the victim was wearing a red scarf around his neck. I imagine this red scarf is part of his costume for the new pirate show.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, you're right. It's written right here in the flyer for the new show. "Featuring the dashing Redstache, with a fluttering red scarf!" </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Although, I have to say, it just looks like a red scarf was added to his OLD costume...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, well, the captain was never one to spend too much money on costumes... But, you know, the captain wasn't WEARING that red scarf...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But in this photo, I believe I see a red scarf...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Yeah, but it's not wrapped around his neck. It's just draped on top of his neck. That red scarf was packed away with the rest of the new show's equipment. It must've fallen on top of the captain when the equipment fell down.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It looks like your "discrepancy" wasn't really a "discrepancy" after all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So the scarf doesn't have anything to do with the case? But there's something about the timing of the stuff falling that bothers me... Hold on. The timing of the stuff falling... The timing... Maybe... my theory has been all wrong from the beginning! Maybe... the bag of coins isn't the murder weapon!</thought>        </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Heh heh. And so your last cross-examination ends in failure as well. You should know that such a feeble slash will never hurt me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmm? And why, pray tell, is that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I'll tell you all right. <thought>If my theory has been all wrong... then I'll just have to fix it!</thought>    </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Mr. Wright. Please do tell the court. What indicates that the body was not dragged into the water after the items fell?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That point? I don't see any particular problem there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right here! No... uh, I mean... right AROUND here! To, uh... somewhere over there-ish... And please also take a look at this area over here as well...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Wright! Your "point" is gradually expanding to include the entire photograph!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>...Okay. I deserved that. The items that fell were props for the new show. A blow-up dolphin and anchor, the bag of coins, the red scarf, swords... If the body was dragged into the pool AFTER the items fell... ...then a certain piece of evidence shouldn't still be in this photograph.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Please try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This red scarf fell at the same time as the bag of coins. But if the body was dragged into the pool after the bag of coins fell... ...then the red scarf wouldn't still be on top of the body! </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Wh-What...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In other words, the victim was already dead when the equipment came crashing down! Therefore, the bag of coins that fell with the red scarf was NOT the murder weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">But it was the defense who claimed the bag of coins was the murder weapon to begin with!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well... yes, that's true. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Do you intend to abandon your original argument?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">After hearing the testimony, I realized my theory about the murder weapon was wrong. Please recall the facts we have learned so far. It's a fact that what Orla bit was the victim's dead body. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">After all, when we saw the victim on the security footage, he was already dead.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But then, Orla carried the victim's body to the side of the pool... ...and knocked down the equipment for the new pirate show that was piled up there. Maybe Orla was trying to alert the humans to the victim's condition. If Orla knocked the items down on the victim after he was already dead... ...then it means the defendant didn't kill the victim with those items!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">BUT THAT'S PREPOSTEROUS! ............Even still, your argument is lacking... If neither the orca's head-butting nor the bag of coins were the manner of death... ...then how do you propose the victim was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A very good point. If the defense is now abandoning its original theory... ...then we would need a new theory as to what the murder weapon was.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ugh... A-All right... <thought>I doubt "I have no clue" would go over well.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">All right! Let's go over what we still need to find out about the victim's body.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What we don't know is how he died and why his body was at the bottom of the pool. I wonder if there's something that would explain both of those things at once?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... How did the victim's body sink to the bottom of the pool...? On a diagram, it's easy enough to move the body to the bottom of the pool... ...but in real life, the water would just cause the body to float.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right... <thought>Hold on... Water? Okay. Then what if we flip that around? What if there was no water? Then the body would go right down in an instant. ...So could the real manner of death be...?!</thought> Thanks for the great hint, Athena. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">What? I helped you, and I didn't even know it?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor! I think we know the real manner of the victim's death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"I think" won't do, Mr. Wright. I expect a clear answer. Now then, what was the real manner of Jack Shipley's death?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What's the manner of death that moved the victim to the bottom of the pool in an instant?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We believe the victim drowned, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah, of course! Let's see... Cause of death was "instant death from a brain contusion." Your answer is completely wrong, Mr. Wright!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You're right, Your Honor. Please let me try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We believe the victim was assaulted with a blunt instrument, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...But nothing like that was found at the crime scene, other than the bag of coins. So if it wasn't the coins, then what was the murder weapon?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um... could we just forget I said that...? You know, about the blunt instrument...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Forget"...? Very well. I'll try to forget it, but I won't forget to give you a penalty!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gah... Please let me try that again.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Please take a look at this diagram of the pool. If there was no water in the pool... ...then it would be very easy to move the victim's body to the bottom of the pool. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">He would drop straight down... Oh, my! Could that be the true manner of death...?! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The orca pool is about 65 feet deep. If the victim were to go from the top of the pool to the bottom when there was no water... ...then he would, without question, have fallen to his death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Death from a fall...!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh... And that's your answer...?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">It all makes perfect sense! If he fell, that would explain the "signs of blunt force trauma all over the body," too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The culprit pushed the victim into the pool when there was no water in it. After doing something to keep the body from floating up, they filled the pool with water. The pool water washed away any signs of blood, so no one would realize that he fell!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">S-Surprisingly, that actually makes sense! Order! Order in the court! I'm just as surprised as you are, but I must have order! If falling was the manner of death, then does that mean the defendant's behavior... ...was the result of being manipulated by the true culprit, as the defense claimed?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it would have to be. All that needs to be explained now is how the real culprit commanded Orla! Ms. Buckler, is there a way to instruct Orla to bite someone? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">What?! What kind of trick would that be?! Of course not!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then could you tell us about the tricks Orla does know?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Well, there's jumping, dancing, and playing volleyball. And she can spin, do the rock 'n' roll trick, and sing the Swashbuckler Spectacular song.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Those sound like pretty nice tricks, but I doubt they're related to this case.</thought>  </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">She's also practicing two new, top-secret tricks. There's the "human rocket," where she shoots somebody up into the air. And then there's the "lifesaver" trick, where she brings a drowning person to the surface.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hey! One of these "top-secret" tricks might have something to do with the case! Now, which of these two tricks sounds relevant to the case?</thought>     </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The human rocket trick shoots a person up into the air. That means Orla shot the victim's body, which had sunk to the bottom, up to the surface! </line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Are you implying that's how the victim's body got to the surface? In that case, when did the bite marks get onto the victim's clothes?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>Oops. I forgot about those.</thought>     </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can't accept your theory unless it explains all of the circumstances of this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Orla has two "top-secret" tricks. The human rocket trick, where she shoots somebody up into the air. And the lifesaver trick, where she brings a drowning person to the surface.</thought>     </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, in the lifesaver trick, Orla brings a drowning person to the surface, correct? </line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You cod it! Orla's still learning how to hold someone gently in her mouth... ...so she sometimes bites into their clothes, but she's never hurt a person's skin. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">She brings a drowning person to the surface?! Then that must be it...!</line>
<line speaker="DePlume">And then the killer whale swam up toward the surface with the victim in its mouth!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That matches up perfectly with what Ms. DePlume said in her testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The real culprit must have used the lifesaver trick command to manipulate Orla!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I still find this very hard to believe. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Then let's see it for ourselves. Let's have Orla show us her trick using a practice dummy.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">...Hmph. As you wish. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution doesn't appear to have any objection. Ms. Buckler, please proceed.</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Okay, sure! I'll show you Orla's fin-omenal trick! Hey, Marlon! Are you ready over there?</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Okay, lemme just go get the practice dummy... ...There! It's in the pool! Ready and standin' by, Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Here goes! Orla's secret new trick, the lifesaver!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">The clothes got torn up a little, but the dummy doesn't have any new marks on it!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet! Fwee, fweeeeet!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">And there you have it! Orla's secret new trick!</line>
<line speaker="Man">Wow! That orca is really something!</line>
<line speaker="Woman">A cute thing like that wouldn't hurt anybody!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Sounds like the gallery loved Orla's performance!</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Athena">That was great! That awesome trick captured everybody's heart!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ho ho ho! Wonderful! I wish I could see more!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Looks like we silenced Prosecutor Blackquill!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you, Orla and Ms. Buckler. And thank you, too, Mr. Rimes. And so now you can clearly see that Orla was manipulated. The bottom of the orca pool needs to be examined immediately! We might still find some evidence of the victim falling to his death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Prosecutor Blackquill, please have that taken care of at once!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Uh, excuse me, Prosecutor Blackquill, but I am requesting further investigation...</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ GAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Tsk, tsk, Prosecutor Blackquill! You have to answer the nice judge politely! Oh, that's right! I almost forgot! The thing you asked for just came in.</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ngh... And you couldn't be bothered to think of a less violent way to deliver it...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What did Prosecutor Blackquill ask for?</thought>   </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ I've been waiting for this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh? And what is that?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............An updated autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! Why did it have to come now?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">During the recess, I ordered the body to be re-examined. Something started nagging at me during the course of the trial, you see. ............Here. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">I take it you'd like me to read it? Very well. "Cause of Death: Thought to be from 65-foot fall"!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But this...! But this is decisive evidence that substantiates Mr. Wright's theory!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?! <thought>It's something... GOOD for a change?!</thought>      </line>
<line speaker="Judge">If the manner of death was falling into an empty pool, the orca can't be responsible. It seems Orla's complete innocence has been proven. </line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph............ I suppose I can't deny that. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">This is fantastic! You did it, Mr. Wright! Prosecutor Blackquill isn't even trying to refute it! Orla is saved!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-Yeah... <thought>Is it really safe to celebrate...?</thought>      </line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear more investigation into this case is necessary. But first allow me to render my verdict. The court finds the defendant Ora Shipley...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">You did it! Thank you so much, Phoenix! Thank you, Athena! Orla and Marlon thank you, too!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Congrats, Sasha!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Rimes">Time to celebrate! Go on! Eat up!</line>
<line speaker="Orla">Fwee, fwee, fweet!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hee hee! Glad to see everybody so happy! And I'm absolutely thrilled about the verdict!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............ ...Thank you, Wright-dono. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?! For what?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... The drained pool... Thanks to you, the truth is finally clear. Fool Bright............ Arrest this woman. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Certainly! Right away, Prosecutor Blackquill! Sasha Buckler, you are hereby under arrest for the murder of Jack Shipley!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-What are you talking about?! What reason could you possibly have?!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Come now. You must have had some idea in the back of your dull, little mind. The true culprit manipulated the orca in order to have false charges brought upon her. ...And who is the only one with the ability to accomplish that? It can only be the orca's trainer!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I'm sure there's some other explanation!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Silence!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I don't need any of your baseless counterarguments... Have you forgotten? In order to enter the orca pool room, a security card is necessary. A security card that only the victim and Sasha Buckler possessed! Ms. Buckler is the only one who could have caused the victim to fall to his death!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No! I don't believe it! Ms. Buckler was so upset by Mr. Shipley's death! She couldn't have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">............Fool Bright. </line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">We asked the security company yesterday to check their security card logs. Their report just came in during the recess. The night before the incident, Sasha Buckler used her card to enter the orca pool room. After that, not a single person entered the pool room! Not until the incident was discovered, when Ms. Buckler and the guard ran in.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">Apparently, the aquarium employees don't know that their card usage is tracked. What's more, Ms. Buckler was seen arguing with the victim before the incident. So, Ms. Trainer, what were you arguing about?</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">It was... a private matter... But it wasn't anything I would kill him over! That's ridiculous!</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Ms. Buckler is the only one who entered the room, and she knows how to command Orla. Besides, I thought her suspicious from the very beginning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You suspected Ms. Buckler from the start?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">The orca did tricks because someone commanded her to do so. Possibly someone with a heart so black as to make her own partner the murder weapon! The possibility the orca killed the victim... The possibility a human manipulated the orca... I looked into both.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So he suspected both Sasha and Orla all along...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">Hmph... My gratitude to you. After all... ...you were the one who drew out that information about the lifesaver trick. The orca you saved was an unwitting victim. A victim made to look like the weapon that killed Jack Shipley.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ungg... N-NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Fulbright">All right, come along, then. Let's have a good, long talk...</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Wait! I didn't kill the captain! And I would never try to frame Orla! Why would I hurt the ones I love like that?! </line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sasha...!</line>
<line speaker="Buckler">Phoenix! Athena! You gotta believe me! I--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sasha didn't kill him! I believe that with all my heart! There's gotta be something we can do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I feel the same way... Could I have done something differently? But never in my wildest dreams did I imagine things turning out like this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would appear that this case has taken on an entirely new suspect. But this trial is only concerned with a ruling on the defendant, Ora Shipley. So I'm afraid this concludes today's trial. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It does? In what way...?</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">It does indeed expose something... the defense's boneheadedness. There is nothing untoward about that evidence, no matter how you bluster.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I agree. There is nothing compelling in that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm definitely losing the judge's confidence in me here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">My opinion? My opinion is that there is nothing wrong with it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... This is my first trial in eight years. It looks like I made a little mistake...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is no excuse, Mr. Wright. I should give you eight years' worth of penalties! </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's been eight years. Can't he go easy on me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Blackquill">I hope you don't think waving your finger about aimlessly... ...is going to help you win this trial!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I agree. I see nothing inconsistent with that evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Urk! <thought>I must have the wrong evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright! I think I have something here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You sensed something wrong with the testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. Let me show you which statement I thought was strange!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks. That would be a big help! <thought>Then I'll just have to compare the evidence with the statement she shows me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright, I don't see any inconsistencies in the testimony. This might be a good time to--</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Press for more information? I think you're right. </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I just can't help but feel that there's more to this statement than meets the eye.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'll put my faith in Athena and press on that statement, then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">When we view your emotions alongside your testimony, we find the unexpected emotion-- <thought>Wait a minute... There really isn't anything strange here.</thought>    </line>
<line speaker="Athena">I don't know, but I think maybe we made a mistake, Mr. Wright...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">......I think maybe you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's take another look! There must be an unexpected emotion here somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The defense's case is insufficient to overturn the prosecution's claims! This court finds the defendant, Ora Shipley...</line>
</xml>