
<xml>
<title>Turnabout Revolution</title>
<line speaker="Trucy">Just so you know... I'm not going to take sides!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Message received, loud and clear.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Good, because I don't like this one bit! You and Daddy should be on the same team!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sorry, Trucy... <thought>Wow, she's really mad.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I'm sorry, too, little lady. This is all my fault.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I'm just worried things will never be the same between Daddy and Apollo... ...if they go through with this.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Is that all? Well, I wouldn't worry about that. That's the way it is with us men. We may fight, but we don't burn bridges.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Really?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Sure. One minute we're trading blows, and the next, we're having drinks together. We're simple creatures at heart. Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">I sure hope you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry I'm late, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena! There you are! What happened with you and Mr. Wright yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">O-Oh, about that... I ended up going to the wrong airport. I was waiting there, thinking his flight was really late... and before I knew it, I dozed off. By the time I woke up, it was already dark.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I figured something like that had happened. Being late and dozing off are the two things you do best.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Ugh. Guilty as charged.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, I take it you have no idea what today's case is about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, strike three, you're out. It's a civil case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You act like I'm speaking Swahili here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. And the other attorney is someone you know very well.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">The trial will begin shortly. Please proceed to the courtroom at once.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Okay, let's do this!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No time to explain. Let's go.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... no. No, it's not, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's the real deal, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-It's nothing like that, Your Honor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. It just so happens that we have different clients in this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What? Do you want to switch sides?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, at least she IS here. I'm really going to need her help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Justice. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't expect me to pull any punches just because you're the opposing lawyer. As I said, the kid gloves are off, and come what may, they'll stay off.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Same here, Mr. Wright! If it's a fight you want, it's a fight you'll get!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">..................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..................</line>
<line speaker="Staff">Right, left, right, left, HALT!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Noble judge, members of the gallery! Good day to you! I am Paul Atishon! This is but the start of my epic campaign! And you all have the honor of witnessing it! I believe the youth of this country are our very future. Too long have they been looked down on and given the cold shoulder! So, to them I say: ask not what you can do for your country, but for me!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Atishon! What is that crazy contraption you're riding?!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. It's my custom-made, election-winning campaign mobile. Beautiful, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You're at a witness stand, not a campaign podium. So come out of there this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Now would the plaintiff's attorney Mr. Wright... ...please explain the complaint filed against the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atishon's complaint against the defendant is simple. The defendant, one Dhurke Sahdmadhi... ...stole my client's family heirloom --- the Crystal of Ami Fey. Mr. Atishon merely seeks its return.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">This wouldn't have happened if that archeologist hadn't kicked the bucket.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. Well, Mr. Justice, let's have your opening statement, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense asserts the item in question is the Founder's Orb, a sacred relic from Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Go on.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It seems someone asked an archeologist -- Dr. Archie Buff, -- to study the orb. Dr. Buff determined that it was a Khura'inese nation treasure known as the Founder's Orb. The very orb that was stolen from a treasure room in Khura'in several weeks ago.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why yes, I saw a news report about that! The theft of a Khura'inese national treasure caused quite an uproar in the kingdom.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we believe it was not, in fact, a theft in the traditional sense. But rather, that it was spirited out of Khura'in by someone for Dr. Buff to study.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You don't say... And...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Around that time, an acquaintance of the defendant learned of Dr. Buff. He made contact with the doctor, who agreed to hand over the orb. Apparently, the doctor wanted nothing to do with it once he'd learned it had been stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems you even have a transfer agreement between both parties.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Sahdmadhi also agreed to return the Founder's Orb to the Kingdom of Khura'in... ...once it was verified it was the real thing.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see... So this dispute centers on... ...whether the item is the Founder's Orb or the Crystal of Ami Fey. That, in turn, will determine the object's rightful owner.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I'd better bring my A game. Going up against Mr. Wright won't be a walk in the park.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Come to think of it, the name Dhurke Sahdmadhi sounds awfully familiar. But I can't recall where I've heard it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh. umm, it's probably your imagination, Your Honor. He's just a tourist, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... My imagination, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...In Khura'in, yes. Here, he's just a tourist.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let's begin the proceedings. Bailiff, would you bring in the first witness?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Ema?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Show some manners. We're in court.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know, it's just... This&#160;is a civil trial, so I was surprised to see a detective take the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I had her do some digging on Dr. Buff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">You disappoint me, Apollo. First, you know I'm not just a detective. I'm a forensic scientist. Do try to remember that. Second, you owe Mr. Wright an apology. After all he's done for you, you have some nerve!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">First, I'm sorry. And second, I'm really just trying to do my job.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You'll never get anywhere with that attitude. Take some advice from someone who's been there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why do I feel like I'm on trial here?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Skye, your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The police have had their eye on Dr. Buff for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor... is a thief? Why am I hearing about this now?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, "cat burglar" isn't something he'd put on his résumé. He was more careful than that. But the fact is, he was a classic treasure hunter.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A treasure hunter, huh... Like people who have thrilling adventures in exotic places, risking life and limb for glory?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I doubt Dr. Buff was the star of his own hit movie series, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Out of respect for the dead, I will say that Dr. Buff wasn't doing it to get rich. Apparently, he only wanted to borrow artifacts to study them. He would then return them as soon as his research was finished. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">According to the doctor's child... ... he would even repair or restore some of the artifacts he stole before returning them. He believed he was honoring the dead by discovering their history through artifacts. But whatever lofty ideals he had, it makes no difference. Larceny is larceny.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, he certainly sounds no different than a regular thief to me. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, let's say for a moment that the doctor really did moonlight in stealing artifacts... Might he not have stolen the Founder's Orb in Khura'in and brought it back here himself?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nope. There's no records of him traveling overseas over the past few years. Plus, he couldn't very well leave his reclusive child at home all alone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Then this really must be the Crystal of Ami Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes. He stole it from the Atishon residence, probably so he could study it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>This is the left hook I did not need.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet you never saw that coming, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, when Mr. Wright said the kid gloves were off, he wasn't kidding.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, you may proceed with your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">The police have had their eye on Dr. Buff for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Chalk it up to good, old-fashioned sleuthing. After investigating countless artifact thefts over the years... ...the police finally zeroed in on him, and the doctor became their prime suspect.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A number of those artifact thefts occurred in Kurain Village, too, if I might add. And they started right around the time the doctor moved there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But he was never arrested. I take it there was nothing concrete linking him to a crime?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">No. Which is why we were never able to get a search warrant in the first place. It's hard to arrest artifact thieves unless you catch them red-handed. Still, the police had him under constant surveillance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">And just today, a number of stolen artifacts were discovered in his study.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">They're not fakes, that's for sure. Take the urn, for example. Apparently, it's an extremely intricate work of art. Its design, cracks, and other features would be impossible to replicate perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, I've had a few run-ins with that urn myself. So I was shocked to see it there in the doctor's study. I can say without a doubt, that that urn was stolen from the Fey clan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Detective Skye, please continue your testimony, if you would.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Among them were a priceless urn and a statue that were stolen from the Fey clan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Yes. For instance... Remember the large relief on the wall? It was chiseled out some ancient ruins in the Kingdom of Khura'in several years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ch-Chiseled out...? Didn't that damage it?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Well, he did restore the parts that were so faded you could barely see them anymore. It seems he intended to return it someday, so one could say his intentions were good. But good intentions are no get-out-of-jail-free card. That's a fact. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If I might add, with respect for the deceased... ...the quality of the restorations was apparently exceptional. It seems the doctor invested a lot of money in hiring an extremely talented specialist.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He sounds like a good man... who took a wrong turn somewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I guess Sarge takes after him in that way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">Any further questions? If not...</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It seems the doctor would do anything to study artifacts, including steal them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">At least five years, as far as we can tell. All the recent thefts had been local... ...but before moving to Kurain Village, he had been stealing from ruins around the world.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Dr. Buff was an international criminal?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ema">This data lends itself to but one conclusion: Dr. Buff was a thief.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">As for the relic at the center of this dispute, he likely stole it from the Atishon residence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Unfortunately, it IS true. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">A police report was filed concerning the theft -- one year ago, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! A whole year ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">August 25 of last year, to be exact. The report state, and I quote... "The Crystal of Ami Fey was discovered to be missing... ...from the Atishon storehouse at 10 AM. The storehouse lock had been picked. Signed, Paul Atishon-Wimperson."</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, a year-old report certainly lends the the plaintiff's claim credence. The doctor could really have stolen the Crystal of Ami Fey.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not only that, Your Honor... ...but the Founder's Orb was only found to be missing several weeks ago. That is nearly a year after the crystal's theft was reported. Therefore, I believe we must consider the orb and the crystal to be two separate items.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Paul Atishon-Wimperson? Not the most awe-inspiring tail end, is it? I see why he cut it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not that he inspires confidence without it. Still, I'd probably do the same in his shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Because Mr. Atishon has stated as much.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Well, I'm not buying it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, I was thinking... The plaintiff's legal name is pretty distinctive. Paul Atishon-Wimperson... Do we have any evidence related to his initials or his name?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We just might. It might even point out a flaw in something Ema said.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You think her logic's faulty?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. If the doctor stole the relic from Mr. Atishon... er, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson... ...then there's one thing the doctor did that doesn't make any sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Especially if Paul Atishon-Wimperson was desperately searching for his stolen relic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Okay, time to go over the evidence again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The trial's barely started and we're already backed into a corner.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">To make matters worse the judge seems to agree with the plaintiff's case. But we've still got to give it our all.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A police report was filed about the crystal's theft a year ago.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But the theft of the Founder's Orb was only reported a few weeks ago. So the crystal's report was filed way before the orb was found missing.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That suggests the stolen relic is the Crystal of Ami Fey, as Mr. Atishon-Wimperson asserts. Hmm... I doubt the police report is a fake. After all, Ema is the one who submitted it as evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Still, I feel like something we learned in the police report is important somehow...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor stole the relic from the plaintiff? Are you sure? Because that statement doesn't agree with a certain piece of evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This contains an email from the doctor's computer.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...E-mail? In that little piece of plastic? ......... I'm afraid I don't understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, umm... This stick here can store all sorts of computer data.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I still don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">H-Here, just look at this! Apparently, the doctor was reporting his research findings to a certain individual. Now, take a look at this. It's the police report that Detective Skye presented to this court. You can see the plaintiff's legal name on it. Paul Atishon-Wimperson.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I can see why'd he drop "Wimperson" from his name, but that's hardly breaking news.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look closer, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........Ah! H-His initials!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. The plaintiff's full legal name is Paul Atishon-Wimperson. Now consider this... The e-mail's recipient address starts with three letters. </line>
<line speaker="Ema">P-A-W...? Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! Don't tell me--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, but I will anyway. The individual who hired the doctor to study the disputed item... ...is none other than Paul Atishon-Wimperson.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">Wait, th-then that means... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. He wouldn't have asked the man who stole his family heirloom to study it. Therefore, how could this possibly be the Crystal of Ami Fey?!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH! ...We never checked the doctor's e-mails. We couldn't even figure out the password to his computer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The plaintiff willingly left the orb in the doctor's care so he could study it... at the behest of his "benefactor"!</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Wait. Then what about the police report? I have all the details of the theft right here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's probably for another relic -- the real Crystal of Ami Fey. He's just using the report as a way to claim that our orb is actually his stolen crystal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Perhaps. So let's get to know your client a little better, shall we? Mr. Paul Atishon-Wimperson!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh. I suppose shutting down detractors is all part of a politician's job.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Answer me this, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson: what is...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's your shoe size?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">How should I know?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, you don't know your own shoe size?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I have all my shoes handcrafted in Italy. And the shoemaker comes to my residence to take the necessary measurements. I have better things to do than memorize trivial information like that.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Makes we wish I'd memorized the Italian for "entitled jerk."</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Maybe this will help you memorize what happens to those who waste the court's time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I really put my foot in it this time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, no matter what his shoe size is, there wouldn't be enough digits. We're looking for a three-digit number.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Let's see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's your favorite food?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Curry rice. It's an old family favorite.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? As in, boil up some rice and dump some curry sauce on top? THAT curry rice?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh, I bet you assumed I would say French cuisine... ...just because I'm a member of the political elite. But nothing beats the delectable curry recipe my ancestors bright over from Japan. And I'm the kind of representative who upholds the value of such traditions!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is his entire strategy really just to pander to "traditional values" voters?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your penalty is served, Mr. Justice. Let this be some food for thought!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, why don't we take another look at the e-mail address?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's fine! I just need another crack at this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What is your birthday?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">My birthday? It's July 11, but what's it to you? ...Oh, I see. You can address birthday gifts to my office. But, full disclosure... I only accept gifts valued at $1,000 or more.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Hm? Why has everyone gone silent?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How can anyone be that self-centered? Oh, right, politician.</thought> Did everyone hear that? He said, "July 11." July 11 -- or rather, "711" -- matches the numbers in the e-mail address. Both the name and birthday are a match! I hardly think that's a coincidence!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">.........Wait... Why you sneaky little--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Looks like someone finally decided to join the conversation.</thought> Would the plaintiff care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I-I would like to say... that is q-quite...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Quite what?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Q-Quite... a thing... you've said. .........</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">No further comments. I stand by my previous statement.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...I'm afraid I simply don't know how it happened. I can't possibly explain matters out of my purview. Perhaps it was a mistake on the part of my secretary?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh no you don't, you slippery eel.</thought> Mr. Wright, would you care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I won't argue your assertion. My client lent the treasure in question to the doctor and asked him to study it. It seems that much is a fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now we're getting somewhere!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">However, it has no bearing on the issue of ownership.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...How so?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atishon, I fully understand your position here. You HAD to hide the fact that you sent the crystal out to be studied. Otherwise, your family would've been very upset if they had found out. It's a family heirloom, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You have got to be kidding me!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Mr. Wright is, well, right, of course. But then, he always is. That's why he's my lawyer. The crystal is a precious Atishon family heirloom, and has been for centuries. But Dr. Buff was so eager to study its proud heritage, I just couldn't say no. I didn't even tell my grandfather.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...I-I was going to explain everything to grandfather later! Honest!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My client's grandfather is very proud of his grandson for following in his footsteps. And if refusing him would've meant dashing the dreams of his doting grandson... ...I doubt the kindly old man could've said no.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, grandchildren ARE meant to be spoiled. That's what grandfathers are for.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor... Please. <thought>I mean, it's been in the family for centuries.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">My grandfather thinks highly of my talents as a politician. That's why he entrusted me with this very important name placard today. So I'm sure he would've been okay with me using the crystal as I saw fit.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Grrr... Grandpa's spoiled little brat.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think the judge is buying it, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No surprise there. He's always going on and on about his own grandchild, after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">...Excuse me. Can I leave now, Mr. Wright? I believe my work here is done.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">By all means, Detective Skye. Thank you for your assistance.</line>
<line speaker="Ema">You're welcome. It's nice to testify at a civil trial once in a while. See you around.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seems the facts have changed somewhat. Mr. Atishon-Wimperson apparently lent his family heirloom to Dr. Buff. Mr. Justice. How would the defense like to proceed?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, umm... <thought>All right, now what?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's hear what what they know about this so-called "Crystal of Ami Fey." Maybe we can find some inconsistencies in their statements.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... Okay then, Mr. Wright. If the item in question really is an Atishon family heirloom... ...then let's hear all your client knows about it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Of course. Mr. Atishon-Wimperson? Please tell the defense everything you know about the crystal's origin.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">All right. Now then, listen and learn. This is the tale of the Crystal of Ami Fey, and the illustrious history of the Atishon clan! Are you ready? Our story begins back in the old country, when the Atishon family reigned supreme...</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">My ancestor was praised as a benevolent ruler.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, that devolved into a great load of self-aggrandizing propaganda fast.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As you can see... ...the Crystal of Ami Fey is an heirloom of the esteemed House of Atishon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you have proof that it has always been in the Atishon family?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have someone who gave a statement to that effect. My client's neighbor -- one Ives Shineto, age 85 -- gave the following statement: "The Atishons showed me the Crystal back when I was but a lad."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Justice. Would you care you to explain that statement to the judge?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh... Er, I didn't mean-- What I'm trying to say is, um...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Never underestimate the memory of your elders. I may forget my verdicts the next day, but the memories of my past are clear as day! Therefore, I find Mr. Ives Shineto's statement to be perfectly credible.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wow, did you see how Mr. Wright got the judge on his side? That's definitely a trick I want up my sleeve.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">*sigh* You're not helping, Athena...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You may cross-examine the witness, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">My ancestor was praised as a benevolent ruler.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It's a name placard. This one here belonged to my grandfather, Abraham Atishon. He had it custom-made during his distinguished political career. It's special because it was crafted from the finest Italian plastic.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I wasn't aware the Italians were famous for their fine plastic...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. You can touch it if you want.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I'm fine.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Very well. I'll just continue with my testimony. My ancestor was praised as a benevolent ruler. But he was also an eminent politician.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">He protected the spirit mediums, a minority back then, from the rest of the locals.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">A smooth and open line of communication with my entire electorate... That is the Paul Atishon way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...? Oh, sorry. I was asking about your ancestor.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh. Whether it's about me or my ancestor... ...feel free to ask me anything you'd like. Transparency in government! That's the Paul Atishon way.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>More like: Dodging questions! That's the Paul Atishon way.</thought> Thanks. I'll be sure to ask when I have something you'll actually answer.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">As I was saying, the Atishon family protected the Fey spirit mediums back then.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Some discriminated against them, you see, while others tried to abuse their power.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes. Some people even treated them like they were monsters. The transformation the mediums underwent when channeling spirits frightened the locals. And then there were those who tried to use them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You mean they sought to control the channeling powers of the mediums?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Discriminating against a minority is absolutely despicable. A vote for me is a vote to end discrimination. I vow to root it out wherever it may be! That is my promise to you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's totally ignoring your questions. It's like you're a moderator at a political debate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, and only HE cares about his talking points. As thrilling as your campaign is, could we please get back to your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh. As you wish. Now then, as for the Crystal of Ami Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">As thanks, Ami Fey gave the crystal she had specially made as a gift to him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. They say she hired a famous craftsman to make it. And they say it's quite valuable, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you were going to take such a priceless family heirloom... ...and just give it to your patron?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh. That's so typical of you ignorant, common types. Making difficult decisions when the chips are down is what being a politician is all about.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But only when it's in service of your own political career, you mean.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">The crystal is a testament to my ancestor's remarkable achievements. And furthermore...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I am a descendent of that great lord.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">You could say that. But I find my popularity to be rather bemusing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Bemusing?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes, my campaign posters keep going missing as soon as I put them up. My avid supporters and female fans are likely taking them home to hang in their bedrooms.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...I guess ignorance really is bliss.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. All this only proves my fine lineage.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">As such, my political power and influence is backed by centuries of history!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Have you never heard of kingcraft?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Kingcraft?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It's the art of ruling as a king. My father drilled it into my head from a young age. And one of its precepts states: "Ruin awaits a ruler who responds to every single issue posed by the masses."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, that answered my question about what he meant by "king of this nation." Progress.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, who is this Ami Fey, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe she was the founder of the Kurain Channeling Technique.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The plaintiff claims she had the crystal made for his ancestor. That would mean it was made in Japan, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I suppose it would.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You stated that Ami Fey had the crystal made for your ancestor. So, am I to assume it was made in Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. The craftsmanship is unbeatable!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, that's strange. I don't see how your so-called crystal could've been made there.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's quite obvious if you take a closer look at this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I don't know about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What I do know, Mr. Justice, is your assertion exudes a mysterious amount of nonsense.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oops.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And I assure you there's no mystery behind a penalty for aimless speculation, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nope. No mystery there, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's go over everything we have on the orb once more. Maybe there's something that can help us prove it wasn't made in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor, I can prove the orb wasn't made in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Take a look at the distinctive design here. According to Dr. Buff... ...it's a mitamah motif dating back to the early days of the Kingdom of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The Kingdom of Khura'in, hmm? And you base this on...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Here, this piece of evidence, Your Honor. These are the doctor's research notes on the Founder's Orb. This is the box in which the orb was originally stored. It features the same pattern as the one found on the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... They do look like the same pattern.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Therefore, I assert that... ...the disputed item must have been made in the Kingdom of Khura'in!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">AAAAAAAAAHHHH! Eeeeeeek! M-My placard...!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I have to agree with Mr. Wright. The pattern alone proves nothing. But that also means there's no basis to claim that the item in dispute was made in Japan, either. Hmm.. At this rate, we are going nowhere fast.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...Argh. He's right -- we're just spinning our wheels here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I wonder if we have any evidence that could break this stalemate.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Hmm... Evidence that could break this stalemate...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The defense would like to present a piece of evidence to the court. A piece that will finally break this stalemate!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh? Well, you've sure piqued my interest. Let's see what you've got.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...All right. I will now prove that this is, in fact, the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And just how does that piece of evidence prove that the relic is the Founder's Orb?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........It doesn't, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not by any means I can fathom.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry, Apollo, but I have to agree with the boss on this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Me too, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Me three, defense!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yikes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time to think that one over again, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, Your Honor...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There doesn't seem to be anything we can use. At least, not at this point.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, unless we can find something, this trial won't be going anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">......... *whew* That's much better.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's his deal?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have a suggestion. Why don't we consider this from a different angle?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm listening...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What if... ...the Defiant Dragons really were authorized to take possession of the relic?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm.. I'm afraid I don't know where you're going with this, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Consider the Orb Transfer Agreement, which states: "I agree to hand over the Founder's Orb to the Defiant Dragons if I will come to no harm." What if, as the last part suggests, this was written under duress? That would render the agreement null and void.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...What are you suggesting, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">While you were on your little cave expedition, I was investigating Dr. Buff's accident. And there was something you overlooked, Mr. Justice. Namely, that his "accident" might have actually been murder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?! <thought>M-Murder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! You do realize such statements are not to be made lightly? Are you suggesting the doctor was murdered by the Defiant Dragons?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, but follow me on this for a sec. The books that came tumbling down were from his archeology shelf. However, among that mountain of books was a single volume on psychology. What's more, there was blood on it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And you feel this is important because...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The took that came tumbling down were from the top shelf -- the archeology books. We know this because the doctor's books were meticulously organized by subject. Archeology took up the entire shelf, so that psychology book is completely out of place. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Come to think of it, the shelves were arranged quite carefully.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's also worth noting that psychology books only take up a tiny part of the bottom shelf. You might wonder why a book on psychology was found amid the pile of archeology books. But I believe I can explain what that single out-of-place book was doing there. The doctor was struck from behind while selecting a psychology book from the shelf.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And that's when the blood got on the book?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Precisely. And to make it look like an accident... ...he was buried under a mountain of archeology books.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I do.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-You do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">On a hunch, I had Detective Skye examine the doctor's head wound. She found that he'd been struck by the corner of some object or another.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait, what?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A would like that couldn't have resulted from a fall to a floor, you know. Do you understand what this means, Mr. Justice? The wound makes it crystal clear that Dr. Buff was murdered!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, THAT was unexpected! Who'd have thought we'd break out of the stalemate like this! He pulled the ladder right out from under us.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Still, if he thinks that's enough to make me back down, he's got another thing coming!</thought> Even if the cause of death was murder, what makes you think it was the Defiant Dragons? You should know better than to hurl baseless accusations!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You didn't actually think I'd come to court without witnesses and evidence, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I would like to request more testimony from the plaintiff. Specifically... ...I would like the court to hear how he saw one of the rebels leaving the crime scene!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He-- He-- He saw whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If he can prove it was murder, that's the end of our client's right to the orb! Did he have this up his sleeve the whole time?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Grrr... How could Mr. Wright do this to us? <thought>He was just waiting to spring this trap!!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Heh.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This trial has taken another unexpected turn. But I must mention, Mr. Wright, that you have yet to identify the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The object used to commit the murder was not located at the scene of the crime. The murderer likely disposed of it elsewhere.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I never thought we'd be deliberating the issue of murder at a civil trial. All right, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh. Prepare to be dazzled! Dazzled by charismatic oration forged in the crucible of campaign battles!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That evening, I was walking alone, lost in thought.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the plaintiff saw a possible suspect fleeing from the doctor's residence? And it was within the window of the estimated time of death?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Datz Are'bal! What in the world were you doing there then?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It seems that Mr. Are'bal was loitering about Kurain Village that day. There's evidence that he was in the doctor's study as well. Isn't that right, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......Ah! You mean the suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Exactly. He must have been in quite a rush to leave that behind. Oh, and by the way, Your Honor... ...Mr. Are'bal just so happens to be sitting in the gallery today.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">See? That's him trying to escape as we speak.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Don't let that man get away!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Wright, you backstabber! Why are you doing this to meeee?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. The... counsel-slash-defense may question the plaintiff-slash-witness once more. ...Ahem. Please proceed, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That evening, I was walking alone, lost in thought.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Society is inundated with serious problems that must be solved. And as a politician... ...I'm always on the job, thinking hard about possible solutions, even on my walks.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Umm... <thought>Thanks for the non-answer.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">While we live out our comfy lives... ...there are starving children who suffer in the back alleys of our major cities. It's not in me to ignore such suffering! A vote for me, is a vote to end hunger. ...And for world peace!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, we are well aware of your outstanding character. Now, please continue with your testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. I can practically hear my poll numbers surging. Now, on with my speech. After all, the voting public must be informed of the magnificence that is me!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I passed by the doctor's house... and that's when I saw Mr. Are'bal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Right here, under this tree. I saw him dashing out of Dr. Buff's front door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And he didn't notice you?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">No. I was hidden by the tree.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is it really all that important to know from where the plaintiff saw Dr. Buff?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, I don't believe it bears any relevance to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, then. Will the witness please continue with his testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, I believe it matters a lot. I ask that it please be added to the witness's testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I was under this tree when I saw Mr. Are'bal."</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I was under this tree when I saw Mr. Are'bal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">A lack of lateral thinking... That is a politician's downfall.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That is why, if I'm elected... I promise to think outside the box!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... uh... The question was, what were you doing under the tree, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Feh... I suppose I can't expect a plebeian such as yourself to understand my grand design.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Oh, yeah? Try me, O Lord of Plebs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson. I believe the court is well aware of your grand political vision. Now, let's have the rest of your testimony, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh, I can hardly wait for the upcoming election.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">He was running out the front door.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes, his behavior was incredibly suspicious. His eyes were darting all around as he ran off in total panic. As soon as I saw that, I knew he had done something, and it probably wasn't good.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Despite that, you didn't report it to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Who would've thought he had killed Dr. Buff? Not me. That's why I didn't report him. </line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the witness didn't notify the police. Is that an important statement, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, it's not important.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... All right, then. Let's have the witness continue with his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, it's important. I request that the witness add it to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Feh. Sure, why not.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"I had no idea Dr. Buff was dead. That's why I didn't call the police."</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I had no idea Dr. Buff was dead. That's why I didn't call the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I am truly ashamed of myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">There's been a gruesome murder in my beloved village. What a fool I've been! I was thinking only of the village's future and world peace! It seems my earnest attitude and industrious nature have come back to haunt me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Only a politician would try to pass off self-aggrandizement as self-deprecation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, you think this is how all politicians will be from now on?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">We're all doomed if they are...</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">If you don't mind, I'd like to continue with my testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It was around 10 at night. Surely that must've been him fleeing the scene of his crime.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...It's true that I've been known as a prodigy from a very young age.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I graduated high school and college with exceptional grades. As class president... ...I reformed stale old school traditions. My exploits were even covered in local papers. But as exceptional as I am, I can't possibly be expected to know everything at all times.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This isn't working. He keeps bending the questions to serve his own needs.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hang in there, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson. I believe the court is well aware of your exceptional nature. Now, would you please continue with your testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. I have the upcoming election in the bag.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">A vote for me is a vote to end such violence. That is my promise to you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Elite politicians such as myself never reveal their strategies. Did you really think I would divulge such sensitive information to the likes of you?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, but, surely you have some sort of campaign platform you're running on?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">................................... ...No comment.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Clearly, his is a platform, told by an idiot, full of sound and fury, signifying nothing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">They're accusing the Defiant Dragons of murder. If this sticks, we'll lose the orb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, we need to sink Paul Atishon's testimony before it's too late. <thought>Mr. Wright is pulling out all the stops. Then again, I'd expect nothing less from him.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">He saw Mr. Are'bal from under that tree? Apollo, maybe there's some sort of an inconsistency there.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Why don't we review the evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah. Maybe there's something we overlooked.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">He didn't know the doctor was dead? Well, I guess that makes sense, considering the body was inside the study.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right, how could he have known? <thought>Guess I could find out where our weaselly witness was when he saw Datz.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">He said he saw Datz from under the tree. If that's true, then...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Did you figure something out?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I think he's hiding something. Let's take another look at the evidence, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, rather than Mr. Are'bal... ...wasn't there's something else that should've had your undivided attention?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Like what? ...Oh, yes, of course! A politician must also keep his finger on the electorate's pulse, and focus on the nation's--</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, but you're way off.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I am? Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would you care to explain, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the witness saw Mr. Are'bal from his position here... ...then he should've also been able to see the doctor's body. After all, it was right next to a huge window.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, I believe you have a point there!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">With the body THAT clearly visible to the witness... ...it's unthinkable that he wouldn't have reported it to the police!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>Did he.... fall asleep?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...........................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson!!!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Huh?! Oh, um. Hmm... There are many sides to any issue.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What did I ever do to deserve this?</thought> In any case, I'd like the court to acknowledge in the inconsistency in the witness's testimony. Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, did you really see Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes! .................. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Oh, I thought I would return to my seat, seeing as I had already answered the question.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This isn't some small town hall debate, so you just stay right there until I say we're through.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I-I'll... have to run that by my campaign manager before I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">*gulp*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Mr. Atishon-Wimperson. I think it's time for you to come clean.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Huh?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...So then, does this mean he DIDN'T see Mr. Are'bal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As your lawyer, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson... ...I advise you divulge that matter we discussed. Silence is no longer an option.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Err, are you sure about this? I'm in the midst of running for office! I can't afford to let any strange rumors get out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't worry. You won't suffer any blowback for what you're about to reveal.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">"Blowback"? I'm not sure I like the sound of that, Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not to worry, Your Honor. Nothing untoward will come of this, I promise. Now then, Mr. Justice. Remember how it was an anonymous caller that reported the doctor's death?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Come to think of it... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ema, who was the first one to discover the body?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">About that... Whoever it was, it seems they wanted to remain anonymous.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ema">It happens now and then. Some people would rather not get involved with the police.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... You're not saying that...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, that's exactly what I'm saying. The anonymous source who contacted the police after discovering the body was... ...my client, Mr. Paul Atishon-Wimperson.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What?! <thought>Y-You don't say...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So you see, he played his part as a concerned citizen -- quite admirably, if I may say so. Isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">.........Y-Yes, indeed... In our society today, there are too many who choose indifference over righteous action. But I don't number among them. That's why I did my duty as a concerned citizen. One might call me THE model citizen -- one worthy of standing above all the rest!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What a real standard-bearer he is, reporting it anonymously.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Oh, and by the way, Mr. Justice. Wasn't there someone else at the scene of the crime when my client discovered the body?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, um, you mean Mr. Are'bal? He would have been leaving the doctor's house right around then... Wait, th-that means...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, it does. In short... ...what my client witnessed was Mr. Are'bal fleeing the scene of a heinous murder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Aaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And that's not all! Based on what we've heard so far... ...Mr. Are'bal looked exceedingly suspicious, and that's putting it mildly. We already know the Defiant Dragons threatened the doctor with bodily harm. And now that they've killed him, the so-called Orb Transfer Agreement is null and void!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo! If we don't come up wit with some sort of counterargument...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A-And what sort of evidence do you have? Can you actually prove that it was Mr. Are'bal who killed the doctor?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That move had "desperate" written all over it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's all I've got, so I'm going with it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Evidence? I suppose it's true that I don't have any...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I-I knew it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But I do have another witness.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You should know I always come fully prepared, Mr. Justice. And my new witness will provide testimony proving Mr. Are'bal's guilt.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Gnrggh!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A new witness? I wonder who it could be.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Very well. Bailiff, please summon our new witness. In the meantime, the court will take a brief recess. I would like both sides to use this time to prepare properly, understood?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wow. I knew Mr. Wright would put up a tough fight, but...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah! Just when I thought we had him, he'd turn the tables on us. He really is the Turnabout Terror.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>We can't let him blindside us again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Datz">Looks like they've got me again! Three times in one year! "Datz" a new record! Har har har har har har!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Datz, please... No more new records -- or bad puns, while you're at it. It's hard enough trying to help you as it is.</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Roger that. I'll be more careful next time!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Datz, is what Mr. Wright said true? Did you really pay a visit to Dr. Buff that night?</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Sure did. Can't remember the exact time, though. All I know is he wouldn't hand over the orb. Someone put it in his head that we rebels were dangerous. That's why he threw me out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So the doctor was still alive when Datz last saw him.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">We still have to prove it, though.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">...Better brace yourself, son. The next witness's testimony could make or break this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I know. Hey, where's Trucy?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">She went to go see her dad.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... Maybe she's still mad.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">More like worried. Worried that this trial will create a rift between you two... ...and that you might then leave the agency.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ha ha ha. She has an active imagination.</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Excuse me. The trial will be resuming shortly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, let's go see what new testimony awaits us.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right, court is back in session. Mr. Wright, you said you had a witness...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Your Honor, I would like to call the lone survivor of the doctor's murder to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wait.. He can't mean... that Sarge is here?</thought> You mean Dr. Buff's reclusive kid? How did you get him to cooperate?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Nothing a little persuasion couldn't handle. The poor child only agreed to help if it meant catching the killer.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Getting a kid like that to overcome his fear... Now that's impressive.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">This must be really important testimony for the kid to come out in public like this.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Wright. Please call your witness to the stand.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Sergeant Buff, at your service, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...He's here as the drone? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Um, Mr. Wright? What exactly is the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Past trauma has rendered it impossible for the witness to venture into public. Leaving home was hard enough. And it seems leaving the witness lobby was just too much. But I would still like to continue with testimony delivered via this drone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I understand it must be terrible to lose one's father like that... ...but testimony via a remote control toy? .........Well, let's take things for a spin and see how it goes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Just who's piloting this trial, anyway?!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Athena">The judge sure warmed up to the idea fast.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I think the phrase you're looking for is "gave up."</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">You disappoint me, Corporal Justice! To think I once called you comrade!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Defending the man who killed Papa?! That's full-on treason, soldier! I hereby demote you back to "private"!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">"Corporal"? "Private"? What's he talking about, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's... a long story.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, are you ready to testify, youngster?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Locked and loaded, sir! Ready to rain lead down upon the perpetrator! Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa met with someone the night he died.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So he was thrown out, but later returned and committed the murder, did he?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, Your Honor. So the man my client saw... ...really must have been the fleeing Mr. Are'bal.</line>
<line speaker="???">Datz:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">It's the enemy! Ready all missiles! And... FIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIRE!!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha! Capitalist pig! I'll turn you into pork stroganoff! And that's just a taste of my ultimate anti-swine weapon!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Whoa! It fires missiles, too?!</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes, well, the witness is all yours, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa met with someone the night he died.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">No. I was in the midst of a crucial defensive siege operation.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right... You're referring to how you don't leave your room, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">You never know where the enemy might be lurking outside the siege perimeter.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What about, you know, school?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Oh, uhhh... I don't go to boot camp! I'm a soldier! A sergeant doesn't associate with rookies still too green to fight!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With a kid like this, I bet Dr. Buff won't be getting any rest in the afterlife, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It was very brave of you to come to the courthouse today. But what was that you said about a siege defense?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Oh, that? Well...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I didn't have eyes on the ground, as I'd already mounted my siege defense, but...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Th-That's... classified.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even so, it may be relevant to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That' right. Such matter need to be handled with a certain delicacy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, ha ha ha. I guess curiosity got the better of me.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">You're all talk and no action, soldier! Out on the battlefield, it ain't the number of pretty words in yer repertoire... ...but the number of bullets in yer gun belt that counts!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">(Easy for you to say. You're the one with all of them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the witness please tell the court what he saw and heard that night?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...I did hear him arguing with someone in his study!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I heard things like, "Where's the orb?!" and "Are you Defiant Dragons really criminals?!" It sounded real volatile, like a war might break out any second!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So the two of them had an argument when Datz came to get the orb.</thought> Did you see or hear anything else?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Yeah. I heard them arguing, and then, silence.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">From my window, I saw the one designated "Datz" getting ejected from the premises.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Like a conquered trooper retreating with his tail between his legs.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A "trooper"...? Well, I guess he does dress like he's in the military.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I bet those two would have really hit it off had they met under different circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, he couldn't exactly leave without the orb...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I bet he was angry that he'd been kicked out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">After that, the man lingered around the perimeter for some time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">He kept hiding behind trees and telephone poles, and stealing glances at our house.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, he couldn't exactly leave without the orb...)</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I bet he was angry that he'd been kicked out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">He must have regrouped and killed my papa in the study later -- I just know it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">That's true. Papa didn't keep our house locked up. He said there was no need because there were only good people in Kurain Village.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yet he ended up dead, anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Only a monster could do what they did to my kind, trusting Papa! There will be no mercy! I vow swift and terrible vengeance! I'll carpet-bomb the killer with everything in my arsenal! FIIIIIIRE!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">While I sympathize with you, witness, you will refrain from firing Gatling guns in this court.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So Sarge saw Datz, too.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And just when I thought things couldn't get any worse. I wonder why he hung around after getting thrown out?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I hate to say this, but if Datz is proven to be the killer... ...we'll lose the orb to the plaintiff. So our only option is to prove the Defiant Dragons had nothing to do with the murder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge, are you hiding something from me?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">H-How dare you question your superior officer like that! You wanna get in on this stroganoff action with pig-boy over there, soldier?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, but I'm afraid lawyers are missile-proof.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Wh-What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Would the defense care to explain?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's simple, Your Honor. Just as he is able to see what is happening in court right now... ...Sarge was able to see what happening in the study there. With his cherished drone, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">H-How dare you question your superior officer like that! You wanna get in on this stroganoff action with pig-boy over there, soldier?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ahhh! Now that you mention it... And to think, the answer was right before our eyes this whole time.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge! You were perfectly capable of patrolling the study that night! So you must've seen something!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Aaaaaaaaaagh! I'm hit! What is this strange new weaponry you're using against me?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Courtroom warriors don't use guns or missiles, because evidence is our weapon of choice! And the evidence has exposed your bald-faced lie! My truth bomb, Sarge... has stripped your defenses bare!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">A t-t... truth bomb?! Noooooooooooo! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH! Mayday, mayday!!! I'm going doooooooown!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my! Are you all right?!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">*cough* *sputter* Evidence... Never have I seen such fearsome ordnance.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Tell it to us straight, Sarge. After all, you want to help your father, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. You want to find out who killed him, don't you? So please. Tell us what you saw that night.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...It's... It's... It's not what you think. I-I... I... I didn't see anything. I swear...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...You sure? You seem awfully stressed for someone who didn't see anything.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Grrrrrrr!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">UWAAAAAAHHH! ...S-Sarge. You need to answer my question.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Shut your piehole, maggot! It'll be a scorching day in Siberia before a lowly private like you orders me around!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...What's with him and Siberia, of all places? But if a scorching day is what it'll take, then maybe it's time to turn up the heat.</thought> Hey, Athena. You think a therapy session might help?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well, it could help alleviate some of his anxiety.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Plus, I'm picking up a lot of discord in Sarge's voice. That usually means the patient wants to say something, but can't for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">And in Sarge's case, I imagine whatever's plaguing him is pretty severe. In that case, I leave it to you and your Mood Matrix magic!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it! Your Honor, I believe I can be of help here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Time for a therapy session, is it, Ms. Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. It will help the witness with his anxiety -- maybe even enough to testify!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then by all means, please prong the poor child out into the light of day. ...Oh, but I assume this will be all right with you, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why not? It's not like we all haven't been through this before.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Wh-What are you butting in for, lady?! There ain't a place on this battlefield for you!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">UWAAAAAAH! First evidence, now analytical psychology?! Where are these WMDs coming from?! ...W-Well, if it's a batle you want, bring it on! You may have started this war, but I'm going to end it, Corpswoman Cykes!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You got it, Sarge. Time to seek out the agony buried deep in your heart.</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Brace yourself!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I stayed in my room with my drone that evening.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I heard Datz and Papa arguing with each other.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Datz got kicked out, but I saw him still hanging around outside.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I was in my room, so I didn't know Papa was dead until the next day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So I'm looking for unexpected emotions and unnatural reactions, right?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Right -- emotions and reactions that don't fit the content of his testimony. When you find one, make sure you point it out to me. Also, remember not to view his emotional reactions in isolation. Sometimes, it's important to see how they change from one statement to the next.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I'll give it a try.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's strange... You reacted with shock when you discovered your father's body... ...yet, you weren't nearly as shocked then as when you saw Mr. Are'bal. Normally, you'd expect the death of one's father to be much more impactful.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Enemy fire! Direct hit!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That IS strange. I wonder what it could mean.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we know he wasn't as affected by his father's death as he should have been. And I think I know why.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge, you weren't as shocked at seeing your father's body as seeing Mr. Are'bal because...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe you were scared of him?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Why you--! How could you even THINK I was scared of that capitalist pig!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you weren't scared?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Listen up, trainee! You feckless amateurs don't even know what true fear is! Naïve little babies like you wouldn't last two seconds out there. So he's your first lesson, private! A heaping spoonful of true, battlefield terror!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I think that means you were wrong. But there's no need to look so bitter about it, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, but that was some bitter medicine... <thought>Ugh, the aftertaste of failure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Did... something else shock you when you saw Mr. Are'bal? Something even more shocking than your father's death?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm, like what exactly, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know... Maybe a mouse or a cockroach?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeuuuwww, gross!!!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Foolish cannon fodder! Vermin are powerless in the fact of my deadly arsenal! I'll pump 'em full of lead!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sounds kinda messy, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Ah! Th-Then I'll develop new weaponry! Maybe a flamethrower'd do the trick...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">S-Sure... As long as you keep it "for vermin use only"...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Guess it wasn't something like mice or cockroaches after all, huh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, but it was worth a try -- especially to see your reaction. <thought>*sigh* What else could it be...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge... Maybe the truth is, you left your room that night. And that's when you saw it -- your father's body.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I-I saw no such thing!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Really? You didn't see his body? All right then, what DID you see?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Err...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Look, Apollo! We've lost some noise!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, just as I suspected... he really did see something. Sarge! Please. Tell us what you saw.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ooh... B-But... .................. ........................... I-I... The moment I saw it, ooh... ...I-I.. I couldn't bear it. I couldn't stand  to lose yet another loved one.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? Am I missing something here?. Is that you weren't very shocked when you found out your father was dead? Because you had already sensed he was a goner somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">M-Maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Please, Sarge. What was it you saw on the night of your father's murder?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ooh... Gah gah gah gah. I-I... I saw... ...Agh. Gah. Hrgh. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! UHWOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's happening?! I don't like where this is going...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH! NO MORE! NO MORE, PLEEEEEEAAASE!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Eeeeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Widget">Help!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I've confiscated your little toy! The battlefield has no place for unauthorized equipment!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">W-Widget...! A-Apollo! I can't continue the rest of the session without him!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">C-Calm yourself this instant, witness! I hereby order you to submit to your therapy session! What in blazes...?!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Lookit me! I'm judge, jury, and executioner now! I hereby convene a military tribunal!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Whoa, whoa... This has gone way too far.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-Bailiff! Arrest that drone this instant!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">RAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAWRRRRRR!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Stop resisting! AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGGGHHHHH! If you don't come quietly, I'll--!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">FIIIIIIIIIIIIRRRE!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Give Widget back right-- EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEKKK!!!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">*huff* *puff* *cough, cough* Whew, finally got him back.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Nice work.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This witness is truly a handful.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ooh... hup, two, three, four... Uwoooooooooooooooooooooooooooh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ms. Cykes, what is the witness's current psychological state?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Let's see... He's emotionally all over the map. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So his out-of-control emotions are in control of him, huh. Does that mean we can calm him down if we can figure out the root cause?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes. So let's see what we can find. Sarge! Can you hear me?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ooh... I-Is that you, Corpswoman Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'm here. Now, I want you to take a few deep breaths. Just try to relax. Try it with me. Breathe in, breathe out. Breathe in, breathe out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">In... Out... In... Out...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And now... Let your emotions take you where they will. Go on, just let it all out!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">UHWOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH!!! All forces, attaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaack!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>...That's the LEAST relaxing breathing exercise I've ever seen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Datz was still hanging around after he got kicked out when...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...I heard more fighting, and I got worried about Papa.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">So I left my room, but suddenly...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...I got dizzy and passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I remember a flame lighting up the room...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...and Papa grinning with delight.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">That's when he must have been killed. If only I hasn't passed out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's it! Sarge... You were overcome with shock and fear when you saw those flames, weren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Was I...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes. Just six months ago... ...you and your mother were caught up in an arsonist's blaze. So it's no wonder you would be extremely scared of fire.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...Y-Yes, that does make sense.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">And maybe, just maybe... ...your subconscious fear of fire was what caused you to withdraw from the world.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What do you mean, Corpswoman Cykes?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">In the outside world, you were bound to come across all sorts of fire. Candles, cigarettes... heck, even the grill at a diner. Even if it's not that often, just the idea that you might see them... ...grew bigger and bigger until you couldn't shut it out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...! I... I think you might be onto something. Candles, cigarettes... Just thinking about them sends a chill down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Wow, the things I take for granted.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Now I see. I was afraid... Afraid of the fire. Strange, I didn't even realize it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">About that fire, Sarge... Can you tell me what it was burning?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Just say calm and maybe something will come to you.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Oh, umm... ............. ..................Oh! I'm starting to remember! I-It was...! It was that relic! That relic Papa was studying... It was on fire!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The orb... was on fire?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Mm-hm. It's still kind of fuzzy...  ...but yes, the "orb" was burning right in front of Papa. And there... in the flames was... ...Mama? Yes! Now I remember... I saw Mama appear amid the dancing flames!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wait... WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-What's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe it's a memory from the fire that killed his mother. Hmm... He might be confusing it with what really happened when his father died.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So let me guess... More therapy?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yep. But this time, it seems there's an inconsistency in his statements. And I think we should be able to prove that with the evidence at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I hope this inconsistency is the key... ...to proving that the relic is really the Founder's Orb!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Datz was still hanging around after he got kicked out when...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...I heard more fighting, and I got worried about Papa.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">So I left my room, but suddenly, I got dizzy and passed out.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">I remember a flame lighting up the room, and Papa grinning with delight.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">The relic was on fire, and I saw Mama's face inside</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">That's when he must have been killed. If only I hasn't passed out!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't blame yourself, Sarge. After all, even if you hadn't passed out... ...the outcome would've been the same.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm talking about the time of death. Your father wasn't killed right after you left your room.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Wh-What?! Explain yourself at once, Private Justice!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You said you saw your father burning the orb, right? But that night, he went out to hide it in a cave. So, what you saw, Sarge... ...was something that happened before your father left to hide the orb.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So you see, you didn't pass out right before he was killed. You passed out right before he left for the cave, to hide the orb in the ruins within.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">S-So, even if I hadn't passed out...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right. The outcome would've been exactly the same. That's because your father, Dr. Buff, was killed after he returned from the ruins. And therefore, Sarge, there's no need to blame yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Oh... I see... .............. ................................ Private Justice... Can... Can you really say I bear no blame in this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Why do you ask?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">.........Because... the truth is... ...if I hadn't engaged in my siege defense, Papa would still be alive.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sarge...</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Papa wished nothing more than for me to lead a happy, healthy life. That's why he quit his job and moved us out, away from the big city. But even then, I didn't have the courage to set foot into the outside world. And in the end... </line>
<line speaker="Sarge">.....................</line>
<line speaker="???">...Um, Sarge?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If you want to make your father's wish come true... If that's what you really want... ...then who's to say it's too late? Why don't you take the first step now?</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">...My first step?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">That's right. You can cast off all your regret. You can stop standing still and start moving forward. You have the power within you. I know from experience. I know what's it like to feel like you do. But only you... only you can decide to take the first step!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">................................ </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If you don't change your tactics now, Sarge... .. the victory you seek in the war you're waging will always lie beyond your grasp.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">................................................ Hmm... I think I understand now. I've... I've made up my mind! </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">As of this moment... ...I will suspend my siege defense indefinitely!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...............Huh?</line>
<line speaker="???">S-Sergeant Buff, r-reporting for duty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">WHAAAAAAAAAAAAT?! I-I-I thought you were a guy!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You're DEFINTELY not the gruff drill sergeant I envisioned!</line>
<line speaker="???">W-Well, my mama was in the Russian army.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was just as shocked, but it certainly explained a few things when I found out, too. May I introduce to you Miss Armie Buff, age 12.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No way...</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Careful, soldier! Don't forget I could blow you away at a moment's notice!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">S-She's just too cute...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So... Have you always been in a wheelchair, Sarge?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Negative. Only since I was injured... in the fire.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Umm... Your voice sounds awfully different from before.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">My drone features a voice modulation device. It's just one of my army's many technological marvels.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, you fooled me. I thought some twenty-something military fanatic was at the controls.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">I-If it's all the same to you, troops, I'd like to continue my testimony! I've just remembered something! And it's as crisp and clear as a trumpet at roll call.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What did you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">It wasn't my mother who appeared in the burning orb. It was some lady Papa had shown me a picture of a long time ago. He said it was the Holy Mother, the founder of Khura'inism. She appeared right there, right in the burning orb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you just say?!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Holy Mother of Khura'inism was in the burning orb? Wh-What does that even mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I have a bad feeling about this.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Could it be...? Could this explain what Sarge means by the Holy Mother appearing in the burning orb?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Armie:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">A piece of related evidence. Wouldn't you agree? Although, to be honest, I'd have to plead the fifth if you asked me how certain I was.</line>
<line speaker="Sarge">Private! Did you really think such a cockamamie plan would rout out the enemy?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yiiiiiikes! {I'd better be more careful!)</line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the orb was burning, maybe the evidence you're looking for has to do with fire.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, I know.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dr. Buff's research notes? What do they have to do with this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look at this! The burning orb, the appearance of the founder -- this part points to both!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm.. I'm not seeing it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, it's... Maybe you can explain it, Athena.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I'M not the one who's supposed to explain things when YOU'RE the one presenting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yikes, she's really mad. I'd better come up with something before her anger burns me to a crisp.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's a legend about the orb involving a mysterious riddle. And this song, in turn, is said to contain the key to solving it. If the legend is true, then I believe the answer lies in this part of the song: "Offer thy prayers as fervent as fire Only then shall the Holy Mother return." ...Well? Anyone see where I'm going with this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Prayers as fervent as fire... ...Ah! You're supposed to... set the orb on fire?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The whole stanza seems to suggest that the founder will appear if the orb is set on fire.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Wait! S-So the doctor! He...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yes, Athena. He had solved the ancient riddle of the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, my!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Papa was a great archeologist. So I believe in him... and I want to believe... I want to believe he achieved his long-time dream of solving that riddle before he died.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, we won't know for sure... until we try it for ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Yes, do it, Private Justice. Please! I want to see what Papa was searching for with my own eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Mr. Justice. I never thought I'd be saying this, but you may burn the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All right, here we go!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Look!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo! The inside of the orb... It's melting!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There's something in there... Ahhhhhhhhhh! Dh-Dhurke! Isn't she...?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Her garb leaves no room for doubt. It's the founder herself! Face and all...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I-I don't understand. The greatest taboo in Khura'inism... ...is the depiction of the founder's face. Yet here it is, hidden within this orb!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sorry, Mr. Wright, but as you can see, the issue is "crystal" clear. This figure is the Holy Mother, founder of Khura'inism. And based on that, this must be none other than the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Don't play dumb, Mr. Wright. The truth of the matter has already been proven! Dr. Buff wasn't killed right after Sarge saw Mr. Are'bal. It happened after the doctor came back from hiding the orb. And you've no proof that Mr. Are'bal was  still around at the time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Urrrrrrrgh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your claim that the Defiant Dragons were behind the crime doesn't hold water. And that means the Orb Transfer Agreement is still perfectly valid. </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Arrrrrrrgh.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Admit it, Mr. Wright. I just burned your whole case to the ground!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ooh... NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I won? I actually won?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Wright! Would you care to respond?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.........R-Respond? ...Um...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I didn't think so!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Wait, did we just win? Did we actually beat the Turnabout Terror?! You're amazing, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Don't just stand there, Wright! Do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Umm, well... I don't think there's any digging out of this hole.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, I think it's time for your concession speech. I have proven beyond a shadow of a doubt that this is the Founder's Orb. The facts don't lie, but you obviously do. How's that for a campaign slogan?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Why-Why you contemptuous peasant...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Hmmm. I think this is a good time to wrap up this trial. If both parties have no further objections, I will render my verdict.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No objections here, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Err... Um... No ob--</line>
<line speaker="???">Atishon:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, but there's really nothing more I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...You haven't forgotten about our little chat... have you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">! ..........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's going on here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't believe they have truly proven that the relic is indeed the Founder's Orb.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.......... <thought>H-He can't possibly have hit on something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. And that's what happened. The founder was revealed for all to see.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Mr. Justice, what about the rest of the legend? </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">According to the legend, once the founder returned... ...she would bestow spiritual power onto the person who solved the riddle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..........Y-You're kidding, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Mr. Justice? Do you feel great spiritual power coursing through your veins?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um.......... no. B-But receiving spiritual powers and stuff... it's all just mystic mumbo-jumbo, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maybe so, but you're the one basing your claim on said legend. And what we saw here does not fully fulfill it, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">N-No, but...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Consequently... You cannot rightfully claim that this is the Founder's Orb!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">..........</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">..........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">..........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's gotten into him? Why is Mr. Wright doing this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It would appear that Mr. Wright has lost a few of his marbles.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Th_That couldn't be further from the truth, Your Honor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In any case... I believe this ai good time for a recess. Both sides will have 20 minutes to prepare. I ask that all arguments be ready by then. Oh, and Mr. Wright? You'd do well to wash up and find your missing marbles by then, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">....................</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Mr. Wright is sure acting funny. I mean, he's famous for going out on a limb, but that last assertion was just plain crazy.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's either a bluff or a Hail Mary. Either way, it doesn't make much sense.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Maybe there's something we're missing here. Although, he seemed perfectly normal when we spoke earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">...Apollo, I have a bad feeling about this. I'm going to go check up on him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's going on with you, Mr. Wright...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hey. Private Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, Sarge.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">I forgot to mention something. O-On the night of Papa's murder, a strange thing happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh? But why are you only telling me about it now?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Well... I didn't say anything before because I thought Papa's death was an accident. But now that we know otherwise, I figured it might be important.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>There's still more to this case?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armie">When I left my room and lost consciousness, I passed out right here. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That's right above the coffee bar.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">Mm-hm. But when I came to... ...someone was pushing my wheelchair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">I was so scared, I beat a hasty retreat -- as fast as my wheels would take me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you know who it was?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">No. It was pitch black. Plus, I fled to my room so fast, I didn't even have a chance to turn on the lights.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Maybe it was your father.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">No, he would have said something to me. Besides, I'd have known if it was him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So then, it could've been... ...your father's real killer?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">My thoughts exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But you didn't report this to the police?</line>
<line speaker="Armie">...I-It didn't even occur to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It's okay. You were obviously still upset, so don't bear yourself up over it.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Apollo, this could be really important information. I think the act of pushing Sarge's wheelchair could be part of some bigger scheme. It's hard to see why else the killer would do such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I should take her statement down as evidence.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, welcome back, Athena. ...Hm? <thought>What's with the long face?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">..........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">How'd it go with Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.......... What should I...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Oops, sorry! Zones out there for a sec. The recess is almost over, so let's go! Ha, a-ha-ha.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">........ <thought>What was that all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">All right. Court is, once again, back in session. Now, umm... Mr. Wright. About that last objection you raised...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We, the plaintiffs, still believe that the defense has yet to sufficiently prove its case. They claim that, according to legend, the Founder's Orb would bestow spiritual power... ...yet the relic in question has failed to do so. Therefore, it has failed its own test.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-I see...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>He's sticking with that ridiculous argument?</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Furthermore... ...even if is the Founder's Orb, it can't be awarded to the Defiant Dragons can't take it. After all, they were the ones who killed Dr. Buff.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, but I'm afraid there are, Mr. Justice. ...Your Honor. I would like to present new testimony to this court. Testimony that will show that Datz Are'bal did, in fact, kill Dr. Buff!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You may call your witness.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I guess Mr. Wright found another new angle.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What new testimony could there be this late in the game?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Fellow citizens! It is I, Paul Atishon, the once and future representative of the people!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Jeez, not him again.</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">My client divulged new information to me during the recess. He remembered something he saw, you see -- something crucial to this case.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>How very convenient...</thought> </line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It was around 11 at night, and I was out on a mobile meet-and-greet around the village.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You saw the murder as it happened?! And you're just telling us this now because...?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. I saved the best for last. It's a tactic known to all the political greats.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The murder weapon was a complete mystery... ...but my client's eyewitness account has finally brought it to light.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">According to the autopsy report... ...Dr. Buff was struck in the head by the corner of some object. I suppose that could very well be the corner of a suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, I wouldn't worry about that if I were you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have physical evidence, too. A luminol test revealed... ...the doctor's blood on Mr. Are'bal's suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Really?! But how does that prove that Mr. Are'bal used it as a weapon?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! <thought>I forgot we'd dusted it right in front of Ema!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">The Turnabout Terror strikes again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... This is quite convincing testimony and evidence. Nevertheless, you may proceed with your cross-examination, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">It was around 11 at night, and I was out on a mobile meet-and-greet around the village.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. It's the perfect time because everyone is at home. You should have seen how the villagers' eyes teared up when they heard what I had to say.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>With tears of frustration, no doubt.</thought> You weren't riding around in your palanquin?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. Some village idiot reported me to the police. I've been banned from using it after dark.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">No wonder, what with all the noise he makes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, what exactly did you see, then?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's when I saw Dr. Buff being murdered from outside his study window!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Indeed. I didn't even believe it at first. I mean, a vicious murder, in Kurain?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There haven't been many murders there, I take it?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">If I'm elected, I promise you that such a terrible tragedy will never happen again! A vote for me is a vote to banish murder forever from our beloved Kurain Village!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Yeah, good luck with that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, please tell the court what you saw at the scene of the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Mr. Are'bal snuck up from behind and struck him on the head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. He was utterly absorbed in a book. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...I see. What did you see Mr. Are'bal do next?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">He climbed up the bookshelf ladder and dumped a bunch of books down on the body. I believe he was trying to make it look like an accident. But that idiot didn't realize I could see everything from outside the window.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>One of those statements doesn't feel right.</thought> Your Honor, I believe the witness made an important statement just now about how...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If the crime was visible through the window, that's earth-shattering testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Is it? Because to my ears, it sounds like a rather obvious fact.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Oh, sorry. I'm good, then.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Very well. Will the witness please continue with his testimony?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor was reading a book at the time of the murder...? That's vital testimony!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The witness will please add that statement to his testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Add statement">"The doctor was standing in front of the bookshelves, absorbed in a book."</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The witness said Mr. Are'bal is an idiot. That's a key piece of information!</line>
<line speaker="Datz">Don't you jump on the bandwagon, AJ! I'm no idiot, you hear!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... I fail to see how that is a key piece of information.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Yeah, I guess it's not, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Then it seems there is no need to add it into the witness's testimony. So let's get on with it, shall we?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">The doctor was standing in front of the bookshelves, absorbed in a book.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I'm a politician, not a superhero! I'm under no obligation to risk life and limb.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">He's sure quick to deny his obligations when there's nothing in it for him.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm getting tired of listening to his endless campaigning and flimsy rationalizations.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">About your testimony, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson... You said Mr. Are'bal struck the doctor from behind when he was absorbed in a book.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yes, that's exactly what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">His weapon of choice: a suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Positive. I saw it with my own two eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yet, despite your certainty, you kept quiet about it until now?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">No, I was waiting. I knew there would be a perfect chance to talk about it later. Information must always be disclosed in a strategic manner. That is one of the lessons of kingcraft, as taught by the Atishon clan.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Is there a lesson, by chance, in the Atishon Kingcraft Guidebook on being honest?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Anyway, I saw Mr. Are'bal commit that heinous crime.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">A big, strong man like him could easily swing a heavy suitcase into someone's head.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo: </line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Gnrk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>But I'm just doing what you always do, Mr. Wright!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Talk about new testimony. He's totally changed his story.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">If he had really seen the murder taking place, you'd think he'd have said so from the start.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe he had some reason to hide what he really saw?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>If so, that might be our only opening.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Dr. Buff was struck from behind while he was absorbed in a book? He must've been really into it.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmm... It doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">What doesn't?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>That Paul Atishon is lying. I'm sure of it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The doctor was standing in front of the bookshelves, absorbed in a book, you say? I'm sorry, but it seems your testimony is completely unreliable.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's quite a bold statement. Well, let's hear you back it up. I challenge you to prove that I am anything but 100% reliable.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">It would be my pleasure. Lately, it seems that the doctor's eyes had gotten so bad, he needed reading glasses. However, his reading glasses were over on his desk. So you see, there's no way he could've been reading a book in front of the bookshelves!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Hrrrrrrngh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm sorry, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, but... ...I'm going to have to ask you to explain this discrepancy to the voting public!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ngah, gah gah gah! I-I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You what?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I-I'll explain it, you lowly cur! I simply made a mistake, you see. The doctor was actually sitting at his desk when Mr. Are'bal hit him over the head!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But then the doctor would have been facing him. Surely he would've seen him and tried to run?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">D-Dr. Buff was nodding off! I could tell because he his eyes were closed, and he wasn't moving!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds more like what you would do.</thought> Then how do you explain the back that he was struck in the back of the head? Isn't that something that should be impossible from the front of the desk?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Oh, um... About that... H-He... He bowed his head when he nodded off. That's when he was clobbered.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... So that's what you saw. Well, Mr. Justice, that sounds like a perfectly reasonable explanation to me. Do you have a problem with the proposal that the doctor was struck while nodding off?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No problem here, Your Honor. The doctor was probably dozing, just as the witness said.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">N-No, Apollo! Wait! If you accept that, then you might as well admit Datz killed the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Your Honor! I, uh, actually do have a problem with that statement...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. But let's avoid careless answers like that, or I will have a problem with you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Guess I blew that one.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, as you were saying, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">There is a problem. A very big problem. The witness's statement doesn't hold up under the slightest bit of scrutiny!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so? Then will you please show this court what evidence you have to justify this?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Gladly, Your Honor. This shows the problem with the witness's claim that he saw the doctor nodding off!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...............Zzz...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">See? The witness has passed out from the overwhelming power of my evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No, Mr. Justice. Your lackadaisical attempt to refute him put my client to sleep. That's all.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I feel a yawn coming on myself. Perhaps giving you this penalty will wake me up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Surely there are better ways to stay awake, Your Honor?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, think about the relative positions of the witness and doctor again.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. That's where we'll find the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, Mr. Justice. See that you avoid these snooze-incusing answers in the future.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...A diagram of the study?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson allegedly viewed the murder from... ...here. And the doctor was allegedly nodding off... ...here. But from his vantage point, the bookcase would've blocked the witness's line of sight.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Why, yes, I believe you're right!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">B-B-But...! Arrrgh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm afraid I have to agree with you there, Mr. Wright. But then we have to ask ourselves, from what vantage point did he see the murder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What are you insinuating, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">From what vantage point could Mr. Atishon-Wimperson have seen the dozing doctor? Once we determine that, I believe we'll finally see the truth behind this incident. The witness saw the murder from... right here!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, umm... He just did somehow? I mean, I just feel like it must've been from there.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Um, Apollo? for some reason, I feel like you're wrong.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... And for some reason, I feel like giving you a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So much for that spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... Looking at it in another way... ...where must Mr. Atishon-Wimperson have been standing to see the doctor nodding off?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Someplace where the bookcase wasn't blocking his view, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. Will the defense please indicate where the witness saw the murder from?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You've got to be kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">B-But that's--!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">it is indeed. But everything only makes sense if the witness was there in the study.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">I-Inside the study? But that's the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. Mr. Atishon-Wimperson -- the man who claims to be a witness to the murder... ...was most certainly in that very room.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A-Apollo, are you suggesting...?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson! Weren't YOU the one who actually swung that suitcase?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Gaaaaaaaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>He has a point... I gave up trying to lift that thing after one go.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">That's right. He's the only one who could've lifted such a heavy object. Now do you understand? The rebel Datz Are'bal is the doctor's killer!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">As long as the suitcase is the murder weapon, the suspicion falls entirely on Datz. You'll have to poke a hole in Mr. Wright's argument somehow, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I will. And with his own technique, no less. If Mr. Atishon-Wimperson couldn't swing the suitcase around... ...we'll just have to consider another way he could've used it as a murder weapon instead. I'm going to turn this case on its head, Mr. Wright, just like you taught me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...You talk big, Mr. Justice, but do you have what it takes?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this should be interesting...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo:">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson's testimony has been filled with one inaccuracy after another. First he stated Dr. Buff was in front of the bookshelves. Now he claims that the doctor was sitting at his desk. So where was the victim REALLY when he was killed? Also, where was his killer, and how was the murder weapon REALLY used?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So the important thing here is the position of the victim and killer related to each other?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Your Honor. If they were positioned a certain way... ...it would be possible to use the suitcase as a weapon without lifting a finger.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You can't mean...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I would ask the court to recall the study's layout. It's quite distinctive, as you can see. Now, if Dr. Buff were sitting in a certain spot, and his killer was at a certain other spot... ...the suitcase would become a weapon ANYONE could use!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Very well, Mr. Justice. Where was Dr. Buff's killer at the time of the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes, I would love to see a demonstration.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Um, well... I can't from here..</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, I have a demonstration for you from here... on how to give a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>So much for that spot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">If the killer didn't swing the suit case, there aren't many other ways to use it as a weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I know. And there aren't that many places to use it from, either.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then. I hope the defense is ready to try again.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Th-There...?!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh... That's...</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Yaaaaaaargh!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>I'm not so sure about that, Mr. Wright. I'd say that evidence of the murder occurring at the coffee bar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Obviously, there is none!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just as I thought. So, if the coffee bar isn't where the doctor was killed... ...the defense's little theory fails to bear fruit</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... Mr. Wright is correct, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Urk! ...Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Don't just stand there, Apollo! If you don't do something quick, we're going to lose both the orb AND the creep, together!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I'm thinking... I'm thinking... Oh! <thought>Wait a second... There IS a piece of evidence that proves the doctor was killed at the coffee bar!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, such evidence never existed in the first place, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The evidence does exist, and I'm going to show you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-You are?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This, right here, is proof that the murder took place at the coffee bar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You don't, Your Honor? Well, I believe Mr. Wright understands perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">All I know is, it's perfectly clear you don't understand what you're talking about.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now that is something I can understand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Me too... Oww.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Apollo, let's take another look at that crime scene photo. Maybe there's something in it related to the coffee bar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I've got it this time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">This brown stain was determined to be coffee. What's more, it was still a bit damp when we saw it yesterday morning.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">One look at this book speaks volumes, I'm afraid, Mr. Wright. It tells us the doctor was having a cup of coffee at the coffee bar. That's when the suitcase came hurtling down, striking him on the head... ...causing both his blood and his coffee to spatter onto it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ack!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Aaaaaaagh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson?!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">.........Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh... What motive could I possibly have to kill Dr. Buff?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>And there it is. That final excuse cornered killers are so fond of.</thought> Well, the doctor never returned your "crystal" to you, did he? Instead, he hid it in the cave ruins. </line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Nngh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Telling him that the Defiant Dragons were a dangerous bunch was a huge blunder. All it did was make him hide the orb. Your lie came back to bite you in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Even worse, the doctor saw the news reports, so he knew the relic was the Founder's Orb. Being the conscientious researcher he was, he knew he had to return it to its rightful place... ...and that meant keeping it out of your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Aaaaaaaaaaaaah...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You were so angry that he refused to return the relic to you... ...that you killed him with your own hands. Isn't that right, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Arrrrrraaaaaagh! .........I-I-I... Th-That is...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">.........Huh? What do you mean, "don't accuse him"? Why would you even say that. Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Er, what I meant was, um... He's a promising politician with a bright future ahead of him. It's in our nation's best interest to avoid burdening him with the taint of scandal.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Say what?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Wright! You'd better do something to change the current courtroom climate... ...or I'll be charged with murder! And you know what will happen to her if that happens.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Arngh!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What's he talking about? Well, I can ponder that later. For now...</thought> Mr. Wright, you can't possibly believe that Mr. Are'bal is the killer. Are you really going to send an innocent man to prison? I thought you were better than that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uhhh... Ummm... </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Mr. Wright? Answer me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Errr... Ummm... UUHWOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOH!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">M-M-Mr. Wright? ...What in the world's going on here?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">.........</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...If you won't say anything, then...! Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, the defense hereby accuses you of--</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Not you, too, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm... It's just, uhhh... I wasn't sure whether I should say anything, but... ...during that last recess, when I went to check on Mr. Wright... ...I overheard something I shouldn't have.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I trust Maya is unharmed.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I can't really say. But just remember... I'm I'm arrested or fail to obtain the treasure... ...there will be consequences. Consequences of the worst kind, if you catch my drift.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Augh!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Relax. All you have to do is ensure I get my hands on that relic. I must deliver it to my benefactor at all costs.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do they want that relic for anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. It's something to do with an old legend. My patron seeks the great power said to be granted to whoever solves its secret.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">....Maya? As in Maya Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yes, the boss's legendary former assistant. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ms. Fey's being held hostage?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">So it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Why didn't you tell me as soon as you heard this?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Sorry. It's just, Mr. Wright spotted me before I could slip away... ...and made me promise not to tell you. He said it would make things more difficult if you found out.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arngh! As if things weren't already hard enough! <thought>So that's why Mr. Wright was acting so strange. I had no idea. This must've been excruciating for him. Think, Justice... There's got to be something you can do!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Justice, about that last statement of yours... I believe you were in the middle of accusing the plaintiff of murdering Dr. Buff... Would you care to continue?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ack! I-I...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Nngh... I'm sorry, Apollo... I'm really, really sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What's gotten into you two?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">......... <thought>If I accuse that slimebag, I put Ms. Fey's life in jeopardy.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. It seems you've finally caught on. I'm far too important to be accused of murder. After all, our nation's future rests squarely on my shoulders. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Nnrgh... Either I give up, or...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Once I present the crystal to my patron, my victory is assured! Then one day, I'll become president -- and then, king! I'll have every politician at my command! Now, retract your accusation!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Arrrrrrnnngh! <thought>I can't kowtow to him, but... but...</thought> The defense would... It would like to retract... the previous accusati--</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Dhurke:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Dh-Dhurke?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">I don't know what's going on here... ...but a lawyer should never look the way you do right now... ... with "defeat" and "resignation" written all over your face.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Even when wounded, a dragon bites down hard, and never lets go till its dying breath. It glares, it roars, and it latches its jaws firmly onto its prey till the bitter end. That's what lawyers do to get to the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Dhurke. <thought>A dragon never yields... ...He's right. It's all over if I give up now! If Mr. Wright's hands are tied, it's up to me to do what must be done! He's saved my neck so many times. Now... it's my turn to save his!</thought> ...Dhurke, thanks for that wake up call.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Heh, now that's the face of a lawyer you've got there, son.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Where there's a will, there's a way. And I'm going to find the way to save Ms. Fey AND see that justice is served!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That scumbag is holding Ms. Fey hostage to ensure he gets the orb for his patron. And it seems said patron believes in the orb's legend. Thing is, the founder DID appear when the orb was exposed to fire, as the legend said. If the legend is true, then we've already solved the riddle, right?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, we've definitely solved the riddle! ...And yet... ...we still don't understand what the part about "bestowing power" is talking about. I need to rethink this!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The legend says that the founder will bestow great power when she returns. But if that's true, it means we haven't solved the whole riddle yet. But how can that be? Are we missing something? ...Wait, maybe... Maybe the part about the founder returning should be taken literally. But how would it be possible for a dead person to return to the world of the living?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I know! Cloning technology! I bet some of the founder's DNA is hidden somewhere in the orb. ...Argh, what am I talking about? They didn't know about DNA and cloning back then. I'd better think of something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I know! Time travel! We could go back to the past and bring the founder here to the present. ...Wait, what am I saying? Maybe I should cut back on the sci-fi movies. I'd better think of something else.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, I know! here IS a way for the dead to return -- spirit channeling! Of course, you'd have to know what he founder looks like first... ...but the orb has revealed her face to us, so what if it's a sign that we should channel her? Given the facts, in order to solve the riddle and receive the founder's power, I'd need...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All I have to do is train as a spirit medium, so I can channel spirits myself! ...Wait, it can't be that easy. And if I ever did become a medium, I wouldn't need the founder's power anymore anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The ability of a medium to channel spirits is the final key to unlocking the orb's secret. That means Mr. Atishon-Wimperson's patron will need one, too. And once that slimy politician realizes that, he won't be able to lay a finger on Ms. Fey!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Everything is going to be okay, Mr. Wright. Because Mr. Paul Atishon-Wimperson can't afford to harm a hair on Ms. Fey's head.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">............Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson! It seems you've chosen the wrong person to take hostage.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Wh-What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your patron seeks to solve the orb's riddle... ...and thereby receive great spiritual power. However, only Maya Fey can truly give them what they really want.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She can?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">What do you mean, "only Maya Fey"?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Think about what the return of the founder really means. We should have considered it more literally. After all, the orb was made in the Kingdom of Khura'in -- the birthplace of spirit mediums.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...Ahh, I think I see now. You need to know what the deceased looks like in order to channel them. But in Khura'inism, depicting the face of the founder is taboo. However, her true face was hidden in the orb. So maybe the orb is telling us... to try channeling the founder.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Exactly. Through a spirit medium, the founder can quite literally return. And if the legend is true... ...the founder just might bestow spiritual power on someone when she does.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's like when Pearls imbued my magatama with spiritual power. If a human could be imbued with such power in a similar manner...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">It is said the founder possesses immense spiritual power. Such a great feat would not necessarily be beyond her-- W-Wait a second! Th-Then the legend is true?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Do you understand now, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson? You are holding hostage the final key to unlocking the orb's secret. And if anything were to happen to her, the riddle would remain unsolved, forever!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="???">Atishon:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She's not the kind of person to be tempted by material gain. And she certainly wouldn't help you if anything were to happen to her cousin.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Urhgk.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Or maybe you'd like to go ask the queen of Khura'in to channel the founder for you.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He could, but he'd probably get executed for requesting such a thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...It's over. Now, confess! You killed Dr. Buff, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ack! Hrrrrrrrrrrrrrngh! It wasn't supposed to end this way!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Mr. Atishon-Wimperson. Are you admitting to committing the crime?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Errr... Um, I-I-I... You're my lawyer, Wright! Do something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's true that I'm your lawyer. And as such, it's my job to defend you. ...However, defending my client isn't the only job a lawyer has. There's something else that's equally as important. And that is finding the truth. </line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Wh-What?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">! <thought>Mr. Wright...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't allow a murderer to walk away scot-free! Therefore, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, I must resign as your attorney.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">No no no no noooo! D-Does this mean... I'm under arrest? NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...I've nothing to confess.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">I said, I've nothing to confess! I don't and I won't, especially not to a plebeian like you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>This guy doesn't know when to give up.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Besides, there's no truth to these allegations! I mean, look at the suitcase. You won't find a single print of mine on it!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">All that means is that you wiped them off, taking care to only leave Mr. Are'bal's.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Heh heh heh. As many a great politician has said before me: no comment.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">In that case, try switching things up, Apollo. Look at the situation from a different angle. Is there really nothing that points to the suitcase being dropped from above?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Hmmm... Evidence that points to the suitcase being dropped from the second floor...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Hmm... If the killer pushed the suitcase from the second floor hallway over the coffee bar... ...that would place him right around here.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ah! Maybe... Just maybe...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thought of something, Apollo?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I believe this piece of evidence to be connected to the dropping of the suitcase.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Atishon:</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, I don't see how that could possibly be related.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Oh, it's not? Tsk, I just wasted a perfectly good reaction! Your Honor! Penalize this pernicious peon!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm.. Yes, well, we all must be held accountable for our words and actions.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What do you think I'm trying to do with Mr. Atishon-Wimperson, Your Honor?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">So the killer dropped the suitcase from above the coffee bar.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Right. Let's look again to see if we have any evidence related to that event.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Come on, Apollo. I'm counting on you.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That... appears to be a statement. But how is it relevant to his case?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the night of the murder, Your Honor, Miss Armie Buff physically left her room. That's when she saw the doctor burning the orb, and subsequently passed out. ...Right above the coffee bar. But with her there in her wheelchair... ...the killer wouldn't have been able to drop the suitcase down onto the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Good point!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">However, according to Sarge... ...she woke up just as someone was trying to move her in her wheelchair.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">...someone was pushing my wheelchair.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">I was so scared, I beat a hasty retreat -- as fast as my wheels would take me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">She must've been in the killer's way and had to be moved. Isn't that right, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson?</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">...Agrk!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And if the killer had pushed the wheelchair with his bare hands... ...we may yet find the conclusive evidence we need.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Honestly, that piece of evidence wasn't even supposed to be here in this courtroom today. And yet... It looks like sometimes, things DO get better.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Unngh! B-B-B-B-But...! Th-This... This wasn't supposed to happen!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No? Well, too bad. Because the evidence that sped away from you that night... ...has come back to haunt you! Right here at this very trial!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">ARGH! UHWAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Your Honor! The defense's final piece of evidence is on this person!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Phoenix:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yes, Mr. Wright?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Umm, I think he's saying that that doesn't jive with anything you've said so far.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It seems Ms. Cykes is the more sensible of you two.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ugh... No need to compare the two of us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did the killer have to move in order to drop the suitcase? Consider that, and the rest should follow.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Okay, I'll get it for sure this time!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Th-That's...!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">On the night of the murder, Sarge passed out... ...only to come to and find that someone was pushing her wheelchair. That's when she fled back into her room.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She didn't physically see a single soul after that... Not until Athena drew her out through that therapy session, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">While the killer was able to wipe the prints on the suitcase... ...the same can't be said for the prints that got away.</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ah. Ah. My fellow Kurainians...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, Mr. Atishon-Wimperson? Try to explain your way out of this one! The podium is all yours!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ah. Ah. P-Paul Atishon, savior of Kurain... I-I... I am not a crook... I... My political career...! It can't end like this! I-I'm destined for great things! Something's wrong... This isn't real! It's a dream! No, a nightmare! Ooooooooooooooooooooh. Huh? What? ...Wait? ...Really? Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">Ahhhhhh! Whoa, no waaaaaaaaay!!! BANZAI! BANZAI! BANZAI! BANZAI!!!</line>
<line speaker="Atishon">................Wait, what? No, please. Wait. Don't go! No... No... Please...Whoa! Grandpaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah! ........................</line>
<line speaker="Judge">M-Mr. Atishon-Wimperson? Are you all right? ...B-Bailiff! Get him to the first-aid station, on the double!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, this was yet another unexpected turn of events. In light of everything that's been revealed, it seems that this relic is indeed the Founder's Orb. And it seems Mr. Paul Atishon-Wimperson can be considered a suspect in Dr. Buff's murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apollo, I want to thank you for everything.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks to you, I didn't have to keep bending the truth. I don't know what I would've done without you.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Er, don't mention it, ha ha ha...</line>
<line speaker="Athena">You were amazing today, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, I couldn't have done it without Dhurke.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Even when wounded, a dragon bites down hard, and never lets go till its dying breath. It glares, it roars, and it latches its jaws firmly onto its prey till the bitter end. That's what lawyers do to get the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>A dragon never yields... Every lawyer should take that to heart.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">As it seems  both sides have no objections... ...would Dhurke Sahdmadhi please take the stand?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">..........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court awards the orb to the Defiant Dragons per the stated transfer agreement. Should the Kingdom of Khura'in claim ownership... ...the matter may have to be deliberated in court all over again. I just hope, or shall I say pray, that I'm not the judge presiding over that one!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Hah-ha ha ha ha ha! Indeed! A trial like that might  spark an international incident. Still, there are bigger and more momentous things astir in the air!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>The revolution... Dhurke's really serious about this.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">This court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Nice work, son! We've finally broken through the last obstacle on the road to revolution!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Revolution... It just doesn't seem real.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Yes, well, to think you actually defeated the Fighting Phoenix... All I can say is, that's my boy! Hah-ha ha ha ha ha!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Well, Mr. Wright did have his hands tied. Who knows if I'd have won if he'd been able to fight me head-on.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">I see it more like you saved Mr. Wright.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Saved him?</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Yeah, remember what he said? He didn't have to bend the truth anymore, and it was all thanks to you!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I don't know about that. <thought>Still, I guess it IS kinda nice to be appreciated.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Trucy">...Um, Mr. Dhurke? Now that the Holy Mother's face has been revealed... ...are you going to have a spirit medium try channeling her? I, for one, would love to see the return of the legendary founder!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, just think about it. Being able to speak to someone right out of the history books...</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Unfortunately, it's not that easy. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo">What? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">A face isn't enough. You also need the true name of the one you're attempting to channel.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Pearl mentioned something like that.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">And the founder's name is only known to the priestess who's been crowned queen. In short, the only person who knows it is the current queen of Khura'in, Ga'ran.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, so without her help, we won't be seeing the founder anytime soon?</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Tsk, that's no fun.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">So, Dhurke, what will you do now?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">First, I'll start tracking the route by which the orb came into Dr. Buff's hands.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Since we now know it was Paul Atishon that asked the doctor to study it... ...isn't he the one who stole it?</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">No, a political nobody like him couldn't get anywhere near the orb, let alone steal it. He must've had inside help. My money is on someone connected to the royal family.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. You said something to that effect back in the cave.</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Whoever it may be, we need to expose their dirty scheme to the light of day.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, I'm sure Mr. Wright has plenty of information, courtesy of his dirty client. He might be able to shed some light on this.</line>
<line speaker="???">Private Justice! </line>
<line speaker="Sarge">That was fine work you did at the trial today! You did your sergeant proud!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">It's all thanks to you and Corpswoman Cykes. With my siege defense over, I can finally sally forth. </line>
<line speaker="Sarge">But the battle's only just begun! One for me, and me alone, to fight!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">To lose your mother, and then your father... What a terrible thing to endure.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah... <thought>And being wheelchair-bound doesn't help.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armie">...Private Justice! I've been thinking... It's about time I stood on my own two feet. After all, I no longer have Papa to coddle me!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh? I'm afraid I don't follow.</line>
<line speaker="Armie">...Take a good look, soldier. This is one small step for man... ...and one giant leap for me! ......... Hold my drone for me, would you, Private Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Y-Yes, sir. <thought>What she is up to?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armie">.........Hrgh! Wh-Whoa...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Sh-Sh-She's... standing?!</line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Wh-What's this?! Sarge! You mean your legs... They're...?!</line>
<line speaker="Armie">The doctor told me that I was ready to walk again months ago. But if I admitted I could walk, I knew I would have to leave the house. So I... I faked it. </line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Makes sense, but...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Armie">I kept pretending I couldn't walk. But I know Papa is watching over me now, and I's hate to disappoint him. So, from this day forth, I'm going to march forward on my own two feet!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>What a brave kid, trying to move forward like this. But it must be so hard this soon after her father's death.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Dhurke">Don't you ever stop. You just keep on walking... comrade. Stay brave, because there will be days when you want to stop... ...but I have faith you'll find a way to muster the strength to push through them.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah, you can do it.</line>
<line speaker="Trucy">Hey, Daddy's back!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">.....................</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Mr. Wright! <thought>What's that look on his face for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, Apollo!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um, is everything all right with Ms. Fey?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">She's safe... for now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Well then, we'd better go save her, quick! Where is she, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...I'm afraid I have some bad news.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya's... not here in the States. She's still in Khura'in. And she's still being held hostage by the mastermind behind this whole thing.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">The mastermind?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...That's right. Paul Atishon-Wimperson was nothing more than a pawn. Maya's true abductor is in the Kingdom of Khura'in.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Wh-Whaaaaaaaaaaaat?! I-I don't understand, Mr. Wright! What in the world's going on over there?!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">But as shocking as that news was... ...it was only the beginning. The beginning of something big -- big enough to shake Khura'in to its very core. ...Revolution. I was being swept up in a mighty wave that nothing could stop. Of course, at the time... I had no idea what the days ahead had in store for us...</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm looking... But what am I supposed to see?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, um... Uhhh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">As your boss and mentor, here's a bit of advice: Never present evidence before you have a good grasp of the situation at hand.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">R-Right... Sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And as the presiding judge, here's a penalty.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Ouch. Double-teamed for doing what Mr. Wright always does anyway.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... And just how does it contradict with the evidence, Mr. Justice?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Um... Could I have about five minutes to figure out the answer to that?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The defense will figure it out before he presents his evidence next time!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Sounds like a plan...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm... It seemed perfectly reasonable to me.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">No, something's definitely not right if you listen really carefully!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A gambler once sang, you've got to know when to hold 'em, when to fold 'em...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh, I love this one! ...Know when to walk away, know when to run!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>I don't know which penalty hurts more: the judge's or their singing.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Is it just me, or does that statement sound a bit dubious?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">You know what... you're right. Thanks, Athena!</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Anytime!</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Now to take another look at the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">You look like you've hit a brick wall, Apollo.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Yeah. It feels like I have, too.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">Maybe you just haven't brought all the facts to light. Why don't you try pressing a little more?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Good idea. <thought>Okay, time to turn up the pressure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Oh, right. Thanks for the reminder, Athena. <thought>All right, let's try that again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Athena:</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">I could sure use a clue or two right about now.</line>
<line speaker="Athena">A person's personality and past shapes their emotional responses. Consider everything you know about Sarge. That's where you'll find the clues you need.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo"><thought>Everything I know about Sarge...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Apollo:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is that so? Would you be so kind as to point it out to the court?</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">...Well if you're going to put me on the spot like that, I admit my confidence is waning.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I could say the same about my confidence in you, Mr. Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Ugh. <thought>I wish you wouldn't, Your Honor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Athena">Say, Apollo... Sarge is saying that his father was burning the orb when he was killed... ...but doesn't that seem funny to you? Considering what the doctor was up that night, it doesn't add up.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">Well, now that you mention it... <thought>All right, I'd better look through the evidence one more time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough! I see no need to further prolong this trial. The Defiant Dragons have failed to sufficiently show their right to the item in question. Therefore, ownership is hereby awarded to... ...the plaintiff, Mr. Paul Atishon.</line>
<line speaker="Apollo">That creep Paul Atishon stole the Founder's Orb right out of our hands. The dream of revolution in the Kingdom of Khura'in died that day. And we returned to our daily lives. As for my relationship with Mr. Wright... The word awkward comes to mind. Let's just say it was never really the same.</line>
</xml>