<xml>
<title>Turnabout Goodbyes</title>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey! Nick, it's you! I'm glad Mr. Edgeworth made it through the day okay. It's a relief...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey. Why'd you do that, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... I don't know. I... just knew I had to do something. I know I'm not the lawyer my sister was... ... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, you did save the trial... Just, behave from now on, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">O... okay.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you been questioned yet?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No... not yet. Detective Gumshoe was here just now. He said "seeing as this is your first offense, we'll let you go after questioning."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whew...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, and he wanted me to get bail money ready. You can pay for me, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How much?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know. I guess they'll send you a bill or something.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Why do I picture giant bales of money every time I hear the word "bail"?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Any luck with Mia...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">None... I can't get through to her at all. I tried... I really did! I don't know what to do... ... I think I probably shouldn't have stopped my training.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... she sounds like she really did do her best. I should check and see if there are any waterfalls in the local area...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wonder if I'll ever see my sister again...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It must be nice, Nick. You can just show that to anyone and say "I'm a lawyer!" But, spirit mediums, well...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I dunno, with your clothes, I bet at least some people would recognize you...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">But these are medium-in-training clothes... I wonder if I'll ever be a proper medium...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Isn't that the enlarged photo Lotta was talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh huh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh... It's nice and big... but you can't really see the faces any clearer, can you?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">My... mother. ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now that I've shown her the picture, I'm not so sure it was the right thing to do. No... I'm pretty sure it was the wrong thing to do.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">I want to see Gourdy, too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">If he really exists.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I'd say a photograph is pretty good proof! Once this trial is over, let's get some fishing poles and go down to the lake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Even if there is a monster in that lake, fishing poles sound like a BAD idea...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">So the markings on this bullet and the barrel of the pistol matched?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, I'm surprised you remembered that!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How could I forget after von Karma rubbed it in so much? So, which one of these are the ballistic markings?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm... not really sure.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Edgeworth's prints are on this pistol, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes... the prints from his right hand. But they must have gotten on there at some other time other than the shooting.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What? Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The shooter used his left hand, after all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry... I'm fresh out of ideas.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... Sure is quiet here with nobody around. Right... I have to get Maya out of that detention cell soon!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Detective Gumshoe's not here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Police">Gumshoe's at the scene again today.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Police">He's a live wire that one. Got into a fight with the chief for not following protocol...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Not following protocol...? I bet he wouldn't help them build the case against Edgeworth...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"Don't do anything rash! Why jump...? ...You have every reason to live!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for talking down a potential suicide.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This must be the chief of the detectives here. He's glued to his computer screen.</line>
<line speaker="Chief">Wha...!? Rook to Bishop 7... Checkmate!? I don't believe it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be playing chess on the computer...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Apparently, Mr. Grossberg is on vacation today. Well, I guess I can come back tomorrow if I need anything.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Expensive-looking mahogany bookshelves, filled with expensive-looking books. Hmm... funny... they don't look like they've ever been read.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A solid mahogany desk. The wood's been polished to a deep luster.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess Mr. Grossberg isn't getting that painting back. I feel kind of bad for him...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">An expensive potted plant. No idea what kind of plant it is, but it's probably the most expensive one available.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A table for clients. Hmm... an elegant ebony case, and if I'm not mistaken, that lighter's made of solid gold. Even I can tell someone here's got money to burn.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are fewer than there were yesterday, but the cops are still around in the park. I wonder if Detective Gumshoe is here today?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I feel winter's chill from the bare leaf trees today... There's a lot of trees here. I guess that's why they call it a "nature park." It's quite pretty when the cherry trees along the lakeside blossom in spring. Today... it's just cold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sign says "Gourd Lake Nature Park." This place is full of families picnicking on the weekend. It's a little cold for picnicking these days, though.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Haven't seen Larry around at all. Probably off paying through the nose on a date with the lovely Kiyance...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The famous Gourd Lake... Its green waters stretch out on both sides... It's a pretty big lake, really.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like the boat rental shop is closed today, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A small boat rental shop. Doesn't look like anyone is around. They're probably closed because of the murder.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are some boats floating at the dock. The murder took place in a boat from this dock... Apparently, the police took away the actual boat that was used that night. Indeed, there's space for one more boat at the dock.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Detective Gumshoe!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! The trial today, it, er... ...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yes? What about the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Well, I was going to say "good show," but it wasn't really all that... Though you did save Edgeworth, I guess... I just wasn't sure how to thank you... you know?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta's camera is staring out at the lake, as usual. Even a novice like me can tell that camera must cost a pretty penny. I hope she doesn't leave it out here to get stolen.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The sign says "No Camping." Funny place to pick to pitch your tent.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wonder why she brought a camping cooker with her? There's a convenience store right up the street... I guess she wanted to get into the outdoor spirit.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't think Lotta takes very good care of her SUV. It's covered with dents. I can't believe anyone would drive their car down here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe? Any idea what strategy von Karma is planning for tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It sounds like he's bringing in another witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Another witness!? Oh, right, he said something about that in the trial today...</line>
<line speaker="Karma">There were two witnesses!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I was wondering who that other witness was! Er... who was it?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">S... sorry, pal. As much as I'd like to, I'm not at liberty to divulge that information.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Oh, right... I wanted to ask you something about Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's up?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Is he afraid of earthquakes? I never heard anything about that before.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Mr. Edgeworth doesn't talk about himself too much, see. But there's one thing that's clear as day... Him hating crime the way he does... And him becoming a lawyer... And him being scared of earthquakes... It all started with that incident.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The DL-6 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep, that's the one. Fifteen years ago... when he saw his father shot before his very eyes! He still feels the pain now, you can see it in his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I wanted to talk to you about Maya Fey...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? She's not out on bail yet? That's strange. I told 'em to let her go as soon as they had their report written up. Man... I don't know what would have happened in that courtroom today if it weren't for her. Seeing her getting dragged out by the bailiff... I'll be honest with you, pal. I shed a tear or two. Edgeworth, he was so moved I saw his lip trembling.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Really!? <thought>Cold-as-ice Edgeworth!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He was really grateful for what she did, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I think it's a little early for you to be proudly waving that thing around. You can be proud of yourself when you get Mr. Edgeworth declared innocent, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That woman really took us for a ride, didn't she? Claiming she was a witness to a murder and all...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, if it weren't for her photograph, Mr. Edgeworth wouldn't have made it today.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, huh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Umm... you were at the trial, weren't you, Detective?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Robert Hammond... He was the defense attorney in the DL-6 Incident trial. He's the one who got the sole suspect off the hook. I wonder what Mr. Edgeworth thinks of him. Not much, I'd wager.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I don't care who you are, no one can tell me that that's Mr. Edgeworth! I mean, come on, it doesn't look like him at all!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But Edgeworth has admitted he was on the boat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Then he's the one being shot, then!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He seemed fine in court today...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Details, pal, details! Whose side are you on, anyway?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>All I'm saying is we have to respect the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yep, it was fired from the murder weapon, without a doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From a meter away... so it would have to have been from someone else on the boat.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you make of this, Detective Gumshoe?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, making something of things is your job!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... right. <thought>Since when do lawyers have to do detectives' work for them!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Maybe you should tell me why Mr. Edgeworth's prints were on the weapon, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? How should I know!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Now, she heard two gunshots, right?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But wait... Look at the Court Record! According to this, the murder weapon was fired three times!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What!? How's that possible!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Where was the third shot fired?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I wonder... Maybe it was a practice shot or something?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sorry to disappoint you, pal. I'm drawing a blank.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'm going to head back to the station. I'll get the report on Maya and get her out of there as soon as I can.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank you. Oh, wait! Umm... I was wondering, how much is bail going to be?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Don't worry about that. Mr. Edgeworth is posting the whole amount.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What? Edgeworth...?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Didn't I tell you? He's grateful to her for what she did. Alright, pal. Well don't forget to go pick her up, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Hmm... Maybe I can get Edgeworth to pay this month's rent, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! You finally came! They just finished the paperwork, I'm free to go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Free at last, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Those interrogators were really mean! They were like "okay, what did you do THIS time?" Like I was some kind of criminal! Can you believe it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, they let you out in the end, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm... Oh, that reminds me... Thanks for bail.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thank Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">He posted bail for you. Said he was grateful for what you did.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mr. Edgeworth did that...? ... I have to make it up to him! We've got to win this case, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you think we should do next?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're kind of lacking in the clues department. We could go to the park and look for Gourdy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I-I was kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Still, if there are any clues out there, the park's as good a bet as any. What do you say? Shall we head down there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sure!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you noticed anything lately?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... You know, I did notice one thing while I was here in detention. It's really pretty comfortable here. It's warm, and they keep it very clean.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I meant have you noticed anything about the case...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... Not much more than that, no.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's probably still upset about Mia. I should leave her alone.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Ahh! Fresh air! I gotta say, freedom feels great.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Behave yourself in the courtroom tomorrow, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh heh. Misbehaving's much more fun.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not going to be so much fun when Edgeworth refuses to pay your bail again.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Right. I'll behave.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, what should we do?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I don't know! I've been in detention this whole time. I think I'll let you decide what we should do. Deal?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well? Any thoughts you want to share?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, I was detention all day. I think I'd like more time to think.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Poor Maya, she probably thought about Mia the whole time she was in there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Don't waste time showing me things! We have to get cracking on this case! You know the enemy has more tricks up his sleeve! He's bringing in another witness!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like Edgeworth is in questioning.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Guess so...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There aren't many cops around today, are there?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They're probably back at the precinct, working up the case against Edgeworth.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey y'all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, it's Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all really did it today...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what did we do now?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Naw, I'm not complaining! See, I did a little thinking. A little... self-reflection, you might say. I realized that bein' a witness is a mighty big responsibility. But I just went up there and started blabbing any old thing that came to mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">So, you see, I want to make it up to y'all.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Make it up"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What did you think of the trial?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">To be honest, I was doin' it half just to say I'd been a witness... Even though I didn't really see anything. I kinda convinced myself I had though... I'm sorry, I know I caused y'all a lot of trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, memory is a tricky, vague little thing.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, I sure know that now. I'll be fine the next time I witness a murder!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>You mean the FIRST time you witness a murder...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about Gourdy?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Right! Well, the way I figure, the trial's only stoking the flames of Gourdy fever! I'll get my exclusive photos and rocket to stardom!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right, Lotta! You go, girl! I wish I could be an investigative photographer too!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Finish your spirit medium training first!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta, what do you mean by "making it up to us"?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, ya see... Actually, I got a bit of information for you.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">That von Karma didn't want me to say nothin' about it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what information!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Now we're getting to the heart of it! See, I reckoned we might be able to do ourselves a little "exchange."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">E-"exchange"? Umm... I thought this was to "make it up to us"...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Right! I propose a little exchange, to make it up to you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What!? Information don't come cheap, my friend!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! I see you thinking "my, how unsophisticated these southern folks are"!!! It's written all over yer face! Let me tell you, most southerners are WAY more sophisticated than you... I'm just the exception, okay? Well, what'll it be? We gonna deal, or not!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what should we do, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We don't have any other leads so I don't think we have a choice here...</thought> Okay. How much?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh? You completely off your rocker? I may not be sophisticated, but I'm not trying to rob the poor!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry... But I've no intention of dealing with you!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nor do we have any money, anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You guys make a fine team, you know that? And I can tell you don't have any money, just look at those clothes!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm thinking I should up the sensitivity of my camera mic. Y'all just be sure y'all don't sneeze or nothing when you're in my part of the woods!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'm glad I did that enlargement.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No kidding. If we didn't have that, Edgeworth would be in prison now, or worse!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's never a lack of drama when you're on a case, is there, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What, are you always on the verge of horrible failure like this!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Careful or the stress'll send you to an early grave.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Thanks for the cheerful message of support!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... uh... You know, I was wondering...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What if you get a picture of Gourdy... and it turns out like this enlargement did?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all crazy!? A blurry picture like this doesn't make a hit story! I need a picture that screams "I am Gourdy! Hear me roar!" I can't turn something like this into the paper! What kind of fool do y'all think I am?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The kind of fool that would turn a blurry picture in as evidence in a murder trial? Not to mention claiming she saw something she didn't see!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yep, I'd have to say I know exactly squat about that.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's painfully easy to know when something doesn't catch Lotta's interest...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">The only fair exchange for information is... information! Listen good-- What I need from you is information about Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whoa-whoa-whoa! G-Gourdy!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">B-but Gourdy doesn't... I mean, Gourdy might not exist!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Then bring me proof that shows he don't!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'll be keepin' watch from the car, okay? You see something, y'all come to me first, got it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-okay...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Right! See y'all later!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, Nick, let's get hunting!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hunting...? You don't seriously mean...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Gourdy? I sure do!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What about Edgeworth!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We're searching for Gourdy for him, Nick! Don't you get it!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Okay... and how exactly do we search for a make-believe monster...? Maybe we can find a monster myth specialist?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wh-what's that?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Th-the Steel Samurai, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo! Maya!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry! What the heck is this!?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Oh, it was my girl Kiyance's idea... She was all "if you like, put this here, it would be, like, really cool!" Dude, she gave it to me along with the banner!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow! That's really impressive she could find those for you!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, she knows a lot of people. And that show's finished now, so she got 'em for free.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Those flags look sadly out of place here. Flapping listlessly back and forth in a cold wind under a cold sky...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I dunno, I think it kind of gives the place a festival atmosphere. It reminds me of the "War of the Eyeglasses"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...? The war of the what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? What? You mean, you don't know the War of the Eyeglasses?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What the heck is it?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Our local fair used to do it ever summer... Huh, I guess we were the only ones.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I ask again, what the heck is it!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Doesn't that Steel Samurai look a little out of place? I mean, it's so huge... I guess it's good advertising.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Something about this Steel Samurai just doesn't work for me.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Really? It looks pretty well made to me.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph. Still a novice, aren't you, Nick. Really... True connoisseurs like Cody and me don't fall for this kind of stuff.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>These Steel Samurai fans are obviously in a league of their own...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's this machine?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That? That's a compressor. I use it to fill up that balloon there with air.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh, neat.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Just got it repaired yesterday! Man, what a drag that was.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yo, Nick! What happened with Edgeworth?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, we made it through the first day in court all right... I don't know how good our prospects are from here on, though.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Larry, did you know Edgeworth's secret weakness? He's terrified of earthquakes! He acts like a little boy!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? That's weird. I don't think he was ever like that in school.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, we were only in the same class for a year. He transferred schools pretty quickly...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Transferred?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Right... when the DL-6 Incident happened. Doesn't look like Larry knows about it, though.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, Larry. What was that big... thing up there before?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Oh, the big guy? I've had that for about a month, yeah. It's a big hit with the kids!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Why wasn't it there yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Huh!? Oh... right. Th-the compressor was busted.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Compressor?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Yeah--it's that little unit by my hotdog stand. That what I use to put air in the Steel Samurai! It broke a little while ago so I sent it in for repairs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh. And here I thought you'd inflated it by yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">That's the guy that’s selling my dogs faster than I can cook 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you think Gourdy really exists?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Nah, I think somebody probably saw something else that they just thought was Gourdy. But I'll keep selling Samurai Dogs until the truth's out!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sorry, Nick. I don't know much about that. I am a mere seller of hotdogs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... It’s always so quiet, here. I wonder if the boat shop is closed for good?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, with the murder on the lake and all... They're probably just taking a vacation till it blows over.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey y'all! Well? Y'all find anything out about Gourdy?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... no, nothing.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, keep moving! It gets cold out here at nighttime.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">It is a little chilly... I... I think I have to sneeze!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wh-whoa! No you don't! No sneezing!!!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaa-cho!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I told y'all NO SNEEZING! See, I set the camera to respond to things a little softer than a "bang." It'd trigger on one of von Karma's finger snaps now!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... I'm sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, well, sorry's nice but what about my film!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... pay the lady.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>*sob*</thought></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I learned something in today's trial, that's for sure. Testifyin' is serious business! That's why I decided not to talk about that case any more.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Whoa--didn't you say you had information about the case!? Tell us that, at least!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Like I said... I'll trade it for the dirt on Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What are you going to do if Gourdy doesn't exist?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I'll quit being an investigative photographer.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">After all, I only have one photo to my name so far...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Was it a good one?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You bet... a yoofoh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A y-yoofoh...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Anyway, if I can't get a career-making photo this time around... Then that's it! I'll quit and go back to school.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Huh? So you really are a university student?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah, well, I'm takin' a break for a bit.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I gotta do what I gotta do to get me a picture of Gourdy! That's why I raised the sensitivity of my mic. Just... watch yourself from now on, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey there, pal. What's up? You look out of sorts. Wait... you didn't go and do something that's going to hurt Mr. Edgeworth's case again!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What do you mean, "again"!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Whatever, have a seat, pal. I'm here for you if you need anything. Besides money, that is.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"You're under arrest! I have a warrant... You have the right to remain silent, you have the right to an attorney..."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for making arrests.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How is the investigation proceeding?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's not, really. We have another meeting coming up... We're supposed to talk about Mr. Edgeworth's motive...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">His motive?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">See, Mr. Edgeworth's father died in the DL-6 Incident... And the guy who got the lone suspect declared innocent was the victim in this case... Robert Hammond. They're saying that's why Mr. Edgeworth shot him.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And Edgeworth never talks about his past... I bet they'll drag that out and hit him with it in court tomorrow, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I gotta admit, it doesn't look good, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Say, Detective Gumshoe. Do you know "Gourdy"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">The monster down in Gourd Lake? Not personally, no.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well... we're looking for him.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh!? Are you out of your minds!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeek!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You got time to go wild monster hunting!? How about doing a little questioning for me then!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... Detective Gumshoe is scaring me, Nick.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I told Detective Gumshoe about the deal with Lotta.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! Try telling him sooner next time!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er, sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I see, pal. Sorry for shoutin' at you. ... Okay! I, Detective Gumshoe, will aid your search for Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I'll loan you one of newest secret weapons for finding evidence!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">You can take whichever one you like!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay, give us the goods!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hold on now, everything in due time. First, let me show 'em to you! These are our best and brightest! Introducing Secret Weapon No. 1: "Missile"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">M-M-Missile?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">He's a K-9 police dog, still in training! Missile! Missile! Here, boy...</line>
<line speaker="Missile">Woof.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Here he is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, he's cute! Look, Nick! Cute dog!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>A cute dog... And this will help us... how?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Missile">Woof.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Next, Secret Weapon No. 2... A fishing pole! Here, this is my own personal pole.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe... we're looking for a monster...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How are we supposed to catch a whole sea monster with a fishing pole!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Never know 'til you try, pal!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Okay, this next one is the last one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>No, please, I'm already overwhelmed by our choices.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Secret Weapon No. 3! A metal detector! Here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe... we're looking for something alive.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Right!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">How are we supposed to find it with a metal detector!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, you never know! It might have been eating soda cans! Well, which will it be!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... I can't make up my mind, Nick. They all seem so perfect!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't make up my mind, either... for the totally opposite reason. <thought>Oh well, I suppose it can't hurt to borrow one of them.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow Missile?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal. Be good to 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Missile">Woof.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's sooooo cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow that flimsy-looking fishing pole?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal. Oh, if it breaks, be sure to dispose of it properly, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow that metal detector?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure what we're going to find with this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Remember: you're hunting for a monster. Anything is possible! Anything!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, can we borrow one of the other things?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm? Yeah, sure, pal! But I have to take back the last one I lent you, department policy. Well, take your pick. Which will it be?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow Missile?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal. Be good to 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Missile">Woof.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's sooooo cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oh boy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow that flimsy-looking fishing pole?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal. Oh, if it breaks, be sure to dispose of it properly, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Er... right.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Can we borrow that metal detector?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Sure thing, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm not sure what we're going to find with this...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Remember: you're hunting for a monster. Anything is possible! Anything!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Missile is a big star in criminal affairs.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why's he named "Missile"?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh... now that you mention it, I'm not sure. But I hear he's aptly-named, for what it's worth.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">It's funny, one day I woke up and I wanted a fishing pole.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you like fishing?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">I've never gone. I just wanted one so bad, I went out and bought it. I've never used it, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Must have been one of those mid-life crisis things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">As you can see, it's a metal detector. We use it to look for bullets in the ground. If you can find that monster with it, all the better!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I'm not so hopeful...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Missile's been acting strangely...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Missile"? Oh, oh right. That little... creature of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, I love lil' doggies! Good boy, good boy.</line>
<line speaker="Missile">Grrraaaaaaarh!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what's wrong, Missile?</line>
<line speaker="Missile">... Yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeeeek! Missile! Misssssssssssile!</line>
<line speaker="Missile">Munch munch munch munch munch munch munch munch Munch munch munch munch munch munch munch munch</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-whoa! Stop that thing! Cannibal! It's eating my Samurai Dogs! ...! ... My Samurai Dogs... *sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow. He ate every single one.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Larry...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">"Sorry"!? "Sorry" don't pay my bills, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah hah hah... <thought>It's going to have to this time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey Larry! Look, it's Missile! Isn't he cute?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">K-keep that mutt away from me! What am I going to tell the big boss?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">There's a "big boss" in charge of your hot dog stand? Nick! Maybe the stand is a front for a mafia money laundering scheme!!!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya... I think you should probably try to look a little sorry about what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh, right!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh... My poor dogs...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">You know, you can't catch many fish in this lake.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I'm not after small fry. I'm after the biggest fry of them all... Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... You really going to try to fish out a monster?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">To save Edgeworth, yes!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Brings a tear to my eye, in more ways than one.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm. Okay, Nick, this looks like a good spot!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A good spot... for what?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Time to do some fishing!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>She's serious...</thought> Umm... What are you going to use for bait?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. "Oh."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Mmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I figured something like this would happen. We should have brought Missile along with us, too. At least then we'd have bait.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...!!! N-Nick...! How could you!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm kidding! I'm kidding!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph! Some jokes are better left untold.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Oof! She hit me!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Okay... Watch this, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Just try not to reel in any empty cans or boots, okay?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Here we go! Ack! M-my leg!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hey! Wh-what are you doing!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Sorry, Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Don't tell me y'all are on some film company's payroll!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, pay her.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Dear, dear...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Lotta!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Oh, cute! He yours?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He's a K-9 police dog! His name's "Missile."</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh. K-9s are the ones they use to sniff for things, right? I wonder what Gourdy smells like...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... I hadn't thought about that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Lotta, wait... For catching Gourdy...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">A fishing pole!? Are you out of your doggone mind!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes! I mean... yes, it's a fishing pole!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Huh.  I never thought of that! Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I don't believe it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Lotta, look at this: It's a metal detector!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">I know what it is. Umm... I'm not sure that's going to pick up Gourdy, though. Unless he's been eating people's watches or spare change or something.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh... I hadn't thought about that.</line>
<line speaker="Borrowing Metal Detector leads to">*beep* *beep* *beep*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! It's beeping! The metal detector's found something!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Sure it loud enough about it. <thought>Whatever it is, it must be in those bushes...</thought> Go check it out, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why do I have to check it out? ... Nick. Look!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh...? An air tank? Huh. The valve looks broken.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I thought it was Gourdy...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Maya, first of all... Why would Gourdy be in the bushes!? And second of all, why would a metal detector react to a sea monster!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? <thought>There's something wrapped around this air tank... It looks like... a string of flags...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, we might as well take it with us now that we've found it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It's heavy...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hmm... Detective Gumshoe isn't here...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Now that you mention it, didn't he say he had a meeting to go to?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ah, that's right... Let's come back later.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"Resistance is futile! We have you surrounded! It's not too late... Release the hostages and come out with your hands up."</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for negotiating a hostage situation.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Umm... So, the tank and the Steel Samurai you were trying to fill up flew away... What happened next?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Well, all that happened on the 20th or so.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The 20th... a week ago.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Now, as far as I could see, the tank went flying out into the lake. So I went out every night in a boat looking for it. I mean, Kiyance gave me that Steel Samurai after all!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And when did you find it?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Just the night before last! It flew way out there! Took me four whole days to find it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>The night before last... was the night of the murder!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Sorry for not telling you, Nick. Actually, I was here on the night of the murder. But, you see, I went home before midnight.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So you didn't know about what happened?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">No...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's too bad...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not all bad. We've solved one mystery at least.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">A mystery...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maybe we should go tell her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">What? An air tank? What about it?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Larry... I wanted to ask you about this tank...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Have you seen this before?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Huh? Me? N-no. Never. Who the heck would go diving in the middle of the winter!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>There's something about the way his eye twitched when I showed him the tank... I think I'd better pursue this line of questioning a little further...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Say... is this air tank yours?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-why would I have a thing like that?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Look--see how there's a string of flags around the tank valve? It's just like the string of flags around your Steel Samurai there.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">...! M-must be a coincidence! There's strings of flags everywhere these days! L-like elementary schools! A-and used car dealerships! L-look, why would I need a tank anyway!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You used this to go diving in the lake, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Wh-wh-what!? Why the heck would I go diving in the lake!? Wait! You... you're not... You're not saying I had something to do with that murder!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">N-no, not at all, just...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Hey, you watch it buddy! I'm not saying anything until my lawyer gets here!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry... Nick is your lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, Larry? She's right.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Bah! A-anyway, I never seen that air tank! Okay?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Yeah, right... Larry is hiding something, I can tell...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You used this to inflate that, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">I-inflate what!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What else? That big puffy Steel Samurai!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Looks like I hit the nail on the head.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Right... right... Actually, umm... See, the compressor I always use was on the fritz. So I tried using the tank to inflate it, just once. And, er, it didn't go so well.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>As I suspected!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess I've gotten to the bottom of that mystery!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Butz">Heh. Sorry!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It "didn't go so well"?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">Er, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you think you could be a little more specific?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">C-c'mon...  Look, it's embarrassing so I really don't want to talk about it...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Tell us! Tell us!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">... Fine. Whatever. It's like what I said, the compressor was busted. So I took the tank and tried to fill the Samurai up with that. And then...</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The valve busted open and made this incredible noise! And that tank there took off like a rocket. And it took my poor deflated Steel Samurai with it!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Off into Gourd Lake?</line>
<line speaker="Butz">It sure scared me out of my gourd, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Butz">See, I tried to use this tank to fill up the Samurai. I was attaching the tank, when it happened!</line>
<line speaker="Butz">The valve just busted open and the whole thing took off! The tank shot up in the air like a rocket... And it took my poor deflated Steel Samurai with it! Man, what a sight that was.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I wish I could have seen it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Me too.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well, Mister Lawyer? I've got the info y'all need! Y'all got the scoop on Gourdy for me yet?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's not going to be that easy to find him, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">You'd better hurry or you won't have that info in time for the trial tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Uh oh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh? Gourdy? Oh, we found him already.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? I haven't seen any monsters yet!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y-y'all for real!? Gourdy really exists!? Wait! I need proof! You get a photo!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't have it yet, but my lawyer instincts tell me the proof is out there.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hah! Nice try, but y'all can't pull the wool over these eyes that easy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That won't work in court either, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, now they're both mad at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I have proof.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">No fair, Nick! It was when I went to the bathroom, wasn't it!? That's when you made contact with Gourdy!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Enough jabbering already, let's see your proof!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">... Y'all trying to make a fool out of me? That don't prove diddly-squat!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmph. We almost had her duped, too.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>We need to do something soon or I won't get that information off of her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Lotta... There is no such thing as Gourdy.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Wh-what!? How can y'all be so sure!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">R-really, Nick!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Y'all got some proof Gourdy don't exist!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The proof that Gourdy doesn't exist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I don't have it yet, but my lawyer instincts tell me the proof is out there.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hah! Nice try, but y'all can't pull the wool over these eyes that easy!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That won't work in court either, Nick...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, now they're both mad at me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Of course I have proof. No lawyer worth his badge would make a claim without proof to back it up. Here's the proof that Gourdy doesn't exist...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><cutIn type="takeThat">Take that!</cutIn>></line>
<line speaker="Lotta">... Hah! All that fancy talk about lawyers and proof had me going for a second there! Y'all better take a good hard look at that badge of yours and consider a career change!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Great, the "investigative photographer" is giving me career advice...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Larry's air tank...?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">What're y'all doing with an air tank?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This... is Gourdy.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Umm... scuze me?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wh-what exactly are you saying, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There's a stand near here... a hotdog stand. There's a giant inflatable samurai doll there. About a week ago, an idiot, who happens to be a friend of mine, tried to fill it. He used this air tank, and when the valve blew, the tank flew into the lake. Apparently, it made a pretty loud "bang" when it flew...</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">A "bang"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The tank, along with the still deflated Samurai fell into the lake. At the same time... A couple was taking a photograph of the lake. This photo!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wait... So... you're saying that Gourdy... Is really the Steel Samurai!?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">... ... Well, that's a fine way to ruin a gal's dreams.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm sorry, Lotta.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Nah, it's okay, you win. I'll give you your info, like I promised.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Poor Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">So, tell us this "information" you have.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">A promise is a promise, I guess... I overheard the cops around here saying something about the witness tomorrow... They said he's the caretaker of the boat rental place up the path here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Boat rental...? There's someone there? I mean, it looks so deserted.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Just an old guy, living all by himself. Y'all should go check it out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Thanks, Lotta! We will! Let's get cracking, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Hold on.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Something else?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Yeah... the night of the murder. My camera clicked twice, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...! Wait... so you have another photo?</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Well... Yeah, but there's nothing in it at all. Just the lake. I figured it wouldn't be much use as evidence, so I kept it to myself. Well, it might not be helpful at all, but... Here, take it.</line>
<line speaker="Lotta">Bye now. Y'all take care. Time for me to pack up and leave.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... Poor Lotta...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It's all Larry's fault. The legend still lives on, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "legend"...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah, the legend of Larry, familiar to all who know him for any length of time... "When something smells, it's usually the Butz."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm. Someone should whip that Butz into shape.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hey, Nick! This is the boat shop that Lotta was talking about!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You're right. Doesn't seem to be anyone around at all.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Well, let's go check it out anyway!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Meg! That you!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Eeeek!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Hey, is that Keith with you!? Where have you two been! I've been worried sick.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">... N-Nick... you handle this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, I think I'll leave this one up to you, Maya.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Meg!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Finally made up your mind, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Meg">M-my mind?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You'll run the pasta shop when I'm gone?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-pasta?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Glad to hear it, glad to hear it! You make your old man proud. When you kids left the house, I didn't know what to think. How'm I supposed to keep this place running, an old man like me? Polly! The kids are home!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! What was that!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">A parrot... the one on the perch.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Keith!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I leave the "Wet Noodle" in your capable hands, sonny.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick? What's the "Wet Noodle"?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Um, based on the available evidence, I'd say it's the name of his pasta shop.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">That's a relief, isn't it, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup... ... *Zzzzz*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He fell asleep...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess he's relieved.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like a kitchen unit. It's pretty clean. Funny, he doesn't look like the type who'd keep things tidy like that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You're forgetting, Nick... He's running a pasta shop, here!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wow, there's lots of various fish in Gourd Lake, aren't there!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">...? Something's funny, Nick. All these fish are saltwater fish.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This fishing pole looks expensive.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, Nick, he has an electric blanket on his table! Looks warm! That's a great idea, we should do that at the office. We can sit down with our clients, snug and warm, and drink hot cocoa!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">And what, talk about murders?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Aw, you're a party pooper, Nick!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow, he has a television in here, too.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Look, a little safe! Hmm... ... It's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... what an amazing parrot that is. Good morning!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hello!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"..."</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He ignored me!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">What, you forgot, Meg? You gotta call her name first!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Her name?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Polly! How ya been!?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">See?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Neat! So the parrot's name is "Polly"!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Too bad all she can say is "hello"...</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Har har har! Old Polly can say lots of things! You just need to know the secret words!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The "secret words"...?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly! Polly! What's your name?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Pol-ly!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hee hee! Cute!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Maya's found a new friend.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... a pasta shop?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup! To think, the "Wet Noodle," will live on when I'm gone! My father started it you know. So that makes you two the third generation! Meg...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Tomorrow, we'll start with the secrets of dough tossin'!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">D-dough tossing?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You, too, Keith.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You'll be the best pasta wrangler the west has ever seen!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">P-pasta wrangler? The west? I-isn't pasta from Italy?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Meg!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You know the best pasta's always been made west of the Rockies, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">R-right, of course. Everybody knows that.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">How long do we have to keep up this all-in-the-family charade?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This old man must know something about the murder...! We're not leaving until we find out what that is.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... this is a boat rental shop, right?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">What're you talking about!? This here's the palace of pasta, the "Wet Noodle"! Though, now that you mention it, we haven't gotten many orders for spaghetti lately. All the kids come up and say "Yo dude, we wanna ride in one of your boats!" That's why I keep them boats out there. Youngsters these days... Darned if I understand 'em!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm pretty confused myself.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... This isn't going anywhere.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But this old man is the witness tomorrow, right? We've got to find some way of getting information out of him!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ack, my memory's gotten worse of late. That's why I just tell everything important to old Polly here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Everything... important? Hmm, I wonder... Polly! What's the number to the safe!?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"... 1228!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Alright!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">H-hey! Polly! Watch it, will ya!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Heh heh. See, Nick? All it takes is a little clever thinking!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>And a criminal mind...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Quick, Nick! Write that number down!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">H-hey! Don't get me involved in your little heist schemes.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I forget the time, but it was pretty dark outside... probably night, ayup.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>It was after midnight, but okay...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Then I heard this "bang!" So I looked outside. Then I heard another one. "Bang!" A little while later, this boat comes back. Then a young man walked by my window here. He was mutterin' something to himself, ayup.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What did he say?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">... Ayup... ... I forgot. I'll remember tomorrow by court time, promise.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">We need to know earlier than that...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes, it is! <thought>I don't believe it! This old guy is the first person to recognize my badge!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">... I get it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup... I got you figured out now! You're not Keith!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick!  Now's our chance to clear things up!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Umm... sir. No, I'm not Keith.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">And I'm not Meg, either!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We're here investigating a murder that took place on this lake the other night.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please, help us!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">... Hmm... a lawyer, huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Please, mister...</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Alright, I'll help. But, on one condition.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">When this case is over and done... You'll run the "Wet Noodle"!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I can't make that promise.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">... I-is that any way to treat your old man!? Bah! You want me help? You've come to the wrong man!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Uh oh... now he's grumpy.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Not to mention he still thinks we're his kids. <thought>Maybe we should just lie and say we'll run his shop?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Okay, we promise.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! Are you sure about this?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Hey, anything to get the case solved. Also... Who wouldn't want to eat "Phoenix Noodles"?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I... guess so.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">That's my boy! Good for you, Keith.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">W-wait, didn't I just say...</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You, too, Meg!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Y-yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Heh heh heh... you bring a tear to your old man's eye, you know. Now, what was that you wanted to know? Speak up, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Er...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Now he's talking to the bird again! How do we get him to talk to us!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You won't be needing that badge to run a pasta shop. Toss it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Uh, um, I think I'll hold on to it if you don't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know about Gourdy?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Nope.</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup, I seen this.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you know something about this, sir!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Keith.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-yes?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">It's okay. You can call me Dad.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... D-Dad! You know something about this!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup. The other night... out on the lake...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yes? Yes!?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">I know all about that! I seen it.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Whaaaat!? Tell us! Tell what you saw!</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Well, I suppose. Since you're taking over the shop and all...</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Polly here's my only friend in the world. Isn't that right, Polly?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Hello! Hello!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Indigo... Blue?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>That didn't seem to work the way I thought it might.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">... *Zzzzz*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He fell asleep...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">You know what? Eh? Little Terry was just here.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">"Terry"...?</line>
<line speaker="Uncle">Ayup, that kid next door. You always used to make him cry, remember? He was wearin' this tattered old coat. Got himself some whiskers growing out of his face.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He must be talking about Detective Gumshoe...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Uncle">He comes up and tells me to come down to court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Really...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Somehow I don't think we're going to get much useful information out of this guy.</thought> Maya... maybe we should be leaving.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I think you're right. Oh, wait--I had one more question.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly! Polly! Have we forgotten something?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">*squawk* "Don't forget DL-6!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh!? What did she just say, Nick?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One more time, Polly!</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">"Don't forget DL-6!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>What!? The DL-6 Incident?</thought> Hey, mister! I-I mean, Dad!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>This is getting weird... Who IS this old guy!?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Why would that bird Polly know about DL-6...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We have to figure out who that old man is.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">What?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">He locked the door, from the other side.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>... Who could that old man be...? I think I need to do a little more research on this DL-6 Incident... Maybe I should ask Detective Gumshoe.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hey, pal! Long time no see! ... You don't look so happy. What's wrong this time?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Actually, we wanted to ask you something...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That must be one of the detectives. He's mumbling something to himself.</line>
<line speaker="Police">"I... I'm not gonna make it... Just... just arrest that guy for me... please... uggh!"</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">... He must be doing image training for dying in action.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">You know the boat rental shop down at Gourd Lake?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Oh, yeah...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The old man who runs it is appearing as a witness in court tomorrow, right?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh...!? How'd you-- Hmm. That was supposed to be top secret.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Do you know who that old man is, Detective?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... Actually... I don't. He's a bit of an odd bird... I haven't been able to get a straight answer out of him. I decided first that he wasn't persuasive enough to stand and testify as a witness. That's why we called Ms. Lotta Hart yesterday. As for who he is... We have absolutely no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... sounds suspicious!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Detective Gumshoe, please, help us...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">H-huh?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">We need to know about the DL-6 Incident!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">That was when Edgeworth's father died. I can't help but think that it has something to do with this current case.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... To tell the truth, I don't know much about DL-6 either. Mr. Edgeworth forbade us from reading the file. So... I'm afraid I can't show them to you, either, pal.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">However... If you can convince me somehow that the DL-6 Incident is related to this case... Well, I guess I'd consider opening the file up.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Thanks, Detective Gumshoe. This was really helpful.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">R-really?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">You seem surprised!</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Huh? N-no, not at all. Glad it worked out for you.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">What's that? A parrot?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The old man at the boat rental shop's parrot. The parrot knew about that "incident"...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">That incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">DL-6.</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Wh-what!?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Polly! Polly! Have we forgotten something?</line>
<line speaker="Parrot">*squawk* "Don't forget DL-6!" *squawk*</line>
<line speaker="Maya">H-huh!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I'm pretty sure that old man must have taught her that word...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">Yeah, but how would that old man know about the DL-6 Incident?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Wait! What if... What if that old man was connected to DL-6?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">N-Nick! You think he might be!?</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">...</line>
<line speaker="Gumshoe">... I get ya. Sounds like you need information on the DL-6 Incident. Through there is the Station's Records Room. I'll give you special permission to go in and find what you need.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">All right! Way to go, Detective Gumshoe! Okay, Nick! To the Records Room!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>I guess it's time we faced Edgeworth's past...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow!!! It's amazing.........ly dusty.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Ten years of files and ten years of dust, I guess.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's find that DL-6 stuff quick!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>Fifteen years ago... both me and Edgeworth were nine years old. We were almost through with fourth grade when he suddenly transferred. Because of DL-6...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick! I found out where the file is!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">O-oh, thanks!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Just let me know what you want to know about the DL-6 Incident! I'll go get the right file!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">It looks like there are files inside that glass case. The case is so dusty I can't see what's inside.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... it's locked.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">They must keep important case files in there.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There are shelves stuffed with case files in the back of the room, too. Forgotten cases, rotting away for eternity...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick, let's get what we need and get out of here. All this dust is getting to me!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">This cabinet is where they keep evidence for current cases. Some of the things are obviously murder weapons. Others are... who knows what. Most of it just looks like random junk.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick... what do you think this clothespin is for?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Don't touch that! It's evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Here are files of collected case reports. There's quite a large volume of reports here.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... these are all case reports!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Yeah. It's like a graveyard of police cases.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">I guess my sister's case report is in here too... quietly gathering dust.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Well, first I have to get a handle on the main facts... like a summary.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Right. Summary... summary... Found it! Here you go.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">December 28... 2001.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That's exactly 15 years ago from the day after tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>So in two days, the case is closed...</thought> The incident took place in the elevator of the district court.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">What!? Is this the same district court where we're holding the trial now!?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Looks like it. There was a large earthquake at 2:00 PM on that day. Part of the court building collapsed, and all of the lights went out.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Wow... that was some earthquake!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">At the time, three people were trapped in the elevator. It took five hours for them to be rescued... Five hours!</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That would be scary like that, in the dark!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">There was a lack of oxygen in the elevator, and the survivors were unconscious.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">The survivors...?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">One of the three in the elevator had been shot... in the heart.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">That was Mr. Edgeworth's father... wasn't it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He said that his father was shot before his very eyes... So Miles Edgeworth was one of the other passengers in that elevator.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Do you have data on the victim... Edgeworth's father?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Yeah, hold on... Victim... victim... Here! Found it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Gregory Edgeworth, 35, defense attorney. If he were still alive, he'd be 50. He had lost that day's case in court, and got in the elevator with his son, Miles.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">"Miles"...!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Miles Edgeworth, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So he was on the elevator with his father!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">From the angle of the bullet and the other evidence, it could not have been a suicide... The murder weapon, a pistol, was found in the elevator. The pistol had been fired two times. <thought>Where have I heard that before...? Huh...! It sounds just like this current case! What's going on here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Got any data on the suspect in there?</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... that would be the guy that my mom got arrested. Hold on... this is it.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">The man arrested as a suspect in DL-6 was... Yanni Yogi? He was a clerk in the court, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">So he must have been the third person in the elevator. Well, then he had to have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">But... he was found innocent. Thanks to his defense lawyer, Robert Hammond.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hammond... the victim in our case!</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. The suspect, Mr. Yogi was oxygen deprived... so much so he had brain damage. He lost all memory of being in the elevator. After he was declared innocent, he disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Hmm... where could Yogi have gone to, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix"><thought>He may be closer than we think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Maya">Let's just hurry up and read these files! This place is so dusty, I want to finish up and get out of here...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">I guess I know generally what happened in DL-6 now. I still don't know what sort of impact the whole thing had on Edgeworth...</line>
<line speaker="Maya">Nick. Are we going to take the whole file? There's too much! We'll never get it out.</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Y-you're right. How about we just take what we think we'll need...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">Right. That's probably all we'll be able to find here. Now, all that's left is the trial tomorrow... I wonder how "Dad" will do testifying in court...</line>
<line speaker="Phoenix">No clues here.</line>
</xml>