<xml>
<title>Twisted Karma and His Last Bow</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still can't quite believe what just happened.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know. I enquired with the bailiff after the court session was adjourned... ...and it seems Mr Vigil was taken to hospital to recover.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="???">Ruuunooo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You were miles away! Anyway, I've brewed a fresh pot of soothing tea for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You and Susie have had an exhausting day so far, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! ......... Thank you, Iris. How thoughtful of you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you happen to know where Mr Sholmes is? When we came out of the courtroom back into the defendants' antechamber, he'd disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...no, I don't know. He just suddenly sprang to his feet and left. All he said was, 'I must leave.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder if he's pursuing the mystery of Inspector Gregson's death...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Well, you know what Hurley's always saying, don't you? 'There are mysteries in this world that should perhaps never be solved.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">'For the construction of a solution comes only at the expense of the destruction of something else...'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What does that mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">He knows very well that when you open someone else's old wounds, you often open your own, too. But he just can't take his own advice and leave well alone. Solving mysteries is too important to him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's so true.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But that's what I like about Hurley, after all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I suppose that's the lot of a great detective in some ways...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">So then... ...let's have tea and then I'll give you a hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Do you have time, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, I've finished this month's manuscript at last. With barely a day to spare before the deadline!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I'm so looking forward to it. A brand new story to read in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, I always hide Hurley's violin in the days before I have a deadline.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you do? <thought>Poor Mr Sholmes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure that's very wise, Iris. How sensible of you!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Now then, my dear fellows, let's make a plan of action before we continue our investigation!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So, how did it go in court this morning?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, we still don't know the truth about what really happened, but one thing's increasingly clear: Lord van Zieks definitely didn't do it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, goodie!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. We managed to uncover several new facts as well!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...there was another development, too. <thought>Kazuma.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's quite clear now... ...that Kazuma-sama is not himself. The way he's acting, it's almost as if he's...possessed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. I mean, at the end of the proceedings earlier... ...he was like a bloodhound the way he was chasing down Mr Vigil's forgotten past. <thought>He's not normally so mercilessly persistent.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's going on in his head, I wonder. I really need to sit down with Kazuma and try to understand what he's going through...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If Gregson was really murdered the day before his body was discovered... ...then Lord van Zieks has to be innocent, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">What?! The day before? Well that should be easy enough to work out just by examining the corpse, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you would expect so. But curiously... ...no time of death was included in the autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, that is curious.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are still unanswered questions about Lord van Zieks, though, aren't there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I mean what was he doing there on Fresno Street that day in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well according to the man's testimony... ...he said he was investigating Inspector Gregson, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it turns out that little room was actually the inspector's secret office...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, that sounds like it has all the makings of a wonderfully devilish plot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then why was that noticeboard in there covered in all those particular papers? Papers about cases with a link to the Reaper. ...I'm starting to get a bad feeling about all this.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear... That sounds more like something horribly devilish...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must start by looking into Inspector Gregson's movements of late!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I never imagined I might have to be investigating an inspector's movements.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, according to the entry in his diary... ...he was carrying out an incognito investigation of the Red-Headed League the day before his death.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! You, you mean he was doing the same as Hurley?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...Mr Sholmes was trying to apply, whereas the inspector was supposed to be investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do wish it had been the other way around...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Anyway, as it turns out, the inspector who went to investigate the Red-Headed League that day... ...wasn't actually Gregson at all. It was Mr Vigil, in possession of Gregson's identification.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm, you know what that sounds like to me? Establishing an alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Yes, you're absolutely right, Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...why would Gregson need an alibi?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would appear that the inspector... ...had something to do that he wished to keep secret.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I don't believe it... I, I always thought he was just a harmless lover of fish and chips...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But perhaps they were seasoned with something a little more potent than salt and vinegar...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps...we should try to move away from food analogies?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well anyway, if Lord van Zieks felt the need to investigate Gregson...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I agree. We must try to find out what he knows.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Vigil, you say? Isn't that the name of the lady who came to visit Hurley yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. To ask Mr Sholmes if he would help her to find her missing husband.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Only Mr Sholmes completely passed the buck to us. ...Actually, didn't you say that Mr Vigil had been taken to hospital? Do you know which one?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, it's St Synner's.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm starting to wonder if all the other hospitals in London have closed down...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But that's amazing, Runo! You've found the lady's husband already!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I suppose I have. By accident.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And ten years ago, while Mr Vigil was the chief warder at the prison... ...he was responsible for overseeing the Professor's incarceration.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So when the convict escaped, he was held responsible and immediately dismissed.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ugh...sometimes I really don't want to grow up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's more. For ten years after that... ...while he was ostensibly working as a pedlar, he also had another secret job. He was paid by Gregson to be his stand-in. To impersonate the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">To impersonate Gregsy?! But, but why?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I have absolutely no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ugh...Ginny was right. I'm starting to think all adults are up to no good now. Including you, Runo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I haven't paid anyone to impersonate me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That means he has ties to the Professor and to Inspector Gregson, though. So I do think we ought to pay a visit to Mr Vigil, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Back to St Synner's, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, have you seen this?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Your armband? The symbol of a defence lawyer in Japan? Runo, you've shown that to me dozens of times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...have I? The thing is, I just feel wrong if I don't have it on my arm, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well if you ask me, I think you should try wearing something different every now and then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh really? Like what?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...I could make something for you, if you like? How about a band that squeezes your arm when the person you're talking to tells a lie?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll keep a space free on my left arm, then.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I thought it was strange, you know. When Hurley suddenly decided to turn his hair red like that, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean, he didn't tell you why? He didn't mention the Red-Headed League to you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'll bet it's because he wanted to keep that four pounds a week all for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, I see. Because your hair has a reddish hue too, you mean? Right...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Anyway, at least I have a good starting point for next month's instalment now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Iris must be the only person who's actually going to manage to benefit from this whole sorry affair...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh...this looks like it's made from real human hair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought it might be.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, people will pay money for long hair that's in good condition. Hurley once offered his hair up for sale, you know. He grew it right down to his shoulders.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?! How much did he make?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No one would buy it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He was told it was 'unruly' apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh. Maybe I'd better give up on the idea as well, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Iris, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...! .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh no! What was I thinking? Why on earth did I show her that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Poor Gregsy...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, have a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's not right. I thought you were supposed to say '<cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn>' or the like when you present evidence?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no. That's only in court.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's not fair! If you won't say it, then I won't look! Hmph!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yay! That was great! Right...next!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright, I get the message. Someone's not in the mood for looking at things...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Iris! You're even more enthusiastic than usual today.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">If anyone has anything to hide, my special Wilson Shooting Iron will soon set them straight!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That...water pistol?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">It's stuffed full of a piping-hot extra-special blend of mine!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then I'm quite sure it will be very effective.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'd better be careful not to hide anything.</thought> Well...it feels a little strange that Mr Sholmes is nowhere to be seen, but still... ...let's go and see what we can find out!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you alright, Mr Naruhodo? It's rather unusual to find ourselves here in the middle of our investigations...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's, it's just occurred to me that I might have forgotten something when we left this morning.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please don't worry. As long as you continue to investigate thoroughly, you won't go far wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Yes, of course! I must get back to work as soon as possible!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No arguments, Prosecutor Asogi. You will continue with the trial exactly as I instructed. Is that clear?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Perfectly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's Kazuma-sama!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Defying Lord Stronghart, by the sound of it. He never did know when to back down.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">On your way now, Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...My Lord. .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma... <thought>He left without saying a word...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Yes? What are you doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...well, erm...I was just hoping to ask you a few questions, if you wouldn't mind.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I wanted van Zieks's trial concluded today. But Prosecutor Asogi's unwelcome inquiries are going to make it take longer than necessary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unwelcome inquiries...?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As a result, I'm losing even more precious time. Currently two hours, fifty-five minutes and forty-one seconds. ...Forty-two...forty-three...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then we must resolve everything before three hours have passed, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...In a miraculous not-even-five minutes? <thought>Anyway, I can't let the man's obvious bad mood put me off... I need information!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Does Prosecutor Asogi believe...that Lord van Zieks is the Reaper?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I wouldn't know. It was ten years ago, in that fateful closed trial, that Lord van Zieks made a name for himself among the judiciary. But the next trial he fought, he lost. It meant the ringleader of a criminal organisation was acquitted...thanks to all the jurors being under duress.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that's awful!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The man's freedom was short-lived. He lasted just three days.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, let me see...he died in a rockslide at his place of work, I believe!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Correct. That was the inauguration of the Reaper of the Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And people believed Lord van Zieks was responsible?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">He was brought to trial himself. ...But it was shown to have been an accident.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he must have had a solid alibi then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Nevertheless, the mysterious deaths continued. In total, sixteen persons perished in unusual circumstances, ostensibly at the hand of the Reaper. ...That's a long run of coincidences.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, the Reaper's true identity may well be revealed by this trial.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And the impact that revelation would have on the British public cannot be understated.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is that why it's a closed trial?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Precisely.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">This country hasn't seen a closed trial for ten years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the last one...was the Professor's? The trial of Genshin Asogi?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, we heard that originally... ...you were going to prosecute that trial yourself, Lord Stronghart.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Van Zieks entreated me to relinquish the prosecution to him. That he might avenge his brother's death. And here we are, ten years later... ...with the son of the man van Zieks had condemned now looking to avenge his father's death in the same way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They do say that what goes around comes around...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">However, it would seem... ...that the new young prosecutor is harbouring some ulterior motive as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma is?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I like my organisation to run smoothly, in the exact manner that I prescribe. As with the giant clock in here, I won't tolerate a single cog being out of step with the others!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah...so that's what all these gears are about in here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If the young man refuses to mesh with the other parts of my great machine... ...I will be forced to take steps.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What, what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... Not something with which you need concern yourself. In any case, all your questions will be answered tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Your defence lawyer's blazon? It clearly means a lot to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes. It's a keepsake from my best friend as well as a symbol of what I'm trying to achieve.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that friend has returned to us now, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, until it's time to return this to him, I intend to keep wearing it proudly on my arm.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that friend is going to face you in court, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...A complicated situation by the sound of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you aware of the Red-Headed League, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No. I didn't read that advertisement.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems they were trying to swindle red-heads.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I see. Well...I suppose I would be in the White-Headed League, if anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That sounds rather like an elderly gentlemen's club.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oops, I have a feeling... ...I might have made a bit of a faux pas there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! That is a long time!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And I hold you entirely responsible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Even though we miraculously managed to fit everything into not-even-five minutes?</thought> ......... Um, I wonder if you might agree... ...to us, um...talking with Prosecutor Asogi?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Discussions between the defence and the prosecution outside of the courtroom are generally frowned upon. However, I will make an exception in this case. Now go! You can find him in his office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let's go to see him at once, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma's my best friend in the world, but... ...I'm really not at all sure I know how to talk to him at the moment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Lord van Zieks is reading, look.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He doesn't seem like he wants visitors, does he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But he must have noticed that we're here, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... What do you Nipponese want?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's no way to greet the lawyer who's trying his hardest to prove your innocence, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Perhaps not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I apologise. So, what can I do for you, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord van Zieks...speaking earnestly!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, the fog will lift over London for the first time in months tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This does feel very, very strange...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I must say, I was impressed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Well...thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Not by you. By your fellow Nipponese. Your prosecutor friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I see. Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's sardonic, don't you think? For a man such as me, so loathing of the Nipponese, to be entirely at the mercy of the two of you. I suppose... ...it's retribution for having played the part of the Reaper all these years.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Played the part...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You once told me that you gladly allowed people to believe you were the Reaper... ...because it helped reduce the amount of serious crime that took place in London.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">If keeping quiet and playing the part benefits the cause - a cause I myself am committed to pursuing... ...then why would I choose to say anything?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the henchmen of a criminal killed by the Reaper attacked you only the other day. And that was just the most recent of many attempts on your life, wasn't it? Someone is clearly profiting from your silence about all this! Someone is using you!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Believe me, ever since the Reaper first appeared... ...I've been doing my utmost to expose him. Or rather...expose the organisation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! It's a whole organisation?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's inconceivable that all those 'accidents' were orchestrated by one man. No, the Reaper always appears to have very accurate information about the accused in each case. Which can only mean... ...that somebody at Scotland Yard is involved.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Someone at... You, you can't mean...?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's taken me many years, but I've finally identified the central figure in this Reaper organisation: ...Tobias Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No... NOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gregson! The Reaper?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...the reason you were investigating Inspector Gregson is because... ...you intended to expose him as the Reaper?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">As I said, the Reaper of the Bailey is no single person. It's a highly secret organisation with close ties to Scotland Yard. But there's no doubt that Gregson was a key member of that organisation.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Are you saying that Gregsy...? That he was behind all those awful criminals meeting their...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Gregson didn't do the dirty work himself.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He was the tactician. His job was to covertly investigate the marks and plot their assassinations. In order to do that without arousing suspicion, he regularly needed a firm alibi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Which is where Mr Vigil came in. Posing as the inspector...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Vigil knows nothing of the Reaper. But the room he rents on Fresno Street was almost certainly the headquarters of the operation. Gregson would have met the assassin there for briefings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So we don't actually know who carried out the killings, then?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Actually, I do have a name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You... WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well if you can name the man, you have the true identity of the Reaper already, then!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Or...if I can name the woman.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">She's a young woman by the name of Asa Shinn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait... WHAAAT?! <thought>'Shin'?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, this perhaps isn't the place to discuss...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No. No, of course not. <thought>We can't mention it here. The fact that she killed Dr John H. Wilson. Because Iris doesn't know and it's very likely that the man was her father.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Asa Shinn... I should let Father know at once!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Kazuma, isn't it? Kazuma Asogi. You say he's a friend of yours.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My best friend. He's the whole reason I got to come to Britain. It was all on his merits. I have nothing but respect for him.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, I understand that only the very best students are selected for such opportunities. And I had a fine demonstration of how sharp he is in the proceedings earlier today. He missed nothing. In fact, his flawless performance very much reminded me...of his father.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Genshin Asogi. The Professor...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's true that the aristocracy at the time was the root of numerous grave societal problems. They were abusing their power. Playing with the common man as pawns in politics...in economics...in war. In many ways, Asogi was carving out a canker from society that we British couldn't deal with ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, I... I see...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But that's precisely why it makes no sense. Klint van Zieks was a noble and upstanding man. He wasn't corrupt. Why did that damned Nipponese have to go and take my brother's life? ...In spite of having once saved mine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He saved your life? <thought>How did that happen?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was ten years ago, on a foggy night. What was to be the Professor's final strike had...sent a wave of panic through the capital.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So Klint van Zieks had already been killed at this point, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Genshin and I were walking down some back streets at a late hour. Of course, at that point, I had no idea of the true nature of the man at my side. All of a sudden...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">We were surrounded. All of our assailants were armed with pistols, their faces obscured by scarves. Klint was not only from noble heritage, he was a brilliant prosecutor as well. The scum of London hated the sight of him. And they had no sympathy for his younger brother, either. I'd been targeted several times before already.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I could hear them murmuring amongst themselves. I knew they were after me. But just when I thought my time had come...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was Asogi's voice. Just a whisper in my ear.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">After that, I don't remember exactly what happened. The next thing I knew, there was silence all around. Genshin lay on the cobbled street. Blood was seeping from his left hand. He'd shielded me. Two days later...they arrested him. On suspicion of being London's most notorious mass murderer ever: the Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How awful for you...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">All at once, I lost the brother I revered and the foreign friend I held in such high regard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm so sorry, Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, it's just something I was hoping to ask your opinion about, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's a serious crime for the defence to attempt to extract information from the prosecution by illegal means.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think we have more of a defence and client relationship now...don't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, thank you...for confiding in me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The Professor, the Reaper and Inspector Gregson... I wonder just how intimately related they all are...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still can't quite believe that Gregson was essentially the Reaper. <thought>Giving assassination orders to Jezaille Brett...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, let's go and inform my father! I'm sure our government will want to hear about this new information.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! That means I get to meet your daddy, Susie! Hurray!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, alright. <thought>Let's head back to the Great Waterloo Hotel then!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I thought it yesterday and I think it again today. This place is so...princely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a wild guess, but I have a feeling you'll think the same tomorrow, too.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">My tea has a finer fragrance than whatever they're serving in the tea room here though, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, look who we have here! This is an unexpected pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...Father!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh! Is this your daddy, Susie? How lovely!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...What a charming young lady. And you are...?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, really? So you're the author of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', are you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's me! Iris Wilson, at your service, sir! Susie's been such a wonderful friend to me over the last year, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, Miss Wilson... I must say I read your work regularly and with much interest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Iris actually lives with Mr Sholmes, you know, Father.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Is that so? Well, perhaps that goes some way to explaining that bright look in your eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hee hee!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You wouldn't be smiling so airily if you knew just how bright she is, believe me.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now then, young Naruhodo. It was a pleasure seeing you in action earlier. As an invitee of the symposium, I was allowed to observe from the gallery. ...After I twisted some arms. And I must say, it was a truly exemplary performance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Well...thank you very much. <thought>Although I'm fairly sure you omitted 'by Kazuma' on the end there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No no no, please don't misunderstand! It was you who impressed me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You didn't miss a step against Asogi. And we all know how capable he is. Really, to have matured into such a fine defence lawyer in less than a year is quite extraordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...very kind of you to say so. <thought>And really nice to hear.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What I saw in court today confirmed what I'd been hoping for. The favour I mentioned yesterday, Naruhodo. I trust you haven't forgotten?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! No, you...you did mention something, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But first! We have something to report, Father.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Of course, of course. Shall we take tea while we discuss matters further?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm... ...I wonder where Judge Jigoku has got to.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father, do you know about the so-called Reaper of the Bailey?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I've heard rumours. Some members of the judiciary explained it all to me yesterday. Of course, when I was a visitng student here in London, the Reaper was yet to emerge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right, he didn't appear until after that case when the visiting students had already returned home.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Lord van Zieks who was in the dock today... That was Barok, the younger brother of Klint van Zieks, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. And he's known throughout London as the Reaper, as you've heard. But the truth is... ...it wasn't him behind all of those mysterious deaths. It was somebody else!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I see... So what you're saying is, there's been a professional killer at work here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly. Someone by the name of Asa Shinn, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...I beg your pardon? Did, did you say...Asa Shinn?! You mean that Jezaille Brett woman who was responsible for killing my great friend?!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh no! A friend of yours was killed?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Um...Professor Mikotoba, I think perhaps we shouldn't discuss this right now...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because the friend the professor is talking about is Dr John H. Wilson. And that's not something we want Iris to find out about. Not like this, anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Ah! I've, I've just remembered something... Biscuits! This hotel...has the most delicious-looking biscuits!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That was rather out of the blue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>She's doing this deliberately.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think I'll go and see if I can purchase some. I wonder...would you like to come too, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh yes! You just try to leave me behind!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So that young girl... ...is called Iris Wilson, is she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">And she's the author of all those adventure stories starring the great detective Sholmes? But the name of the credited author isn't Iris, is it? It's Dr John H. Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know. That's the name of her father, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Her father? Dr John H. Wilson... I was deeply indebted to the man for all the kindness he showed me during my time in London. That's why I was keen to reciprocate and invite him to the Imperial Yumei University four years ago. .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But he was murdered last year...by Jezaille Brett. <thought>Why? Why would the hand of the Reaper stretch all the way to Japan?</thought> Iris knows nothing about that case. But it seems very likely that the victim, Dr Wilson, was her father.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well...I can't say that we ever spoke about his family. So I don't know if he had a daughter or not. But I think I can say with some certainty...that he was never the great detective's partner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...it could have been another Dr Wilson, you think?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well...John and Wilson are both common names, after all. Still, it's probably best not to mention this to the young lady until we can be sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's what we thought, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">We're back! With cinnamon biscuits!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh! They smell delicious, Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I think cinnamon will go very well with the tea they serve here. Don't you, Susie?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. I'm sure you're right, Iris!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I haven't seen Judge Jigoku for a while, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Guilty! Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But that 'guilty' is still ringing in my ears...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, now you mention it, I haven't seen him since this morning, either. I suppose since the symposium's opening was postponed he'll have gone to explore at the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That reminds me of something you mentioned yesterday. About Judge Jigoku having once been in the dock himself?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes... It was all tied up with that accursed trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The closed trial...of Kazuma's father...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Seishiro was trying to mitigate Genshin's guilt, so he took to the stand to testify. But he...got a little carried away and, um...actually managed to break the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">He also said some contemptuous words about the British Empire...for which he was charged.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear... Although it's worryingly easy to imagine him doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, it was all alright in the end. He was acquitted and we returned home to Japan together.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes, talking of Seishiro... ...I have a copy of the photograph we all took together here yesterday. ...Please.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, what a lovely picture!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It certainly seems to shout, 'We've arrived in Britain!'</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">None of us had any idea what was coming when we took that, did we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No... No, that's so true...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I haven't seen Judge Jigoku for a while, have you?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Guilty! Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But that 'guilty' is still ringing in my ears...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, now you mention it, I haven't seen him since this morning, either. I suppose since the symposium's opening was postponed he'll have gone to explore at the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That reminds me of something you mentioned yesterday. About Judge Jigoku having once been in the dock himself?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes... It was all tied up with that accursed trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The closed trial...of Kazuma's father...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Seishiro was trying to mitigate Genshin's guilt, so he took to the stand to testify. But he...got a little carried away, and um...actually managed to break the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Seishiro">He also said some contemptuous words about the British Empire...for which he was charged.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh dear... Although it's worryingly easy to imagine him doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, it was all alright in the end. He was acquitted and we returned home to Japan together.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you mentioned a favour that you'd like to ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Well, this...fateful trial that you're fighting... One way or another, it will be over before long. And when it is, I'd like you to accompany me back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You want me to do...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">WHAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">F-Father! What's the meaning of this?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now, Susato, you should understand. You've seen how our courts work firsthand. Japan's judicial system is in its infancy. Especially when it comes to defence.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The Supreme Court of Judicature is in desperate need of a good defence lawyer. As soon as possible. Really quite urgently, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">B-But...I've not even been in London a year yet!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I've read all of Susato's reports. I'm well aware of your extraordinary talents. And having seen you in action with my own eyes earlier today, there's no question: You, Naruhodo, are precisely the man our country needs.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So...you'd be leaving then, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But then...what am I supposed to do, Father?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... You came here to serve as Asogi's judicial assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Oh, yes...she's supposed to be Kazuma's assistant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Our government is still in the process of deciding how best to deal with his situation, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You've always chosen your own path, Susato. And I trust your judgement. ...In this matter also.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Please, the pair of you... Don't look so downcast. It's merely a suggestion, you understand. A hope, if I'm honest. But I won't force you. All I ask is that you consider it, and come to a decision by the time this trial concludes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...alright.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You, you won't leave...will you, Runo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>The thought hadn't even crossed my mind. Up until now, I've just been trying to do what I believed to be Kazuma's will. But it turns out that he's still alive, so... ...where does that leave me?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this, Professor Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah...Kazuma's armband. He was wearing that when he left for Great Britain. How curious. It doesn't strike me at all as odd to see you wearing it. It rather suits you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Are you intending to return it to him?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes... I mean, it has his name on it. Now that we've found out he's alive, it doesn't make sense for me to keep it.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, if you ask me... ...I think Kazuma would be delighted to see you wearing it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, I'd feel honoured if that were true.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor, thank you very much for this letter of introduction.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">You're welcome. Only too pleased to help if I can. The words Easterner and Westerner mean nothing, really. If you spend time to get to know people... ...it soon becomes apparent that we're all just humans at the end of the day. Far more alike than most will admit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It would be wonderful if everybody saw it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sadly, not everybody can. We all have our failings, though. As I said, we're all human.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I see now why he's such a respected scholar. It's his magnanimous spirit.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, Father. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I look forward to next month's instalment, Miss Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh good! And please, do come to Baker Street sometime, won't you? We'd love to entertain you!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I would be delighted. The best of luck for tomorrow, Naruhodo. And... ...give my suggestion your full consideration, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I will. <thought>Going back home...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know, Kazuma-sama has always meant a great deal to my father. I'm sure he'd love the chance to meet with him and talk to him about all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, no doubt...</line>
<line speaker="???">......... Asa Shinn... Of course! It's so obvious!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">How could I have neglected to consider the possibility before now?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Agh! M-Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley! Where have you been?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, I joined you all for tea, of course. What an extraordinary question.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I...didn't notice you at all.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No matter, no matter! Anyway, to more pressing concerns. ...Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! ...Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I must dispatch a telegram to your country at once. It is a matter of much urgency.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To...Japan, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tell me, to whom can I entrust the task? Quickly now! Who?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, well... ...my father has just now left to send a telegram to the Imperial Police Bureau of Japan himself.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I see. Well, he looked reliable enough for a bearded fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't think what Father sports could be considered a beard, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">There's not a moment to lose! Kindly ask your trusty unshaven father to see this is sent!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I will, but...what is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No questions at this time, if you please, Miss Susato. All we can do is pray... ...that for once my deduction is awry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Doesn't that imply that your deductions are normally correct, Mr Sholmes? Which isn't exactly-</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now then! You may be surprised to learn that I am a very busy man. I certainly have no time to hide behind settees and eavesdrop on other people's conversations.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's what 'joining us for tea' meant...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I leave the sending of this in your hands then, my dear fellows.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Wait a minute! Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">He just sort of ran off, didn't he? At quite a pace.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And left the unpaid bill for his tea behind, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I must catch up with Father at the telegraph office at once!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">And I'll run and call us a cab straight away!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And there was me thinking everyone would be clamouring to pay Mr Sholmes's bill...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is the ward where Mr Vigil was brought, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>To be frank, I'm a little worried about seeing him again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Ah. The lawyer. Hello again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are, are you feeling better now, Mr Vigil?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes, thank you. Somewhat better.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm so sorry to have caused you to... I mean, it was because of me. If I hadn't exposed your secret and forced you to remember things you'd obviously tried to forget...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... The prosecutor was here until a few moments ago, too. You just missed him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>Kazuma beat us to it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">He said much the same as you. He was very apologetic. But the truth is...I brought all this upon myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Please, don't think like that...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Keeping it from Evie - my wife - all these years... I've carried such a sense of guilt. But that's not the worst of it. Over time...I obviously came to deceive myself as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You mean...about your dismissal?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Looking back now... ...I'm beginning to think that perhaps Inspector Gregson didn't stumble across me by accident at all. I mean, he compensated me so generously for acting as his stand-in. He was clearly concerned for my wellbeing and... doing what he could to help.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So perhaps Gregson knew exactly what had become of Mr Vigil all along, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'm sure this is just deserts for ten years of lies and deception, but... ...it wasn't me that helped the Professor escape ten years ago! It wasn't me! I swear it! I swear it's true!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Vigil...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sure you'd rather not dredge up even more from your past at this time, but... ...if possible, could you tell us exactly what really happened?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... I want to. I need to get all this off my chest. I just want someone to tell me what I should have done!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This notice caught my eye before, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose it's some sort of slogan for the ward? A cheerful welcome message perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's see... 'Pay with good cheer; leave with good cheer.' Well look at that! You were spot on, Miss Susato. It is full of 'cheer'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I wonder how many discharged patients pay their medical bills with good cheer, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Once I had to have a very painful injection when I fell ill with a cold. I felt awful already. So why did I have to suffer the sting of the injection as well as the bill? I yelled at the doctor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...what terrible treatment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These must be the patient's treatment notes. Let's see... 'Tendency to jump from windows. Remember to place cushion at base of wall outside.' ...Aren't we a storey up from the ground here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Poor Mr Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't help feeling that there's a better solution to the problem than a cushion, though... <thought>Finding something you'd lost isn't always a happy experience, it turns out.</thought> Pursuing the truth can be...a very dark business sometimes, can't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...I'm afraid it can.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are all sorts of medicines in this cabinet, look. I'm not sure if it's safe leaving them in reach of everyone like this.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. I can imagine if you were peckish, you might try some of the pills.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well, at least there seems to be a little lock to secure the cabinet doors.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't imagine that would stop you if you were hungry. I worry that you'd break the lock.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Hunger doesn't turn me into a criminal, you know, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, patient treatment notes... What do these say, I wonder? 'Endlessly obliging.' I suppose that's referring to the patient in this bed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I would think so. And until Mr Vigil is a little more stable... ...it's probably just as well that he has a kindly person in the neighbouring bed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The 'endlessly' part is a little worrying though, isn't it? I mean, what if Mr Vigil suddenly declared that he'd like to take a trip out of the window? Would this endlessly obliging patient simply open it for him and say, 'Be my guest'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Let's check with the doctor later.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah look, a pair of crutches. Before we came to Britain, I hadn't realised they were used here as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I imagine they were imported into Japan from Great Britain in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, so no one in all of Japan broke a leg before their arrival? Anyway, the sight of these things doesn't bring back good memories for me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. Did you injure yourself once and need to use some?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When I was little. I thought they looked fun, so I borrowed a pair to play with. But then I slipped and sprained my ankle.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">They contain powerful magic, those wooden staffs: the power to heal, and the power to harm!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I think a certain cheeky little boy managed to cause the harm all by himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are lots of bottles in that cabinet there, aren't there? Do you think it's safe to keep them there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee! If you were a patient here, I feel sure you'd take some medicine by mistake when you were half asleep!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That is a worry. But at least the cabinet has a lock, even if it's only a flimsy-looking one.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I've no doubt you'd manage to unlock that somehow while you were half asleep as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...There are limits even to what I can do when I'm half asleep, you know, Miss Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Inspector Gregson was obviously engaged in a special operation of some sort. He was investigating something that even Scotland Yard couldn't know about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Details of the Reaper's marks, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">It was when he had to carry out those investigations that I would take his identification and impersonate him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You'd pretend to be the inspector and carry out investigations on his behalf?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Oh no! Never! A common street pedlar couldn't possibly carry out a proper police investigation! All I would do is go to the specified location and make a little hoo-ha. Just something to leave an impression. So everyone there would think, 'A detective called Gregson was here.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...that's what you were doing on the day prior to the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes. He asked me to make an appearance at the park on Lime Street for the Red-Headed League event. So as usual, I flashed the inspector's identification around and was very vocal about my presence.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But then you were taken prisoner! By those red-headed fraudsters.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you would always make a point of showing Gregson's identification and generally being loud?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">That's what the inspector asked me to do, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well that's one way of becoming a legendary detective, I suppose. ...Not a good one, though.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">And as you know, I suffered this bruising around my neck at their hands. But the following day they kept their word and released me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Without returning the inspector's identification to you, however.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">We had arranged to meet in the Fresno Street room at five that day so I could report back to the inspector. But at the agreed time, that's when I heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">It was at midnight on 17th June ten years ago. That was the time scheduled for the execution.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the Professor's execution never actually took place, did it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or rather, the execution itself must have been used to effect the plan of escape. I hardly dare to imagine what a chilling plan it was...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Barclay was renowned for being the highest security prison in the country. Everything that went in or out of the place was searched multiple times. But...there was one notable exception. Or rather, one notable loophole. Something that was never questioned.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have a feeling I know what that loophole was now. The coffins into which the bodies of the executed convicts were placed, correct?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">...Yes. Once the coroner had confirmed the death of a condemned convict... ...the body was taken in its coffin for immediate burial in Lowgate Cemetery just behind the prison. The chief warder first had to sign the necessary papers. And after that no member of staff was permitted to touch the coffin containing the body again.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">When executions took place, only the executioner and the coroner were permitted inside the chamber. I would wait in the adjacent room for word that the condemned convict was dead. On that occasion, once I had that confirmation, I went into the mortuary to find a lone coffin, as usual. The procedure was that I would sign the paperwork having checked the coffin, then nail it shut. But for some reason that day, the coffin was already nailed shut.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I didn't think anything of it at the time. I assumed that my deputy must have checked the coffin and nailed it shut before I arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you mean...?! The coffin contained...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes. I can only imagine that Asogi, having escaped his execution somehow, was alive inside the coffin. The coffin was then taken out through the main gates and deposited in Lowgate Cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Presumably there wouldn't have been enough air inside to breathe for long.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So in the early hours following the burial, somebody dug up the coffin again to set Genshin free.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But in the end... ...he was fatally shot in the graveyard anyway. What on earth really happened in Lowgate Cemetery that night, I wonder?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'm afraid I really don't know. All I can say with certainty are two things: Asogi couldn't possibly have escaped that way without help from somebody working in the prison. And that somebody...was not me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously, you knew the man then? The Professor, I mean. Genshin Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes. I remember him well, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would you mind...telling us what you know?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Well, having been condemned to death as he was, any contact I had with the man was short, obviously. After that trial, which was carried out behind closed doors, attended only by elite members of the judiciary... ...they called for his execution to be carried out at the earliest possible opportunity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The outcome of the trial was set from the beginning, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a time of delicate diplomacy, when Britain and Japan were in the process of signing an important treaty. That meant that this potentially destabilising case had to be dealt with swiftly and discreetly.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The man had less than a week in total. As I was the chief warder, I oversaw his short stay in the cells until his final hour. I remember being struck deeply by his noble character and incredible resilience.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">He was a killer of many men, but he was always quiet and polite. He was a gentleman, and a man of intellect. In fact, I couldn't bring myself to believe what he'd done, so I asked him one day.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Those five members of the aristocracy whose lives were taken... Were you really responsible?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The following day, the closed trial took place. And the verdict was no surprise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Guilty.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">That night, when he was brought back to his cell... ...I saw something. Something...unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something unusual? What?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The last will and testament...of Genshin Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">As I said, it was on the night following his trial, after he'd been found guilty. I was doing the rounds of the cells, and when I looked into Asogi's... ...I noticed that he seemed to have a sheet of paper in his hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... <thought>His last will and testament then, presumably.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">As soon as he noticed me, he hurriedly shoved it behind his back.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...why did you find that so unusual? Isn't it normal for a man to pen a will when he knows his death is nigh?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes, that's true. But there were special conditions to Asogi's incarceration, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of conditions?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Well...even though he was held in a cell designed for condemned inmates... ...he was allowed to keep his personal effects with him, with one exception.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? He was allowed his things? <thought>That is unusual, certainly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Of course, he'd been convicted of killing five members of the aristocracy... ...but at the same time he was a guest in our country from the Empire of Japan. The powers that be were determined that his final days shouldn't be needlessly uncomfortable.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what was the exception you mentioned...to the personal effects he was allowed?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">That's the point. He wasn't permitted to have writing utensils. Specifically, no pens or paper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...he was prevented from leaving any written record of what had happened to him?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes, that was the long and the short of it. I've no idea where he obtained that paper. Any writing materials would have been confiscated from him upon his incarceration. As I said, he hid the paper behind his back and then he pleaded with me:</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">What did you just hide behind your back?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">But...you know it's against the rules.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Alright then. But what's on that paper?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How can a will be a weapon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">So I decided to pretend I'd seen nothing. And I let him keep his will. But then later... ...it just seemed to vanish without trace.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! What do you mean, it vanished?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would seem that isn't the end of the story of this mysterious will.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I was the only person who saw Asogi's will, but...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...But somehow it disappeared.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">It was after Asogi's 'execution'.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Which was actually an elaborate jailbreak!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The warders gathered up Asogi's possessions that were in his cell. They were all to be sent back to his family home in Japan, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To poor Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you're saying that it wasn't anywhere to be found among his personal effects? The will, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">That's right. Though I didn't search through them myself. But Governor Caidin was livid. He was screaming, 'It cannae have disappeared completely!'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That...doesn't quite make sense though, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, we'd understood that only Mr Vigil was aware of the will's existence. In which case, how did the prison governor know to look for it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I really don't know how he knew. But it certainly seemed as though he knew of the will's existence from the outset. Only he didn't refer to it as a will. What he said was... ...the 'Asogi Papers'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Asogi Papers...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I really can't tell you anything of the subsequent events. Because...well...of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Your dismissal...and the way you blocked it all from your memory...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'd forgotten all this until today. I don't suppose it's relevant to the case, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well anyway, thank you very much for sharing it with us, Mr Vigil. We're very grateful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Vigil, would you mind casting your eyes over this?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... Ugh... My head... It's, it's throbbing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no! It's too soon, Mr Naruhodo! It's too much for him!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's too much for me seeing him swoon like that. <thought>Maybe I should lay off the evidence for a while...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no, not at all. Thank you again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But what will become of you now?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Well, impersonating a police officer is a criminal offence, of course. I imagine that once I'm fully recovered, I shall be arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm so sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Don't be, please. This was all my own doing. I always knew that this day would come.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I wish you well. Goodbye, Mr Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! Before you go! There's just one thing!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Y-Yes? What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The Asogi Papers...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'd be very grateful if you'd make no mention of the things I told you about them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Presumably for some good reason?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... It's my understanding that their very existence is a closely guarded secret. If it became known that I'd remembered... Well...it could be rather troublesome, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I understand. <thought>Some sort of will that Genshin Asogi penned just before his death. Which the man himself claimed was his last 'weapon'... I wonder... Perhaps it had something to do with his plan to escape...</thought> If there's anyone who might know more about a document that Kazuma's father left behind...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...It would be Mr Vigil's governor!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then we know precisely where we must go. Back to Barclay Prison!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well...at least he seems to be on the mend.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know... ...his disguise as Mr Gossip was really quite masterful, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't remember anything about it except for the floppy lip.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I imagine not even his wife would have recognised him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps. But did he really have to take it quite so far?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Och, back again, are you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, yes... Hello.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I've heard all aboot your investigations. I read the report just now. You've found him, eh? Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, luckily.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Well, anyhoo... ...the laddie does'nae work here no more. So your case is nowt to do wi' Barclay. I would'nae like you...to get the wrong idea aboot that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, yes. Mr Vigil stopped working here ten years ago now, so...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, we've seen his dismissal notice, haven't we? He was given the chop!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, kimmer. You ken very well. So...how aboot a wee handcuff biscuit?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, they really are like little handcuffs! ...And as hard as irons, too!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">So? What's brought you doon here the day?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...there's something else we'd like to ask you about, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Is that so?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We believe there might have been a document that disappeared from Genshin Asogi's cell. I think it's been called the Asogi Papers or something?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... Did I no say? Gregson's death is nowt to do wi' things that might have happened at Barclay. Leave the past in the past, laddie. Let's not footer aboot wi' irrelevant details.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>His expression's changed completely. We're clearly onto something here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">That murderer's botched execution... And the whole miserable escape... They were Barclay's darkest hour, aye. A shocking embarrassment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because the convict had a collaborator on the prison staff, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">...Aye, for shame. The coroner who confirmed the death o' the man after his execution, Courtney Sithe. And my chief warder at the time, Vigil, who was in charge o' the whole affair.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But Mr Vigil says he didn't know anything about it.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">The rascal would'nae say otherwise, eh? ...More handcuffs?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! How could I say no? ...You can never have too much iron in your diet!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When Mr Vigil was handed his dismissal notice as a result of what had happened... ...he was so despairing, he jumped out of your office window, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I dinnae like to say, but that's just Vigil trying to get oot of it. Do you no think he would'nae have jumped from the shock of his crimes being exposed, eh? ...I do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You would'nae say otherwise though, would you?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Of course, I cannae shun all responsibility myself. I should'nae have let him deceive me. Actually, there's barely anybody that kens what went on at the time now. Wi' Gregson having been murdered, and Dr Sithe forbidden from having any visitors.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No visitors? Someone obviously doesn't want her giving anything away...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...we're not going home empty-handed!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">And I would'nae dream of sending you packing wi' nowt, kimmer. Here...take a handcuff or two!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Well it would be rude to say no! ...Wouldn't want to become anaemic!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I suppose...if there's anybody who might still ken aboot what happened back then... ...it'd be that lass from the forensic division. Maria Gorey.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maria...Gorey?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, Sithe's daughter. She did'nae have no more. Just the one. But the wee bairn's followed in her mam's footsteps. You dinnae ever see her wi'out a scalpel in her hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="???">Mama, what is this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Agh! <thought>Wh-Where did SHE spring from? And...did she just call the doctor, 'Mama'?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Dr Sithe's daughter, Maria Gorey... We could do with talking to her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...she's Dr Sithe's daughter, but her surname is Gorey?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, there's some family history, I'm sure, but I dinnae ken the ins and oots of it. She grew up watching her mam working wi' the bodies of folk who'd died in strange circumstances... ...and decided to do the same wi' her own life. I cannae understand it myself.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps she was driven by a deep respect for her mother...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Perhaps... Anyhoo, she was in charge of Gregson's autopsy, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right. And the coroner responsible for this incomplete report...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Someone told me once that the wee lassie always loved her mam's stories aboot cutting up bodies. There's even a rumour that she used to listen to the funeral march as a lullaby.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well then perhaps...her mother might have told her about the autopsy from the case ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, I'd say there's a fighting chance at least. After all, that was a life-changing case for all of us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We really need to speak to Miss Gorey herself about this, I think.</thought> Well...thank you very much.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I'm no happy aboot any part o' this. It took years for Londoners to finally forget the whole Professor business. Can you no gi' up on this, laddie? Stop asking pointless questions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm sorry. I don't like dredging up these painful memories for everyone.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Can you no just stay away noo? Leave me alone and dinnae come back here, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">How d'you come to ken aboot that, laddie? There's no many folk even here in the prison who've heard o' those papers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well... <thought>I can't tell him Mr Vigil told me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid our sources must remain confidential, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've been led to believe the papers are actually a last will and testament. Is that right? The Professor's... Or rather, Genshin Asogi's...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... Aye, that's right. ...You're well informed, Jimmy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh, is that the end of the silent treatment?</thought> But then after the convict's execution, it mysteriously vanished from his cell, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Havers, no! You're off at half-cock there. I think you did'nae quite get your facts straight. It was there in the cell, exactly where it should've been.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... <thought>Not what we heard elsewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Let me just have a wee holk aroond in here. I'm sure I can find it... Aye, here ye are.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The Last Will and Testament of Genshin Asogi'... Written with a calligraphy brush...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Of course, I cannae read a word of those Japanese squiggles. But I mind it says he leaves all his worldly possessions to his son back in his homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's correct. That's the gist of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So these...are the Asogi Papers?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, of course they are! Papers written by Asogi, nae doubt aboot it. There's no mystery here, laddie. That's your lot! After all the stramash o' that slaister of an execution... ...we sent the man's possessions back to his clan in Japan... and that was the end of it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we ought to make a record of this, Mr Naruhodo. Just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">One thing afore you go on your way, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Those papers are nowt to do wi' Gregson's death. I'd prefer it if you did'nae make no mention of them ootside this office. Or rather... ...I would'nae just prefer it. Consider it an order from the highest levels of oor government.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">How d'you come to ken aboot that, laddie? There's no many folk even here in the prison who've heard o' those papers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...well... <thought>I can't tell him Mr Vigil told me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid our sources must remain confidential, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Hmph...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We've been led to believe the papers are actually a last will and testament. Is that right? The Professor's... Or rather, Genshin Asogi's...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... Aye, that's right. ...You're well informed, Jimmy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh, is that the end of the silent treatment?</thought> But then after the convict's execution, it mysteriously vanished from his cell, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Havers, no! You're off at half-cock there. I think you did'nae quite get your facts straight. It was there in the cell, exactly where it should've been.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh... <thought>Not what we heard elsewhere...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Let me just have a wee holk aroond in here. I'm sure I can find it... Aye, here ye are.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'The Last Will and Testament of Genshin Asogi'... Written with a calligraphy brush...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Of course, I cannae read a word of those Japanese squiggles. But I mind it says he leaves all his worldly possessions to his son back in his homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's correct. That's the gist of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So these...are the Asogi Papers?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, of course they are! Papers written by Asogi, nae doubt aboot it. There's no mystery here, laddie. That's your lot! After all the stramash o' that slaister of an execution... ...we sent the man's possessions back to his clan in Japan... and that was the end of it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we ought to make a record of this, Mr Naruhodo. Just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">One thing afore you go on your way, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Those papers are nowt to do wi' Gregson's death. I'd prefer it if you did'nae make no mention of them ootside this office. Or rather... ...I would'nae just prefer it. Consider it an order from the highest levels of oor government.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So...this is the office of 'Prosecutor Asogi' now, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama is...doing so well for himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Even though he's always forced to kneel on the floor Japanese-style in that dark corner?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's his habit to sit seiza-style whenever he's working!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, it looks like our journey here was wasted. The prosecutor appears to be out.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Perhaps we should discuss things with another prosecutor we know first?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's see, what have we here...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...it would be very underhand to glean information from Kazuma-sama's office while he's absent.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We should wait until he's here before we start nosing around!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Of, of course, yes. <thought>She doesn't take any nonsense when it comes to Kazuma, does she?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I thought it wouldn't be long before you paid me a visit, Ryunosuke. I was right about what I said, wasn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That you have all the makings of a great defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well I...always believed that you'd fulfil your dream of advocating in the British courts. <thought>I just never imagined for one second that it would be as a prosecutor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Seeing you stand in a foreign courtroom, so gallantly realising your dream, Kazuma-sama... I'm...truly happy for you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And I am truly thankful to you, Judicial Assistant Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... ...I always thought it would be fun for you and I to shake up the British legal system a little together. This isn't quite how I envisaged it, but... ...I suppose it's just another twist of fate.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I've learnt a lot of things during my time in London. About how Susato-san's father was himself a visiting student here once, along with Judge Jigoku. And... ...about what happened with your father.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then you'll have no difficulty understanding. Why I had no choice. Why I had to find a way to get to Britain as a visiting student myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I want to hear it from you, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...As you wish, Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks's fine collection of hallowed chalices and bottles, all neatly lined up.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, he's extremely particular about all that. He has a strict regime for everything from the storage of the casks to the bottling of their contents.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gosh, you must be having a really tough time of it being his apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Actually, no.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He's so particular about it all, he refuses to let anybody else touch any of it. So it's been quite easy for me, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Talk about weird.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's Lord van Zieks's incredibly stylish desk.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's not my style, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I notice you've been working at the little table on the floor, kneeling down seiza-style. I thought it was some kind of punishment set up by Lord van Zieks when I first saw it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I find it the most comfortable way to work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't do it. After a couple of minutes of sitting with my legs folded under me, they start to go tingly.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't exaggerate, Ryunosuke. ...We both know you can't even manage a minute.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you know who the man in the portrait is?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Why would I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! But you're Lord van Zieks's apprentice!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, apprentice, not friend. And during the time I was suffering from amnesia, I didn't even notice that picture.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...really? <thought>I mean, it's not the smallest picture...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I wouldn't have the first idea what the man decorates his office with.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What the...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's a scale model of the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, I realise that. ...Does the prosecution office make a model of the scene for every single case?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Apparently so. Sometimes it helps to visualise things better and notice things you hadn't spotted before. Actually, the miniature noticeboard is my work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Be honest...you enjoyed making that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You disturbed the bats, did you? Fitting companions of Lord van Zieks, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually... ...I've seen things flying in Lord Stronghart's office, too. Doves, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Perhaps you have to like birds to attain rank in the judiciary here... Although bats aren't birds, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... How about a sparrow for you?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What's that supposed to mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Nothing. Sorry. Just thinking out loud...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Casks floor to ceiling, just like the last time we were here. Hallowed barrels, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They're arranged according to vintage, flavour and region. Every week, they're all taken out and put back in order.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Every week?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Lord van Zieks can't seem to settle on the perfect way of arranging them, you see. Vintage, flavour and region don't neatly coincide, that's the trouble.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gosh, being his apprentice must be a real challenge.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Actually, no.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He considers the task too important to entrust to anybody else, so he does it entirely on his own.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So he's a barrel of laughs here AND in court, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's getting on for a year now. Since what happened on the SS Burya. <thought>We were heading across the oceans from Japan to Great Britain... ...when a bizarre serious [sic] of coincidences led to those tragic events.</thought> I thought...I'd lost my best friend forever.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I must have been unconscious for a long time. When I awoke, I was lying on a bed. It was a narrow little room. There was a posy of flowers by the pillow. It took me a little while to realise that I was in the cabin of a ship. I slipped out of the room and headed up onto the deck.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Were you already suffering from amnesia at that point?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. I didn't know what had happened or where I was. There was just this voice in my head.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was a calling I couldn't ignore. It compelled me relentlessly. Out on deck, I saw that I was on a huge steamship and we were docked in a large port.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It must have been Hong Kong!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it must have been. Presumably just before they were due to carry your 'body' off the ship.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I had no idea of the situation. But I did have the feeling that this was in some way my last chance. So I concealed myself among the disembarking passengers and went ashore. Then I disappeared into the crowded streets of that foreign port city... ...so I could plan my onward journey to Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just under a year ago, with all my past memories lost to me, I was left behind in Hong Kong. Everything was foreign to me. The sights, the sounds, the smells. My head reeled. I was truly at a loss. I realise now that I'd escaped as a dead man. With nothing but the clothes on my back. No money, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how terrifying for you...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Luckily though, I had two feathers in my cap.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">One being your knowledge of English, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right. And on the back of that, I was able to pick up some work as a deck hand on a cargo ship. Eventually, after calling at countless ports, I finally arrived at Dover. That must have been some three months ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Your formidable tenacity of purpose showing itself again. <thought>I mean, the man had lost his memory and had literally nothing to his name... ...but he still managed to make his way to London on the opposite side of the world.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of course, I had no idea why I'd moved heaven and earth to get here at that point.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...how did you end up becoming Lord van Zieks's apprentice, then?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That...can only be called an extraordinary stroke of luck really. You see, I was stopped at the border because I had no papers. They took me straight to Scotland Yard. And by sheer coincidence, Lord Stronghart was there to attend a meeting. That's when the second feather in my cap came into play.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would that have been your knowledge of the law?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, exactly. Lord Stronghart was curious about an Easterner with intimate knowledge of British law. He took me back with him to the Supreme Court and assigned me to the Prosecutor's Office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And then, nine days ago... ...you finally got your memory back after the trial involving Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes...I did.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ever since I first met you at Yumei, you talked about your dream.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Mark my words, Ryunosuke. I'll be chosen as a visiting student, and make my way to Great Britain someday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you know the entire time? About what happened to your father here?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Sixteen years ago... ...when my father left on that exciting trip to Great Britain, I was just a boy. We took a photograph together the day before his departure. ...It's my last memory of him. But what I remember most about my father...is his unswerving sense of justice. Six years after he left, a gentleman called at our family home. He told me that Genshin - my father - had been taken ill in England and passed away. It was Professor Mikotoba. Your father, Susato-san.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ever since then, the professor was very good to me. He even helped to fund my university education at Yumei. I'll be forever in his debt. But nevertheless...I just couldn't bring myself to believe what he'd told me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then one day, a letter arrived at our house from Britain. There was no indication of the sender, so I opened it assuming it was from an old acquaintance of my father. ......... What I read in that letter changed my entire life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What did it say?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It said that my father had been a mass murderer, and the writer cursed the Asogi name.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As a result of that letter, I found out what had been hidden from me all those years.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Presumably the letter was sent from a relative of one of the victims. If whoever it was had been a member of the judiciary, he could have been present at the closed trial. The letter revealed that my father had been sentenced to death. Executed for being a killer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm, I'm so sorry you had to find out that way...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I imagine the British government did its very best to silence whoever sent that letter. But someone who knew the truth and couldn't bear the resentment was always going to be a problem.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But still! It, it could have been written by anyone. Why would you believe such a thing?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There was a newspaper cutting included with the letter. It was the first I'd ever heard of the Professor and his terrible killing spree.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...what did my father have to say about the letter?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I couldn't bring myself to show it to him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Because he'd deliberately concealed the truth from me by telling me my father was taken by a fatal illness. That couldn't have been easy for him. And he'd done it out of consideration for my feelings. So instead...I showed the letter to Judge Jigoku.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, to the other visiting student...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He faltered for the briefest of moments, but then he just laughed the letter off. But in that moment, I saw it on his face. He was undeniably shocked. Shaken momentarily, before recovering his poise.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A year later, my bereaved mother succumbed to the strain of grief, and she too passed away. That's when I made up my mind. That one day...without fail... ...I would cross the seas to Britain and seek the truth for myself. The truth about my father, Genshin Asogi. And I wouldn't let anyone stand in my way!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What we learnt today in court turned things completely on their head. It was an impressive piece of lawyering...Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks isn't the Reaper, you know. I almost don't want to believe it myself, but it turns out that Inspector Gregson himself, the victim, was...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's clear that the inspector was behind the Reaper's activity all along.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? <thought>You mean, you knew?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The real question is, who's been giving orders to the inspector? ......... Yes, Barok van Zieks is the real Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And I know that ten years ago, it was him... ...who decided my father must be a mass murderer and sent him to his grave!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No! He was merely seeing that justice was done as the law dictates. He's not to blame.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ultimately, it's people who condemn people. The law is just a tool that they use to do it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And when a man condemns another, he must take responsibility for his actions. Of course he must. But I know for certain...that my father would never have taken another man's life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">On the contrary, my father's life was taken... by the Reaper!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...this is your armband.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Actually, I think it's yours now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're the defence lawyer. You have a talent for it. ...I've always known that you would. And now you've chosen to take that path in life. As your friend, I couldn't be happier for you. Or more proud.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you keep hold of that. Besides, I'm a prosecutor now. That armband would have no meaning to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Well, if you're sure. Thank you...my friend.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was shocked when I found out they were related to the case. The Red-Headed League, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Personally it wasn't their plan to swindle everyone that surprised me. It was the fact that so many red-headed people gathered from all over London that day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A certain great detective being among them...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I expect those two are in their cells as we speak, wishing they'd never dreamt up their little plan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Or maybe they're busy plotting their next one...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Reaper... At last I get to take my revenge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma... Lord van Zieks isn't responsible for your father's death. And he's not the Reaper. He's the defendant and deserving of a fair trial.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You mean like the one my father had?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's a closed trial now, too. The conditions are exactly as they were ten years ago. And even if it ruffles some feathers...I have a plan to show that man for what he really is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This came up in the trial, didn't it? As something a little dubious, I mean. The fact that no time of death was recorded on Inspector Gregson's autopsy report.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, there were some unexpected turns in the courtroom earlier. The suggestion you came up with certainly took everyone by surprise. The idea that the victim died the previous day at some other location is quite something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, considering when the pocket watch had stopped and the scorch marks on the candle... ...it's certainly a distinct possibility. The evidence and the scene both point to it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... To be honest, it bothered me too. So I paid a visit to the autopsy room earlier. The coroner responsible wasn't there, but I got a name. It's Dr Gorey.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um, if it wouldn't trouble you, Kazuma-sama... ...we'd very much like to speak with the coroner, too!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Of course. The last thing I want is for anything to be brushed under the carpet. Scotland Yard's autopsy laboratory is behind Lowgate Cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lowgate Ceme... By Barclay Prison, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ah, you know it, do you? The prison where my father was incarcerated... and robbed of his life.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...thank you. We'll pay a visit to the laboratory later today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There's only one place where defence lawyers and prosecutors should discuss evidence. The courtroom. So it seems you're still confused by the situation. ...That's what I make of it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I get the feeling my friend's always going to have the edge over me, isn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What for?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">For this. You safeguarded the soul of the Asogi clan.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it is a famous sword that's been in your family for generations. My only slight regret is that I never got the chance to draw it before I returned it to you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Karuma is said to have been forged by a master swordsmith during the Sengoku warring states period. I come from a long lineage of warriors, many of whom were expert swordsmen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well then, you're a chip off the old block, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This blade - Karuma - is the symbol of the Asogi clan's honour and might. Apparently, one of my father's apprentices even took the blade's name for a surname.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Karuma... It does sound formidable, that's for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Sixteen years ago, when my father was a visiting student here in London, he had this sword forever at his side. Which is why it means so much to me that I have it by my side again now too. And that...is all thanks to you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It was an honour.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Now...I have preparations to make for tomorrow. Perhaps I said a little too much.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma, you've...changed.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, Ryunosuke, I haven't changed at all. It's you who's changed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I can completely understand your resentment of Lord van Zieks given what happened. But the fact is, those events and this case are, well...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Unrelated? Is that you want to say? How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Never mind. That man is the Reaper. And it's for that reason that the inspector was killed. I'm going to prove as much in court tomorrow... by whatever means necessary!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't let you do that, Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I know you'll do what you have to as a lawyer. But I'm sure I don't need to tell you that I won't be taking any prisoners in the courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I would expect nothing less.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Until tomorrow then...in the Old Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Someone's sharpening again...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">You're still not dead? Anyway, I don't have anything more to tell you about that specimen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Actually, we're not here to ask you about Inspector Gregson. We were hoping to talk about your mother, Dr Sithe.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's something the governor of Barclay Prison mentioned. He said that she was responsible for confirming the death of the Professor after his execution.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This place...really is creepy, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...being a dead room, it's probably full of the spirits of the dissected.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But actually...there's a rather pleasing scent of roses in the air!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well...being a dead room... ...the coroner probably needs a bold scent like that to mask the odour of death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Iris... ...do you think we could change the subject?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wh-What was that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... Erm... Dr Gorey?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...that noise before...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I was sharpening my tools. I'd be dead meat if I didn't keep a perfectly keen edge on them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">R-Right...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">When following the collagen fibres in the dermis, an expertly sharpened scalpel... ...cuts like cheese. Would you like a demonstration?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, yes please! I'd love to see!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Then...I think you'll do nicely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?! N-No! No, I wouldn't do nicely at all! I mean...maybe some other time!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Tsk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Was that a tut? Well...we came here to ask questions, so...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A table and a set of sharp tools... When you consider each in isolation, it all looks quite innocent. So why is it that when you put them side by side, they seem so horribly disturbing?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It might be best not to ponder it too deeply.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">That's Mama's dissection table. It's too high for me, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it is...?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">If I fell from that height in my sleep, it would really hurt.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Wha...?! You, you mean you sleep in here?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...Autopsy work is very involved. It's usually too late to think about going home when I'm finished. But I have bad dreams when I sleep here, and I always end up falling onto the floor. So I'd like to exchange that table for a lower one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe you should just go home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Those large jars seem to have pale things floating around inside them. I suppose they're fruit liquors or something. Or like the pickled umeboshi plums we make back home.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes, let's assume they're something completely innocent like that!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Ah, that jar you're looking at up there contains monkey brains.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">The composition is similar to the human brain, so they make for interesting study material. And in the next jar along, we have monkey-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! No more monkey anythings! ...Please.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...If you say so.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... The time when I still thought it was just some pickled umeboshi plums seems so long ago already...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at all the bottles on the shelves in these cabinets! What an assortment of chemicals!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">These ones here are labelled 'Highly Toxic'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, that's worrying. Because there are also things that look like salt and pepper shakers in there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! And they actually say 'salt' and 'pepper' on them! The doctor probably spends a lot of time in this room, I suppose. Perhaps she has meals here sometimes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Life goes on...even when you're surrounded by death...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This looks...different to before.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course, Mr Naruhodo. Miss Gorey is a young maiden. She has all sorts of charming little dolls and the like around her place of work, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, you're right. Perhaps she's not so strange after all.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...They're how I practise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Mama always says that operations and dissections require speed and accuracy. So I take out my needle and thread and stitch three new dolls every day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...right...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I used to make livers or kidneys or intestines... ...but Mama told me to make something more friendly instead.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... That's...quite different to what I'd imagined.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, look at this! What a magnificent display case! The cherry wood has been polished to a high sheen, and the intricate carving is a joy to behold. Western cabinet makers really are very skilled, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It's ten people.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It's made from the bones of ten different people, all mixed together. Some of my best work!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I was admiring the case, actually. The scary skeleton inside is...something I intend to ignore as best I can.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... You're strange.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I wonder who is the strangest...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That looks like an owl and a crow up there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. And they haven't even twitched since we came in here...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well no, they wouldn't have. They're taxidermy mounts, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...I was afraid you were going to say that. I've been trying very hard to tell myself they're just sleeping with their eyes open.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think perhaps you were wise to put something like your daruma doll on display in the office instead...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, we have actually met before. I'm a lawyer, if you remember...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">You're not dead yet...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...so Mama said I wasn't to cut you open. She's so strict about things like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...good. <thought>Dr Sithe has some scruples at least...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear... It looks like she's not interested in talking to us. For the time being, anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For the time being? You mean...until we die? I hope that's a way off...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, but...I wasn't planning on dying any time soon.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Tsk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Surely there's some less drastic way of making her listen...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...why doesn't this autopsy report include the victim's time of death then? It's really the most crucial detail.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I was told not to write it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! By whom?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Mael Stronghart. The Lord Chief Justice. He came here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord Stronghart came...?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">He said that from the witness statements about the gunshot and the other evidence, it was obvious. The man clearly died at 5 p.m. on 1st November, when the gunshot was heard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But that's not the time of death you wrote on the report. You didn't write anything. Was there...some reason you didn't include it?!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Gorey... ...if you're hiding something under Lord Stronghart's instructions... ...then sooner or later you're going to go the same way as your mother.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Give it here then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm? <thought>What's she scribbling so furiously?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">There.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You've, you've written...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Indeterminate'.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean by that? Why was the time of death indeterminate?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">When the specimen was brought in, it was still fresh. So the time of death could easily have coincided with when the gunshot was heard. But...there was one small discrepancy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What discrepancy?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">There was some fried fish in the pocket of the specimen's overcoat. And that fish...had started to rot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">If the victim liked fried fish, he presumably liked to eat it before it went off.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...yes. What are you really trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It's possible that someone tried to manipulate the apparent time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Manipulate the...? Is that even possible to do?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Theoretically, if you were to chill the body in ice, you could delay the onset of putrefaction. And if the overcoat wasn't on the body at the time...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Then only the fish would have started to rot!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">With today's science, it's not yet possible to determine if the body was chilled or not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But today's science is advanced enough to let you freeze a corpse, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But surely... ...to chill a corpse like that would require an enormous electrical refrigerator. And I don't imagine many households in London are equipped with such a device.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">No, definitely not. But maybe in a factory? Or some other special places?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't recall seeing any factories or suchlike on Fresno Street, though. I wonder...if the inspector's body had been chilled somehow... ...what might the actual time of death have been?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I couldn't say for sure. But at the most, it might have been a day earlier.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In other words, it would corroborate your previous deduction, Mr Naruhodo. That Inspector Gregson was killed a day before his body was discovered, at a different location.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Did you inform Lord Stronghart of this possibility?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">He simply said that there were no electrical refrigerators of that size in the vicinity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Dr Gorey...we actually came here to ask you about this.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... He was very good.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Good? Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">His skin didn't snag my blade once. And very little mess. His joints dislocated easily and his muscle tissue was a pleasure to work with.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-We can skip those details! But...there is one thing about the report that's caught my attention. You don't seem to have recorded a time of death.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...! ......... That's not my fault!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>That made me jump.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then please! Tell us what happened!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... I don't know why...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Don't know why what?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Why I couldn't write a time of death on that report. It's just...the Lord Chief Justice was so insistent. I couldn't bring myself to defy him. I'm...just like Mama. .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It looks like she's as troubled by all of this as we are, in her own way.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About this photograph, Dr Gorey...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Who's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? It's, it's Inspector Gregson, of course! The victim of the case!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Ah, I see. I don't remember the faces. Internal organs, muscle tissue, bullet trauma... Those are things I remember.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...please try to also remember that I don't want to know anything about all of that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...could I ask your opinion about this?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... Don't forget... ...you're responsible for putting my mama in jail. Why should I help you?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">If you don't mind, then...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's gone back to sharpening her blades.</thought> Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Not now. Or my baby here might start to rust.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps we'd better leave Dr Gorey alone.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Maybe we could try again later if we manage to find some more clues...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's have a closer look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Then again, let's not. At least, not while she's armed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, one other thing... It's something the governor of Barclay Prison told us. He said that your mother, Dr Sithe... ...was responsible for confirming the death of the Professor after his execution.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">The Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Apparently you always enjoyed listening to your mother's stories about her work, so... ...we were wondering if you might know something about what happened ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... That's not all Mama did.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">My mama... ...carried out the autopsy of Klint van Zieks as well!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Really?! <thought>The brother of Lord van Zieks. The Professor's final victim...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">The idea of carrying out an autopsy on a member of the aristocracy was completely unthinkable back then. But the detective in charge of the investigation insisted and it was miraculously authorized.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That detective being Inspector Gregson, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Quite an accomplishment for one man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">That autopsy provided the vital clue needed to arrest the killer. And Mama was there for that historic event.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What does all this mean...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">You know, that amazing autopsy happened right here in this very room. The Professor and Klint van Zieks... ...they both spent their final moments before their burial on that dissection table there. So this lab - Mama's lab - was instrumental in some of the country's most important events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She really is proud of her mother.</thought> I wonder if you'd tell us more about exactly what happened back then, Dr Gorey?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">The Professor's execution was Mama's first big case. She had to be in attendance at Barclay Prison's execution chamber... ...and sign the certificate to confirm the convict's death. Mama is the best coroner in the world, you know. I was...so proud of her.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But the execution didn't actually take place.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">No. And worse still, Mama actually helped with the jailbreak. ...I didn't want to know.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...  You found out recently, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I believed in her. In Mama. But... ...now I wonder if I'm starting down the same path as her.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean, because you omitted the time of death on this autopsy report? But that's because Lord Stronghart forbade you from including it.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">...Just like Mama. I'm sure she was coerced by somebody, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's my feeling as well.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">There's no doubt that there were powerful forces at play ten years ago. The execution couldn't have been staged without a lot of people at the prison knowing about it. Obviously the prison governor must have been in on it as well.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">The big man with the little handcuffs? According to what he told us... ...he was tricked by the chief warder. He says he knew nothing about it.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Of course he said that. I'd say the same thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Just who was behind that jailbreak all those years ago?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mentioned the autopsy of Klint van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It was at a time when carrying out autopsies of murder victims was very unusual.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's still not a practice that's observed in our country, even now.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It turned out that he was the Professor's final victim. And when the autopsy was performed... ...Mama was present...although only as the secondary assistant. The person leading the procedure was called Dr John H. Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. My daddy!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">And there was one other person present: the primary assistant. He was a visiting student from the Far East.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait...a visiting student?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It must have been my father...Yujin Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I had no idea Professor Mikotoba had been involved in something so important!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">But the outcome of that historic autopsy... ...was the discovery of a vital piece of evidence that led to the capture of the Professor!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So that's how they came to identify Genshin Asogi as the infamous mass murderer...</thought> Do you happen to know anything about that piece of evidence? Can you tell us any more?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... Would you like to see the records for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... Would, would that be alright?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">What's the point of keeping records if people can't look at them? They're filed under 'V' at the back of those cupboards. With the other records from the last decade.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you! <thought>Let's see... Van Zieks... Van Zieks...</thought> Um...that's strange.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">They...aren't here. There's nothing under 'van Zieks.'</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">There must be!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps somebody took them away?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">No. No one's allowed to take documents related to the Professor case out of this room. ...But you're right. They're gone!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, when was the last time somebody looked at them? Do you remember?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">It was... Oh yes, I remember now! It was two years ago. A 'consulting detective' came one day saying that he'd like to see the records.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No... You, you don't mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Herlock Sholmes was his name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Deep down, I knew that was coming.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Do you think...he stole the records?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, surely not! Iris, that can't be right...can it?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I-Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I've just remembered something very important I have to do. I'm going to have to leave you now!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! This is very sudden, Iris... Well, we'll come with you, then.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh no! No no, there's no need! You and Runo can take your time here. Bye for now, then! Good luck!</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Wait a minute, little girl.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hm? ...Me?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">I remember now. You've been here before, haven't you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have you, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">Yes, two years ago. When that detective came... ...you were with him, weren't you? You were a living specimen then, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's the way it usually works, yes...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Was I...? I, I really don't remember. Anyway, sorry, but I must dash!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'll brew up a pot for you when you get home!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's the matter with her? She's behaving really strangely all of a sudden.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gorey">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, in that case, we won't keep you any longer, either.</line>
<line speaker="Gorey">......... It's been quite a while since I had any visitors. This was really fun! But next time you come, I'd prefer it if you were ready for dissection.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I can't make any promises, sorry. <thought>It's a bit strange that the records of Klint van Zieks's autopsy have disappeared... ...but I think we've asked all we came to ask now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The police are still busily investigating in here then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Gina's nowhere to be seen. Where is she?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it has been blissfully quiet, hasn't it? <thought>Perhaps she's out investigating on her own, practising what her boss taught her...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I expect she'll be back before too long. Shall we wait?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Actually... ...there's something different about this room since the last time we were here, isn't there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We could always use the time to investigate more thoroughly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The photograph of Mrs Vigil...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Realising the identity of this lady was a very great clue to exposing Mr Gossip's true identity. He obviously loves his wife very dearly. ...Which is why he felt he couldn't tell her the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The transformation was incredible, wasn't it? Just from that big twisted lip.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, he went to extraordinary efforts to play the part of Hugh Boone convincingly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Although...it didn't really seem like it was much of an effort to me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hm... Now you say it, I have to agree.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's almost as if that was Mr Vigil's true character.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...People really are very hard to fathom at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There are details of cases stretching back over ten years on this noticeboard. Yes, a history of Lord van Zieks's defeats in court.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think that's an appropriate description. Although...when you consider everything on the board, it's certainly true... ...that all these people had a background of dubious dealings.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And in the end of course... ...the board itself concealed the inspector's own death.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my... It really doesn't bear thinking about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This revolver... Just who does it belong to?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, we know it's of the type issued to members of the police force and judiciary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Gregson's own gun was found on his person.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And of course Lord van Zieks has admitted to losing the firearm with which he was issued. Such absent-mindedness... Not dissimilar to you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm starting to think the cold, hard prosecutor and I could become friends after all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then I wish you every success!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It catches your eye as soon as you enter the room, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's such a bright colour, it certainly makes an impression, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...They can't possibly commit any crimes, can they? I mean, red-heads stand out like a sore thumb.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid with our jet-black Japanese hair, we stand out almost as much, here in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah... I suppose that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... You mustn't think of committing any crimes, Mr Naruhodo. </line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wasn't!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If it turns out that Gregson didn't actually die in here at all... ...where on earth could he have been killed?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well one way or another, we must find out. For the inspector's sake.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know, you look awfully pale again today, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...sorry. When I start thinking it all through, I conjure up some horrible images in my mind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your imagination is the culprit here, then. Most certainly guilty!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd never have imagined that this little figurine would turn out to be a watch winding key.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose it's a policeman because the pocket watch was a gift from Scotland Yard. It seems there was much more to Inspector Gregson than we ever realised. He was clearly a brilliant man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's the fish and chips that threw us off. I feel as though it ruined his image.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I really don't think we should blame one of Britain's staple cuisines...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But think about it. Imagine if it was Mr Sholmes. How would you feel if instead of that old briar pipe that's always in his hand, Mr Sholmes had a bag of chips?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Rather disappointed, if I'm honest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Using a candle as a timer device... Very ingenious, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, the culprit arranged it so that the firecracker would be set off at five o'clock, and then left.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that a loud bang was heard at precisely the moment Lord van Zieks arrived, yes. If only he hadn't picked up that gun from the floor...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Something you probably told yourself once upon a time, I imagine?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I've learnt that lesson by bitter experience. I would have turned and run a mile for sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Which may not have done you any favours, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...This little trunk wasn't here before, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! ...It appears to be made of metal. It must be very heavy. I wonder to whom it belongs... There are some initials on the outside, look. 'T. G.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's ask one of the policemen if they know how it came to be here.</line>
<line speaker="???">Ooooooi! Wot d'ya think yer doin'?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's my trunk, that is! 'Ands off!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-Where were you hiding?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I dunno, ya leave somefin' unattended for a few seconds, an' every Tom, Dick an' 'Arry's got 'is greedy eyes on it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm...just a wild guess, Gina, but...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot? Spit it out, 'Oddo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is it fair to say that you've only owned that trunk since this morning's trial?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot?! W-Wot are you tryin' to say?! Come on, this trunk goes wiv me everywhere! Always 'as! Where've ya been the last year?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Trying not to incur your wrath, mainly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">You should 'ear them talkin' at the Yard now... They should be ashamed o' themselves. They're sayin'...that it was the boss who killed all them bludgers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...you mean the whole Reaper thing?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah... Apparently the boss was investigatin' stuff that no one else at the Yard knew nuffin' about. Stuff to do wiv all them criminals wot got off scot-free.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the ones prosecuted by Lord van Zieks who used bribery and corruption to evade conviction.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well then obviously it was that bloomin' Reaper givin' the orders, weren't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...why would people be suspecting Inspector Gregson of being involved in the killings?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">There was a notebook 'idden in 'is office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no... <thought>This doesn't sound good...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">It...'ad details about all the crimes that 'ave been pegged as the Reaper's work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No... Did you see it, Gina?! Did you see that notebook?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">They wouldn't flamin' let me! Cos I'm 'just an apprentice' apparently! But it was me who found it! And 'e was my boss!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I was pretty miffed about it, so... ...I sneaked a peek at wot it said anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's our Gina!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you managed to see what was written in Gregson's secret notebook anyway, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Way I see it, it's my right to read wot 'e wrote.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And what had he written, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Dates, times, places, names... An 'ole long list of 'em. All details about the bludgers supposed to 'ave been done in by the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...there could be an explanation for that! Perhaps it was a record of the inspector's investigations into the Reaper's activities.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Exactly! That's wot I said! That's the first thing you'd think, right? As it 'appens, it was full o' names I recognised anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, the Reaper's targets were almost exclusively known leaders of London's criminal underworld.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well yeah, but...there was one name right at the end that was a bit odd.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the end of the list, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I'm pretty sure the date against it was 31st October.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! The day before the inspector was found dead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So? What was the odd name?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It weren't like a name I've ever seen before. It was somefin' like, erm... Nah, it's no good. I can't remember it. I don't think it was an English name, put it that way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... What a pity.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">There was somefin' else, too. I dunno if it matters, but the same name kept comin' up over and over. 'Shinn' it was. Don't s'pose it means anyfin' but...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Did you say 'Shinn'?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Eh?! Wot, it does mean somefin'?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Lord van Zieks knew the name, too. He mentioned her as well. The woman who actually did the deeds... And now we find out her name appeared in Gregson's secret notebook...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We haven't seen you for a little while, have we, Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well o' course not! I've been busy, ain't I? Investigatin' an' that. The lads at the Yard are tryin' to trace the boss's movements the day before it 'appened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The day before... That would be the undercover investigation into the Red-Headed League, then.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Only the boss didn't go, did 'e? Ya found some cove wot was pretendin' to be 'im, didn't ya, 'Oddo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, it was Mr Vigil who actually went to the park on Lime Street that day, posing as Gregson.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well anyway, you ain't the only one turnin' stuff up. I've got me own ways of gettin' results! When me an' me partner 'ere get together, there's nuffin' we can't track down!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, little Toby! He's such a faithful friend!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...have you tracked anything down, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot d'ya think, eh? 'Course we 'ave! Can't tell you, though. Police business, innit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Anyway, the point is, if you lot ever need any 'elp... ...you know who to turn to, right? Me an' the 'ellhound 'ere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right... <thought>Because he looks oh-so hellish, honest.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We haven't seen you for a little while, have we, Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well o' course not! I've been busy, ain't I? Investigatin' an' that. The lads at the Yard are tryin' to trace the boss's movements the day before it 'appened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The day before... That would be the undercover investigation into the Red-Headed League, then.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Only the boss didn't go, did 'e? Ya found some cove wot was pretendin' to be 'im, didn't ya, 'Oddo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, it was Mr Vigil who actually went to the park on Lime Street that day, posing as Gregson.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well anyway, you ain't the only one turnin' stuff up. I've got me own ways of gettin' results! When me an' me partner 'ere get together, there's nuffin' we can't track down!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, little Toby! He's such a faithful friend!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...have you tracked anything down, then?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot d'ya think, eh? 'Course we 'ave! Can't tell you, though. Police business, innit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina, about your 'hellhound' there...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Chief Inspector Toby, you mean? 'E's the pride o' the force, 'e is!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In Japanese, 'police dog' means something quite different, and not altogether nice to those involved in crime. But here in Britain, it's a wonderful compliment, it seems! For a canine, at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It should be. After all, in the Great Exhibition case the other day... ...it was Toby here who managed to locate Drebber's workshop.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Maybe it's time for another demonstration of wot this superdog can do, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do we have something the chief inspector could catch the scent of, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He...might be a little too keen, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! Arooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">AAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The chief inspector made short work of Gina there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look what he's gone to!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! That trunk clearly still has a very strong scent... ...of Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words... ...it must have belonged to him!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Oh alright! It's a fair cop, I s'pose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you nearly got away with it, too...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You always talk so proudly of Chief Inspector Toby's nose and what it can achieve... Did it not cross your mind that he might identify something that was right next to us?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah...that was a bit of a bloomer, weren't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's enough now then, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think it's time you told us the truth about that trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The chief inspector said 'woof' to that, 'Oddo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps...that particular item didn't excite him very much.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Ain't you got nuffin' else?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll have a think...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina, about your 'hellhound' there...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh! Ya wanna see another demonstration of 'is amazin' nose, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, we're trying to trace Inspector Gregson's movements, so...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Come on, 'Oddo, wot ya got for 'im?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Do we have something the chief inspector could catch the scent of, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff*</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He...might be a little too keen, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! Arooooooooo!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">AAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The chief inspector made short work of Gina there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Toby">Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look what he's gone to!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! That trunk clearly still has a very strong scent... ...of Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words... ...it must have belonged to him!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Oh alright! It's a fair cop, I s'pose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you nearly got away with it, too...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You always talk so proudly of Chief Inspector Toby's nose and what it can achieve... Did it not cross your mind that he might identify something that was right next to us?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah...that was a bit of a bloomer, weren't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's enough now then, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think it's time you told us the truth about that trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Toby">...! *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* *Sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff* Woof!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The chief inspector said 'woof' to that, 'Oddo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps...that particular item didn't excite him very much.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Ain't you got nuffin' else?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'll have a think...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It, it weren't like that! It, it just weren't!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you talking about?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I know wot's goin' through that 'ead of yours! But that ain't wot 'appened!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright then...what DID happen?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well...like I said before, we were tryin' to trace the boss's movements. So I let Toby 'ere 'ave a whiff o' the boss's overcoat. And as soon as I done that, 'e went off like a shot... ...straight to that Sandwich.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To a sandwich? Not to a bag of chips?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! I believe Gina means the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh, I forgot about THAT Sandwich...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, 'e 'ad it 'idden between them wooden boards of 'is! The boss's trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean, when they heard the sound like a gunshot and all piled in here...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Exactly! 'E nabbed it from the scene!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Me and the chief inspector gave that Sandwich a good grillin', an' ya know wot 'e said?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I thought it might fetch a g-good price, and the chap wouldn't be n-needing it any more, so... B-But that's all I did! Nothing more, n-n-nothing less!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Would you Adam an' Eve the cheek of it, eh?! Stealin' the dead boss's stuff to flog!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Miss Venus wasn't the only one to meddle with the scene of the crime, then...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How could they?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So anyway, that's 'ow it 'appened. An' it's a pretty decent trunk, so I figured I might as well make use of it. Is there summat wrong wiv that, eh? Well?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe you and Mr Sandwich should try to find the answer to that question together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You know that this armband is to show that you're a defence lawyer in Japan. Have I told you that?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, defence lawyers... Whose side are you lot on anyway, eh? Tryin' to 'elp criminals get off the 'ook.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks isn't the Reaper. I firmly believe that, which is why I offered to advocate for him.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, but wot if yer wrong? Wot if 'e really is the Reaper?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">If it turns out 'e did do it, 'ow are you gonna feel then, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I have to believe in my client. It's all I can do.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot are you on about? I am the police!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina...if you wouldn't mind... ...could we maybe examine it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, alright then. Do wot ya want wiv it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank you! We shall make a detailed record of our examination of the evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have you seen this huge gash across the side of the trunk here? It's gone right through the leather and into the metal behind.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh, for a metal chest like this to have been so badly damaged... Whatever made the gash must have struck the side of the trunk with considerable force.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder how it happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at this dark stain here. Do you think...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I'm afraid so. I think it's blood.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, I knew you were going to say that. So that presumably means...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That this was present at the scene when Inspector Gregson was killed. It's the most logical conclusion, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To think Gina's been carrying this around with her... <thought>If you didn't know any better, I suppose it does look like a grease stain from all the fish and chips...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's have a look inside...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look, there's something inside!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ooh, let's see... It appears to be a passport...authorising him to travel overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was Inspector Gregson about to go on a trip abroad, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps the date of departure might tell us something. That was... Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was for travel on 31st October! Just one day before the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gregson went to France the day before his body was discovered...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look, there's something inside!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ooh, let's see... It appears to be a passport...authorising him to travel overseas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was Inspector Gregson about to go on a trip abroad, then?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps the date of departure might tell us something. That was... Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was for travel on 31st October! Just one day before the incident!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? Really?! <thought>Gregson went to France the day before his body was discovered...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you see that? There's something stuck in the side of the trunk there. It's glinting.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks like a fragment of metal of some sort. But it's wedged in so tightly, I can't remove it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well don't cut yourself. You'd better leave it, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter with Toby? Why's he acting so aggressively towards me all of a sudden?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo, be careful! It must be the trunk!</line>
<line speaker="Toby">Ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff ruff!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Toby! Oi! Wot are you doin'?! Yer gonna lick 'is face off!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! Mr Naruhodooo! Gina, quickly! Hail a carriage!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo! Are you alright?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Miss Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, conscious again at last. A blessed relief, my dear fellow! After all, to drop dead after a moderate licking by a small terrier... Most unseemly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is or isn't seemly is irrelevant here, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so glad there's no lasting damage. How are you feeling?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm fine, thank you. Did...you bring me back here? <thought>Ah! What's this on my head? A, a bandage?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Sadly we had no ice. So that's a compress of sugar water.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sugar water?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't worry, Mr Naruhodo. It's a first-aid treatment that my father taught me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So, let us take tea when you're feeling up to it. But of course...no sugar in the patient's cup.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...the bump on my head is throbbing sweetly enough, don't worry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hee hee. Whenever you feel ready, then...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...thank you for your concern, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, think nothing of it. I must say I was quite startled... ...when I heard that you'd been attacked by a dog. For a moment, I feared that infamous murderer of so many had come back from the dead!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...You mean, the Professor?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Fortunately, I see your prized throat is unscathed. That stiff, turned-up collar of yours obviously afforded some welcome protection.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Was I that close to death?</thought> All I really remember is the dog licking my face over and over and over again...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, if you wish to avoid such troubles in future, a little mustard spread on the cheeks should do the trick. I should think that would balance the sweetness of your bandage rather splendidly.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina, I'm...really sorry.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's daft, innit? If ya asked me a year ago, the cops could go 'ang for all I cared. But we've gotta 'ave police, ain't we? To catch the bludgers. So us divers can go about our business in peace.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait...sorry? I, I don't think I can have heard that properly...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E said 'e was gonna teach me everyfin' I needed to know to be a detective. But all 'e got round to showin' me is where the best flamin' fish 'n' chip shops are!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Actually, that reminds me... Gregson said he was supposed to be going to Paris in the near future, didn't he?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...no. I'm sure I'm reading too much into things. It's just that the timing seems very coincidental.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You know, the boss was actin' a bit strange recently. Like 'e was always in a rush...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... ...What on earth is going on in here? Am I having a bad dream?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, no. It's an old German folk song. Rather a fine rendition, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's the least of my concerns.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris? What's the matter?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um...who is that sprawling-I mean, that...relaxed gentleman over there?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris...? Um... <thought>Is she even listening?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Excuse me, sir! I do apologise for troubling you whilst you're singing so merrily, but... ...would you be kind enough to explain the situation?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Well that worked.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A crooning gentleman and a mute young girl... A rather tantalising juxtaposition. And one that appears to have incited the gods of deduction within me to find their voices, too.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah! Mr Sholmes! Do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The strains of reasoning within me are playing now as a delightful duet. One melody sings of a reunion full of nostalgia.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Whilst the other... ...is a morose theme about the great secret you're trying so desperately to conceal, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's turned as white as a sheet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So as usual, you've instantly seen to the very heart of the matter!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And by the time my own brief performance is over, I feel sure this gentleman's song will reach its finale. So then...to music-land, where all is sweetness and delicacy and harmony! Pray, do enjoy Herlock Sholmes's latest 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Firstly, we consider the gentleman's nationality. Clearly he's a German with no grasp of the English language... ...as evidenced by the Germanic song he sings and his apparent inability to understand when asked to desist. So...why is the man here at all, and in such apparently high spirits? The answer of course, Iris...is clearly known to you. Indeed, we need only follow the gaze of those bright, young eyes to unravel that particular part of this mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The reason for the man's mildly irritating warbling is revealed by the herbal tea! You obviously offered our German guest a cup of your latest herbal blend. The tea's delectable flavour has made the man's spirits soar... ...and resulted in this joyful ditty tumbling incessantly from his lips. I eagerly await sampling the flavour myself, that I may join the fellow in his state of elation.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nnnnnn...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Now to the next question: Who exactly is this gentleman availing himself so thoroughly of the settee?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it happens, a number of years ago now... ...a certain gentleman of German origin engaged my services in solving a particularly delicate case. He required the retrieval of letters once sent to an acquaintance, that might have proved...problematic. In order to conceal his noble identity, he also arrived at my office in a mask. The gentleman's name was Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond von Ormstein... ...the King of Germany.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If my memory serves...the mask worn by this gentleman is identical. Yes, there can be no question! That mask belongs to the King of Germany! It would appear that His Majesty remembers the fine service I afforded him... ...and has decided to show his face again, mask and all, in order to express his gratitude. A well-mannered monarch indeed. Wouldn't you agree, my dear fellow? So the identity of this masked visitor is in fact my former client...the King of Germany! Indeed, his son is currently in London as well, enjoying the wonders of the Great Exhibition.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which leaves us with one remaining imponderable. Yes...you, young Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But your apparently inexplicable silence...is unable to hide the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, the reason for your muteness is concealed inside that knapsack! A five pound note, I believe. I must say, as your compatriot, I'm deeply saddened. It would appear that you've allowed yourself to be bribed into silence by His Royal Highness. Earning yourself some spending money in exchange for keeping quiet about the King's secret.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nnn...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And now, the final piece of the puzzle... What is this secret you strive to hide with your silence, Iris? Ah, yes! We need only follow that brief, involuntary twitch of your eyes to find the answer. You were attempting to abscond with that coffee cup! My favourite coffee cup, in fact. Or should I say, the handle of my favourite coffee cup? It appears that His High-Spirited Highness broke it in the midst of his high jinks.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nnn...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which leads us to the sad truth... My favourite coffee cup has been broken by the King of Germany - and Iris, you tried to conceal it from me! ...I shall have a bill sent via governmental channels to the German royal family for its replacement.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thus concludes Herlock Sholmes's great deduction... of this painful puzzle...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">With your silence as well, the fellow's jovial warbling rather rings in the ears, does it not?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Um, Mr Sholmes... ...I must say something does rather trouble me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pray, Miss Susato, do tell.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">His Royal Highness... ...doesn't appear to have moved a muscle since we arrived.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you haven't said a word, either, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If Mr Sholmes has it all right, you might as well own up to it now.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Your reasoning isn't entirely without substance, I must admit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...one other thing, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yet another grievance, Mr Naruhodo? Surely not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I actually read the story of that case recently. The one you were just describing. And according to that at least, it wasn't the King of Germany, it was the King of Bohemia.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Goodness, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's quite true. Master Gotts, the prince, testified to that in court. In his words, 'I have come to see the Great Exhibition all the way from my home in Bohemia.'</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I would ask you to keep that minor error to yourselves. ...It could easily become quite a scandal.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I believe, Mr Naruhodo... ...that it's our turn now to make some corrections to a number of minor errors that may have slipped in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, even Mr Sholmes is willing to admit he might be slightly wide of the mark this time. <thought>Although it's clear that Iris is definitely hiding something. We need to find out the truth behind this mysterious scene!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But one truth is incontrovertible. My favourite coffee cup is no more... So...shall we embark again... ...on a joint presentation of Herlock Sholmes's 'Logic and Reasoning Spectacular'?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Firstly, we consider the gentleman's nationality. Clearly he's a German with no grasp of the English language... ...as evidenced by the Germanic song he sings and his apparent inability to understand when asked to desist. So...why is the man here at all, and in such apparently high spirits? The answer of course, Iris...is clearly known to you. Indeed, we need only follow the gaze of those bright, young eyes to unravel that particular part of this mystery.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The reason for the man's mildly irritating warbling is revealed by the herbal tea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what, it's some mix of herbs that gives you the urge to sing?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness... I should like to try some.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I'd like to hear your singing, but this man... Just how long does he intend to keep up with that tune, do you suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As I said, he's been stock-still the entire time. And if you look closely... ...his lips aren't moving either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So I'm not sure what's actually responsible for the spirited singing. But I suspect the answer lies at the end of Iris's gaze.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, the cup's empty, that's for sure. So I suppose this mysterious gentleman must have drunk the contents.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Iris's special blends are quite delicious, I agree. They always make my heart sing. So I can understand wanting to vocalise those feelings, certainly. In fact, Mr Naruhodo, you often erupt in boisterous laughter after drinking Iris's tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I do? Maybe I should take some lighter laughter lessons from Susato-san in the near future...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We, we know this mask!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! You're right!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...does that mean...? No, surely not! It couldn't be...could it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, it's most definitely not him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, no...of course it's not. ...Thank goodness. But then, why is this gentleman now wearing it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid once again, I really have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, this...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Is a gramophone, still rarely seen in our own country.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The sound certainly appears to be coming from the horn.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But machines singing! That, that can't be right!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Science and technology are changing the world rapidly, Mr Naruhodo. What's right is changing, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...it's too much for my brain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, at least we've found our answer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then I would say this calls for a demonstration, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pray, put on the mask and show us what peculiar things it makes YOU do! ...You have us on the edge of our seats!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry, I'm far, far too shy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The song starts to get inside your head after a time, doesn't it? But...is he really singing it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right. And if you look closely... ...the man's mouth is open, but his lips aren't moving at all. The gentleman...couldn't be a waxwork, could he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">One step at a time, Mr Naruhodo. Let's identify the source of the singing first.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I thought that was an insightful suggestion.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The reason for the man's mildly irritating warbling is revealed by the gramophone!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed! For no well-bred gentleman would break into an obscure folk song when making a social call. In other words, this gentleman isn't singing at all. In fact... ...it would appear that the fellow is unconscious!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah. The music seems to have stopped now.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I ask you, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why would I have purchased a recording of that gibberish?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How should I know...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, never mind. On with the deduction! Who exactly is this gentleman availing himself so thoroughly of the settee?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it happens, a number of years ago now... ...a certain gentleman of German origin engaged my services in solving a particularly delicate case. He required the retrieval of letters once sent to an acquaintance, that might have proved...problematic. In order to conceal his noble identity, he also arrived at my office in a mask. The gentleman's name was Wilhelm Gottsreich Sigismond von Ormstein... ...the King of Germany.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If my memory serves...the mask worn by this gentleman is identical. Yes, there can be no question! That mask belongs to the King of Germany!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Although we've already established that it was actually the King of Bohemia.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems Mr Sholmes intends to persist with his Germany theory for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Come to think of it, the young prince was wearing a mask as well, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Master Gotts? The young boy whom you had in tears?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't remind me...or anyone else.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you suppose all members of the aristocracy of mainland Europe wear masks?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sure they do. ...Well, probably, anyway. The point is, that mask doesn't belong to any king.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, that's right. As we well know. Because we can identify the true owner of this mask!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sholmes:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! I, I just thought this might be the mask's true owner, but...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not as far as I'm aware. Now remind me, who are you again?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I do my best to forget those who so spectacularly hamper my logic and reasoning. Make your exit, please! Leave the deduction limelight to those who deserve it, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I thought you'd forgotten my name...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We of all people should know that mask.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. After all, it's been here on the coffee table for some time now. Although how it came to be there, I really don't know, actually...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Let's not worry about that little detail for now. The point is, we ought to be able to clear up the matter of who owns the mask very easily!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, there can be no question! That mask belongs to Kazuma Asogi!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In other words! My memory is sublimely unreliable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Only you could try to make that sound positive. Kazuma's mask has been languishing on this metal chest for several days. Though that doesn't explain why the gentleman is wearing it now...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But it is now a simple matter to determine our guest's true identity. After all, the gentleman is unconscious. We need only excuse ourselves in advance, gently lift the mask and peer beneath it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I, I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">AAAAAAH! F...Fa... Father!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm afraid, Miss Susato, you must be mista-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No! ...I think not, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Then it would appear our logic and reasoning has once again revealed the truth. This mysterious visitor...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Is my unconscious father...Yujin Mikotoba!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Logic and reasoning? ...Or just looking and saying?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which leaves us with one remaining imponderable. Yes...you, young Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But your apparently inexplicable silence...is unable to hide the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, the reason for your muteness is concealed inside that knapsack!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's a five pound note poking out from Iris's knapsack, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, I can't be sure. Most money that we encounter is in coin form.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. I'm not even sure if we've seen any banknotes here in Britain at all, have we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But anyway! Father would never have paid money for Iris's silence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...He certainly seems like the silent type himself, though, judging by his present state. <thought>There must be some other reason for Iris's silence, I suppose.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps what Iris is trying so hard not to give away with her eyes... ...is something entirely different!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now I think about it... ...Iris always wears that little bag on her back, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. Though it's easy to forget about it because you can't see it from the front. There are two little felt dolls attached to it as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Are there? I had no idea. I don't remember ever seeing them before. ......... Is it possible there's always a five pound note poking out from her bag that I just haven't noticed before, too?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I couldn't say with absolute certainty, but I think... it's unlikely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This slipper features in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes', doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does! When I first saw it there on the mantelpiece, I very near fainted with excitement!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Doesn't Iris keep her elevenses in there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes, that part was never mentioned in the stories.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We could swap it for the Japanese equivalent of a slipper for fun. In other words, for a wooden geta sandal.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But then it wouldn't be possible to hide anything inside!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Which matters because...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This metal chest? It contains important documents, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Details of all the cases Mr Sholmes has worked on over the years... ...written up by Iris's father, if I'm remembering correctly. Iris insists that the chest is kept locked at all times. She's never once shown me inside.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, its contents are invaluable to her, I suppose. And entirely irreplaceable. But look at it now... The catch is unlocked for once.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>So it is!</thought> ......... That's hard to ignore.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Very. I've never seen that chest unlocked before, in all the time we've been staying here at Baker Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And I've secretly been eating them! A symbiosis that I'd thank you not to disturb, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...How have I ended up being the person at fault here?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If Iris is refusing to talk, it's surely because she's trying to hide something. So all this must be related to some secret she has.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well I certainly don't wish to force her into revealing something she'd rather keep to herself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that might mean your father never opens his eyes again!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Don't you think that might be a little melodramatic?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the reason for your muteness is concealed inside that metal chest!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An excellent observation. For upon closer inspection, there is something different about the chest's appearance. It's kept locked at all times, yet now...the catch is open.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Evidently, this has something to do with your refusal to speak, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nnn...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But it's a simple enough matter to incite you to speak, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Here we go...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Nnnnnnnnn! NOOOOOO! Hurley, don't!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-MR SHOLMES!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">MR SHOLMES!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">HURLEY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... He's dead...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Never!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh Hurley... I told you not to open it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...so you've found your voice now, Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words...what just happened clearly reveals the truth here. Yes, the real reason for your silence until now is...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This is somewhat different to the usual 'dance of deduction' you perform with Mr Sholmes, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, he's left me alone on the ballroom floor, so I'm going to have to dance this next part solo. And anyway, I need to get to the bottom of this, for my own peace of mind. Now then...Iris isn't usually the silent type, so...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You mean you don't actually know the answer yet? Despite that knowing point of the finger before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Miss Susato... ...sometimes a man needs to point his finger first and think later.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh. Well...if you say so. I think we'd better examine Iris more closely and try to rescue the situation, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris always dresses in these frilly clothes, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've always thought this skirt is rather delightful.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's pretty sizeable with all those frills. Sizeable enough for a sizeable secret!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...You seem to be rather fond of that idea. But you certainly can't go investigating further.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Does it look like that's what I was thinking?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">For some reason, this knapsack is really standing out as suspicious to me today!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's quite sizeable enough for a sizeable secret, that's what I say!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps it is. But we certainly can't open it up to look inside without Iris's permission.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No...you're right. Who knows what might pop out and punch us?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a key she's holding, look. I'm sure that wasn't in her hands before, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, you're quite right. It's appeared...as if by magic.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's strange... A big, old iron key... <thought>Where did it materialise from?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A typical answer of yours, my dear fellow...being wide of the mark by a sizeable margin.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Miss Susato, what are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, you've been left alone on the dance floor, as you say. So I'm trying to fill Mr Sholmes's shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...you've certainly captured the cutting sarcasm.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, of course! I nearly forgot...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You really didn't need to capture that part, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My dear fellow, you would appear to be rather caught up in that idea!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Miss Susato, what are you...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, you've been left alone on the dance floor, as you say. So I'm trying to fill Mr Sholmes's shoes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's, um...very refreshing.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, but of course! I nearly forgot...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You don't need to imitate every move, you know...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How wonderful to hear Iris's voice again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's just a shame it took Mr Sholmes being thrown across the room to make it happen.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, that gives me an idea... If we threw you across the room as well, she might talk some more!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Iris made a sudden movement just before she spoke that's playing on my mind. I think we'd better have another good look around, whilst trying not to be too rude by staring at her.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, do try to be sensitive, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, the real reason for your silence until now is...that key behind your back!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When Mr Sholmes was thrown into the air before... Just before you called out to try to stop him, you slipped something out of your mouth. That 'something' is the key now in your hands. No doubt the key to the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're so... You're so clever, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So now it becomes clear. Thanks to Mr Sholmes's graphic demonstration... ...we can well imagined what happened here.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">B-But...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Mikotoba also opened that metal chest only to be punched into the air... ...and land sprawled on the settee.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But, wait! That doesn't explain all the facts. What about the stylish scarf...and the cup of tea. And above all... ...why would he be wearing Kazuma-sama's mask?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, for those curious details...I can think of only one explanation. Clearly an unbelievable miracle took place in this room. Isn't that right, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Consider how the room was arranged before this whole painful experience took place. When Professor Mikotoba opened the chest, completely unaware of what awaited him inside... ...the mask was flung into the air just as he was, only to land neatly on his face when it fell back down. And the teacup's journey through the air ended when it caught on the unconscious professor's finger.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You, you mean to say that the stylish scarf...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...is actually just a tablecloth. This is the great detective's office, after all - a place of miraculous deductions. Would you expect anything less?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Yes. You're right. It happened exactly as you said. ...Brilliant, Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thus concludes Ryunosuke Naruhodo's great deduction... of this punchy puzzle!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So then...why don't I make a fresh pot of tea for us all?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">An admirable performance, Mr Naruhodo. But in the final act of the show there, you rather missed everything of importance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If you would cast your mind back to my earlier deduction... Iris...clearly you're hiding a great secret.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...She is...? <thought>From the look on her face... ...Mr Sholmes must be right. Whatever that great secret is...the cat isn't out of the bag yet.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So I put it to you again... You were attempting to abscond with that coffee cup!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It really is a shame about Mr Sholmes's cup.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It must have been smashed when Professor Mikotoba opened the chest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...so many things seem to have been broken here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But now that the deduction has taken a different direction... ...Iris doesn't seem to be trying to hide the broken cup any more.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In other words, her great secret is something else.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Let's put our observational skills to work here one final time then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes's favourite cup...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or what's left of it. Just the handle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was obviously hurled into the air along with Professor Mikotoba. If only it had been this cup that had caught on his finger before it hit the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes... But anyway, whatever Iris is trying to hide... ...it's clearly not this handle.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Look! There, there seem to be more papers there... <thought>Is Iris trying to hide them underneath the tray?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The, the insignia, Mr Naruhodo! It's an official Scotland Yard document!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? But...why would Iris have...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must ask her!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>An official Scotland Yard document...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely this time - at last - the knapsack is going to be the answer!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm really not sure why you're so intent on showing Iris's bag to be complicit in these events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because! It's a sizeable bag, big enough for a sizeable-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Big enough to carry things around, Mr Naruhodo! That's what bags are for.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...So...the knapsack might never see the limelight, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I really wouldn't like to say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, with that answer you haven't righted my reasoning in any way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, that's true.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As a logician, you will never surpass me. The science of deduction and analysis requires long and patient study. I'm several steps ahead of you. And your attempts to correct me serve only to highlight your deficiencies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...this is what you get for agreeing with someone? <thought>(I need to reconsider my answer, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps you'll allow me to offer an opinion here. As far as I can tell...much like that bag, your deduction doesn't hold water, my dear fellow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wasn't suggesting she was trying to make off with a bag full of water.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. That would be madness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We were very nearly taken in completely by Iris then, weren't we?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's rather charming that you could be deceived by a ten-year-old girl, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't think it was only me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, you're right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think what Iris is hiding... ...must be extremely important somehow. Don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We're so close now! This great deduction is within our grasp, I'm sure!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were attempting to abscond with that case file!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Iris...as you know very well... ...nothing escapes the attention of a great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We visited Scotland Yard's autopsy laboratory earlier today. And Dr Gorey informed us... ...that the autopsy report of Klint van Zieks had gone missing.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Klint van Zieks... Hm, yes, I do seem to recall... ...that some years ago I asked to see the report in question. You were with me, weren't you, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I... I...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...it...was you, Iris...? So those papers you have there are...?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sorry... FORGIVE MEEEEEEEEE!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In truth... ...I would like to have thought I could have predicted the booby-trapped chest. But it caught me completely off guard. I was very nearly the 'late' consulting detective Herlock Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ugh... I'm sorry, Hurley.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you mean, this autopsy report really is...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes, I took it from the lab. Even though I knew it was very important.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Was there something in it that troubled you, Iris?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... Not exactly something that troubled me. Something I'd been looking for. When I saw this report... When I saw the writing in it... ...I knew it was Daddy's.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the writing...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Your father's writing? What do you really mean?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Iris? <thought>It must be something that's hard for her to talk about.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Forgive me for interrupting, my dear fellows...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes! What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I feel as though the poor unconscious gentleman on the settee has been somewhat forgotten.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">AAAH! F-Father!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Perhaps we should find our guest somewhere more peaceful to rest? Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Would you be so kind as to lend him your bed? We must do our very best to make him comfortable, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes, of course. I'll help you carry him up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So will I!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No no, I can manage alone, thank you. You have tea to enjoy. We wouldn't want Iris's brew to stew.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Because there's no better way to make the professor comfortable than dragging him upstairs like a trunk.</thought> I wonder... <thought>Perhaps that was deliberate. Maybe Mr Sholmes is making himself scarce to give Iris the chance to talk more freely...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must use this opportunity to talk with Iris... ...and find out what's going on!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Would you like to tell us about it, Iris? About your father.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I'm sure I told you before, didn't I? That Daddy used to be Hurley's partner.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. And that notes about all the cases they solved together are kept inside that metal chest.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">That's right. Hurley told me, you see. He said that Daddy's somewhere far away now, so we can't meet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's one way of describing it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Then, when I secretly unlocked the chest and read through the papers inside... ...I started to build up a picture in my head of what Daddy must be like.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, that's only natural.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're just like any other girl of your age.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I read that Daddy was a professor of medical science, so I studied and took my degree, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-Well, that's only natural...I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that respect, you're not quite like any other girl of your age, though.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But...there was one thing that I could never find out. Daddy's name.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">His name wasn't anywhere on any of the notes that he'd made about his work with Hurley. But then one day...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's what happened, is it? When you saw this autopsy report, you finally managed to work it out. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it was the handwriting in the report that caught her eye.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">When I saw the writing on that report, I could hardly believe it. 'I know that handwriting,' I thought to myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because it was the same as the writing you'd seen on your father's case notes?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Exactly. I was desperate to compare the two properly. I needed to see them side by side. I asked the doctor in the laboratory, but I was told I couldn't take the report away. And even worse, I was told that was the first and last time we'd be allowed even to look at it there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you decided...to steal it.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... When I compared the autopsy report with the case notes I had here... ...there was no doubt. The handwriting was exactly the same. It was Daddy's.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the signature of the coroner at the bottom of the autopsy report...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Read 'Dr John H. Wilson'.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">So that's how I finally found out. I learnt Daddy's name at last.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ever since then, I've called myself Iris Wilson. And that's also when I had the brilliant idea... ...of writing stories all about Daddy's exciting times with Hurley. I decided there and then that I'd write 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Iris... I had no idea the stories had quite such a deep personal significance for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can see why the autopsy report was so important to her now. And why she was prepared to break the law to get her hands on it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris, about this piece of evidence...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's not in the mood to talk at the moment, then. ...I suppose that's understandable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This is really all my fault.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Hurley...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I made a promise, you see. That until the time was right... ...I'd keep the details about your father a secret.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I know... I've been very naughty. I'll take the autopsy report back to Dr Gorey and apologise, I promise!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes...we'll go together, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then...let me look after it for you until we get there.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">......... I must go and water my herbs, I think! I'll see you all later.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor Iris... She must be feeling awful. I know Mr Sholmes is here for her, but still...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aaaaaah! Wha...? H-How...? What's the meaning of this, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Mr Sholmes...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh dear me. So...you've noticed, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But... That, that would mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What on earth's the matter, Miss Susato? You've turned as white as a sheet.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's this autopsy report, Mr Naruhodo. The one from ten years ago. The writing... ...isn't Dr Wilson's at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? Wh-What do you mean? How could you possibly know that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Because! I know this writing very well! This writing... It's my father's!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAT?! Professor Mikotoba's?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. It's true. And...now you know, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">N-No! I don't know anything! What on earth does all of this mean, Mr Sholmes? <thought>Because the idea that's slowly forming in my mind... ...it's just too extraordinary to believe!</thought> Please! You have to explain!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...this autopsy report was actually penned by Professor Mikotoba then? But that makes no sense! It's not possible, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not possible? My dear fellow! Pray, take a deep breath and think again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. In some ways... ...it actually makes a great deal of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it does?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ten years ago...is when Father returned to Japan after his extended study tour in Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And prior to his return, where was Dr Mikotoba engaged?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, of course! He was an assistant in Dr Wilson's laboratory, learning about forensic science.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And as an assistant, he would have aided with the dissection work, making detailed notes... ...which would be assembled into the full autopsy report. Once the work was complete, the head coroner would check the contents and put his signature on the document.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In other words, the only writing of Dr Wilson's in the report would be his signature at the end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see... So Iris got the wrong end of the stick, you mean? She saw that, and assumed the whole report had been written by Dr John H. Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which is very understandable, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What a complicated situation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...this autopsy report was actually penned by Professor Mikotoba then? But that makes no sense! It's not possible, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not possible? My dear fellow! Pray, take a deep breath and think again.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you're right. In some ways... ...it actually makes a great deal of sense.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it does?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ten years ago...is when Father returned to Japan after his extended study tour in Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And prior to his return, where was Dr Mikotoba engaged?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, of course! He was an assistant in Dr Wilson's laboratory, learning about forensic science.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And as an assistant, he would have aided with the dissection work, making detailed notes... ...which would be assembled into the full autopsy report. Once the work was complete, the head coroner would check the contents and put his signature on the document.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In other words, the only writing of Dr Wilson's in the report would be his signature at the end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see... So Iris got the wrong end of the stick, you mean? She saw that, and assumed the whole report had been written by Dr John H. Wilson.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which is very understandable, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What a complicated situation...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thinking about it... ...most of what we know about you, Mr Sholmes, comes from the published stories of your exploits.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' written by Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And we really have no way of knowing... ...what's fact and what's fiction.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Most troubling for you, my dear fellow, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what about this supposed partner of yours? Did he really exist or not?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, you've come straight to the point, I see.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...And please come straight to the answer!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I believe Iris explained it in one of her instalments. He was a trusted comrade, and the only person I could truly have called a friend.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And did this partner of yours truly make a record of all your cases? Are his notes really stored inside that metal chest?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Absolutely, my dear madam. Absolutely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...where's your partner now?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... We rarely meet. You see...he lives on the other side of the world.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if this autopsy report and the records of all your old cases were penned by the same hand... ...and if the autopsy report was written - though not signed - by your famous partner... ...there would be only one logical conclusion.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pray, impress me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your partner would have to be Yujin Mikotoba. In other words...Miss Susato's father.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... 'Pon my word, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You are coming along wonderfully. You have hit upon the method at last! You've finally grasped the art of deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Allow me to introduce you... ...to my great friend and partner...Mikotoba.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">P-Professor Mikotoba!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Does, does this mean... ...that you're the real Dr Wilson?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No no no! My dear, I'm still my old self: Yujin Mikotoba, your father!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Of, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is obviously too much for Susato-san to take in.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I must say, though... ...how my old friend has attained world-wide celebrity as a great mystery-solver is the greatest mystery of all!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I still remember the first time we met... Ah, pray remind me...when was it again, Mikotoba?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sixteen years ago, Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah yes, quite! Sixteen years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I'd just arrived from Japan with Seishiro and Genshin. I was in search of lodgings close to the hospital. Some comfortable rooms at a reasonable price.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But rents are devilishly high in that particular area.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That's right. So I decided I needed someone to share lodgings and the expense... ...and was fortunate enough to be introduced to Sholmes who found himself in a similar situation.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I was a callow fellow back then. A mere shadow of the great detective you see before you now. I was working at the hospital's chemical laboratory at the time, indulging my curiosities for little gain.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">And the situation of our cohabitation led to us pursuing cases together, you see. Hard to believe it was a mere six years. We had a great many adventures.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But in the last year of Mikotoba's stay in Britain, that most infamous of cases presented itself. The case with which you've become rather familiar yourselves: the Professor killings.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">After the trial...Seishiro and I were summoned back home.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hardly surprising, given the circumstances.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So there you have it. And as you know, all the details recorded by my trusty chronicler remain in that metal chest.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This is just amazing! Professor Mikotoba really IS Mr Sholmes's famous partner!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Father.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">G-Goodness, my dear. What a cutting look!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">As your daughter, I'm very proud to learn that you were the great detective's great partner. But nevertheless... ...there's another mystery that I really must ask you to explain now.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">And, and that is...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know very well what it is. The unresolved matter of Iris's father!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>Of course! I'd almost forgotten about that one!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... I should have seen this coming, I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Iris told us... ...that all the notes about the great detective's adventures that are in that metal chest... ...were written by her father. Isn't that correct, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That is indeed what I told young Iris.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But if you're Mr Sholmes's partner, Father, and you wrote all those case notes... ...then Iris's father...must be you!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... 'Pon my word, Miss Susato... You are coming along wonderfully as well. You, too, have hit upon the method at last! You've finally grasped the art of deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Wha...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What you've always told me, Father... ...is that my mother died when I was born sixteen years ago. And you left me in Grandmother's care whilst you embarked on your study tour of Britain. And I've always accepted that. But... ...all this about Iris...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ooh, there it is! Susato-san's ice-cold stare!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No! Now hold on a minute! It, it was very complicated. I mean! It's, it's really not what you think!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Then perhaps you'd like to explain exactly what it IS?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...There it is! Now the eyes go from ice-cold to red-hot, just before she...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No really! You've, you've got the wrong end of the stick! Sholmes! Say something, man!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'To the Red-Headed League'... The advertisement certainly draws one's attention, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It does. Although the best I could do to fit in would be some lipstick, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You should partake yourself, Mr Naruhodo! 'To the Caught Red-Handed League'... What do you think? As a defence lawyer, it could be an excellent way to net more clients.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yeees...I can think of two problems.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh? Pray tell...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well firstly, all of these new clients would therefore be criminals. And secondly, I would have to pay each of them four pounds a week.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, one gets nothing for free in this life, Mr Naruhodo. You should know that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear fellow, without wishing to sound rude... ...I'm currently in the middle of a very important blink. Perhaps some other, more convenient time, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is there a set time for your 'important' blinks, or are they an all-day affair? Just so I know...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Sholmes? <thought>When did he get all dressed up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Whilst I don't like to interrupt this exciting exploration of the past... ...Mikotoba and I have an urgent matter that requires a short excursion.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But it's very late, Mr Sholmes. Where must you go?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, my dear madam, is that not obvious? My partner and I must pursue our natural enemies! So, get your coat, Mikotoba! The game is afoot!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">B-But, Sholmes. I really must give Susato a full explanation, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Later, my dear fellow, later. Our carriage awaits downstairs already.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... You haven't changed one iota, have you? I mean really. I visit our home after ten long years... ...and when I open that chest in a fit of nostalgia, I quite inexplicably pass out. And as if that wasn't enough, when I eventually regain consciousness, I'm plunged straight into all this!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father, please...go with Mr Sholmes now.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've no doubt that whatever happened, you were acting in everyone's best interests. I trust you. Completely.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Susato...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And sending the great detective and his great partner off on renewed adventures together... ...is more than I could have hoped for in my wildest dreams!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Very well, then. We'll speak again later.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...I believe your own work is done for the day. I wish you the best of luck for tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, Naruhodo. Good luck in battle. ...And in reaching a decision.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A decision? About whether to go back to Japan, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>