<xml>
<title>Twisted Karma and His Last Bow</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm right in thinking that these scales are a symbol of the defence in law, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They're supposed to symbolise treating everything equally...and fairly. That's why they're always in the middle, balanced. Equal measures on both sides.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Recently though, whenever I see a set of scales, I can only think of the enormous Scales of Justice.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's entirely understandable. They are such a powerful symbol in the courtroom, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the thing about the Scales of Justice is... ...they're always leaning one way or the other. They're only ever in balance right at the start.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It must be something peculiar to the British... I'm afraid I can't shed any light on it, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's very fine embroidery here that shows the name of the armband's owner. In this case...Kazuma Asogi. So I'm always carrying my best friend's hopes and dreams with me on my right arm just here. All the time. To be honest, it's something that weighs very heavily on me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh, I didn't realise it was such a burden, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think it's why my right shoulder aches so much.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Are you sure that's not to do with you reading in bed or the like?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Mikotoba is due to arrive at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! I'm so glad we got here in time! .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san hasn't been the same since what happened. Not that I'm surprised.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The truth about Kazuma-sama's father...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you suppose my father knew?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That he was actually the mass murderer, the Professor, you mean? <thought>I knew that's what she was thinking about.</thought> There's a good chance, I'd say. I mean... ...they did come here to London together sixteen years ago, didn't they?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's true...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Come to think of it, didn't you say... ...that Professor Mikotoba knew about Kazuma going missing in Hong Kong as well?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. But for some reason, he wasn't at liberty to talk to me about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That probably means he knows, then... ...about Kazuma showing up here in London with amnesia, and that he's regained his memory now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="???">Ah, there she is!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh... Father!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hello, Susato! How are you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm very well, thank you. We're delighted you've arrived safe and sound!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hello, Mr Naruhodo. Very kind of you to take the trouble to meet us here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no, not at all. It's my pleasure.</line>
<line speaker="???">We've heard all about your extraordinary exploits here in London, you know. The news has crossed the seas.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it has?</line>
<line speaker="???">I always look forward to reading the monthly reports that arrive with the steamships from Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...I, I see. Well...thank you very much! <thought>Who is this man? And why do I feel as though I've seen him before?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Hm... I take it from your expression that you can't quite place me.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">In that case...how about a little reminder, Seishiro? A firm tap should do it.</line>
<line speaker="???">Yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A, a firm tap? What?</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Here we go, then... I hereby pronounce the defendant, Ryunosuke Naruhodo... ...GUILTY!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... OOOOOOH! Y-You're...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court will now hear the trial of Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y... Your... ...Your Excellency!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hello, Judge Jigoku, how are you? It's been a long time.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Hah hah hah hah hah! Good, you've remembered now! That really did the trick! Guilty! Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Only I was declared not guilty, wasn't I? And there was no laughing at the time...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">So, London again after all this time... Hard to believe it's been ten years. To be honest, I never thought I'd be back.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Neither did I. I didn't imagine Japan would ever be invited to an international symposium like this. Though, really, I doubt anyone did, to be honest. It's all thanks to you, isn't it, Seishiro?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">What are you talking about, Yujin? Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course, Judge Jigoku... He must complete the set. He's the other man, who sixteen years ago... ...came to London with Kazuma's father and Professor Mikotoba. He's the third visiting scholar.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, all those passport checks and luggage searches at the border took rather a lot of time. I must say, I'm very envious of your ministerial status. You didn't have to go through any of that, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Ah, I knew you were jealous! Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? Ministerial status?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, didn't you know? Seishiro here is also Japan's Minister of Foreign Affairs. It was his personal insistence that allowed you to take Kazuma's place here on this study tour.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Guilty as charged! Hah hah hah hah hah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. Well, thank you very much. <thought>He's really every bit as important as he looks.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah yes now, Naruhodo... I received a telegram from Lord Stronghart yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, you did?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It appears that...some things came to light in a trial you were involved with eight days ago. About what happened ten years ago. That...tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Could you tell us any more about it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at those cases just left there on that trolley. Aren't they worried about thieves? I know I am.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Haven't you seen the porter over there? Don't worry, he's obviously keeping an eye on everything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, so it's a trap, designed to catch any chancers who might be tempted!</line>
<line speaker="Porter">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Why did the porter give me such a scathing look just now, do you suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...some might say you look a little suspicious with your jet-black clothes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not everyone clad in black is some sort of ninja with intent to steal, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Have you seen all those sparkling jewels up there? They must have gathered every gem in the world for that!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...it's called a chandelier, I believe. It's designed to provide elegant lighting in large, spacious rooms like this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... So they had to gather every gem in the world just to illuminate one room?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...It's probably electric light bulbs that are actually throwing the light.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... If I tried to hang something like that from the ceiling in the office, it would be scraping on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps chandeliers aren't for you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That desk is known as the hotel reception. Anyone wanting to spend the night has to report there to sign in for their stay.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, so do you think that's the head clerk behind the desk there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I'm sure it must be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd love to stay in a grand hotel like this for a little while, wouldn't you? Just to know what it's like.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...If the hotel fee was paid through our stipend, I'm afraid it might bankrupt our homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>True. London gives the word 'expensive' a whole new meaning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Look at that. It's a picture of the Crystal Tower.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, the Great Exhibition is one of Britain's most prestigious achievements in recent years. I wonder how tall it is? It really does represent the pinnacle of scientific achievement in so many ways...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a twenty-metre-tall chimney on the bathhouse near my lodgings at Yumei University. The attendant there is always boasting that it's the tallest object in the neighbourhood.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure. Did you know that over the Channel in Paris, there's a tower that's three hundred metres tall?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAT?! How, how many times taller than the chimney at Yumei Sokin hot-springs is that? And if it's that tall, how does it draw properly? The smoke would get stuck, surely?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I don't think it's that sort of tower, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, how was the voyage here?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, fifty days at sea is a long time by anyone's standards.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">But it wasn't as bad as when we first came sixteen years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">No, that's true. Then I truly wondered if we wouldn't be drifting in the vast ocean for the rest of our lives. This time we followed the same route as you, so we were able to relax and enjoy the experience.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Ah, so you stopped in France's beautiful capital, Paris?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">We did, yes. Though only for one night. And yesterday evening we left the Port of Dunkirk for Dover.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Just in time for the symposium, in fact. It starts tomorrow!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's wonderful that you were invited to attend such an important international event. I'm very proud of you, Father.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's thanks to Seishiro here. Sixteen years ago he managed to ingratiate himself with Britain's Attorney General. I'm sure that's why he was invited. And I suppose you could say I'm something of an appendage by default.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Speak for yourself, Yujin. You were close friends with the professor of forensic science at a major hospital.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, well...I'd rather not dredge all that up, really.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">No... There's been a lot of water under the bridge since then, but it doesn't bring him back.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma's father, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Professor... The killer who took the lives of five members of the British aristocracy... ...was actually Kazuma's father, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">That's correct. Genshin Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Genshin...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You knew, I presume, Father?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Yes. He was a close friend at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Genshin came to Britain as a police detective. He was studying investigative techniques at Scotland Yard. I've never understood what drove the man to commit such heinous acts.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It was a closed trial, so the public never knew the truth. And he was executed with little ado. To this day, very few people know what really happened, even in our homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But what about Kazuma? Did he know? Did he know the truth about his father?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">No no, of course not. He was told his father passed from sickness.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">However... ...I suspect he may have had his doubts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Why?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">As you know, I tried to guide Kazuma growing up, as if he were my own son. Then one day, he came to my office at the university and said:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've decided...I want to travel to Great Britain and study there!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do, do you think... ...he wanted to come here to investigate his father's death?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I don't know. But when I looked into his eyes, I did know that there was no way I'd be able to stop him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something else came to light in that trial the other day, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, having disappeared in Hong Kong and been missing for almost a year... ...Kazuma's since turned up here in London, working as the apprentice of Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">What?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">WHAT?! That's news to us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So... ...Lord Stronghart's telegram neglected to mention that part, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Professor... The killer who took the lives of five members of the British aristocracy... ...was actually Kazuma's father, wasn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">That's correct. Genshin Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Genshin...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You knew, I presume, Father?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Yes. He was a close friend at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Genshin came to Britain as a police detective. He was studying investigative techniques at Scotland Yard. I've never understood what drove the man to commit such heinous acts.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It was a closed trial, so the public never knew the truth. And he was executed with little ado. To this day, very few people know what really happened, even in our homeland.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But what about Kazuma? Did he know? Did he know the truth about his father?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">No no, of course not. He was told his father passed from sickness.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">However... ...I suspect he may have had his doubts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Why?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">As you know, I tried to guide Kazuma growing up, as if he were my own son. Then one day, he came to my office at the university and said:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've decided...I want to travel to Great Britain and study there!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do, do you think... ...he wanted to come here to investigate his father's death?!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I don't know. But when I looked into his eyes, I did know that there was no way I'd be able to stop him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As you know, we both thought Kazuma had died on the steamship during our voyage to Great Britain in January.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But he didn't die. He's alive. ...As you knew, didn't you, Father?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">In actual fact, no. What I did know... ...is that when your ship docked in Hong Kong, he mysteriously vanished.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">We sent a team of investigators to Hong Kong to try to ascertain what had happened, but to no avail.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But he's still alive? And here, in London, you say? ...I never dared even to dream it.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Why on earth did the young man not make contact?! The government and the police have been chasing clues fruitlessly for months now!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...it seems that he was suffering from amnesia.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">What? Amnesia?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When we first came across him again here in London... ...he didn't know who either of us were.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Hm, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He only regained his memory eight days ago.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">This is unbelievable...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes... It's quite miraculous... I wonder why Lord Stronghart didn't let us know. I must speak with him urgently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I wonder how Kazuma's been these past few days... Would it be wrong of us to go and visit him?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">That began sixteen years ago now. It's a distant memory, really. It was Yujin here, Genshin Asogi and myself. We were the original three. The first judicial scholars from Japan to travel overseas to study.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ocean voyages were not what they are today, I can tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Sixteen years ago... Things were tough for their generation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Your father was an exceptionally fine medical student at Yumei University at the time, you know, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, Grandmother told me.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">He went to do research at a great London hospital to study autopsy - practically unheard of in Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes, it was an eerie place, sandwiched between the back of a prison and a burial ground.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh, not more talk of graves...</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Very often, there's no one willing to deal with bodies following autopsy work.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So you see, autopsy labs have something of an unavoidable relationship with graveyards and prisons.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not my cup of tea at all...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Do you remember that Scottish prison governor? Caidin, his name was. He was a good man.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Yes. But then of course, in our sixth year here, everything changed with that dreadful case. When Genshin was arrested...for a series of the most gruesome murders.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I simply couldn't believe it. I'd known the man for years.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">I was a witness at the secret hearing and I tried to speak in his defence, but...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">But you went a little too far and ended up facing charges yourself, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Well...suffice to say that after that trial we were sent back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">There was nothing more we could do to save Genshin. He was a lost cause, sadly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Mikotoba, I wonder...could, could I show you something?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Why do you seem so nervous?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I suppose because I'm a student showing something to a professor. That's always quite nerve-racking.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, I'm sorry I perturb you in that way, but anyway... I'm afraid I have nothing useful to say about that, really.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">Yes, I'd like to get this trunk up to my room as soon as possible.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I...I'm so sorry! I shouldn't have held you up here for so long.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'll call for the porter, then. Just wait here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san's gone off at a run!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I'd like to stay and talk more, but I do have various preparations to make for tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, of course! It must be a big responsibility representing our entire country. I wish you the best of luck!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Naruhodo... ...I hope you'll keep an eye on Susato for me. Keep looking after her as you obviously have been.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh no! I, I mean, if anyone's looking after anyone, it's her looking after me!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well I do appreciate you being there for her. After all... ...I've been a miserable father to her. I've thoroughly let her down.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Well, it was sixteen years ago that I started my long study tour here in Britain, as you know. The very year Susato was born.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, I heard.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">The birth of my daughter was the most joyous event of my life, but... Well, sadly it was accompanied by the most tragic event of my life, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh...yes... Susato-san hinted at something like that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a rather turbulent time at home...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">...Anyway, I won't bore you with the details. The point is, I became rather less dependable than befits a grown man. And it was then that Seishiro offered me the opportunity to study here in Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Jigoku">I was too worried about you to leave you behind. So perhaps I was a little heavy-handed when it came to persuading you to accompany me to London.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">So...that's what happened in a nutshell. And that's also the reason why I now feel compelled to give my daughter as many opportunities as I dare. Though the world does not readily afford young women such things, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...completely understand, Professor.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">......... Ah, one other thing, Naruhodo... If I may be so bold, I have a favour to ask you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really? Of course! What can I do for you?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, the thing is, I-</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so sorry that took so long!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Now then...allow us to take your bags!</line>
<line speaker="Porter">Allow me to take your bags!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">One moment, if you please, porter.</line>
<line speaker="Porter">Of...of course, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">That machine around your neck... It's a camera, I believe?</line>
<line speaker="Porter">Quite right, sir! Just five shillings for a lovely photograph to commemorate a wonderful stay at the hotel, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, I think given the occasion, we could justify the expense.</line>
<line speaker="Porter">......... Ah! Yes, yes of course!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'd like to thank you for coming with me, Mr Naruhodo. It's really made Father very happy, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, well, I'm pleased, then. <thought>But we were interrupted before. Professor Mikotoba was about to ask me something.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Shall we return to Baker Street, then? I expect Iris will have some delicious tea waiting for us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, let's go. <thought>I'm getting more and more anxious about Kazuma, though. Perhaps I'll try to meet with Lord Stronghart later and ask after him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Here's the final draft of the opening address for tomorrow's proceedings. I've supplemented your original with the figures you asked for from the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I see. Excellent work. Thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...You're welcome, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's Lord van Zieks doing here...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">My, there seems to be an awful lot of tension in the air, wouldn't you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This place is stifling enough as it is. We really don't need any more tension.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">My apologies. I didn't notice you come in. Your small stature and dark dress make you all but invisible to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! No no! It's entirely my fault for wearing black, I'm sure.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">From now on, you must dress in white from head to toe whenever you come here!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Now then, Mr Naruhodo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes, My Lord! I'm right here!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Ugh... Kill me now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Is something wrong? Perhaps it's a little too hot in here for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, no, not at all! I mean, I've never experienced a room at such a perfect temperature!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">If you're sure. The beads of sweat carving their way down your face seem to suggest otherwise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because of the daggers you're staring at me with, mainly.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As you're no doubt aware, my International Forensic Science Symposium begins tomorrow. In fact, your father arrived in London earlier today, I hear, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Yes, that's right, My Lord. He's extremely honoured to have been invited.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I'll leave the remaining preparations for the meeting room in your capable hands then, Lord van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I will attend at once.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">He gave you a very cold stare as he left, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. But I haven't done anything...have I?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">These past few days, my feet have barely touched the ground, I must say. My dedicated right hand of many years was recently put out of action in spectacular fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. ...Is your left hand still of service?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! He's talking about Dr Sithe!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>Of course...</thought> I'm, I'm terribly sorry about that. I was just, um...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Fear not. You've done nothing wrong. Dr Sithe's own wrongdoing precipitated the situation. You needn't concern yourself with it any further.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That would be a lot easier to do if it weren't for the piercing stare you're giving me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Lord van Zieks is doing an admirable job of holding the fort. Though disturbingly, his apprentice has been missing since yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">O-Oh... <thought>Missing...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's become of Kazuma-sama now...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You couldn't read all of these books even if you were reincarnated six times over as a bookworm! <thought>Can Lord Stronghart really have read all of these?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thinking about it...Father's study is full of books that look as though they've never been read, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pedlars of books are forever pushing their wares on him, you see. And I think he's just too kind-hearted to refuse them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a phrase for that in Britain. People would say they 'saw him coming'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It makes me wonder if perhaps the vast number of books on the shelves in here... ...are a sign of Lord Stronghart's overwhelming kind-heartedness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure you could afford to have a kind heart if you had to keep Lord van Zieks in line, could you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">These very European suits of armour are still glaring at each other across the carpet, I see. In a way, they feel like guardians of the Lord Chief Justice's office.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose...they're rather like the lion-dogs that guard shrines in Japan, aren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Aren't they a bit too human to be called 'lion-dogs'?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Did you know that it's a dream of mine to keep two cats one day?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I feel as though we've gone off at a bit of a tangent, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As ever, the enormous clock is diligently maintaining its rhythmical tick-tock today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Watching machinery at work can be quite mesmerising, can't it? Ironically, you can completely forget the time. What I particularly enjoy is watching the enormous wheels of a steam locomotive turning. When I was a little girl, Grandmother often used to take me to watch the railway engines, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's an open fire for me. I could sit and watch the flames for hours.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! We could install one in the office! An enormous wheel, turned by an enormous steam engine!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Perhaps we could start with a simple fireplace?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just sitting behind that desk must make you feel so important, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would you like to have an office like this, Mr Naruhodo? With such a grand desk?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who, me? No...I don't think so.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, imagine if you suddenly found yourself needing the toilet. You'd have so far to go!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... How...true. Perhaps the important people who work in ostentatious offices like this haven't considered such things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...I'm going to take that as a compliment.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Not long ago, visitor numbers to the Great Exhibition exceeded thirty million.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th-Thirty million?! <thought>Are there even that many people in the world?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">As a comparison, Mr Naruhodo, the population of the imperial capital Tokyo is two million.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I will be opening the International Forensic Science Symposium in the exhibition's main auditorium. This event has been two years in the making. Two years of preparations and negotiations with other countries.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It sounds like a tremendous achievement. Congratulations.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The twentieth century will see the wholesale adoption of forensic investigation techniques. And cooperation between policing organisations around the globe will be essential. Which is why... ...this landmark first symposium had to be hosted here at the heart of our great British empire! In order that Scotland Yard can become the leading investigative organisation in the new world!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's the same as ever, I see. That passion of his is quite something...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're every bit as passionate in your own way, I'm sure, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I'm the only person in this country who truly cares about a future that embraces forensic science. It was my intention to become Her Majesty's Attorney General and reform the Yard from the ground up. So the disgrace of the Forensic Investigation Team has been a bitter blow to my ambitions.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I first established the Forensic Investigation Team a year ago. Experimentally, to start with. With Dr Sithe at the helm, it was steadily accruing an impressive record of achievement. I was on the verge of changing its name and elevating its status to a full-blown Forensic Investigation Department.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And...can you not do that now?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Obviously. Nobody wants to hear anything about it at the moment. Even I can't keep this story out of the papers. Six million Londoners will be cursing forensic science now. This incident will set back our country's advancement in the field by a good ten years, I'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Unintended repercussions of our trial...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We simply couldn't have overlooked what had happened, though.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Of course not. We should all be grateful to you both. Anyway, I'll still reform this country's policing when I become Attorney General. This might delay my plans, but it won't alter them. Nothing will stand in my way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, about Lord van Zieks's apprentice...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes, that came as a surprise to me, I must say. That you and he are old friends.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...How did he become an apprentice to Lord van Zieks in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... It came about three months ago. An unidentified Asian man was apprehended by border police. They found him hiding aboard a large goods vessel.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! So he stowed away to get here!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">He had no papers to identify him. No passport. And he was suffering from amnesia, too. Other than the fact he was clearly of Eastern descent, there were no clues as to who he was. So I decided to assign him to Lord van Zieks. That way I could keep an eye on him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But then...why the mask?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I didn't want to burden Lord van Zieks with tiresome explanations about why he had an Eastern apprentice.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because it would be so much easier to explain why he was wearing a mask...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">He's proving to be a great help to Lord van Zieks. I have high hopes for his future.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By the way, do you know where he's gone?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No idea. But I believe he's left London for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I take it you also didn't know. That the man's father was one of our country's most infamous criminals, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Genshin Asogi...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What we learnt from that trial eight days ago was a huge shock. Finding out my friend's father was...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah yes. Genshin Asogi. The Professor case ten years ago caused a great stir here in Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They were such awful murders. And unprecedented. Using a ferocious dog as a murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And no one would have believed the culprit was a foreign student invited to study here by the government.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">So the true identity of the killer couldn't be made public then, and can't be made public now. Nobody in your country knows it was him. And neither do the citizens of London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The main motivation was to avoid aggravating relations between our two nations at the time, I understand.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Correct. However... ...it has to be noted that there were some supporters of the Professor's apparent cause.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Supporters of a mass murderer?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">The majority of the man's victims were a blight on the aristocracy of the day. Somewhat ironically, their deaths actually benefitted society as a whole. ...Or so a fair few thinkers in London believed anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...I see... <thought>But it was still murder, wasn't it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... It seems very similar, doesn't it? To the idea of the Reaper of the Bailey.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, could I show you this, Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...I'm the Lord Chief Justice. I'm not here to offer advice about evidence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Especially when the evidence in question is so dull.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah, so that's the real reason.</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">Uèèèèèèèèèèèèè uèèèèèèèèèèèèèèè!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-What was that?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A, a man screaming! In a most unflattering way!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think... Could it have been Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! I do hope not...</line>
<line speaker="???">Uèèèèèèèèèèèè! I don't-a do it any more!</line>
<line speaker="???">Mon ami, mon ami... Stop zis disgraceful display, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who, who are these people? <thought>Look at their hair! It's bright red...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think...they must be clients of Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right, you two. Yer comin' wiv me now. Down to the clink.</line>
<line speaker="???">No! Not in prison! It is dark and damp and I don't-a like it!</line>
<line speaker="???">Bof! Ze darkness, it is my friend. I am not scared!</line>
<line speaker="???">Uèèè uèèèèèèèèèèèè! But you are always scared of the dark!</line>
<line speaker="???">Shut your mouth, you idiot! I will sit quietly in ze dark and plan our next daring 'eist!</line>
<line speaker="???">Uèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèèè! I don't-a like this! I don't-a like it!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well tough! We'll finish this down the Yard! Now get movin'!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">By then, Ginny! Have fun!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh yeah, thanks, Iris! And thanks...ya great detective!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Heehee! Gina makes a fine detective herself, doesn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Susie! And Runo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello, Iris. We're home!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Well? Did you find your daddy?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! We arrived at the hotel just before he and his friend.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh! Well that's great news. I hope I'll get to see my daddy again soon...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah...yes...of course...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Dr John H. Wilson...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">So, Iris! All that remains now is that greatest of problems known to man!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But before we concern ourselves with that, I believe some tea is in order, don't you, my dear fellows?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Is something wrong, Mr Naruhodo? Do I have a crumb or suchlike on my face?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uh... <thought>Not so much on your face... ...as on your head, I'd say.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Come along then, everyone. I've brewed a lovely special blend. Time for tea!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whatever is going on here today?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In that case, let us sit and drink now. For I am in fact expecting a guest later today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've finally managed to remember this behemoth's name. The Great Analytiscope.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't think it was here when I left for Japan, was it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, because it was with the pawnbroker.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! That's given me a wonderful idea! I could pawn everything that's on your desk! The office would be tidy at last!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Don't even joke about it, Miss Susato. ...You are joking...aren't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's all sorts on these shelves: chemistry apparatus, books, papers and...lots of things I've never seen before. It's all heaped up so high, I can't help feeling that the whole lot is going to topple at any moment.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and yet it doesn't. The epitome of Mr Sholmes's brilliance!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I don't get it. As it happens, I'm quite well practised when it comes to stacking shelves myself. Just the other day, the shelf in my office finally gave way under the strain, though.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It looks as though it might topple, and it does. Yes, the epitome of your disarray!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I really don't get it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is Mr Sholmes's famous violin. The one he found being sold for a song at a pawnbrokery. What's it called again? A 'Shodi-something'...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes, this wonderful instrument features in 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes'. It's a world-famous Stradivarius!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stradi...what?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Stradivarius, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Stragi... Stragivor...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you even trying now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We'll come back to this another time, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I do like this fireplace. It's one of the best things I've seen since we arrived in the country, in fact. Although...I do yearn for a Japanese kotatsu. Putting your legs under a warm, blanketed table is so comforting.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do be careful, Mr Naruhodo. Don't mistakenly put your feet into the fire, will you? You'd suffer terrible burns, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I worry sometimes about how Susato-san sees me...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">This looks like last week's edition.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's that article circled in red ink there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's in an advertisement column. It says... 'To the Red-Headed League'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Red-Headed League? What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't know. I've never heard of it before, but...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Is something on my face?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Clearly this has something to do with that...lively hair.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The mask Kazuma wore when he was assigned to Lord van Zieks as his apprentice. When he cast it aside after the trial the other day, I just sort of picked it up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We ought to give it back to him, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But he has his memory back now, doesn't he? And I can't help feeling he might turn around and tell me coldly to wear it myself...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...isn't he your best friend?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My eye is always drawn to this big metal chest that Mr Sholmes and Iris use as a coffee table.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Isn't it where Iris keeps her very important papers?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It is. So you'd think that they'd treat it with more care, really. But only the other day, I saw Mr Sholmes kick it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose something must have been frustrating him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a shame to mistreat the furniture, though. Was it damaged?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The chest was fine, but Mr Sholmes was doubled up on the floor for almost ten minutes!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... That is a painful tale.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah yes, Mr Sholmes's curious collection of trinkets from the various mysteries he's solved.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's one of my favourite parts of this room. Full of items with such exciting tales to tell! And I do believe he's added to it since I last looked. Now there's a mysterious pince-nez, a mysterious little box, a mysterious horseshoe, a mysterious biscuit...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think that last one might just be one of Iris's unfinished snacks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Iris's pretty little tea set is set out beautifully as ever, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it's only by carefully taking care of a tea set that you can make good tea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is...that a roundabout way of telling me I need to tidy my desk?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo, you do overthink things at times.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This blackboard is where Iris scribbles down her latest ideas, isn't it? Let's see... Oh, she seems to have drawn a lot of little stick figures all lined up, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">'Cheap apples at the market' is what all of them say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! The little figures can speak?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">All your questions would be answered if only you would read this month's Randst Magazine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So I'm the only one who can't make any sense of this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's Iris's wonderful collection of medicines, potions and chemicals. Just look at all the little bottles she's squeezed onto the shelves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, and there are charming little ribbons tied around the bottles, too. But the labels aren't quite so charming, are they? This one here reads 'Deadly Poison'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I've been so excited about the idea of helping Iris with her experiments, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just try to avoid any bottles labelled 'Deadly Poison' or 'Highly Explosive'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If I've remembered correctly, this large and imposing lump of iron is called a 'typewriter'.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">To think that every single one of 'The Adventures of Herlock Sholmes' blossomed from this very machine! Ah...it's such a dreamy thought...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I actually had a go on it the other day. The metal bars that move when you hit the keys got all tangled up somehow and that made Iris angry.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo... ...you're ruining my dreamy thoughts. Please don't do that again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...now I've made Susato-san angry as well...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Mr Sholmes...who were the two gentlemen that were here before?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh, just a pair of petty criminals. Nothing of significance. Of course, they have to make a living somehow. And when the mood takes me, I'm willing to turn a blind eye to all manner of infractions.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">When the mood takes you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All manner of infractions?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But when such fellows set their sights on Mr Herlock Sholmes, well...that's when their luck runs out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! You were the target of a crime, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But I quickly devised a plan to entrap them and deliver them to our young detective ally.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You should have asked Gregsy to come, too. We could have had an arresting tea party.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I did send word, but no answer was forthcoming. The man is consummately in the wrong place at the wrong time. There's a word for it, I'm sure... Aha, I have it! A 'bungler'. That's the word.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's a good job he's not here to hear you say that. <thought>So those red-heads had been up to no good...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder what the men did...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...what was that about 'the greatest of problems known to man' that you mentioned before?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Is it another fiendishly intricate case, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Hm, how should I best explain it? Are you aware of the theory of evolution by natural selection, perchance?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...well...I think I've heard talk of it somewhere... possibly.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a revolutionary scientific theory that was newly proposed forty years ago now. According to its author, Mr Darwin, we humans were once apes who lived in the treetops.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, what?! We, we were apes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. And from the very moment those apes descended from the canopy to live as humans... ...it has been our lot to be at the mercy of the greatest problem known to man.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Our lot...? What is this great problem, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why, is it not obvious, my dear madam? The problem of rent!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Haah.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...did you not receive a rather large sum of money from Madame Tusspells only the other day?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pshaw! A large sum? One potted herb for Iris and a new motor car for me later, and all of it has quite disappeared, I assure you.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Honestly, Hurley! You know you squandered it.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes, well, anyway...two days ago... ...I discovered the answer to man's greatest problem! For the coming month at least.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what was the answer?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Why...there is a substantial clue before your very eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't tell me! Let me see...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Humans are sorry creatures, unable to see what is in front of their noses. Let me give you some assistance. Don't look, but observe me very closely. There is one particular feature about my person that has changed. You should notice it in the end, I think...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In the end? It's been stabbing me in both eyes right from the very beginning of our conversation!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think we might need another clue before we uncover the full answer, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thanks for the hint. I'll be tearing my hair out if this charade goes on much longer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes, isn't it about time you told us the truth? Just over a week ago, you said to us:</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I will now tell you something of the first importance, my dear fellow: Great detectives are wont to lie. ...It will serve you well to remember that.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That case aboard the SS Burya in January... Kazuma wasn't killed. And you knew he wasn't dead at the time. So what was really going on?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... The fellow was unconscious for a very long time. If he hadn't regained consciousness when he did, his life would have been in mortal peril.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Of course, a side-effect of the prolonged comatose state was amnesia, as you now know. It was a simple enough task to silence the crew.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">After they'd carried him out of the cabin, I assembled them in the lobby area. Then I made them swear... ...to leave him unconscious and have him unlade from the ship in Hong Kong as a murdered corpse.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how horrible...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It was necessary to find some material with which to persuade the crewmen to keep their word, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why?! Why do it in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... I will be at liberty to elaborate in due course. But for the time being, I would like to reassure you: I didn't foresee subsequent events.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What events?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">His disappearance in Hong Kong.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...I believe I may have made a gross error of judgement.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what is the Red-Headed League, which seems to be the subject of the advertisement you've circled?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You noticed it in the paper, then? That, my dear fellow, was going to be the source of this month's rent payment!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was? How?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">According to the advertisement... ...the Red-Headed League is a distinguished institution of fellows of unspecified governance. In fact, the only condition for becoming a member...is having red hair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...doesn't entirely surprise me.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">But listen to what the lucky red-heads receive once they join: An unconditional salary of four pounds a week!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Four pounds a week?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why? What are they paying people for?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That I don't know. No details are given in the advertisement.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But surely every red-headed person in the country would be flocking to join in that case...</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You're right, Susie. There's no time to lose! I'll put in my application at once!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So will I! Just...on the off-chance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That might be stretching a point, I think...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">The trouble is, they have a fixed number of members, you see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see. So once a certain number of people have joined, no one else can.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But as luck would have it, one member recently passed away!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It wasn't particularly lucky for the red-head in question, I feel, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...So you decided to try to join in his place?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Correct. I mean, look at me! Have you ever seen such a red-headed fellow?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...no.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So why? WHY did it have to go so wrong?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What, what on earth happened?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A blunder, Mr Naruhodo. Though it pains me to admit it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What did you actually do to your hair, Mr Sholmes?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm glad you asked, Miss Susato. What you see atop my head is neither dyed nor a hairpiece. I changed the colour of my hair overnight...by the wonders of chemistry!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Chemistry?!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I was conducting some research into a method of rejuvenating spent tea leaves. And in the course of my work, I stumbled upon a potion that when taken, turns one's hair a flame-like red. Would you like to try it? It will make every hair on your body perfectly crimson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think I'll pass.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Mr Sholmes, is it quite safe to drink? Surely it's bad for you, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Heh heh heh... Ah, amateurs are always hampered by such fears.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! I should never have doubted you, Mr Sholmes! You mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">But of course! To earn four pounds a week, one must be prepared to turn a blind eye to a little danger.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...That degree of red signals more than just a 'little' danger, surely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">So anyway, Hurley left full of confidence yesterday with his new red hair... ...for the park on Lime Street where the Red-Headed League were interviewing prospective new members.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So what went wrong?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The whole park was choked with red-headed folk, like a coster's orange barrow. I queued for eight hours solid before at last, I reached the front. But when the panel of interviewers saw me, they immediately said: 'Ah, Mr Herlock Sholmes! Are you in disguise to conduct an investigation?'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So naturally I had no choice but to reply: 'Shh! Don't give me away!' After which, I could do little else but turn and leave. Then this morning! When I looked in the mirror, irritation stirred within me. So I turned that pair in to the police.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear, what a disaster. For Hurley and those two red-heads.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Erm, Mr Sholmes, about this...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">...Tell me, Mr Naruhodo. Is this the first time you've shown me this particular trinket?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...I don't really remember, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">If my saying that it's a collar for a breed of miniature canine with a particularly long neck... ...were to precipitate a 'here we go again' from your lips, we could be sure it was not the first time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Deduction, you see, my dear fellow. Deduction!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks as though someone's circled an advertisement in this paper, Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">'To the Red-Headed League'? Hm... Does that strike you in some way?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was thinking that just maybe...it might be related. To your bright-red hair.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">......... Heh heh heh heh heh... So, at last you've learnt to apply my methods, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In the first instance, and quite indispensable... observation!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Believe me, I could have seen that hair with my eyes shut.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So then! Allow me to regale you with the details of my latest exploits.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Regale' or 'boast'...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Sholmes, you mentioned before... ...that you were expecting a guest today?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed, Miss Susato, that is correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not another of those red-headed gentlemen that were here before?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Not at all. They were petty villains. The guest I am expecting is a client.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">A young gentlewoman who wishes to appoint the services of this great detective, no less!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how wonderful, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">You must stay and observe the fashion in which a great detective receives his customers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Must we?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I have you in my clutches now, rent! Just as I have you in my clutches, red-heads! Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha hah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That hearty laugh is masking rather sinister thoughts, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, the lady isn't due for another hour yet. Don't feel as though you must wait around if you have other things to do.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Aha! Here is my guest now. My latest client! With money to spend!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Ooh, I do hope it's an exciting case, Hurley!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Remember, Iris, we are at present gripped by the greatest problem known to man. I must be willing to accept any case, no matter how unstimulating. Save locating a runaway, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Don't spare anyone's feelings, will you?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh dear... I'm afraid that Hurley can lack a little tact, especially just before the rent is due.</line>
<line speaker="???">Mr Sholmes! Mr Herlock Sholmes! Please... Oh, please... ...please find my husband! He's run away!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">To upset me?</line>
<line speaker="???">I beg your pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Never mind. A personal matter. My apologies. What exactly are you trying to say, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I didn't say a word.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Come, my dear madam, be seated. Iris, some tea, if you please?</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's the matter, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, it's...it's just that gentlewoman... I feel sure I've seen her somewhere before. Very recently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...! Yes, now you come to mention it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Evie">As I explained earlier, my name is Evie Vigil. I implore you to take the case, sir! Money is no object. Simply name your figure!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Money and wealth are of little consequence to me, madam. Being offered a case to solve is reward enough.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh, Mr Sholmes! You are the picture of benevolence!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I will of course make a mental note of your offer, however. For...contingent reasons. I trust you will remember your words also.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Um...if I might enquire, sir... ...this gentleman and lady would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...me?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">What I am about to tell you, I should like to communicate in the strictest confidence, you understand.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, these are my friends. I assure you, you may say before this pair anything which you may say to me.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Ah...I see...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I can vouch for the gentleman personally. After all... ...he's hard of hearing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...Why did I ever get my hopes up?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Forgive me for asking, Mrs Vigil, but...have we met somewhere before? Quite recently, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pshaw! My dear fellow, what is your intention? Clearly you have no ability to differentiate the facial features of the English. If you wish to invite the lady to tea, you must do so in a more gentlemanly fashion.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Is it possible... ...that you're the nice young lawyer from the trial I attended last week?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>I knew I recognised her!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Juror No. 2">To have a man's fate in the palm of one's hand... Oh gosh! Oh golly! It sends shivers down my spine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I didn't quite recognise her because she's acting so differently now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Evie">It must be very difficult for you as a lawyer. Being hard of hearing, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh dear! I'm so sorry! Don't worry if you can't hear. It was frippery really, nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Now look what you've started, Mr Sholmes. Thank you very much.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I believe it would be prudent for you to sit quietly in the corner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Tell us about your husband, madam.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Mr Vigil - my Daley - is forty years of age. I have a photograph here...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hm...an entirely unremarkable gentleman...by appearance at least. How long have you been married?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">It will be fifteen years this year. We have a cordial relationship, and my husband's income is more than adequate so we live quite comfortably.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As it would appear. I need only look at you to know these things.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh gosh!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your dress is the latest style, your hat clearly regularly groomed and your eyes are animated. In short, you have no inkling as to why your husband might have disappeared. Correct?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">That's right. He's a kind man with a strong sense of loyalty...and he rather dotes on me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Which would point to the possibility... ...that he has become embroiled in some incident or other.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh, that is exactly what I fear must have happened, Mr Sholmes! I'm quite beside myself! My husband's employment is somewhat unusual, you see. What if he's incurred some miscreant's ill will?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What exactly is your husband's line of work?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">He's a warder at the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A guard? That is 'somewhat unusual'.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...your husband is a prison warder.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">That's right, yes. Well, in actual fact, he's the chief warder.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed? I see... Well, chief prison warder certainly qualifies as something of a specialist occupation.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Yes, it does indeed. My poor husband must prepare those dreadful punishments...and see that they're carried out.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>'Dreadful punishments'...? Does she mean capital punishments?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Evie">And at such times, he must occasionally spend a night or two in the prison dormitory. But for that extra responsibility, he is remunerated more handsomely than the other warders. Of course, we make no mention of my husband's work to the neighbours.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Yes...I believe your prudence is justified. Tell me, at what prison is your husband engaged?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Barclay Prison, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Really? Barclay? Oh, a fine establishment! If I'm not mistaken, there is a large cemetery just behind it.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Yes, that's correct. Lowgate Cemetery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>No! Lowgate Cemetery? The very place we were discussing in court! That's unbelievable!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Unbelievable, my dear fellow, and yet undeniable.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Sorry, Mr Sholmes, I'm afraid you've lost me.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, pay no heed, madam, pay no heed. A private matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This can't really be a coincidence...can it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">So...to the matter of your husband's disappearance. When did you realise he was missing?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">...Please try not to laugh. It was yesterday.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I'm sorry? Yesterday?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That really is recent. Laughably so.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Evie">The truth is my husband does at times have occasion to spend the night away for his work. It's not at all out of the ordinary for him not to return home at night. But this is different! For him not to make any contact for a whole day! That has certainly never happened before! Oh, my dear Daley! Whatever can have happened?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">My dear Mrs Vigil, please, calm yourself. Now then...have you contacted the police?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Why, naturally! But sadly... ...they refused to listen to my pleas as my husband has only been missing for one day. I was asked to wait patiently at home.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">In truth, Mrs Vigil, I concur with the police. However! Let us not be hasty! I see no reason why we should not engage my deductive powers to track your husband down anyway.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh, thank you, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And furthermore! Let me assure you! A chance to solve the greatest problem known to man for another month has no bearing on my decision. I seek only to put a sweet smile on another Londoner's face. ...That's really all there is to it.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">You have my eternal gratitude! I shall pay any sum you care to mention!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>You seek only to put this suite's rent in your landlady's purse. THAT's all there is to it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mrs Vigil, would you mind casting your eyes over this?</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh my poor Daley... Where have you gone? What's become of you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid she's too worried about her husband to pay any attention, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Either that, or she just doesn't want to be bothered with me.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">Oh, please report to me soon with good news, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Fear not, madam. In a day or two, I shall be contacting you with a heartening report, I'm quite sure.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">So soon? Oh, how splendid, Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good news should be delivered early, I always say. If you would be so kind as to leave the photograph of your husband in my possession...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Thank you. Now, allow me to show you the door.</line>
<line speaker="Evie">I can't thank you enough, Mr Sholmes. You've been simply marvellous!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">You know, I think it every time, Hurley... ...but how do you come out with such nonsense? Good news in a day or two? Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I can't be sure, of course. But then I didn't swear on it. I merely gave the good woman some hope. I hope to be able to give her good news, one might say. After all, the rent must be paid by the end of day tomorrow. If by that time I've successfully located Mr Vigil, we shall be mutually relieved. Wouldn't you agree, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Don't look at me with those pleading eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, my dear fellow? Did you hear the details of the case?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...my hearing is surprisingly good, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Excellent! And what did you make of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I was surprised to learn where her husband worked. At Barclay Prison, I mean...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Ah, so you noted that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course. Especially with the mention of Lowgate Cemetery...</line>
<line speaker="Drebber">Lowgate Cemetery as at the rear of Barclay Prison. So it was renowned among us students at the university for being haunted by the ghosts of condemned convicts.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Barclay Prison is where that notorious man was incarcerated!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Professor...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And now a warder from the prison has mysteriously disappeared, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's all very peculiar...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. But nothing you can't handle, I'm quite certain, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Run along to the prison and see what you can glean, would you? It's the prison governor you want. No doubt the man is equally worried.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...aren't you going to go yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Surely you needn't ask. I can't possibly be seen out with this hair!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...But didn't you go to Lime Street with that hair?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">That was a quite different matter. So, I leave it in your capable hands. Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm rather busy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course you are...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The spade is still here, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Please, Mr Naruhodo. It's not a spade, as I think you well know. It's a shovel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It didn't take long to reignite that old argument.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah, I have an idea! Let's give the implement a name, like Professor Harebrayne named his tools.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ooh! I never thought of doing that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">From now on, then, let's call it 'Ryunosuke'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no no! It's clearly much more of a 'Susato'! <thought>The old argument has taken a new and unexpected turn, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Whenever you serve me tea, it always takes me back to Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know you're not particularly fond of the bitter taste, are you? So I do always try to pick out less bitter matcha for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She does often serve up an unusually mellow blend, it's true. But the anticipation of the taste in my mouth makes me bitterly worried anyway...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is very difficult for you, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The steam is rising gently from the kettle as always.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It doesn't feel right somehow unless it is. But...the steam hash an unusual scent today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps the sweet potatoes that I brought back from Japan with me are ready.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gulp...*</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Mr Naruhodo! I heard that, you know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tears of joy, Miss Susato. From my mouth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You see? I've been keeping my desk beautifully covered in papers as always.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You really must tidy it all up, Mr Naruhodo. No more excuses.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But Miss Susato, the way I see it... ...all these papers building up on my desk like this are a reminder of my wonderfully diverse daily life. I like to leave them as they are so I never forget how lucky I am to have such varied experiences.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that case, you should definitely have a thorough tidy. Then you'll be able to see your papers building up all over again and feel that joy renewed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Still can't beat her in an argument. Even though I'm the lawyer here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That daruma doll is still winking at me, look. I wonder when he'll finally get his other eye filled in...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well you should know, Susato-san. I entrusted the task to you.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The truth is... ...I have already decided when that will be.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Really? When?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That's my little secret.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a lovely photograph we took together when I had to leave London. Though it was a sad day. But I happily have the same photograph on display in my room at home, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Now that we're all back together again... ...it would be nice to take a new photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes! That would be wonderful!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your room across the hall is undisturbed, of course. I don't suppose I'd be permitted to see inside now that you're back though, would I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You know very well that only Iris is allowed inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I heard you two giggling together in there again last night.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">You can visit Mr Sholmes in his room, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Last time I did that, he tried to convince me to drink some strange concoction he'd mixed up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">All the sea life seem very content in there, I must say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've noticed something recently, actually... The anemones breed at a most extraordinary rate.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, really?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a mystery why the whole seabed isn't buried in a mountain of them, actually.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, how splendid! That really is a mystery, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I wish there was someone here to explain Susato-san's strange reaction to that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">My desk is just as it was before I left.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sumi ink and a calligraphy brush...even though we're in England now. That strikes me as typically you, Miss Susato, and typically not you at the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well I do enjoy all the wonderful new things to come out of the West in the cultural revolution, of course. But I'm not ready to give up my brush just yet.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And anyway... Susato-san can write more neatly with a brush than most people can with a pen.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Practice makes perfect, as they say!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's good news that Professor Mikotoba arrived safely, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it's wonderful. And the fact that Father has been invited to this important international event... ...really makes me very proud to be his daughter!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your father, Judge Jigoku, us. ...And Kazuma, of course... There's an ever-increasing number of Japanese here in Britain's capital, isn't there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, yes, I suppose so. But...London does have a population of six million people, so I think we're still a minority.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san's father who came here as a visiting student sixteen years ago, and Kazuma... It's almost as if some great power has been at work, drawing them here across the ocean to London. And I feel as though the waters are starting to swell again now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I stayed up late to mend that for you the other day, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you! You did a really seamless job.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're very welcome. It's all in a day's work for your judicial assistant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The only thing is...I accidentally dropped it into the Thames yesterday and now it...rather smells.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Then take better care of it, please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...It was all going so well...until I ruined it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The Red-Headed League... It's not something we could ever aspire to, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But I'm determined to try!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Your hair is completely black, though. Beautiful, but black.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps you know that in our homeland, this colour of hair has traditionally been described as green-black.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That sounds a lot like a contradiction if you ask me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So some people clearly see it as green in Japan, even though it's black! In which case, I'm full of hope something similar may happen here in Britain!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That level of optimism is...something I should learn a lesson from.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, about this, Miss Susato. Do you notice anything unusual about it perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm, I'm so sorry! I don't, no... I'll redouble my efforts and spend more time doing research so that next time I won't let you down!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I think perhaps you're taking your role as judicial assistant a little too far...</thought></line>
<line speaker="???">This place is full of hardened criminals. I cannae remember the last time a civilian was doon here. And you dinnae want to talk to an inmate, but to me?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">D'you ken who I am? I'm the governor, Barry Caidin......... hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...yes...it's a pleasure. I'm Ryunosuke Naruhodo, defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">And an Easterner, I see. Does that mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I'm a visiting student of law from the Empire of Japan.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Japan?! Did ye say Japan?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Well there's no any of your kind in here, laddie! Maybe you should try the prison next door, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I didn't notice another prison next door, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Anyway, we came to ask you some questions about-</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I dinnae like to be so direct, but... ...I've no intention of speaking wi' the likes o' you suspicious-looking Easterners. Now get oot of my hair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So as soon as he finds out that we're from Japan, he reacts like this... That surely means...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think...it's because of the Professor case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You think so too? <thought>Ten years ago... ...Genshin Asogi - also known as the Professor - was incarcerated at this prison.</thought> And then, after his execution, he apparently re-merged from his grave in the cemetery behind the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I, I might 'ave known! You're sniffing around aboot that case, aren't ya? You're agents, eh? Part of the Professor's great web, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! Not at all! We're just-</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Get gone wi' ya! Before I punch yer lights oot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're going, we're going! <thought>Clearly the ghost of that killer still haunts this place... We're not going to get anywhere here. Unless we can somehow prove to this man that there's nothing suspicious about us...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Governor Caidin...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What are you thinking, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I feel sure that name came up in conversation recently somewhere. I was wondering if whoever mentioned him might have some ideas to help us.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Come to think of it, I have the same feeling...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I said, get oot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Governor Caidin, could I at least show you this?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>How many times can one man turn his back on you in a single conversation?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's Professor Mikotoba over there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Ah, hello, you two! I was just taking a moment to catch up on the world now that I'm unpacked.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But where's Judge Jigoku?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Yes...he's not the relaxing sort. He's taken himself off to pay his respects to all the legal bigwigs.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Having only just arrived in the country today? Goodness, he is full of energy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Professor, you mentioned something before... About how you'd known the prison governor at Barclay Prison.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Oh! ...Governor Caidin, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it is the same man!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father! We must speak with the governor! But he refused to talk to us. He said we were suspicious Easterners.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Well, I'm sure if I accompanied you, it would be a very different story.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, would you?! That would be wonderful! If you have time now...</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Sadly, as you can see, I'm very busy at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Busy drinking coffee on a comfortable settee?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Now now, I have rather a lot to prepare for tomorrow, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! S-Sorry... <thought>I didn't say that out loud, did I?</thought> You Mikotobas are alarmingly good at reading people's thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or could it be that you Naruhodos are alarmingly bad at hiding your thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Let's not fall out now. I have an idea....</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's he writing on that piece of paper?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Here's a letter of introduction for you. Hopefully when he sees my name, he'll change his tune.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... Thank you!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">Good luck, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Professor Mikotoba is obviously trying to relax on that settee there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father has only just arrived after a very long voyage from home. And tomorrow, he will speak at an important symposium that will garner the attention of the whole world. He needs a little peace and quiet now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I was just about to think that!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Pardon?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's one thing reading my thoughts, but at least let me have them first!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... Perhaps my brain works too quickly...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Professor Mikotoba has wonderful handwriting, doesn't he? 'This dark-suited young man is not in the least bit untrustworthy.' ...Is it just me, or does that me sound extremely untrustworthy?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do wish he'd at least called you a 'nice young man'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm really not sure that would help.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...it looks like this is some sort of steamship ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Yokohama departure: 11th September">London arrival: 1st November'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, that's the boat that Professor Mikotoba and Judge Jigoku came on from Japan, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think it called at Dunkirk on the north coast of France for a night before finally arriving in Dover.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>To think it's been almost a year since we arrived in Dover on the SS Burya...</thought> It seems a shame not to keep your ticket as a memento of your trip, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I agree. I have mine safely in my diary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I keep mine in my wallet, so I have it with me at all times. ...Oh, well how strange! Where could it have gone?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you like this on purpose, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Did I imagine it, or was that comment accompanied by a little sigh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...it looks like this is some sort of steamship ticket.</line>
<line speaker="Yokohama departure: 11th September">London arrival: 1st November'...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, that's the boat that Professor Mikotoba and Judge Jigoku came on from Japan, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think it called at Dunkirk on the north coast of France for a night before finally arriving in Dover.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>To think it's been almost a year since we arrived in Dover on the SS Burya...</thought> It seems a shame not to keep your ticket as a memento of your trip, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I agree. I have mine safely in my diary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I keep mine in my wallet, so I have it with me at all times. ...Oh, well how strange! Where could it have gone?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Are you like this on purpose, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Did I imagine it, or was that comment accompanied by a little sigh?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the letter of introduction your father gave us.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, he's clearly well respected if he's able to give out letters like that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Definitely. Professor Mikotoba is obviously held in high regard outside Japan as well as in.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so proud of everything he's accomplished.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A letter of introduction from me would only hold good with Mr Natsume, I expect. And Iris, maybe.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Penned by Dr Mikotoba, I see. It's been ten long years...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But you remember my father, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Certainly, I remember him. And the two other visiting students. Of course...Mikotoba was assigned to the hospital laboratory, so we rarely met. Jigoku on the other hand studied our justice system under my personal supervision.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, I see...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As I said, that was ten years ago now. But I'm pleased to see they've both made names for themselves in their particular disciplines.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you'd just cast your eyes over this, Governor Caidin...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">What's this then? You cannae pull the wool over my eyes, you good-fer-nothin' Japanese student! ......... Mikotoba? That, that young jock from the forensics laboratory? That Mikotoba?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Exactly! Him!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear, perhaps I should have said something sooner... I'm Yujin Mikotoba's daughter, Susato.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Jings! You're the young man's daughter? And ya did'nae think to mention that afore?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I, I do apologise...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, well, ye'd best take a seat then. Can I offer you a cup of tea, perhaps? And dinnae forget to try one of these wee handcuff biscuits!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your father's influence is nothing short of amazing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm bitterly regretting not announcing who I was from the outset now.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">So then...what can I do for you, hen?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...we're currently investigating a case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's one of your warders, you see. He's gone missing.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Missing?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. It's surely been reported to you as well, being the prison governor.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... I have'nae heard nothing of the sort. There's no missing persons in my prison!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But...how can that be?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's Mr Daley Vigil, your chief warder...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Eh? Vigil?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right. His wife came to us and asked us to investigate his disappearance. <thought>Let's skip the part about him only going missing yesterday for now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Clearly that means something to him...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would you be so kind as to tell us what you know, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye... Aye, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Th-This grandfather clock is...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Is fitted with a terrifying blade that keeps dropping down!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">It's modelled on the guillotine - a French execution device. You might have heard of it. And yes, afore you ask: it can chop.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Heads off, you mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Havers, no! Carrots and parsnips and so forth.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">If you place a large carrot at the bottom there in the morn, by evening it'll have been cut clean in two.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Well...the blade must have an almost indescribable edge on it, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose these are all former governors of Barclay Prison, are they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Either that or former inmates who the governor has sent to the gallows.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear...they all have such severe expressions, I really couldn't deny either possibility.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Especially the one on the extreme right. His expression goes beyond 'severe' into a whole new territory...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">...That one's me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aaaaaah! I'm, I'm terribly sorry, sir!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Is it a prerequisite of the job, perhaps? Having a severe expression, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Of course it's not! Although...it is taken into consideration.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...A lot.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An axe, a hunting rifle and four pairs of handcuffs... That's a daunting collection.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Ah, there's a story behind everyone of those.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean... ...the rifle was a famous killer's murder weapon? And the axe was wielded by an infamous executioner? And the handcuffs were once used to immobilise a fierce four-legged beast when it was arrested?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think you're in the realms of fantasy now, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Not those kind of stories, Jimmy. That axe was the one I used to chop down the cherry tree at my hoose. Mrs Caidin was'nae best pleased.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">And the cuffs on the left are the ones I caught my first burglar with back when I was a bobby.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The stories were a little different to those you imagined, I think, weren't they?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, to my relief...and in some small way, my disappointment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd never have expected to find a parrot in a prison! It must be the governor's pet.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Given where we are...it's hard not to see the poor creature as a prisoner.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Aaaaaah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Has, has the bird learnt to mimic the plaintive cries of the inmates in the cells?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Och, no! He was one of three siblings, you see. And he still calls oot the names of his two brothers like that all the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Right...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, aye, I hear ya, laddie. You want your dinner, eh, Did'nae-do-it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's a very large cabinet full of papers, isn't it? It's labelled 'Inmate Register', look. And all the files are in alphabetical order.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">That's fifty years worth of records of Barclay's inmates. Whether or no they left alive after serving their term. All the details aboot the crimes they committed are recorded in there. Like an epitaph, you might say.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...A record of crimes and punishments... How dispiriting.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And yet... ...this man seems to be enjoying tea and biscuits as he talks about it.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We understand that Mr Vigil is the chief warder here at the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, that he was. Strong sense of responsibility and dedicated to the job, no doubt aboot it. He was a fine warder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Sorry, did you say 'was'?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye. He does'nae work here no more. He left the job.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When was this exactly?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">There's a question. When was it aboot...? It cannae have been much less than... ...ten years ago now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">T-Ten years ago? He stopped working here ten years ago?!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, as I mind it. D'you ken, I have'nae heard the fella's name in all that time. That's a worry if he's gone missing, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but Mrs Vigil made no mention of it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think perhaps, Mr Naruhodo, that his wife simply doesn't know. I think she's unaware that he no longer works here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Governor Caidin, can you tell us what happened? Why did Mr Vigil give up his job here?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">That's...important, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Yes, I believe it may be.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What are you thinking, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't help wondering...given that it was ten years ago...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Which was exactly when the Professor was being held at this prison.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So Mr Vigil actually resigned from the position of chief warder ten years ago, you're telling us? What happened to make him leave the job?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... In actual fact, he did'nae leave the job willingly. He had no choice in the matter.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean...he was dismissed?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">It was...after a particular walk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry? A walk?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, that's oor word for it in here. A walk to the gallows.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An, an execution...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">It's the job of the chief warder to prepare the gallows tree and oversee any executions, you see. Only...Vigil did something unthinkable on that last walk he was manning.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What did he do?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I'm sorry, but...I cannae reveal that information. But I can tell you that it's verra rare for a chief warder to be relieved of his post.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why wouldn't Mrs Vigil know about it? She appears to be under the impression that her husband still works here.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">I would'nae ken anything aboot that, I'm afraid.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Can you perhaps answer one more question about the circumstances of his dismissal?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">And what would that be, hen?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That last execution that Mr Vigil was responsible for overseeing... Was it by any chance...the Professor's?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>My thoughts exactly...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... I'm sorry, I really am. But I'm no at liberty to answer that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My father came to Britain all those years ago in order to study forensic medicine. But you seem to have been well acquainted.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">The dead room, the prison and the cemetery have a lot to do wi' one another. After all, they need fresh corpses for forensic research. D'you ken?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes, I can imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The advancement of medical science isn't always particularly palatable...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Your father worked in the laboratory just on the far side of the graveyard. In the basement of St Synner's. It's still in use today.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">St Synner's... <thought>That's come up before, I'm sure...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. We've been there.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Mikotoba and I aft used to ride in a carriage together and negotiate terms.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For more 'fresh' material, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, and we used to sit in here for hours and gab on aboot dissection and all sorts. Och, it takes me back. Over a pot of tea and a plate of cuff biscuits, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How charming...</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">......... He was a good fella, your father. Reliable, and dead set on his work. But I'm afraid... ...I'll never understand you Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Because of Genshin Asogi, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">What's that there, then?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's actually the sign of a Japanese defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Well...if you have to wear something like that to prove who ye are... ...perhaps I should wear these handcuffs, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think maybe they're more of a sign of the people you catch than you yourself.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, that's true. Ye've got me there, hen.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They're not actually a sign of anything, are they?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Well...how aboot that? A friend of Mikotoba turnin' up after all these years. And his wee bairn, even.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My father speaks highly of you, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">D'you ken, I can see the resemblance now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, especially around your eyes. Ye look dead like him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... What an interesting observation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not the delighted reaction from Susato-san that he might have been expecting...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Governor Caidin, would you have a look at this?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Och, would'nae you rather have a wee handcuff biscuit?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...no, thanks. I'd rather you just cast your eyes over this.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Or maybe you prefer real handcuffs, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no! Neither for me, please! Lovely offers, though!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Thank you so much for your time, Governor.</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Oh, one moment afore you're away, hen... I'm sure I have it here somewhere... Ah, found it. Here, take this as a wee souvenir of your visit to the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What is it?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">That's Vigil's dismissal notice. It's ten years old now of course.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Are you sure?</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Aye, it's no trouble at all. It's no the original, mind.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you very much, Governor Caidin!</line>
<line speaker="Caidin">Well in return... ...do me a favour and never come back here. That case is closed.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, I think we ought to return to Baker Street for the time being.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. We need to report back to Mr Sholmes with what we've found out about Mr Vigil. <thought>What will he tell Mrs Vigil, I wonder?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, look, we have an opportunity here now, while the governor is away...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo! You could be imprisoned if you were caught!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's a good point. Perhaps not, then.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We're back!</line>
<line speaker="???">Hello, you two!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">I thought you'd be back before long, so I baked some scones for us all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! So that's what the delicious smell is.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Greetings, my dear fellows! You've returned a good deal sooner than I was anticipating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...hello, Mr Sholmes. .........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hello, Mr...Sholmes... .........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Say nothing. Your thoughts are written all over your faces in any case. It turns out that it may have been advisable to test my hair colour restoration tonic before application.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Pray, tell me. What of our warder friend? Have you garnered some new information?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, um...yes. Something very surprising, in fact. Though it's not a patch on your hair, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It most certainly isn't. But still, we discovered that-</line>
<line speaker="???">SHOOOOOOOOOLMES!!!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Drop everyfin', Sholmes! This is more important!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I can't Adam an' Eve it... *Sniff, sniff...*</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's happened?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Clearly a very grave matter indeed. For Miss Lestrade made no mention of my hair whatsoever.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">It's...it's the boss...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean? <thought>Inspector Gregson?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss is... He's... He's dead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What...?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">They, they just found 'is body. Shot...wiv a pistol...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...but... Inspector Gregson?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He was...murdered?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">No... Not Gregsy...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Come in, my dear girl. Tell us the whole story.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">*Sniff, sniff...*</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are you serious, Gina?! Inspector Gregson was... He was really shot?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I, I don't know much about wot 'appened meself yet. They're still there...investigatin' the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Where did this take place?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">A little rented room in a buildin' full o' flats on Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">The outskirts of town. Nowhere near his home. He was perhaps investigating a case then...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The thing is...no one at the Yard knows nuffin' about no case around there.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh. How strange...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss was... 'E was so good to me. I know I ain't up to much yet, but... ...one day, I was gonna show 'im! I was gonna show 'im I'd become a proper detective!</line>
<line speaker="Iris">Oh, Ginny...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So! Who did this? Do you have any idea who the culprit is?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">They got 'im already.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Already?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They've caught the shooter so soon?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">A witness reported somefin' was goin' on, and the boys got straight down there an' took care of 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Who?! What awful person did this?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... I, I still can't believe it meself...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... It was the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The- Wait a minute! You don't mean... ...they've arrested Lord van Zieks for it?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's right! That Reaper bloke's gone an' shot the boss!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No! <thought>Lord van Zieks...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Are you quite sure, Miss Lestrade? It's Barok van Zieks the police have arrested?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I saw 'im wiv me own eyes. In the interview room at the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't believe it...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But there were witnesses. An' they're all sayin' it was 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So you mean...there were actually multiple witnesses?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">They 'eard the gunshot, apparently. An' when our lot got to the scene... ...there was only the boss and that Reaper bloke in the room!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But there's no way Lord van Zieks would have taken Gregson's life. I...I just don't believe it!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I don't believe it, either!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, Gina, I wanted to show you this...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No, what am I thinking? This is hardly the time, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot are you sayin' sorry for? You didn't do nuffin'!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well...anyway... ...I'm takin' a cab over to the scene right now. Please come an' all! As soon as ya can! You've gotta 'elp!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It's a detective's lot to appear wherever some sinister plot has unfolded. Little wonder we all look haggard. Sometimes these things are almost too much for the nerves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes...</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What use is there in being a great detective if I fail to see something like this coming, hm?! How could I let this happen to Gregson?! To Gregson...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Mr Naruhodo, I shall leave at once to begin my investigations.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Of course, yes. We will, too.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">It would be helpful... ...if you could talk to Mr Reaper and see what you can glean. I'm sure you were intending to do so anyway. Until later, then!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Inspector Gregson, dead... And Lord van Zieks arrested...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Iris">Runo! Susie! I've called you a hansom. It's waiting outside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thanks, Iris. Shall we, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't believe it! Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's awful, isn't it? But we must carry on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know, but...it's just so much to take in. I don't know where to start.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We must start with a thorough investigation of the scene. And we must interview Gina. Then we must go to the prison to speak with the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Thank goodness I have you, Miss Susato. You have it all under control as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You're too kind, Mr Naruhodo. But I'm afraid I don't have all the answers. I really have no idea how to be around Iris at the moment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh yes...that.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>This really is an out-of-the-way part of London. I doubt many people find their way down this back street. So this dust-ridden rented old room is where it happened then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So this is...where poor Inspector Gregson lost his life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes... And the police are already hard at work investigating, it seems. <thought>I don't see Mr Sholmes anywhere, though... Perhaps his investigations have taken him elsewhere.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oi! Wot d'ya think yer doin' there?! Every one o' them drawers 'as gotta be taken right out so you can look underneath an' all! I want the space above this ceilin' checked, and don't forget to look inside the chimney stack, too! Blimey! Ain't you lot never gone over an 'ouse lookin' for dough when the owners are out o' town?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Gina's obviously got some unique investigative techniques she wants everyone to adopt...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh, so you've turned up at last. Mind you, I ain't been 'ere long meself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello again, Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Sholmes 'as only just left. Yer lucky ya missed that. 'E went prancin' around in 'ere, pointin' at stuff an' flickin' that 'at of 'is an' then just scarpered.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! He's finished investigating already, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah... 'E didn't stop to say nuffin' to no one. Not even me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina! Would you mind if we investigated, too?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Listen, 'Oddo... ...yer a lawyer, right?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...yes. Why?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well, yer not thinkin' of...tryin' to 'elp that Reaper bloke, are ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>Poor Gina... She's never going to forget, is she? That trial will haunt her forever.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gina, if you don't mind me saying... If Lord van Zieks really is responsible for this crime... ...he will be duly and fairly judged in court.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... I suppose yer right, yeah. Go on then, 'Oddo! Get investigatin'! I wanna know the truth about wot really 'appened 'ere!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Thank you, Gina!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">An empty fireplace makes a room feel even colder than it would be otherwise, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's thick with dust, look. I think it would be fair to say it hasn't been used in a very long time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words... ...whoever lived in this room must have been extremely hardy in cold weather.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Or nobody lived here at all, and merely visited when the occasion arose. ...I wouldn't like to say which is more likely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">N-No, that's right. It's one or the other...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...it's a photograph stand. I suppose it must be a picture of one of Inspector Gregson's family members. Ah.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wh-What's the matter? Your eyes look like they're about to pop out of your head.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They are! Look, Mr Naruhodo! Quickly!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm...why do I feel like this woman is familiar somehow?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course she's familiar! We met her only this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aah! It's... It's... It's... ...Mrs Vigil!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This...makes no sense. Why would there be a picture of Mrs Vigil in here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To be frank... ...I don't think I've ever been more stumped.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sorry to say, I have no idea either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's really no question, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's the same woman we met only this morning! It's definitely Mrs Vigil! A little younger-looking, perhaps, but still...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aha! Perhaps she has a younger sister who looks just like her or something!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But the photograph does appear to be rather old, doesn't it? And anyway, the question remains: why would something like this be in here?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right, the question does remain. And I remain as stumped as I ever was by it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">This looks like some sort of noticeboard or something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it's absolutely covered in scraps of paper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...Ah! Mr Naruhodo, look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This, you mean? It's an autopsy report, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And these are case notes here. And details of prison inmates!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...in fact they're all the sort of documents that only a detective could normally acquire. <thought>What on earth went on this room?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Some old newspaper cuttings... Ah! And this one here!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, the advertisement, you mean? 'To the Red-Headed League'! B-But why? What's that doing here?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Whoever occupied this room was clearly interested in it for some reason...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Oh, Inspector... Ohhh, sir...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Poor man. He can't possibly be able to focus on investigating when he's so upset.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">Sorry, sir. Can't see a thing, sir. Too many tears, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right. Perhaps I'd better leave you to your work, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is presumably the murder weapon, then...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, oh my... ...It is real, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think so. Guns are so rare in Japan, I really know very little about them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's one way to know for sure, Mr Naruhodo. Fire a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! If I did that, I'd be looking for a skilled lawyer to represent me in court. <thought>Slightly safer just to ask someone who might know, I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is presumably the murder weapon, then...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, oh my... ...It is real, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think so. Guns are so rare in Japan, I really know very little about them.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There's one way to know for sure, Mr Naruhodo. Fire a shot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! If I did that, I'd be looking for a skilled lawyer to represent me in court. <thought>Slightly safer just to ask someone who might know, I think.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ever since we came in here...I can't take my eyes off this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Funnily enough, neither can I!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...a hairpiece, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is! It IS! A bright red hairpiece!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I suppose the fact that it's right there next to where the body was found... ...means we have to accept that...Inspector Gregson wore wigs, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And in such a flame-coloured red, too...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's a colour we've come across very recently elsewhere, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Exactly! This is a vital clue, I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ever since we came in here...I can't take my eyes off this thing.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Funnily enough, neither can I!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...a hairpiece, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is! It IS! A bright red hairpiece!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I suppose the fact that it's right there next to where the body was found... ...means we have to accept that...Inspector Gregson wore wigs, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And in such a flame-coloured red, too...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's a colour we've come across very recently elsewhere, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Exactly! This is a vital clue, I'm sure of it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So I suppose...this is where the victim...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right. The rope is laid around the body to show exactly how it was found. Poor Inspector Gregson himself has already been taken away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And would probably be under Dr Sithe's scalpel by now if not for what happened last week...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">From the shape of the rope... ...it would appear that the inspector was curled up in a ball.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Are you feeling alright, Mr Naruhodo? You look like you've just seen a ghost.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know it's just a rope, but... Well, it conjures up quite a terrifying image, that's all. Especially with that bloodstain next to it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, I do understand. In some ways, what we picture in our minds can be even worse than reality.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Susato-san is so strong, though. She's taking this far better than I am...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...what's this?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would appear to be a little model policeman. It's rather charming, isn't it? In a way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Seeing as it's on the floor here...do you think it belonged to Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's a little hard to imagine Lord van Zieks playing with something like this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's only about eight centimetres tall. It could have fallen out of someone's pocket, I suppose.</thought> I think we should record it as evidence, just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I agree. It is rather delightful, after all. In a way.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is rather endearing in a way, isn't it? This little London bobby.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You do realise that you keep saying how charming it is 'in a way', don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The truth is...on closer inspection his face scares me a little.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it is supposed to be a policeman. Looking charming isn't generally in the job description as far as I can tell.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, I suppose not... In a way, that makes me a little sad, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The top of one of the candles in this candle holder has been completely blown off.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, there's wax spattered on the wall behind, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose if a bullet had hit it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does seem likely that the bullet hit the candle... ...having first passed through the inspector's body.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Now that wax on the wall looks like blood to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The top of one of the candles in this candle holder has been completely blown off.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, there's wax spattered on the wall behind, look.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose if a bullet had hit it...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It does seem likely that the bullet hit the candle... ...having first passed through the inspector's body.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... Now that wax on the wall looks like blood to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Somebody's very haphazardly nailed those boards over the broken glass, haven't they? You couldn't even really call it a window any more.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, if you remember the window in Mr Natsume's room, that was totally blocked up with bricks. This one does at least still let in some light, so you could say-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You could say nothing more about it. ...I'm starting to feel even more sorry for Mr Natsume now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, excuse me...</line>
<line speaker="Policeman">If you're looking down on us from the great beyond, Inspector, don't worry. We'll look after things at the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I've interrupted some deep thoughts there...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina, what was Inspector Gregson doing here in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's wot I wanna know! ...It's wot? 'Alf a year since I got out o' the clink? That's when I decided to give up me divin' an' become a detective instead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">OH yes,  Mr Sholmes twisted the inspector's arm to agree to take you on as an apprentice, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Summat like that, I think. Anyway, the point is, I didn't really know much about the boss 'til then. But it turns out, 'e's a bit of a legend at the Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Goodness! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">They say 'e managed to solve some really tricky case... just like that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He did?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yup. An' ever since then, 'e started goin' out on all sorts o' investigations, but always on 'is own. No one else at the Yard even knows wot 'alf the cases 'e's workin' on are, apparently.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's not how it's supposed to work, is it? <thought>So what was the 'legendary inspector' doing in a dingy little room like this?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">I know 'e 'ad a lot of respect for the Reaper an' all. An' look where that landed 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Respect for the Reaper? In what way?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I 'eard 'im say as much. 'I take my 'at off to that fella,' were 'is words.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Not how the general public feels, is it? Most people are terrified of the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, the boss said that's exactly why 'e respected the bloke.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I didn't realise Gregson held the Reaper in quite such high regard.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">'E said somefin' else to me an' all... That I didn't need to worry about the Reaper, cos 'e only goes after people wot are bad. It did kind o' set my mind at east when 'e said that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is this place, then? Does anyone live here?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Apparently it's bein' rented by some cove called Hugh Boone.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hugh Boone...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a sort of...here-today-gone-tomorrow name that, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, 'e's wot we call an unidentified person. We 'aven't been able to get in touch wiv 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see. Well, judging from appearances... ...I'd have to say this place hasn't been lived in for a long time. If ever.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Right? All the lads from the Yard piled down to get stuck into the investigation... ...but there's so little 'ere, no one knew wot to do wiv 'emselves.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... I do wonder...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, could it be that this Hugh Boone... ...is in fact Inspector Gregson himself?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? How could that be?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well if he was investigating on his own... ...it's quite possible that this was in fact some kind of secret office of his.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'd, I'd never even considered that!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Nice work, Sooze! We're actually followin' a line of inquiry like that ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You are?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">If you look around the room, you'll see. There's a few things that hint at it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>We should really investigate this place in detail...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I see that's where the poor inspector was found, over there.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, that's right. They said...it was a single bullet wot did 'im in. Apparently the bullet went right through 'im an' struck that candle tree on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Oh yes. It's blown one of the candles apart completely.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">An' the gun used is there on the floor. It's the Reaper's, innit? No denyin' that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?! Really?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How do you know that?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Take it easy! I, I dunno wot to do wiv meself when you stare at me wiv them big wide eyes. I'm only sayin' wot I've 'eard. I dunno much about guns meself. But there's some bigwig lawman or wotever who said so. Why don't you ask 'im?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A 'bigwig lawman' is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">Anyway, Fresno Street runs along under that window there. There were some street sellers just outside who 'eard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! But...I don't recall seeing anybody outside.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Yeah, they've all been taken down the Yard for questionin', that's why. We're talkin' about the Yard's legendary inspector 'ere, after all. They'll be gettin' a grillin'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you think we might be able to speak with those street sellers ourselves?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I doubt it. The lads at the Yard will just wanna know wot yer snoopin' for and you'll be up for a grillin' an' all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So we can't interview the witnesses, then. Shame...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This armband is proof - in Japan at least - that I'm a defence lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">And this badge is proof that I'm a detective! So yer all gonna 'ave to start callin' me Inspector Lestrade!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case, you'll have to start calling me... Well, anything but ''Oddo'.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I could call ya 'Defender Narra-'Oddo' if ya like. ...But it don't really trip off the tongue.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No...it doesn't have a great ring to it, does it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh, that business? Yup, Inspector Lestrade 'ere soon 'ad that one buttoned up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I thought it was Mr Sholmes who led that pair into a trap, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... Listen, 'Oddo. It ain't easy goin' from East End diver to Scotland Yard detective, right? But anyway, it's all part o' the charm, innit? Bein' a bit loose wiv the truth when it 'elps.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's wrong for so many reasons.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Maybe...I should get Iris to write stories about me! 'The Adventures of Inspector Lestrade'!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina, what do you make of this?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Wot is that? Evidence? Worked somefin' out about wot 'appened, 'ave ya?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...um...no, not exactly.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I ain't been long enough in the job to get all this deductin' business yet. But I swear I'm gonna get the person wot did this to the boss!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I suppose this must have been the murder weapon.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, oh my... ...It is real, I suppose?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I think so. Guns are so rare in Japan, I really know very little about them. <thought>Perhaps someone more familiar with firearms could shed a light on things here.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I've always wondered what the underside of a hairpiece looks like.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That doesn't surprise me at all, Mr Naruhodo. You always want to see what lies beneath, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm not sure that's quite how I'd put it. You must have to use lots of bird lime to keep it in place on your head. So it doesn't get blown off in a gust of wind, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...That might be a little more inconvenient when you wanted to take it off again, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The helmet of this charming policeman appears to be a little worse for wear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not convinced about the 'charming' part, but yes, you're right... ...the head part looks like it's been fairly heavily manhandled. Almost as if somebody has enjoyed twisting it around and around for fun.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shall we try twisting it around and around, too? For fun. Ah! What's that?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It...appears to be some sort of key.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it's tiny, though! It couldn't be a key for a door. Not at that size. <thought>So what is it for, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">The helmet of this charming policeman appears to be a little worse for wear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not convinced about the 'charming' part, but yes, you're right... ...the head part looks like it's been fairly heavily manhandled. Almost as if somebody has enjoyed twisting it around and around for fun.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Shall we try twisting it around and around, too? For fun. Ah! What's that?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It...appears to be some sort of key.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it's tiny, though! It couldn't be a key for a door. Not at that size. <thought>So what is it for, I wonder...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This looks like...some sort of key.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it does. A very tiny and simple key.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's a little key doing inside a figurine of a policeman in the first place? And what's it for?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! There are some black marks here, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, they...look like some sort of scorch marks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So perhaps the bullet struck the candle here, do you think? It's only this one candle that's been cracked in half, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I think you might be right. Firearms are rarely used by criminals in Japan... ...so I'm afraid I'm not particularly knowledgeable about them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There he is. Lord van Zieks behind bars...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">So it's true. He really was arrested...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's sitting with his back to the wall, reading something. I don't think he's noticed us.</thought> Erm...Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...Fancy meeting you here. The last place on Earth I'd like to be, with the last person on earth I'd like to see.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I couldn't very well not come. We heard what happened. That you... That Inspector Gregson was...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Go home. This has nothing to do with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Forgive me, Lord van Zieks, but I must disagree.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Inspector Gregson was very helpful to us on a number of occasions. We're indebted to him. At the very least we owe it to him to find out the truth about his death. You must help us with our investigations, please!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... There's really nothing I can tell you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What were you just reading at the back of the cell there? Was it something related to the case?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...This? The Yard isn't quite so cavalier with its information as to share case details with a suspect. This is...a letter from an old acquaintance.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh. Who might that be?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Someone you know, as it happens. Albert Harebrayne.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Of course, yes. I keep forgetting they went to the same university.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And I would like to read my correspondence in peace. So let's get this over with, shall we? What is it you want to know?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Strange... I mean, let's face it, Lord van Zieks never minces his words... ...but they seem to have less bite than usual somehow.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Can you at least tell us your side of the story, Lord van Zieks? What happened?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... How much do you already know?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We know that the inspector was shot dead in a small, rented room on Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that you were found there by the police when they arrived on the scene and immediately arrested.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We were told that there was nobody else in the room, and that some witnesses heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then you're well informed. And there's really nothing I can add. The truth is, I don't know what happened myself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...the gunshot! Obviously you didn't fire the gun, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm not in the habit of shooting the people I work alongside. I also heard the noise. However... ...before I had a chance to investigate, I was apprehended by the arriving officers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So he doesn't actually know what happened...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If I might ask, what were you doing in that place to begin with?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I don't need to answer that.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">After all, you're not representing me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He is going to need a lawyer, though...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who is going to be representing you in court, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Anyone other than you, I should imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haaah...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Would I be right in assuming...that you have no representation as yet?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Defence lawyers shy away from any trial involving the Reaper, as I'm sure you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But this is different.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In my career, of all the defendants I've prosecuted, only nineteen have ever been acquitted. Of them, sixteen subsequently died in mysterious circumstances. Questions will be asked now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Surely not!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I assure you, no defence lawyer will want to touch me with the end of a barge pole.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you didn't actually have anything to do with those people's deaths...did you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... It's been ten years now that I've been known as the Reaper of the Bailey. Believe me, nobody wants to know the true identity of this killer more than I. However... ...it seems things may come to a head before I have the chance to uncover the truth about that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What does he mean by that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>After the trial... ...Professor Harebrayne was supposed to go straight back to Germany, I thought.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's a letter to inform me of his safe arrival at home. I arranged his passage by sea and rail. It's a relief, I must say. He should now be beyond the reaches of the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Because the Reaper doesn't follow people abroad, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes. So it seems. Your stooped little Nipponese friend, for example. You told me he was keeping well in Japan when I enquired the other day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. He's an author now. Happily working in Tokyo.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So Professor Harebrayne is safely back in Germany now.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think you know that this is worn by people in my country to show that they're defence lawyers, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And I think you know that I believed you to be merely playing at lawyer-craft...initially. But it would seem your armband may actually imply some dormant talent after all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks! Do you mean...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Let's hope you wake up soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I was clearly daydreaming. I almost thought I got a compliment there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...It's not for me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, that's...not why I was showing you it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I suppose... ...if it was a Black-Headed League, you would have no hesitation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">None whatsoever!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Sadly my own hair could no more be described as black as it could red. ......... What coloured league should I then join?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">People are troubled by the most unexpected problems at times...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, it's just something I was hoping to ask your opinion about, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's a serious crime for the defence to attempt to extract information from the prosecution by illegal means.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright, I get the message. But I don't see what's illegal about me asking...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was a two-second silence, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Well in any event, if you'll excuse me now. ...I wouldn't like to detain you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I was wondering, Lord van Zieks... If you'd like... ...I'd be happy to advocate for you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...! ...You trust me, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. I've heard you speak many times in court. I've seen how you treat people. So I'm quite sure that you would never have taken another's life. ...It's just, my feelings can't be used as evidence in a court of law, sadly.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... It's a very gracious offer. However... ...I trust no one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Not the police, not the judiciary...and not you Nipponese.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But please...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I have no intention of engaging your services.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>The chasm between us is just too wide and too deep, it seems...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I'd appreciate it if you don't visit again. Then neither of us will waste any more time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps we need to dig a little deeper... ...and find out more about Lord van Zieks and what happened to Inspector Gregson.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">...You've made good time.</line>
<line speaker="???">I took an express train back to London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can hear Lord Stronghart. Can you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it sounds as though he's talking to someone.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Is everything in place?</line>
<line speaker="???">I had a private compartment on the train so I could check all the paperwork.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I-It's...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah, your timing is impeccable!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It, it is?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No doubt you have heard the sickening news? About the Reaper's latest devilry.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure you don't believe it of course, though, Lord Stronghart. That Lord van Zieks could have done such a thing to Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">......... I believe only in the facts. And the facts in this case point to one thing: The unavoidable accusal of Lord van Zieks for this crime. We must bring charges against the Reaper for taking the life of our legendary detective.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no, surely not!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's a truly regrettable situation. Tomorrow the forensic science symposium finally begins. At the very least, though, we can show the world our justice system's swift and equitable processes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So does that mean...the trial is tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Precisely. In fact, this is a fine opportunity for introductions.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Ah, but of course! You're already acquainted, aren't you? Mr Asogi here will be present at tomorrow's proceedings... ...leading the prosecution.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait... WHAAAAAAT?! <thought>Kazuma...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">As I'm sure you're aware, he's a very capable practitioner of law.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama...a prosecutor...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm sorry for all the worry I've caused you. But...it'll be alright now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Has your memory completely returned?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, completely. I remember everything. Including what I was coming here to do.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama... ...I can't tell you how happy I am to see you alive and well like this. But...how did you come to be here in London when you were suffering from amnesia?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...It was the voice. This past year... ...I've been hearing it in my head constantly, saying the same thing over and over: 'Go to London. That's where your destiny awaits.'</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was that voice that guided me here to London.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so sorry for what's happened...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Anyway, my memory might have returned to me... ...but there's something that won't return to the way it was before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh? What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm a prosecutor now. ...So I'm sure our paths will cross again very soon.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">I'm sure you can imagine that tomorrow's trial will be closely followed all over London. In fact, no. People all over the empire will be watching closely to see how it unfolds.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no salvation for anyone in a trial prosecuted by the Reaper of the Bailey. And now... ...the Reaper himself must stand in the dock.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Quite so. The public want answer answers about the Reaper. Answers about how and why those who escaped conviction subsequently died mysterious deaths.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Lord van Zieks firmly denies any involvement in such matters.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And there have been thorough investigations that have proven him to be innocent.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That's certainly true. Or it has been, at least, until now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No, tomorrow's trial... ...will mark the start of a new chapter in our country's great judicial history!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...Kazuma will be prosecuting tomorrow?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That's right.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...he's a defence lawyer, Lord Stronghart!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Accomplished young law practitioners cannot pick and choose their roles.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">And imagine what it will mean for the prosecution to know the strategies commonly employed by the defence. A devastating combination, wouldn't you agree?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Absolutely. I've no doubt at all that Kazuma will be razor-sharp as a prosecutor.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But...why Kazuma-sama? There are surely many other highly skilled prosecutors in Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was a personal request. I asked to be assigned to the trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You, you asked for this? But why?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It'll all become clear tomorrow. I'm guessing you intend to stand for the defence, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Although the Reaper appears to be turning down all offers of representation.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I'm surprised such a personal request would have been upheld. It seems...unprecedented. Quite exceptional, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">You are quite right, Miss Mikotoba. Tomorrow's trial will be unprecedented and exceptional in every way.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah...</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">After all, the accused is one of Britain's greatest prosecutors. The pride of the empire. It would be unwise to give the public a reason to perceive it as the judiciary closing ranks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So that's why you're happy to let a foreigner handle the prosecution?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ryunosuke... ...let's see how your skills have been honed after practising law in this land for so many months!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma, I... <thought>I don't understand why you're being so hostile to me now. This isn't going to end well, my friend...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, we noticed that there was a gun at the scene of Inspector Gregson's death. Do you know if it belongs to Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">That would be a question for the lead detective investigating the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well the thing is... ...she wasn't sure, so she told me I should ask somebody higher up who might know.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's right, Mr Naruhodo. Be direct!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">It's certainly a model that's issued to all personnel involved in law enforcement, yes. Which includes prosecutors, as I'm sure you can imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">In that case...it could actually have belonged to the victim!</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No. Gregson had his gun on his person.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What about Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">He claims it's currently not in his possession.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">According to his story, he lost it. In short...it's more than a little suspicious.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But just because the gun in question is the same type as the defendant's is no proof that it's actually his.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">No, of course not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nevertheless, the situation is grave for Lord van Zieks...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is the type of revolver that's standard issue for members of the judiciary, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes. And when I asked about whether records are kept about who they're issued to... ...I was told that for the past five years, they've been engraved with a unique serial number.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh, but as far as I can tell... ...there's nothing like that on this gun.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which tells us that it must have been issued longer ago than that.</line>
<line speaker="Stronghart">Remember, tomorrow's trial will go down in our empire's history. There's much you could learn...from the public gallery.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Sorry to have taken up so much of your time. We'll see ourselves out.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Before you go, Ryunosuke...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...what is it, Kazuma?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I just wanted...to thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama... What...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You took my determination to heart and brought it with you over the ocean in my stead. And you carried out my role to perfection.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You always were intent on studying British law in order to change our own justice system. It was your dream, and Mr Naruhodo didn't want that to die with you!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. But I had another purpose for coming here.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I actually have a favour to ask.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-Which is...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This trial I'll be prosecuting tomorrow... I'd like you to be there to see how it ends. Right in front of me...as the defence counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Why? What's this all about?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I know you have what it takes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...Lord van Zieks would never put his fate in my hands.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">On the contrary. He recognises your talent.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He does?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...It's not easy to see behind the facade sometimes. Here, have a look at this...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's Lord van Zieks and Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In a photograph that must have been taken some time ago by the look of it. And who's the third person?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It was displayed very prominently in the detective's office.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In Gregson's office, you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. What I'm trying to say is, if you really think you can trust the Reaper... ...you might find that some straight talking makes him take a different view. Take it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't understand. Why are you giving me this?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just hurry, Ryunosuke! Visiting hours at the prison are almost over.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What are you doing, Kazuma...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks is still reading that letter.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've been gone quite some time, though...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Either he's an incredibly slow reader...or it's an incredibly long letter... I might even be able to read English faster than he can.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was intending to ignore you entirely... ...but I can't turn a deaf ear to such an insulting Nipponese.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! Um...sorry. I didn't think you'd hear that.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I had the case notes brought to me in secret. I was reading them to pass the time.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, we heard that your trial is set for tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Which is none of your business.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...have you found a lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">How many times must I reiterate the same thing: this is nothing to do with you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In other words, no.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">We were just talking to Lord Stronghart and...the prosecutor for your trial has been decided.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'd expect nothing less. Though I have no idea who it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's...going to be Kazuma Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...! Asogi?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That made the colour drain from his face...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Haah, well then... ...it seems I'm going to have to engage in conversation with you again after all.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ten years ago, my older brother, who was the Director of Prosecutions at the time, was murdered. And the killer, as you know...was a visiting student from the Far East. Not a single day goes by...when I don't curse the name Asogi!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Genshin Asogi was Kazuma-sama's father.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">So what cruel twist of fate is this now, ten years later? The man's son is to crucify me in some kangaroo court?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still don't understand why Lord Stronghart apprenticed Kazuma to you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It's what he does. No doubt he knew of the young man's true identity from the outset.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But what could he have been hoping to achieve?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And let's not forget that it was only eight days ago that Kazuma recovered from his amnesia. Why would Lord Stronghart assign this trial to somebody like that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Hm...Asogi... That name is the very epitome of my bane. The bane that is you Nipponese.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Right... Your hatred of all us Japanese...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'd only just been appointed as a prosecutor when it happened ten years ago. My brother Klint, the Director of Prosecutions, was hunting down a mass murderer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The so-called 'Professor'...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Assigned to the investigation as his partner... ...was a certain visiting student dispatched from Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that was Genshin Asogi?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Exactly. I developed a deep respect for the man. He seemed noble-minded and chivalrous in the extreme to me. ...But none of us saw the true nature of the man. So I lost everything when it happened. My esteemed brother...the people I believed in...and any semblance of right prevailing over wrong!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...how awful...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">To avenge my brother, I prosecuted in Asogi's trial. It wouldn't ordinarily have been allowed, but I beleaguered the ascribed prosecutor until he consented.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you mean by the ascribed prosecutor?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The man in charge of the Professor case inquiry: Lord Mael Stronghart.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, what?! Lord Stronghart?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">He was a highly accomplished prosecutor. But he agreed to relinquish the trial to me and act as my adviser instead. Since that time, he's the one person to whom I've felt indebted.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm sure he must have seen your zeal for the case and recognised your potential as a prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Anyway, time passed, but then earlier this year, who should arrive in London...but you.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And, of all things...as a lawyer.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I felt your animosity the first time I ever faced you in the courtroom. Your obvious deep loathing of us Japanese.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I kept telling myself it was illogical. But for so many years, that hatred had festered inside me, I could no longer control it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And I can understand why, now I know the history.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">But in the same way that I've long felt the Nipponese to be the bane of my life... ...to Kazuma Asogi, I am the bane of his. The Reaper who sent his father to the gallows. He's looking for revenge, and he intends to take it in court tomorrow.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Gregson's transfer to the Paris Police Prefecture had finally been arranged for the coming month. But he'll never make it to France now. ...It's a tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, come to think of it he did mention something about that, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder...does it happen often? Being transferred internationally, I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...It's the first time I've ever encountered it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Paris police welcoming an English detective is... almost inconceivable. I can't imagine what kind of magic Gregson must have worked to put that arrangement in place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...It sounds like that mystery has even the Reaper perplexed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid to say... ...that we were very ignorant about Inspector Gregson's standing. We hear that he was considered something of a legend at Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Again, it was ten years ago that he first made a name for himself. By uncovering a decisive pair of evidence that exposed the Professor's identity. If it wasn't for Gregson's singular approach to the case, the discovery would never have been made.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of approach?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">After my brother's life was taken, the inspector pushed for a full autopsy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Why is that so surprising?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Autopsy was considered a desecration of the body at the time, and rarely performed. And my brother was of course a noble. That made the idea of it even more unthinkable. But something Gregson had dug up in his investigations made him determined it was necessary. His powerful conviction somehow influenced the House of Lords and as a result...I could avenge my brother's death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you must have had great confidence in the inspector's abilities, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And it's even more inconceivable that you would have taken his life!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I don't have confidence in anyone.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And I'm sure Gregson felt the same way. I've no doubt he thought of me only as the ominous Reaper, just like the rest of London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What really went on between Lord van Zieks and Gregson, I wonder? What was the true nature of their relationship?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Gregson's transfer to the Paris Police Prefecture had finally been arranged for the coming month. But he'll never make it to France now. ...It's a tragedy.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes, come to think of it he did mention something about that, didn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder...does it happen often? Being transferred internationally, I mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...It's the first time I've ever encountered it.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The Paris police welcoming an English detective is... almost inconceivable. I can't imagine what kind of magic Gregson must have worked to put that arrangement in place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...It sounds like that mystery has even the Reaper perplexed.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid to say... ...that we were very ignorant about Inspector Gregson's standing. We hear that he was considered something of a legend at Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Again, it was ten years ago that he first made a name for himself. By uncovering a decisive pair of evidence that exposed the Professor's identity. If it wasn't for Gregson's singular approach to the case, the discovery would never have been made.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What sort of approach?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">After my brother's life was taken, the inspector pushed for a full autopsy.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! Ten years ago?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Why is that so surprising?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Autopsy was considered a desecration of the body at the time, and rarely performed. And my brother was of course a noble. That made the idea of it even more unthinkable. But something Gregson had dug up in his investigations made him determined it was necessary. His powerful conviction somehow influenced the House of Lords and as a result...I could avenge my brother's death.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you must have had great confidence in the inspector's abilities, then.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And it's even more inconceivable that you would have taken his life!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Inspector Gregson...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About the gun used to shoot the inspector that was found at the scene...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Ah yes... That's not mine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? Because common opinion seems to be that it is.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... What do you expect me to say to that?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord Stronghart informs us that you claim to have misplaced your firearm.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... As embarrassing as that is, I'm afraid it's true.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When did you lose it, then?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That...I don't know.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was issued with a revolver when I first became a prosecutor ten years ago. I must have stowed it somewhere, I suppose. Or left it somewhere, perhaps.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... You have something in common with Lord van Zieks after all, Mr Naruhodo: a talent for misplacing things.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No no no! This is nothing to do with me! Don't drag me into it!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Don't make the mistake of associating me with this... Nipponese!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... The rift is very wide, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it's not decisive evidence, clearly. But it doesn't look good, that's for sure.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks, we came by this old photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...! Where did you get that?! It was taken when I became a qualified prosecutor. It's almost unbelievable. I, I assumed it was long lost.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, is the man on the left there...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, that's my brother. Klint.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It had to be, really.</thought> Apparently this picture was prominently displayed in Gregson's office. He had a deep respect for you, you know. ...Were you aware of that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Respect?! That's...nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, we've heard someone attest to it very clearly. <thought>Inspector Gina Lestrade, no less.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Well...maybe once, yes. There was a time things were like that. We were brothers in arms...jovially discussing the future of justice and other such lofty subject matter. ......... That was a nice glimpse of the past. I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I feel as though I got a nice glimpse of the past then, too. There was a glimmer of light in his eyes. A brief twinkle. An insight into the true nature of this man known to all as the stone-cold Reaper of the Bailey.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Lord van Zieks, we came by this old photograph...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...! Where did you get that?! It was taken when I became a qualified prosecutor. It's almost unbelievable. I, I assumed it was long lost.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um, is the man on the left there...?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, that's my brother. Klint.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It had to be, really.</thought> Apparently this picture was prominently displayed in Gregson's office. He had a deep respect for you, you know. ...Were you aware of that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Respect?! That's...nonsense!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, we've heard someone attest to it very clearly. <thought>Inspector Gina Lestrade, no less.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Well...maybe once, yes. There was a time things were like that. We were brothers in arms...jovially discussing the future of justice and other such lofty subject matter. ......... That was a nice glimpse of the past. I thank you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I feel as though I got a nice glimpse of the past then, too. There was a glimmer of light in his eyes. A brief twinkle. An insight into the true nature of this man known to all as the stone-cold Reaper of the Bailey.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! <thought>That's the first time he's ever used my actual name.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I've lost all confidence in my country's justice system. I don't trust the police, the judiciary or lawyers. But there's still one thing I'm willing to believe in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What's that?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That which you see in the eyes of another across the courtroom: a simple determination to know the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">From the very first time we clashed in the Bailey almost a year ago now... ...I couldn't deny it, even though I dearly wished I could. 'Here is a loathsome Nipponese...who has absolute integrity as a lawyer.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">There are only two other men I've known with that same look in their eyes: My brother, Klint. ...And Genshin Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The man he idolised and the man who betrayed his trust in the most hideous way...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... When you showed me that photograph just now, it reminded me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean, this photograph?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Back then I was able to laugh. I was free of the shackles of mistrust that plague me now. I looked to the future with hope. Since then I've protected myself against betrayal by refusing to trust anyone. But at times the mire into which I've sunk makes it almost impossible to breathe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm...so sorry...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... So Mr Naruhodo... ...I want to believe in that look in your eyes. I need to believe in it. ...In tomorrow's trial...will you advocate for me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Of course I will. It would be an honour.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm so pleased, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Then my life is in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For Lord van Zieks... ...that must have been an incredibly hard thing to ask. Which is why I simply cannot let the man down. Tomorrow...in the Old Bailey...against my old friend, Kazuma!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Nothing particular of note...</thought></line>
</xml>