<xml>
<title>Twisted Karma and His Last Bow</title>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's that old familiar feeling again... The crushing pressure of this historic courthouse.</thought> ......... <thought>Actually, no... it's a little different today. There's an even more menacing tension in the air.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">There is a menacing tension in the air here today, isn't there? I suppose...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I think so. It can only be the result of the menacing appearance of the defendant.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A little more courtesy, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my! I, I do apologise!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">However...you're certainly not mistaken that this trial is far from ordinary.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm not privy to the details. However... ...I understand that no jury has been selected.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">A trial without a jury?! Well, well that's just like... ...the trial of the Professor ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>A closed court...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Good morning, my dear fellows!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Have you made note of my hair, Mr Naruhodo? An outright victory for science, you must agree!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... To be perfectly honest, so much happened yesterday that, well... ...I completely forgot about your little hair problem.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Hah! What to one man is a 'little hair problem'... ...is to another a day of drinking dubious potion after dubious potion. You have no idea how my stomach ails me this morning!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear! How awful for you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm afraid you only have yourself to blame, Mr Sholmes.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And good morning to you, Mr Reaper. I'm delighted to see you looking so full of vim.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">And I you. I see London's celebrated great detective is as active as ever.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Oh, you exaggerate, my dear fellow. Compared to my paltry engagements with a few trivial cases... ...the Reaper's overbearing presence is a far greater deterrent to the black roots of crime in our capital.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">And whilst I may not agree with your methods... ...there is at least one point on which I would readily commend you.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What an honour. And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Your eye for a good lawyer, sir.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">M-Mr Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">After all... ...behind this lawyer there is a very great mind. My own.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">I wish only to say that you should be prepared for quite a trial, Mr Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="???">Sorry to barge in...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Gina! <thought>What's that on her arm? It's a mourning band, I suppose...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Father! Shouldn't you be at the symposium?</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">It's been postponed. So I have some free time. I decided to come along with the police inspector to see our country's up-and-coming student in action.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Mikotoba">I shall be very interested to see the fruits of your studies over the past year.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it's an honour to have you here! <thought>Let's hope there are some fruits to see...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... 'Oddo...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh! ...Yes, Gina?</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Why d'you agree to this, eh? Why d'you take 'im on?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">This, this Reaper bloke... Everyone says it was 'im wot... ...wot killed the boss.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm sorry, Gina. But I just don't believe that.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Well if it weren't 'im, who was it?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know that...yet.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I don't care who calls 'im wot. The Reaper's just a name. 'E's just a person at the end o' the day. An' if it turns out it was 'im wot killed the boss...then God 'elp 'im!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... Fiery eyes indeed... Yes, the culprit deserves every ounce of your loathing.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">At least that may be some solace to the deceased.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">......... P-Please, 'Oddo... ...get whoever did this. For the boss.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Gina...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I 'ate feelin' this useless, but there's nuffin' I can do. So you've gotta find who done this and make the wretch pay!</line>
<line speaker="Bailiff">Counsel for the Defence! And the defendant! Court will be in session shortly. Make your way into the courtroom at once, please!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Alright then, here we go...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's time, Mr Naruhodo! Lord van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session. We are here to conduct the fair and just trial of the defendant, Barok van Zieks. Counsels for the defence and prosecution, are you ready to begin?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...The defence is ready, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The prosecution...is more than ready.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh, Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I've been wishing to see you in court again for so long, it feels... But I never pictured it happening like this. I never thought I'd be facing you behind the prosecution's bench.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The so-called 'Reaper of the Bailey'... ...has been a scourge like no other, undermining Her Majesty's justice system. Today we must uncover the truth behind this scourge.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In other words... ...this trial is going to be a lot more far-reaching than Inspector Gregson's murder.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">The truths revealed by these proceedings may have unpredictable repercussions through the judiciary. Accordingly, they are to be conducted as a closed trial, with no members of the public present. By Her Majesty's direct orders.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How will that work, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The burden of all arbitration and adjudication falls on my shoulders. Therefore, as you will see... ...the jurors' bench shall remain vacant today.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If no members of the public are present, might I ask who is currently occupying the gallery, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">They are members of the judiciary, here to witness proceedings and ensure an equitable trial.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Members of the judiciary...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh my...this is a very unusual trial already.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There is of course another, unprecedented aspect to these proceedings on which I must elaborate. The counsels for the prosecution and the defence are both aliens of Great Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... I believe it takes an outsider to see the truth sometimes. And as I stand here in this courtroom now, I'm quite certain... ...this is the reason why I had to come to Britain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Let us commence proceedings. Prosecutor Asogi...your opening statement, if you please.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Certainly, My Lord. The incident took place on 1st November at just after five o'clock in the afternoon. The location was a building of flats on Fresno Street on the outskirts of the city. The victim's body was discovered there in an old single-room rental property.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Inspector Tobias Gregson. A name known very well indeed to this court. Not least for his miraculous resolution of one of this country's grimmest cases ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The Professor case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How sure are you about the time of the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Several witnesses on the street outside heard the gunshot, and all have reported the same time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, that's what Gina told us, too. There were a number of witnesses.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I have here a plan of the room. The victim was found curled up in one corner. It's believed that he was shot from the front at point-blank range and died instantly.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... How has the range been determined?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There were scorch marks around the entry wound. Such marks are caused by the gunpowder used to fire the bullet. But powder hot enough to leave scorch marks is only ejected a few inches beyond the end of the barrel. In other words, it only happens when the target is at point-blank range.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see, yes. Thank you for the detailed explanation, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The murder weapon was found lying beside the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And have you managed to ascertain the owner of this firearm?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, My Lord. Not conclusively.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Bravo, Kazuma-sama... ...for not trying to use the gun as evidence when its provenance can't be proven.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Furthermore, My Lord... As I've explained, the revolver was fired at extremely close range. The bullet passed through the victim and struck the wall behind him. There is a candelabrum mounted on that wall... ...and the tip of one of the candles in it was found to have been blown off by the projectile.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We noticed that too, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, that's right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Thank you for the thorough report, Counsel. The setting of the crime is clear to me. You will submit the plan of the crime scene as evidence, please.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As you wish, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is this Fresno Street room Inspector Gregson's private abode?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, My Lord. The room is rented to a Mr Hugh Boone. But there is precious little furniture inside, and it is generally in a poor state of repair.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So what on earth was Gregson even doing there?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Presumably he was investigating some case or other...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When a policeman was informed of the gunshot from the witnesses and rushed to the scene... ...he found only the deceased inspector and the accused standing alongside holding the revolver. The attending officer arrested the accused on the spot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So...the details of the case are clear.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that case, the prosecution would like to call its first witness.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A name please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Naturally...the accused himself.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">L-Lord van Zieks?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As a prosecutor, he believes in the oath of office he's taken and will be compelled to tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, let the defendant take the witness stand!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So, witness...state your name and occupation for the court.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Barok van Zieks, Old Bailey prosecutor.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I presume, Lord van Zieks, that you heard Prosecutor Asogi's opening precis.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I did.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It is alleged that you were found at the scene of the crime... ...and that you were arrested by the arriving police officer. Can you confirm this?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then I'm sure the court would like to hear you explain some things away. Namely why you were there in the room on Fresno Street at the time in question. And what exactly took place.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I intend to explain away nothing. I will simply tell the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must say, Lord van Zieks, I never imagined this day would come. Or rather... ...I didn't want to imagine it would come. But since you became known as the Reaper... ...a part of me has been dreading it.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your formal testimony then, witness!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was investigating Gregson, and my inquiries had led me to that address.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That testimony is the whole truth?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...you heard a shot being fired in a room with no living occupants... ...and moments later a corpse somehow appeared before your eyes. Is that it? You're right, you haven't explained away anything. In fact that would barely qualify as an excuse.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I thought you were my mute apprentice. Yet it turns out you have a way with words... Prosecutor Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... It would appear to be a singular tale indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Singular isn't the word. It's laughable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's got into Kazuma? He's not behaving like himself at all...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, then. Counsel, you may begin your cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I was investigating Gregson, and my inquiries had led me to that address.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You were investigating the inspector? What on earth for?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... I'm not at liberty to say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'd identified a distinct possibility that Gregson was involved in a case I was investigating. Regrettably, though...he was killed before I could secure the proof I needed.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is the court to understand then, that on the day in question you followed the victim to the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...No. I was privy to his movements in advance.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I stole into his office in the Yard and consulted his diary. The address on Fresno Street was noted in the 5 p.m. entry.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You illegally entered the man's office? In Japan that alone would constitute a very serious offence.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As it does in Great Britain, I assure you. Is that not the case, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...I was aware of the possible consequences.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So, in summary, you were investigating the victim... ...and yet you refuse to tell the court why.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I didn't realise British prosecutors enjoyed such freedom to choose what to divulge under oath.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh... <thought>Why did I ever think I could defend this man?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When I first entered the room that day, it was dark inside and I saw no one.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Had you ever been to the address before?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, never. I only learnt of the place as a result of my investigations into Gregson's activities. There was no light inside when I entered, so it was all but impossible to make out anything.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But at 5 p.m. the sun would only just have gone down. It would still have been reasonably light outside.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The room has a window, but it was boarded shut. Very little light found its way into the room from outside, so it was extremely murky inside. I wouldn't have noticed if the victim was already lying on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">There was no artificial light in the room, you say? You're quite sure?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I'm quite sure that the part of the room where the body was found was very dark. I have a feeling there was a small oil lamp burning on the desk, though I couldn't say for certain.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Look, Mr Naruhodo... There is a small desk in the room just here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I remember. And there was an oil lamp on it. As well as the framed photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">When I entered the room, I closed the door behind me and started towards the desk to investigate.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what did you find?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Nothing. I never actually reached the desk.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">A moment later, I heard the gunshot. I spun around, and saw the revolver on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...who fired the gun?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I have no idea. I didn't see anybody else in the room.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But you say it was very dark in there?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Yes, that's right. All I can tell you is, I didn't sense another's presence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Aha! Then could it be... ...that the gunshot actually originated from somewhere outside the room?!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">No, that's out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Without doubt, the sound emanated from inside the room. I could smell the gunpowder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh, this is going from bad to worse...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And you say that's the point at which you noticed the revolver on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Correct. And I foolishly picked it up. That was carelessness on my part.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Presumably, then, the gunshot you heard came from the firearm that you somewhat hastily took in your hands.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">In point of fact, My Lord...I believe it did not.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The barrel of the revolver I picked up was cold, and there was no smell of spent powder.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But, but then...where on earth is the gun that WAS fired?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Whilst I would like to oblige you with an answer... ...I'm afraid I can't. I, too, would dearly like to know that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuuuuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Just as I picked the firearm up to examine it, the door flew open and I heard a man scream.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A man, you say? One of the witnesses, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right. One of the street merchants working on Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Who are these merchants?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A number of them had set up their stalls directly beneath the boarded window of the crime scene. A match-seller, a newsmonger and a pedlar. They've all given statements saying they heard the gunshot. And without thought of danger, they ran inside to see what had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes...Gina told us about that yesterday, didn't she?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They burst through the door with some force, it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">They did. And almost gave me a heart attack in the process.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But you're supposed to be the Reaper...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">The first man to come in immediately noticed the revolver in my hand and fled.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A policeman patrolling on Fresno Street heard the commotion... ...and was able to arrest the accused shortly after the incident occurred.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Anyway, the man's scream drew my attention in that direction.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">It was only then that the body of Inspector Gregson appeared before me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...what do you mean by that? In what way did the body 'appear'?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">I honestly can't explain it. But it's the truth. As far as I was concerned, the body hadn't been there until that point, and then suddenly...there it was.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you perhaps hear the sound of the victim falling to the ground just beforehand?</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">......... At that moment, what I heard... ...was the sound of the door flying open and the scream of the man who came inside first. Nothing more.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">After the man fled, I examined the body. I was stunned to find that it was Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Most curious circumstances indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">How the inspector was killed, or how his body seemed to appear out of nowhere... ...I have no idea.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So...that's Lord van Zieks's account.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Do you have any thoughts, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...mainly that it really doesn't ring true in all sorts of ways. Who fired the gun if there was nobody else there? And how did the corpse just appear in front of him?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">So...you think that Lord van Zieks is lying?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, I don't think that. I mean, if he was going to lie... ...I would expect him to have come up with a more credible story, wouldn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I completely agree. I think he genuinely doesn't know what really happened himself. So we must do what we can to fill in the gaps.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, first and foremost, we need more information!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Surely the court has heard enough!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">My Lord, the cross-examination has clearly revealed... ...that the accused, Barok van Zieks...is lying on multiple fronts!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... What is THAT supposed to mean?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Good gracious, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In his testimony just now... ...he claims that he failed to notice the victim's body because the room was dark.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That's correct.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No...that's impossible. As proven by this candelabrum.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How does that prove anything?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If you examine the tip of the long candle, you can see it has been blown off by a powerful impact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One would assume that the projectile from the firearm passed through the victim and struck the candle.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The problem comes when you consider the other two candles, which are clearly of a different length.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, I can see that only the candle that appears to have been struck by the bullet is long.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">We could reasonably expect someone to have lit all three candles together. Which begs the question of why only one has ended up longer than the others.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That...must be because that particular candle was extinguished when the others were still burning... ...Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right. When the candle was hit by the bullet, it obviously went out. But the other two candles would still have been burning. So the fact is... ...the victim's body would have been illuminated by the light still thrown by the candelabrum! And the accused's claim that he couldn't see the body... clearly contradicts those facts!</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And now to the next lie.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's more?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The accused also claims never to have visited the scene of the crime before.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">That's the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that almost empty room, the police discovered something very unusual. A board covered from top to bottom in police documents and newspaper cuttings.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, that's right. We saw it, too.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It goes without saying that the contents of the police documents cannot be divulged. However... ...they included a number of reports from various historical cases. The oldest of which...was from ten years ago.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ten years ago? This is starting to sound familiar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And there is a common thread linking all of the documents on that board.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed? What is this common thread, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They all relate to cases prosecuted in court by Barok van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">All of them?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And furthermore...all those cases are ones in which the defendant was acquitted.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Interestingly, none of those defendants are alive today. Because all of them have been sent to their graves...by the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh no...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In short! That dingy little room... ...is the Reaper's secret hideout...and his base of operations!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The, the Reaper's hideout?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And yet the Reaper would claim never to have been to his own secret hideout? No one would believe that. No, the truth is...we've been looking at this backwards.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Backwards? Explain, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Inspector Gregson was investigating the identity of the Reaper. When he discovered the location of the man's secret hideout...he was killed. As I'm sure everyone can imagine...by the Reaper's hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! Very well. I hereby state the current opinion of the court. Barok van Zieks is an outstanding prosecutor who has rendered great service to his country. However, it is with deep regret that I must concur with Prosecutor Asogi's contention... ...that the defendant's testimony exhibits a number of stark inconsistencies with the known facts.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">All I have done is state the truth as I know it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma's done a brilliant job as ever. He's drawing on his experience as a defence attorney to build his prosecution case...and it's formidable.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel... ...you will submit the board that you just showed the court as evidence. I believe it to be fundamental in establishing the facts surrounding the Reaper's existence.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Thank you, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And now, the prosecution would like to call new witnesses to the stand. Witnesses who saw events unfold on the day in question.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">There are details of a whole raft of cases dating back years on here, aren't there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This paper from ten years ago is browning with age, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Out of interest, the most recent thing appears to be this newspaper cutting here.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh. It's the same Red-Headed League advertisement that Mr Sholmes had picked out.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And do you remember? There was a red hairpiece at the scene, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Was Inspector Gregson an exponent of the Red-Headed League, then?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh. What's this...? Mr Naruhodo! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes. It's a smudge of some kind. In fact... ...it looks just like a handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the colour... That's blood, isn't it? Oh dear... How disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Oh. What's this...? Mr Naruhodo! Look!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh yes. It's a smudge of some kind. In fact... ...it looks just like a handprint.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the colour... That's blood, isn't it? Oh dear... How disturbing...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">They were mentioned in the previous testimony too, if you remember.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. The street sellers who heard the gunshot and went running into the room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, lead the witnesses in! The defendant may step down from the witness stand.</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Certainly, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...witnesses. State your names and occupations for the court.</line>
<line speaker="???">Names?! We don't use names. Far too fancy for the likes of uz.</line>
<line speaker="???">We're just free an' easy. Sell what we like, live where we wanna live...</line>
<line speaker="???">I g-give them all a vacant stare as they w-walk down Fresno, and spin a few w-words into a verse for them.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah... Would I be right in assuming that all three of you make your living by selling wares on the street?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Hehe, everyone calls me Gossip. I sell jaunty little titbits to passers-by, you know.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Jaunty little titbits?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Got an absolute smasher for you, sir. Right up your ginnel, it is! Sixpence is the price, and not a penny less!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Wait! You're, you're actually trying to sell it to me now?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Oh, c'mon sir! Don't tell me you're not interested!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Try the man.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Give him the money and see what it is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pay the man, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, alright, sixpence it is.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">You won't regret it, sir! Now, got your listenin' ears on? Just between uz...a young couple on Sleight Street have just had twins!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........  Um...is that it?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No, that's not it. It's gossip, in't it? It wants to spread. But that bit's up to you and your mouth, of course. I've got more, you know. Want another juicy one? Sixpence a piece, it is. If you're curious...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I am curious, yes. About what's going on just under that fat bottom lip of yours. Namely that unusual bruise or whatever it is that's poking out from under your collar...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What about the next witness, then? What name do you go by and what do you sell?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Me? I'm Venus. That's what everyone calls me. Funny, innit? I sell these lovely little fireworks to all the local school kids. Sixpence a pop! What d'you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You weren't exaggerating with 'little'. Do they actually sell?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh yeah. The second years can't get enough of my Venus firecrackers. 'Specially when I tell 'em that if they get a hundred they could blow up the school!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Not the most savoury of ideas, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">What d'you say then, eh? Wanna part with sixpence for a pop?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait, what?! You, you want me to buy one?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Tell you what, I'll let you in on a little secret: If you get a hundred of 'em, you could blow up the whole courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Try the woman.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Give her the money and see if she's right!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Pay the woman, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, alright, I'll buy one.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Lovely stuff! Right then...this is something a bit extra, just for you: The Venus Special! Only six 'undred pence!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">S-Six hundred!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">It's a hundred of my regular fireworks. Nothing 'little' about that, is there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And there'd be nothing little about the punishment if I blew up the Old Bailey, either.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And the last witness... What name do you go by and what do you sell?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you had an idea, Mr Naruhodo? You're staring at the end of the string of fireworks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry. It's just that it's the 'Venus Special'. I was wondering what six hundred pence worth of fireworks would sound like.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Shall we find out?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? B-But...she said it could blow up the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... A-Alright, that was a fairly sizeable bang.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My ears are still ringing, Mr Naruhodo. It sounded almost exactly like...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Have you had an idea, Mr Naruhodo? You're staring at the end of the string of fireworks.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry. It's just that it's the 'Venus Special'. I was wondering what six hundred pence worth of fireworks would sound like.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... Shall we find out?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What? B-But...she said it could blow up the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... A-Alright, that was a fairly sizeable bang.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">My ears are still ringing, Mr Naruhodo. It sounded almost exactly like...</line>
<line speaker="???">I'm a th-thinker me. Think all sorts of thoughts. I think, therefore I am. I am, therefore I think...I think. Because I stand there on the street, w-watchin' the w-world go on about me, they call me 'The Observator'.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Get out if it, old man! Everyone calls you Sandwich and you know it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...you don't actually sell anything?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">A p-p-problem shared is a problem halved, as they say. I give advice, I do. And think w-what it means. I d-don't actually sell anything, no...come to think of it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Pity.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No more purchases today...please.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, we have quite a cast here, it seems.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They conduct their business on Fresno Street from morning until night, My Lord. And always in the same place: directly adjacent to the crime scene.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I see. And thus they heard the gunshot, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not only that, but they very bravely ran inside to see what was going on and witnessed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well I'll be beggared, I thought! ...Just between uz.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Venus de Milo, what am I to do? What a terrible thing I saw!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">W-What I think is...if all w-what we see is light and shadow, p-playing with our eyes...is any of it real?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The court will hear the formal testimony of these three witnesses now. You will describe in detail what you witnessed and heard at the time of the incident.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">We saw the whole thing from start to finish, we did. Everything from the moment they went in the building.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">It was less than a minute after the Reaper had gone inside that we all 'eard a big bang.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Seems to m-me that quick-to-talk is quick-to-walk. Gossip couldn't wait to go and see what had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I ran into the room and there he woz. The Reaper, gun in hand, standin' over the dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I was scared 'alf to death, me. So I ran off to find a copper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If these witnesses were there the whole day and saw everything... ...who did they see going inside the building?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Only the victim, Inspector Gregson, and the accused, Barok van Zieks.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I've seen pictures of that Reaper in the paper. I know what he looks like. And just between uz...folk love stories like this. I've made meself a tidy sum already.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But wait! The room was just one of several flats in the building. Someone from another flat could have done it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">All those flats on Fresno Street are unoccupied.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">'Course they are. They're small, damp, dirty and expensive to boot.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The room in which the inspector was found is the only property in the building that's currently leased.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And we know the leaseholder's name, don't we. It's...Hugh Boone.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... The testimony the court has just heard would appear to leave little room for doubt. It's becoming increasingly difficult to see how anyone other than the defendant could have committed the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Thank you for your candour, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel for the Defence, you may proceed to cross-examine the witnesses.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, My Lord! <thought>In a closed court like this without a jury, the judge is the only person whose opinion matters. I have to break down this testimony. Somehow!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">We saw the whole thing from start to finish, we did. Everything from the moment they went in the building.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say 'they', who do you mean exactly? Inspector Gregson and the defendant, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I suppose so. The likes of uz don't know the names of the high and mighty. But I'll tell you one thing...it was the old Reaper that went in last, that's for sure and certain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just behind Inspector Gregson? Did they arrive at the same time as each other?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No no, not at all! The first fella must have gone inside a good fifteen minutes before we heard that gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim arrived fifteen minutes before?! Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Am I sure? Am I sure?! Doz it seem likely that I'd have forgotten a fella with bright red hair like that, doz it?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Yeah, 'is hair really were red, weren't it? Redder than my flamin' fireworks, even.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">That, that fiery red mop's still b-burnt on the inside of my eyelids, it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait a minute! You're saying the man was a red-head?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Weren't you listenin', chum? Aye, he woz a red-head. And he had a big trunk with him, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Inspector Gregson's hair isn't red. Not by any stretch of the imagination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems likely that the person you saw wasn't in fact Inspector Gregson at all, but some other third party.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No. I hate to break it to you, but the witnesses are correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just have a look at this photograph of the victim taken at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes, that's... <thought>That's Inspector Gregson alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...a red hairpiece.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course! We saw one on the floor when we investigated the scene, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still refuse to believe Inspector Gregson wore a hairpiece, though... <thought>So then why on earth would he have been wearing something like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...the colour does seem to suit the man, one might say... The photograph will be submitted as evidence, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what became of the trunk that the red-headed victim was supposedly carrying?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I was informed that no trunk was found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it just disappeared?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">What, do you expect uz to have been watchin' the buildin' every second, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">We definitely saw 'im in the dock goin' in, though. No question about that!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say 'they', who do you mean exactly? Inspector Gregson and the defendant, Lord van Zieks?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I suppose so. The likes of uz don't know the names of the high and mighty. But I'll tell you one thing...it was the old Reaper that went in last, that's for sure and certain.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just behind Inspector Gregson? Did they arrive at the same time as each other?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No no, not at all! The first fella must have gone inside a good fifteen minutes before we heard that gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim arrived fifteen minutes before?! Are you sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Am I sure? Am I sure?! Doz it seem likely that I'd have forgotten a fella with bright red hair like that, doz it?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Yeah, 'is hair really were red, weren't it? Redder than my flamin' fireworks, even.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">That, that fiery red mop's still b-burnt on the inside of my eyelids, it is.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wait a minute! You're saying the man was a red-head?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Weren't you listenin', chum? Aye, he woz a red-head. And he had a big trunk with him, as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But Inspector Gregson's hair isn't red. Not by any stretch of the imagination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems likely that the person you saw wasn't in fact Inspector Gregson at all, but some other third party.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No. I hate to break it to you, but the witnesses are correct.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just have a look at this photograph of the victim taken at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Y-Yes, that's... <thought>That's Inspector Gregson alright.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And...a red hairpiece.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Of course! We saw one on the floor when we investigated the scene, didn't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I still refuse to believe Inspector Gregson wore a hairpiece, though... <thought>So then why on earth would he have been wearing something like that?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...the colour does seem to suit the man, one might say... The photograph will be submitted as evidence, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what became of the trunk that the red-headed victim was supposedly carrying?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...I was informed that no trunk was found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it just disappeared?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">What, do you expect uz to have been watchin' the buildin' every second, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">We definitely saw 'im in the dock goin' in, though. No question about that!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">It was less than a minute after the Reaper had gone inside that we all 'eard a big bang.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">By which presumably you mean the gunshot?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I sell these little things, don't I? How would I know what a gunshot sounds like? But I've always thought it probably sounds a bit like this... doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you say that you heard the noise almost as soon as you saw the defendant here enter the building?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">That's right. It was almost straight away. 'Bang!' it went. Just like that.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well he's the Reaper, in't he? It's what the French call a fait accompli. When the Reaper's around, people are goin' in the ground! I mean, that's what he doz, in't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think we get the message.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Reaper couldn't allow the inspector to live after he'd discovered his secret hideout. There can be no clearer motive for the crime.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm...yes... It's certainly an eminently credible motive.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Great.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And at that point, you ran inside. Is that correct?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Seems to m-me that quick-to-talk is quick-to-walk. Gossip couldn't wait to go and see what had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So, when Gossip ran to see what had happened, did you go, too?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">W-Well me... I'm a b-bit hampered, see. All the signs are that, that I c-can't move very well.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You were a way behind, presumably. With that sandwich board around your neck and that big sign in your hand.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What a great burden you bear. Pardon me for asking, Mr, erm...Sandwich, but... ...is it possible you and I have met before?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">...! I-I'm not anybody, me. The signs are w-what make me who I am right now. I sign, therefore I am.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you weren't employed as an omnibus driver just under a year ago then?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I might be mistaken, but I believe his trembling has intensified, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. He's clearly been through a lot.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">'Turn down King Henry Street and the Black Widowers Arms is just there.'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear. You've made him hide behind his sign.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Life is full of surprises...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I ran into the room and there he woz. The Reaper, gun in hand, standin' over the dead body!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So then you were the first person to arrive on the scene. Is that right?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">That I woz! Kicked the door open like a professional, I did! And yelled out, 'What's goin' off 'ere?!'</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Lord van Zieks claims all he heard was a man's scream, though.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And was it dark inside the room?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No, not dark at all! There were candles burnin' on the wall.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really?!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">And there was a fella collapsed on the floor. Just between uz...it's the first thing I noticed when I got inside.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah. I, I see... <thought>Even though Lord van Zieks claims not to have seen any such lights on the wall...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">The next thing I noticed was someone standin' right beside the body.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The accused, Barok van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">That's right! The pale-faced Reaper himself! I woz a little shocked, I won't deny it. But I'm no lily-livered coward. I stood my ground and gave that Reaper a cold, hard stare myself!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you have something to add, Mr Sandwich?!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">......... There's, there's really n-n-nothing to me. Empty in the head, I am. Just two slices with no middle. S-So I don't know what you could w-w-want with me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I think that maybe you just remembered something? Having heard Mr Gossip's last statement, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">W-What I think is...we're all nothings really. We try to d-dress ourselves up as something else, but at the end of the day, w-we're all just street sellers.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">That's enough out of you, Sandwich. Keep your trap shut now. Unless you want uz to make you into a real sandwich!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">W-When he saw the Reaper, he f-f-fell clean over on his backside!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...That's it?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Oh, you rotten beggar! I told you to keep that a secret!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">He screamed, he did. Screamed and s-scrambled off on all fours. ...That's all I w-w-wanted to say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Gossip! Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">The floor was dead slippery, that's why. Planted my hand in a filthy pool of blood, didn't I? Yuck!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?! <thought>A pool of blood?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">But listen here! Even when I woz sprawled on the floor... ...I still kept giving that Reaper a cold, hard stare! And don't you forget it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let's just go back a little. Did you say you got blood on your hand?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I, I did, aye. Happens to the best of uz at times, dozn't it? So I was scared! So I slipped over! ...We can keep it just between uz, can't we?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, Mr Gossip! I'm going to have to ask you to add that information to your formal testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Oh... If I must.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witness will amend his testimony to include the aforementioned details at once.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And was there anyone else in the room at the time?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No, of course not. Not at first. But then this old stiff came waddlin' along behind me, of course. Only him, mind.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I can't handle stairs so well, as you can imagine. Especially on the w-w-way up.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you couldn't have just failed to see someone?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">It was a bit dingy in there, I grant you. But there were the candles on the wall. And the lamp on the table.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">There was n-nowhere anyone c-could have been hiding. You m-mark my eyes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I slipped over and got blood on my hand, so I quickly wiped it off on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You wiped your hand on the floor?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well...who wants blood on his hand, eh? Horrible stuff. And they might have thought I'd done it. Hmph! No ta!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you didn't think that might be a problem?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Doz it really matter if I left a few grubby handprints on the floor? They'll get cleaned up in the end, won't they? Don't make such a fuss, that's the message from all of uz!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Is something wrong, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, My Lord. I didn't remember anything in the report about a bloody handprint on the floor, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">D-Don't come at me with all that! You can't intimidate me! I know what I did! I wiped it off! On the floor! The blood!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>I wonder... Could that be what happened...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't have all the answers yet... ...but I think we may have just uncovered a vital clue!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Venus">I was scared 'alf to death, me. So I ran off to find a copper.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you didn't run into the room with your friends?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">......... I'm not that sort of girl.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I'm a timid little thing, me. I was too scared to go in there.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, right... I see.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Old Lippy and the 'Wich ran in there, an' then I 'eard a sort of old lady scream.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well that wozn't me, I swear. If I were a gentleman, I'd stake my honour on it.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I wondered what on earth was goin' on.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which is when you went to find a policeman?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">And I ran into a copper as soon as I turned the corner. So I brought him straight back to the place. ...Didn't I do well, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Just between uz...that copper's eyes nearly popped out of his head when he saw the Reaper.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I've n-n-never felt more uncomfortable in, in all my life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And the defendant was arrested on the spot, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Considering the catalogue of killings the Reaper had carried out... ...it was a particularly inauspicious end.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...If I can't find any holes in this testimony...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid the judge will give a ruling of guilty, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The truth is, though, their combined testimony is fairly damning.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Unfortunately, there don't seem to be any obvious problems with their statements, do there?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Still...if Lord van Zieks really is innocent, then I'm almost certain... ...that we'll find something in there that doesn't quite add up.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">You don't think... ...that one of these three could be the true culprit, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't know. But what I do know... ...is that there's more to this case that has yet to be brought to light!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you wiped off the blood from your hand on the floor of the room... Are you quite sure about that?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well, well what else d'you expect me to have done, eh? Doz it really matter?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The police found no such handprint on the floor during their investigations. What exactly is the defence asserting?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you listen, you'll find out...Prosecutor Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Certainly, there was no bloody handprint found...on the floor.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What are you trying to say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There was a handprint in blood left very clearly at the scene... ...on the back of this noticeboard.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Ah...ah...AAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah yes, indeed. Indisputably a handprint in the distinctive colour of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Aye, you're dead right! That's my right hand! I'd know it anywhere!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The witness very definitely testified that he wiped his hand on the floor. Any handprints on the back of the board are irrelevant!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not if the board itself had fallen over onto the floor. In that case, it's quite possible for the witness's handprint to have ended up there.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Just look at the floor plan of the room. The noticeboard was in the opposite corner of the room to the victim, and in an upright position. Even if it had somehow been toppled and was lying on the floor at the time... ...it would have been a considerable distance from the body.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I fell over when I came across the body. So I woz basically right next to the corpse. Not on the other side of the room!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words, the defence's assertion is contradictory!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...it is.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a very definite contradiction here...for which there must be a reason.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I take it that you've formulated a proper hypothesis, Counsel? Regarding this apparent discrepancy between the witness's account and the handprint found at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I have, My Lord. This discrepancy between the witness's account and the location of the handprint is explained by...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If Mr Gossip ended up with blood on his hand and wiped it off on the floor as he says... ...it must have left behind a mark somewhere. Just as a mark has been left behind on the back of the noticeboard.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The prosecution has already established that the handprint on the board is irrelevant.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Exactly! Which means there must be another handprint somewhere!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No! The police report made no mention of a handprint anywhere on the floor! And I understand that you've examined the scene in person, too. If you'd come across something the police had missed... how do you explain the cold sweat?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite. The defence counsel's cold sweat is a sure indication that a penalty is due.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That sweat was just from the warm-up.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There should be a bloody handprint on the floor. So where did it go...? I'm ready to give the proper explanation to the court now, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The witness claims to have wiped his bloody hand on the floor, yet no sign of that remains at the scene. The simplest explanation is that the witness is lying.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just because it's the simplest explanation doesn't make it the correct one...Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Positing perjury simply because it suits you... You bring shame on your Japanese heritage!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I would ask you not to oversimplify matters again, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't remember fostering that kind of simplistic thinking in you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Since when were you my father? Anyway, I was always taught to consider all possibilities.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then show me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There should be a bloody handprint on the floor. So where did it go...? I'm ready to give the proper explanation to the court now, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The real contradiction here is the handprint itself, not where it was found. As the court can see...it's upside down.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! So it is! If the witness had put his hand against the board, the fingers should be pointing upwards.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What, what does that tell us?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It tells one simple fact! When this handprint was made... ...the board must have been lying on the floor as I previously suggested. Which means that after the incident...it must have been moved!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're claiming that somebody moved the noticeboard after the shooting? Then tell the court who!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I, I don't know that yet! But the point is... ...when you consider all the testimony we've heard so far, we can now be very clear on one point!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And that would be...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The position of the noticeboard at the time of the incident, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So, Counsel, I must ask you to clarify your assertion for the court. At the time of the incident, where do you maintain the noticeboard was situated?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness! Hm, no...I'm afraid I don't quite see your logic.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm disappointed, Ryunosuke. In Japan, we're taught to have patience and respect for our elders. So until His Lordship sees your logic, you will know your place and not move from that spot!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">UAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">How brilliant of Kazuma-sama! That almost sounded unreasonable at first, but he was just thinking of you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Unreasonable? Try unfathomable. Anyway, I think I have the answer now. I know my place! ...Or rather, I know the board's place!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is the only possible location!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Immediately adjacent to the doorway...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the court would think back to the testimony given by the defendant earlier... ...he said that when he entered the room it was dark, and he couldn't see the body.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">By 'eck!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If the noticeboard had been here, the body would have been completely hidden from view. And the light from the candles would have been blocked, making the room appear darker.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But the accused also claims that the victim's body simply 'appeared' before him.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's true. Or, in his precise words...</line>
<line speaker="Van Zieks">Just as I picked the firearm up to examine it, the door flew open and I heard a man scream. It was only then that the body of Inspector Gregson appeared before me.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I don't know about callin' it a 'scream', but he woz talkin' about me and no mistake. Cos it woz me that kicked the door open.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you look again at the floor plan... ...consider what would happen if the door to the room was thrown open with force.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That, that can't...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The door struck the noticeboard, knocking it over, and making the victim's body visible.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My client has told nothing but the truth! He has simply described what he saw.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Argh!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Counsel, how has this not come to light before now?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">After the incident, somebody must have righted the board and moved it... ...into the position where the police, myself and my colleague saw it when investigating the room.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Witness! What have you to say for yourself?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Whaaaaaat? Me, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You and your fellows were there at the scene before anybody else. It goes without saying that you must know something about the position of the noticeboard!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The witnesses in the stand will testify again. You will each explain exactly what you did upon arriving at the scene of the crime!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Eh, stop lookin' over your glasses at me! I get the message.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I don't know anythin' about that there noticeboard! I just wiped my hand on it, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well don't look at me. I 'aven't got a clue about it. I was doin' business with some second years at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I don't know anything about anything. I'm j-just a bystander, me. J-Just a sign at the crossroads of life.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">It woz that Reaper, I bet. He's got a face that screams 'board'.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I c-can't see how this changes anything anyway. The detective still died w-when we heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... So none of you can elaborate further...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Shaken by the crime they witnessed, and with only the light of a few candles and an oil lamp by which to see... ...we can't expect these witnesses to be able to give a more precise account of what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">That's right, yeah. It don't pay to expect too much.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">It's m-man's endless quest for knowledge that's d-d-destroying the world. That's w-what I think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you? Really.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In any case, as the testimony shows... ...even if the noticeboard was moved by somebody following the incident, it makes no difference. When the gunshot rang out, the accused was the only person at the scene.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In short, the only person who could possibly have committed this crime...is Barok van Zieks! None of this wrangling over the board changes that simple fact.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Quite so, quite so. Does the defence still wish to cross-examine the witnesses despite the circumstances?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Most certainly, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. Then you may proceed, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I don't know anythin' about that there noticeboard! I just wiped my hand on it, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you admit that it was the board you wiped your bloody hand on?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Admit it? What's to admit? It's there plain as day for all to see: a smashing print of my right hand!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Perhaps you wanted to hide that handprint... ...so you righted the noticeboard and pushed it into the corner, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No no! Imagine the weight of that great lump! Do I look like a powerful and well-nurtured man?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well did you see anybody else moving the board?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I've got nerves of steel, I can tell you, but even I have my limits. There woz a body on the floor in front of me, and the grim Reaper himself standin' over it. And there woz precious little light inside, either. My bottom lip was all aquiver.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words...this witness is unable to give definite testimony on that point.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, yes...so it would seem.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well don't look at me. I 'aven't got a clue about it. I was doin' business with some second years at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">When you say you were doing business with them, you mean you were selling them fireworks?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Yeah, what else? There's the Priory School just round the corner, see. Those cheeky little so-and-sos 'ave got a plan to blow their school to kingdom come.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Haah...</line>
<line speaker="Venus">So I've been tellin' on them. Lettin' their teachers know what they're up to.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oh...you have?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Yeah, wouldn't want anyone to get 'urt. So I let the school know the kids are playin' with dodgy toys. Then - praise the Lord - the teachers take all the fireworks off 'em. And then - praise the Lord again - the kids all come back to me to buy more. Everyone's 'appy, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...What a racket.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">'Course. And sometimes the teachers give me a little bonus to thank me for lettin' 'em know. It's a busy old life, sellin' explosives.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Venus is a guileful goddess indeed...</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well, tellin' bare-faced lies is kind of my thing, really. I'm ever so good at it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something wrong, Mr Sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">If, if I said it was, could we just l-leave it at that? Would that be the end of it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...no. Did Miss Venus's statement just now bring something to mind, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">......... Philosophical thoughts. Deep, philosophical thoughts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hm?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">L-Let's say there was a great liar. And that g-great liar said, without batting an eye... 'Tellin' bare-faced lies is kind of my thing. I'm ever so good at it.' W-Would those words of hers be a lie, too? Or the truth? In which case...she's n-not a liar. Ooh, it's a h-hellish paradox, that one. Don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I'm not entirely sure, to be honest. But...it seems to me you're suggesting Miss Venus has been lying...are you?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">..................</line>
<line speaker="Venus">What are you on about, old man? Tryin' to cause trouble, are you? Keep on like that... ...and I'll wrap your whole body in firecrackers and set 'em off. That'll give you somethin' to tremble about!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You have a startlingly disturbing mind behind that sweet and innocent face, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So Miss Venus HAS lied in her testimony! Is that what you're saying, Mr Sandwich?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">......... Well...if it m-means I'll be burnin' in hellfire for the r-rest of my days...so be it. Yes, that's what I'm saying.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Can you elaborate, please, sir?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">......... Old b-blabbermouth here headed for the r-room where the g-gunshot seemed to come from... ...but there w-w-was someone else who crept up the stairs b-behind him, too. That's right! That rotten liar over there!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Heh heh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean to say... ...that you did in fact betake yourself to the scene of the crime after all?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">......... What did I tell you, eh? I said I was good at tellin' bare-faced lies, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, you mentioned it...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well... ...that revelation rocked the whole courtroom, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Who knew firecrackers packed such a punch?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">So you did indeed visit the scene of the crime, did you, young lady? Good grief!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well, now you come to mention it... ...I suppose perhaps I do clearly remember climbin' the stairs to the room, yeah.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Either you clearly remember it or you don't.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...I shall consider a fitting punishment for this perjurious act later. For the time being, you will immediately amend your testimony to reflect the truth!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh yes, My Lord. Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...scary.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...The important point is, you didn't go inside the room where the inspector was killed, isn't that right?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Definitely not. Wouldn't 'ave dreamed of it, would I?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Maybe I did sneak along behind Gossip and 'ave a little peek into the room where it all 'appened.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You make a habit of lying, do you, Miss Venus?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well...I s'pose so. ...I don't really know, to be fair. If you want my advice, though, I'd take everythin' I say with a big pinch of salt.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Alright, but you did in fact go to the room where the victim was killed on the day in question, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! As if I would! I can't think of anythin' more terrifyin'!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The truth, please.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well alright, just a bit then. I mean, a girl my age is curious about stuff, ya know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you touch anything at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! As if I would! I mean, there was a dead body on the floor!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The truth, please.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well alright, just a bit then. I 'ad a look to see if there was anythin' I could sell. So I did give the place a once-over. But it was nothin' to write 'ome about.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right. Now, I hesitate to ask, but... ...you didn't move the noticeboard by any chance, did you?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! As if I would touch anythin' like that! Just a few bits of loose change is all I 'ad!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The truth, please.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well alright then. I thought there might be somethin' worth 'avin' underneath it. So I blasted the flippin' thing- Sorry, flipped the blasted thing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're, you're telling us... ...that you DID move that board?!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I think that did slip out, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Wha...? You daft barmpot!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I don't believe it... The girl doesn't think.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So! Did you find anything then? Something that you might have taken, perhaps? To sell?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! I should be so lucky! In my imagination-</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The TRUTH now!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">...I might 'ave found this old pocket watch under the noticeboard, I s'pose. But a bit o' junk like this can't be worth much, if you ask-</line>
<line speaker="???">AAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">So it was you, was it? You're the one wot took it!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">G-Gina?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Young lady! May I remind you where you are?!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That watch... That watch there... That was a present to Inspector Gregson from the Yard for a big case 'e solved ten years ago!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The Professor case, no doubt.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss used to wind it up every evenin' wivout fail when 'e was waitin' for 'is grub to come at the pub.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I see.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">I swiped it off 'im once an' blimey was 'e upset! 'E gave me a right earful. Said 'e 'adn't missed a day in the last ten years, polishin' it an' windin' it. It meant the world to 'im, that watch did.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Possibly not the best thing to go diving for, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Venus">It's not all that, though. I took it to Jabez's that night to ask 'ow much it was worth. But the old dealer wouldn't touch it. Wouldn't give me a penny for it. Said it wasn't workin'. Knocked about and worthless he called it.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Agh! I knew I should've lifted it!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That watch must be submitted as evidence at once!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! Just, just so long as you promise to give it back when we're done!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Not a chance! I'll swipe it from ya if you try to get your grubby mitts on it again!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's enough. Hand the watch to the bailiff forthwith!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Now now, children, watch your manners...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Good Lord! The glass appears to be broken.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">More than likely, it shattered when the inspector was shot.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">It doesn't tick any more, either. Which is why Jabez didn't want it. What a waste, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, indeed. It appears to have stopped at the hour of five.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Exactly when the gunshot was heard, then...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Which supports the prosecution's claim, of course...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well, it would appear that the mystery of the moving noticeboard has been solved at least.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And as predicted, it had very little bearing on the case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now then, continue with your cross-examination, please, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You...certainly know how to lie...</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, it was nothin' really. Just a little porky.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">With not-so-little implications...</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Did you know? Everythin' in the world apart from the truth is a big fat lie! ...If you believe that, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'm lost.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">As am I. This desecration of the truth is really rather disturbing. I think perhaps we should move on to the next witness, hm?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The glass over the face really is badly cracked, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">What a shame when the inspector clearly looked after it so carefully.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I imagine Mr Sholmes could repair it, don't you?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I should think so.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's very adept at things like this. A useful man to have around, in fact.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">But kindly remember that he's a great detective, Mr Naruhodo! Not an odd-job man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's a tiny little stub sticking out from this small hole here, look.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I suppose there must have been a little knob or something on that for setting the time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In that case, seeing as we know the inspector took such good care of this watch... ...it probably broke when the incident occurred, didn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes! Of course!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which could mean that there's a small part of the watch still at the scene, maybe...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah... There's a tiny little keyhole here. Can you see?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh yes. That's probably for the winder used to wind up the mechanism.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It looks a little unusual, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, you'd need just the right key to wind it, I imagine.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Why do I feel as though I've seen something...? Something a bit like a key that's about the right size to fit in this hole...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It would be wonderful if we had the key... Let's check carefully over what we've already found.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is where the little policeman figurine's key goes in to wind the watch. Winding it up every single day for ten years without fail...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, it was obviously a thing of great importance to the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Or a reminder of the past, lest he forget...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Miss Susato! Do you think perhaps this key... ...could be the key for Inspector Gregson's watch?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh! Yes, it could be! Let's try it at once! There's not a moment to lose!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I knew it! A perfect fit!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">And look! The inspector's watch has started going again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah, so it has obviously just not been wound up, that's all.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What is it, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...if the watch isn't actually broken after all... ...I have a feeling it could have profound implications! .........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>She's deep in thought now. Perhaps I'd better start thinking deeply, too...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So this is the little key used to wind the inspector's pocket watch.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It was a mystery at first. Why it should be a policeman, I mean. But it's because it was a gift from Scotland Yard, in recognition of Inspector Gregson's hard work.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...If its head did fall off from overuse, it might seem a little inappropriate, don't you think?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">That's...the British sense of humour for you, I think.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The helmet of this charming policeman appears to be a little worse for wear.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm not convinced about the 'charming' part, but yes, you're right... ...the head part looks like it's been fairly heavily manhandled. Which stands to reason, really, doesn't it? I mean, it gets turned around and around every day.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...I hope it doesn't fall off in the end.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I don't know anything about anything. I'm j-just a bystander, me. J-Just a sign at the crossroads of life.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But...you did go to see what had happened in the room, didn't you?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Fresno Street is my whole w-w-world. It's all I know. And I know all of it. I have to make it my b-business to know, if I want to h-hold my sign up high.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you did go to see what had happened.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">It's not the d-destination that's important...it's h-how you get there, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did you notice the noticeboard in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">...If you think about it, we're b-both the same species, aren't we? Both different members of the sign family. So if I'd spotted it, I m-might have tried to t-trip it up out of a sense of rivalry, I admit.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Someone really needs to tell you that you're Homo sapiens not Homo signiens...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Does that mean that you didn't notice the board?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I can only r-r-repeat what I said before: I, I don't know anything about anything. I'm j-just a bystander, me. J-Just a sign at the crossroads of life.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...In which case, just who was responsible for moving the noticeboard?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">It woz that Reaper, I bet. He's got a face that screams 'board'.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What exactly do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Oh, come on now, don't tell uz you've not noticed. He looks like he hates everythin' in the world, that fella. But not noticeboards. They're the one thing he likes. You can see it in his eyes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I can't say I'd ever noticed.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I'll tell you one thing for free, though: I never took my eyes off that man on the floor. Or off the Reaper. Not for a second.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well, I was that scared, I couldn't. You never know what a fiend like that might do if you look away, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... If you didn't take your eyes off the defendant... ...you should be able to confirm categorically whether or not he was the one who moved the noticeboard.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">......... Aye, that I can. The Reaper did nothin' of the sort. I can swear to that! I couldn't have missed it if he'd heaved the thing upright again and dragged it into the corner!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Right...glad we've cleared that up.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What happened to the face that screams 'board'?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I feel your pain, Kazuma.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I c-can't see how this changes anything anyway. The detective still died w-when we heard the gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It was five o'clock in the afternoon that you all heard the loud bang, wasn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Maybe the n-noticeboard fell over, or maybe it d-didn't. Maybe I fell over, or m-m-maybe I didn't... But the Reaper's f-fate is sealed either way, because of that gunshot w-we all heard. So your fate's sealed, too.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My fate?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">That's right. The defence is fated to lose. And the prosecution to win.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>In other words, it all hinges on that single gunshot. So if I could just find some problem with that part of their story...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It may be possible to change all our fates!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Of course...n-none of that changes the fact that I heard what I heard...does it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not much to go on...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">As you've pointed out, Mr Naruhodo... ...there's no question that the noticeboard was moved. So somebody must have done it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But it did happen after the event, so... ...maybe Kazuma is right and it's not relevant to the case.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">But it seems to have been deliberately positioned so as to hide the body from view. So I feel sure that there's some deeper significance to all of this.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I know what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I've no doubt there are more clues to be uncovered. You're on the right track, I can feel it. So follow your instincts!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Alright, then.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm afraid that's not necessarily the case.</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Oh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">At the scene, we found this key to the winder of the inspector's pocket watch.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A key...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And having wound the pocket watch, we discovered that it in fact still works. You see, the watch didn't stop because it was broken at all. And that fact... ...completely undermines one of the most fundamental premises on which this entire case has been built!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! B-But Counsel... ...the watch was stopped at almost exactly five o'clock.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Yeah, which is just when we 'eard that gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">It is. Exactly the hour.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The time that was showing on the watch tells us nothing other than when it wound down. It's merely a coincidence that it happened to be at five o'clock.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Even if that's true... ...the three witnesses here all heard the gunshot at five o'clock. So that's obviously when this crime was committed!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, that doesn't hold!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Why not?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Recall what Inspector Lestrade said only moments ago:</line>
<line speaker="Gina">The boss used to wind it up every evenin' wivout fail when 'e was waitin' for 'is grub to come at the pub. Said 'e 'adn't missed a day in the last ten years, polishin' it an' windin' it. It meant the world to 'im, that watch did.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The victim was in the habit of winding his watch once a day...in the evening. We can reasonably assume, therefore, that he wound the timepiece on the evening before he died as well.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, that would be entirely reasonable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But if that's the case... ...you wouldn't expect the watch to have completely wound down by five o'clock the following day.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Oh! Aye...</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Well 'ow do you explain it then?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In summary, the evening before the day of the incident, when the gunshot rang out in that room... ...the inspector was already unable to wind his watch.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You, you can't mean...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What would stop a man winding his watch if he's been in the habit of winding it every single evening for ten years? The obvious answer...is that he was already dead!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! Counsel, that is a most extraordinary claim!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Extraordinary isn't the word! It's absurd! You claim he was already dead the night before? Do you really think that Scotland Yard's coroner would have overlooked something like that?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! W-Well, um...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">On that subject, there is something rather surprising... There's actually an omission in the coroner's report. The time of death is not noted.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! That's, that's right!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Wait a minute! You're forgetting that my legs went from under me when I kicked the door in.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Like I said, I planted my hand in a dirty great puddle of blood.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. So the victim's blood hadn't dried. It was fresh.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">He catches on fast, dozn't he?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that blood could be explained in any number of ways! It could have been put there afterwards. Some fresh blood could have been poured over the victim's body after he-</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Does my learned friend think that fresh blood is available on every street corner?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, it needn't necessarily have been human blood, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">We've been told previously that Scotland Yard has no way to identify blood as human.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The problem is currently being researched. At present, you are correct. It is beyond our abilities.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So then...a chicken's blood could have been used, for example.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">It's certainly a possibility that it wasn't the inspector's blood at all.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But the gunshot was heard at five o'clock that afternoon. That's beyond question!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is it, though?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Given that the time of death of the victim has already been called into question... ...it isn't beyond the realms of possibility that what these witnesses heard wasn't a gunshot at all.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Oh, please! What are you tryin' to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Uz lot know what we heard! And it woz a loud bang that came from that there room!</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Now y-you listen to me! A street seller's ears are his l-l-livelihood.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't doubt your ears, sir. But all you can state with certainty is that you heard a noise.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself then, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A noise that sounds like a gunshot could have been made with...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Oh really? A demonstration is in order then, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, please, show the court how you could use that to create a noise like a gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...We're waiting, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I may have been mistaken.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It looks like you've been making a lot of noise yourself... Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! <thought>Ugh...Kazuma's got a devastating way with words in English, too.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I realise it may be difficult to retract what you said and present some different evidence, but perhaps...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, I was thinking the same thing myself.</thought> That's because I'm convinced there is some evidence that could produce a similar noise!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something like this. The culprit could have set off one of these to fake a gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! The very fireworks that are sold by the witness?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">...Now 'old on a minute! Are you sayin' I did it?! My pretty little firecrackers only make a little pop anyway. See?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Not a hundred of them together. The Venus Special that you sell for six hundred pennies sounds like this:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As the court can now attest...it sounds very much like a gunshot in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Agh agh agh agh agh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're trying to suggest that somebody set one of those fireworks off at the scene?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm suggesting that somebody knew the defendant was in the room at five that day... ...and sought to implicate him by creating a sound like a gunshot for these pedlars on Fresno Street to hear!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But even the accused himself has testified that he saw no one else in the room at the time. Whether it was a gun or a firecracker, the only person present to cause that bang was Barok van Zieks!</line>
<line speaker="Venus">One whiff of a match and my firecrackers go pop. See? It's why people like 'em.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I fear for your fingers, young lady.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Recently during my time here in Britain, I've learnt of a very useful invention indeed. Something called a, um...a time bomb.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good heavens! A bomb?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, a device that allows you to blow up whatever you like, whenever you like.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Mr Naruhodo. I worry that your unfortunate phrasing there...may lead to yet another international incident.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! No no no! Wait! ...It's, it's the 'whenever you like' part that's important.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A timed device?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! Exactly! A timed device! Something of that nature could have been planted at the scene. A device that was able to produce the sound of a gunshot long after the culprit had left.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Your extravagant claim will have to be substantiated with evidence, Counsel. What proof do you have to suggest in any way that a timed device was employed to create the gunshot sound?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I...did think so, My Lord. But it's becoming increasingly clear... ...that we've all been very misguided here.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes, by you.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No, Counsel, the time has come for a penalty. Without delay.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh...no time to clear the area before the blast...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As the court has already discussed, the tip of one of the candles in this candelabrum has been blown off.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed. Because it was struck by the bullet, which presumably passed through the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I don't think that's possible, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Not possible? Why?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Because of the scorching. There are gunpowder scorch marks clearly visible on the broken candle.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">There are? ...Goodness, yes! But is it not the case... ...that there was also scorching on the victim around the bullet entry wound?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, there was. But as we heard earlier... ...scorching like that only occurs when the target is at very close range - a matter of centimetres from the gun.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Which means that the scorching on the candle can't possibly be the result of a gunshot.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You're suggesting it came from the fireworks?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">How can that be, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The fact that there's such visible scorching on the candle... ...suggests that the fireworks must have been right next to it when they exploded. Or to put it another way...the candle and firecrackers were joined together.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that is how these three witnesses came to believe they'd heard a gunshot at five o'clock.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... Well...what a plot... And this implies that the victim could have died earlier than we've been led to believe. The previous day, even.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Now...now...now just hold your horses! All uz lot here saw the victim goin' into the building, remember?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">I, I couldn't forget that flame-coloured hair even if I w-wanted to.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The person you saw entering the building wasn't the victim at all. ...Consider this.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously anybody can wear a wig. So the person that these witnesses saw entering the building fifteen minutes before the incident occurred... ...could easily have been someone else entirely wearing the red hairpiece.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Someone else?! Do, do you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It was the same person who contrived the firecracker trick. In other words...Inspector Gregson's killer!</line>
<line speaker="???">Pfft...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the candle was used as a sort of timer device to set off the firecrackers... That's a really ingenious idea...though obviously it's a shame it was used for such a wicked purpose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I wonder if there aren't some more positive uses for a timer device such as that... Ah, I have the perfect application! It would be a wonderful way of waking you in the mornings, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I think I'd prefer that you continue to wake me in person, if it's all the same to you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ha ha ha ha ha ha hah! Oh, very impressive, Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">K-Kazuma?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I'm really quite amazed you've come this far. But after all, wasn't I the one who told you... ...that you had all the makings of a great defence lawyer?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I also noted the lack of a time of death in this report. A stark omission. But as far as I'm concerned...this whole country's justice system leaves a lot to be desired!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! Prosecutor Asogi! What do you mean by that statement?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I hear that many of the leading members of Britain's judiciary are present to observe this trial today. So we cannot allow even the slightest doubt to be overlooked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The defence's assertion about the time of death based on the victim's stopped watch is just conjecture. But...while the possibility exists that my learned friend may be correct...we have a duty to explore it.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Well, certainly...I would agree with you.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And what immediately comes to mind is of course... ...what was Inspector Gregson doing and where did he go on the day before the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you know?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The inspector always carried out his investigative work alone. His movements were treated as confidential within Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Even within the Yard?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">However, considering the evidence we've been presented with so far... ...I'd say it's fairly apparent what case the man was pursuing. Wouldn't you, my learned friend?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I do have a feeling about what case he might have been investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I agree. Surely... My Lord! The defence believes it can explain to the court... ...the case that was being investigated by Inspector Gregson at the time of his death!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well, Counsel. Present your argument to the court. What evidence is suggestive of the case being investigated by the inspector on the day prior to the incident?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Congratulations, Ryunosuke Naruhodo. You deserve a reward for that expert display!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">AAAAAARGH! <thought>Did, did you just draw Karuma on me, my friend?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I think, Mr Naruhodo, that there's one particular piece of evidence... ...that really does stand out in showing what case Inspector Gregson was investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! I have the answer now!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I believe this red hairpiece points to the answer.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">We might assume it was part of a disguise used to carry out an undercover investigation.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Surely not! Such a brightly coloured hairpiece would only serve to make the inspector more noticeable.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's quite true. It would definitely have made him stand out in a crowd. Except, that is...in a crowd of gentlemen from the Red-Headed League.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The, the Red-Headed League?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So...you'd already worked it out.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What on earth is this all about? Is there such an extraordinary league of gentlemen?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The Red-Headed League is currently under investigation for a grand deception.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A deception of what nature, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">They've been targeting red-headed men across all of London and tricking them out of small sums of money. Two men were arrested for the misdemeanour only yesterday, in fact.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! The defence calls for those two men to be summoned at once!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">T-Two red-heads?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Inspector Gregson clearly infiltrated the Red-Headed League using this hairpiece. So it's very likely that he had direct contact with these criminals. And it's quite possible that such contact led to...more serious events.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I concur that we cannot in good conscience leave this new avenue unexplored.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well done, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...it's another possible line of enquiry for us at least.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The prosecution will make immediate arrangements for the charged men to appear. Bring these two Red-Headed League conspirators before me, Prosecutor Asogi!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">At once, My Lord.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. We will have a thirty-minute recess. Court is adjourned!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Oh, there you are, 'Oddo!</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">What kept you, my dear fellow?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Hello, Mr Sholmes. Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">You sure about wot you said in there? That the boss...you know...actually died the day before? It's pretty 'ard to swallow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes, I was shocked by the revelation too, Gina.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">As was I! Possibly more shocked than both of you!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...It's not a competition, Mr Sholmes. <thought>But I was more shocked than all of you put together.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">This is the autopsy report in question, is it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. It's strange that there's no time of death noted. I suppose there's a simple explanation. Or perhaps...it was a deliberate omission.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh dear... If it was deliberate... ...it puts me in mind of the last case we worked on...and Dr Sithe.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. Anyway, it seems that on the day before Lord van Zieks discovered his body... ...Inspector Gregson was investigating the Red-Headed League. So perhaps something happened with them. Come to think of it... ...you had trouble with those league men too, didn't you, Mr Sholmes? You were taken in by their trick.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">No no no! Naturally, I wasn't 'taken in' as you put it. My sleuth-hound interest was merely piqued slightly by the rare scent of a weekly four-pound income.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...And that scent masked the underlying scent of deception, I suppose.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The two criminals in question are the pair we saw being arrested yesterday, aren't they? In Mr Sholmes's suite, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">That's right, Sooze! An' it was me wot took 'em in! Thanks to a tip-off by a good, law-abidin' citizen.</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Indeed. Yours truly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So it's going to be that pair in the witness stand next, is it?</thought> Something doesn't quite make sense to me, though. The day before Inspector Gregson was found, you hadn't had trouble with the Red-Headed League yet, had you? Why would the inspector have been investigating them?</line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">Well, the likely explanation would be... ...that Gregson's own sleuth-hound interest was piqued by the rare scent of a weekly four-pound income.</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Don't tar 'im wiv the same brush as you, Sholmes!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, well... Then there's the whole issue of Inspector Gregson being investigated by Lord van Zieks for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The Reaper...the Red-Headed League... Inspector Gregson...Lord van Zieks...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...And Kazuma.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I feel as though he knew we'd arrive at this point somehow.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Gosh! I, I think you're right...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What's he really trying to achieve here today?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Sholmes">All the answers will soon be revealed. ...Observe the time, my dear fellow. This recess will be over very shortly.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, you're right. <thought>Kazuma was determined that he should be the one to prosecute this trial. And he was determined that I should take the defence. Just what is it that he's hoping to make me see, I wonder? I get the feeling we're a long way from the end of this trial yet...</thought> Are you ready then, Miss Susato?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Yes!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In the name of Her Majesty the Queen, I hereby declare this court to be in session again. We resume the closed court hearing of Barok van Zieks, here present, who stands accused of murder. Now then, Prosecutor Asogi...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Have you summoned the witnesses as requested?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Yes. The two members of the Red-Headed League who planned and carried out the deception. They arrived not long ago from the local prison by police carriage.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. Bailiff, usher the two men into the courtroom!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">These two men are currently being held by the police on suspicion of attempted extortion. You may omit your occupations. But please state your names now for the court.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I am Fabien de Rousseau. A descendant of ze great de Rousseau family from Nice, en France.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">And my-a name is Peppino de Rossi! I am the third son of the great familia de Rossi - the landowners from Napoli!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The two men first became acquainted at a boarding school for European nobility.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zose who graduate from Temsik are ze future leaders of Europe. ...But! Do you 'ave any idea 'ow boring it is to be born wiz noble blood? ...Alors! I make it my mission to get ze better of ze world by employing ze little grey cells of my brain. Zat is all I am trying to do, uh.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...that's the only reason for this whole grand deception you've been carrying out?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">...Oui. You could say zat.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Not bad, ay? He has the grand ideals, but the petty plans! This strange combination is-a the charm of the Hairlarious Brothers! Si, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">......... Listen to me, Peppino. I 'ave two sings to say to you:</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Eh? Che? Are you about to tell me one of your grandi anecdotes? Evviva!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Firstly, I want you to stop calling me zis 'capo'. And secondly... ..we are not ze 'Airlarious Brothers. Zis is serious business.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Che bello! There it is! The capo's trump-a card: the furrowed brow! It is deep, uh, capo? The furrow, and the meaning of your words!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The court has been led to believe that under the banner of the 'Red-Headed League'... ...you have conspired to swindle money from unsuspecting members of the public. Is this true?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui. C'est a.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">And what exactly was the nature of this deception by which you planned to defraud?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">...Alors, I will explain it.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No, capo! Leave it to-a me! As you see, we both have the vivid red hair, no? At school, we were teased for this without pity. The capo here, he was many times behind the schoolhouse, crying like the Trevi Fountain. 'U! Zose dogs! One day ze world will respect us red-'eads!' Every night, he would bury his-a head in his-a pillow and weep for the injustice.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">C'est bien, Peppino! Enough! I will explain ze rest. Ze first step was ze newspaper advertisement. About one week before ze plan was put into operation, we listed ze same notice in every paper in London.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, we saw that notice. It was this one, I believe. Entitled 'To the Red-Headed League'.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui. C'est a. I am honoured zat you 'ave seen it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It states that the only condition for joining the league is having flame-coloured hair. And that if you satisfy the interview panel and are admitted into the league... ...you could receive a weekly income of four pounds.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">On the date specified, red-headed hopefuls gathered in droves at a park specified in the advertisement. And from each person present, this pair took an application fee of five shillings.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">And wiz ze money, to France! It was a plan most elegant, non?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No, it was most dishonourable. But to be frank, I'm stunned anybody was foolish enough to be taken in by such an obvious trick.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">The park was described by one witness as 'choked with red-headed folk, like a coster's orange barrow'.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And the day on which all these men gathered to apply was the day before the victim was discovered. Crucially, these two men spoke face to face with every single person present that day.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui. I 'ave seen more red-'eaded people in one day zan I will see in ze rest of my life.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, si. And-a now, every time I see the capo's hair, I feel sick to my stomach!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Anyway, why 'ave we been summoned 'ere today?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze date for our trial was not until tomorrow, I was told.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Naturally, neither of these men have been told any details about this trial. They've only been shown this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very good. So, Mr de Rousseau and Mr de Rossi, you will now give your formal testimony for the court... ...on the subject of the gentleman pictured in this photograph.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Of course. We are always ready to 'elp wiz ze law.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">We 'ad more zan one thousand red-'eaded people assemble in ze park on Lime Street zat day.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But I don't recall the man in this-a photograph. Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Non, I don't remember 'im. Obviously 'e is dead now. But I assure you, 'e was not in ze park.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Allora! This victim is-a nothing to do with us!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">You 'ave a lot to answer for, Peppino. It is your fault zat we got caught in ze first place.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You've given sworn testimony that this man in the photograph was not present. Can you be certain?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, oui. I am quite certain. We did not interview zis man.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Nobody looking like-a this came to the park. This, I can promise!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It must be noted that you have been arrested for a grand deception, however. Accordingly, this court has little confidence in your assurances.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">...!  ...Uffa! With this attitude, we get-a nowhere, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He's really-a sulking now...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">This confidential document was obtained directly from Scotland Yard. It records an entry from the inspector's private diary dated the day before the incident. It reads, 'Lime Street, Red-Headed League, Undercover.'</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ah! I have the answer! Maybe there was another, similar event in the park on the day in question, ay?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zat is ridiculous.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>There's no question that Inspector Gregson was investigating the Red-Headed League. Which means it's quite possible that's when he was killed!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. The defence may proceed with the cross-examination now.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah. Yes, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">We 'ad more zan one thousand red-'eaded people assemble in ze park on Lime Street zat day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A thousand people? That's a very big crowd.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">It was quite a spectacle. Red-'eads 'ad come from all over ze capital.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, the capo here, he has the magnetismo animale, ay? Nobody else could attract-a so many people. If I could be born again, I would be the capo!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">All zose people wanted was ze money, Peppino. Ze four pounds per week.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you suggesting that you spoke personally with all one thousand applicants?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, oui, zat we did. Because every one of zem paid us five shillings.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">We take-a their names and we take-a their money! And we take-a their addresses as well. Then I tell them we take-a some days to let them know by-a post, e finito! Maybe...two minuti a person? We start early in the morning, and we stop late in the night.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you earnt five thousand shillings in one day?! <thought>That's a small fortune!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Who'd have thought there were a thousand such gullible red-heads in London to start with.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>One of whom was a great detective with chemically altered hair...</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But I don't recall the man in this-a photograph. Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">He doesn't look at all familiar?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No, I don't-a think so. And this is a wig, ay? He was trying to trick us! I do not like the people who are trying to trick the other people!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Says the con artist.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If between them they interviewed a thousand people with red hair... ...it would be unreasonable to expect them to remember every face.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No no, signore. I may be small... ...but my memory is very large! I never forget a thing! In my opinion, I do not think this-a man was in the park.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>But he's not going to give the court a definite, it seems.</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Eh, capo? You didn't see a man like this, uh?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Non, I don't remember 'im. Obviously 'e is dead now. But I assure you, 'e was not in ze park.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But according to what you've said, you spoke with a thousand or more people that day.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, zat's true. My eyes were burning by ze end of ze day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Surely then, you can't actually remember every single face. How are you so certain... ...that this particular man wasn't present?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Normally, the red hair is very distinctive, ay? But not when you have one thousand red-heads crowding around. Then it is just an eyesore! But if there was some other information you could-a give us, maybe then we would recall.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zat is not ze line, Peppino. Remember, we do not remember 'im. We are sure of zat fact, uh? If zere was a man wiz a red 'airpiece, but 'is moustache did not match ze colour... ...zen I do not sink I could 'ave forgotten 'im.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma said these two had only been shown that photograph and they'd been told nothing else at all. But what if I fed them just one other detail about the victim. For example...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can certainly appreciate that just knowing the man had red hair wouldn't help you remember in this situation. But what if I told you that the man's name was Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze man in ze photograph is a Monsieur Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Names, they are boring! I did not-a listen to any of them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Oh.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">It was not a real interview, uh? It was just for-a show. Why would I remember the names?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zat's right. Zis changes nothing. Ze man in ze photograph was not zere. As we 'ave already said.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm... It seems there's little to be gained from pursuing this point further.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Tell zem again what you said before, Peppino.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, capo, si! I say it again and again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can certainly appreciate that just knowing the man had red hair wouldn't help you remember in this situation. But what if I told you the man in the red hairpiece was actually a detective?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze man in ze photograph? A detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It would appear he found your notice in the paper suspicious and decided to investigate incognito.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">......... ...Sorry, but zis changes nothing. No detective came to ze park. I am certain of zat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something to add, Mr de Rossi?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">......... Che? Si, I am always adding something! Parmesan, olive oil, pepper...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What I mean is...did you not agree with your friend's last remark by any chance?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Eh? What-a did he just-a say? About the detective?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Keep your mouth shut, Peppino! You 'ave said enough already.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But-a why, capo? What is the problem? There was a man who said-a, 'I am an inspector from Scotland Yard.'</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good Lord! Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! Explain this volte-face in your testimony, witness!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Is simple. A man who was at-a the park said to us that he was an inspect-</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zere was no such man.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ma dai! What are you saying, capo? Have you forgotten, ay?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I 'ave forgotten nothing. Nobody like zis came to ze park.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Basta, capo, basta! You beat me at-a many things, but not two: the memory and the meals! Like I said, when is time to eat-a the pasta, no one is-a faster!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">But you are inferior to me in every other way... so shut up!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Uuurgh... Trop tard... Ze damage is done...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed it is, sir.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, zere was a man who came to ze park and 'e said 'e was an inspector from Scotland Yard. 'Owever! 'E looked nothing like ze man in ze photograph. 'E was someone else!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Because! To start wiz, 'is face was completely different.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si...is true, is true. The man who came was-a younger. His-a face was clean-shaven. His-a eyes were sadder. His-a chin was thinner.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">No resemblance whatsoever, then!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Anyway, I was not going to be fooled. I took ze obvious precaution and said to 'im... ...'If you are really a detective, show us ze proof!'</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, si, the capo here, he doesn't take-a no nonsense, ay?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">But 'e was well prepared. 'E said 'e 'ad identification.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I-Identification? You mean, official police inspector's identification?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is most unconvincing.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry, My Lord?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel, no incognito inspector would offer his identification for inspection. It's quite out of the question.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Definitely. Why would he expose his true identity?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Clearly ze papers were fake.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Certo, capo! You are a genius! As we say in-a Italia, it takes a thief to recognise another, ay?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what happened after he announced that he was a detective?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">'E became very annoying. 'E said, 'You are under investigation.' So I took 'is papers from 'im and chased 'im out of ze park.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">It was fantastico! And look, here is-a the identification!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you stole it from the man?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">He had it-a coming! He made us very scared. But he was-a not who he said-a he was!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Indeed, the person described does not appear to have behaved as a true inspector would. However, I believe it would be prudent for these identification papers to be entered into evidence.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Hmph. But I-a like them!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Now, let us return to the witnesses' testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">In any case, if such a man 'ad come incognito... ...'e wouldn't 'ave just said, 'I am a detective,' would 'e?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...no, I suppose not.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm...sound logic, I must agree.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Tell zem again what you said before, Peppino.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ay? Ah! Si, capo, si! Is-a best we move on!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can certainly appreciate that just knowing the man had red hair wouldn't help you remember in this situation. But what if I told you the man was always munching on a packet of fish and chips? Do you remember a man who was eating incessantly?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Not really. I was looking only at ze 'eads of ze applicants. I wouldn't 'ave noticed ze fish and chips any more zan ze caviar and smoked salmon.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Or-a spaghetti! Me, I love the spaghetti!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Really? I had no idea...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Tell zem again what you said before, Peppino.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, capo, si! I say it again and again!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, I suppose we should see what this inspector's identification looks like inside...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it definitely looks fake, doesn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Out of interest, what name is given?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Probably just something plucked out of the air. It's...'Tobias Gregson'... Wait, what?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">......... This Scotland Yard insignia... ...looks genuine to me.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But how?!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the department and identification number details are all correct as well.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Since when have you known those?</thought> Do, do you mean to say...?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I know it seems incredible, but yes... ...I think this is a genuine identification book issued by Scotland Yard.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But that's... That's unbelievable! <thought>This is the real thing after all?!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This Scotland Yard insignia looks genuine to me.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And the department and identification number details are all correct as well. There's no doubt that this really is Inspector Gregson's identification.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Allora! This victim is-a nothing to do with us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But we only have your word for that.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, but what else can we do, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>True...</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa! We are not having much-a fun these days! First we are arrested, then we are shown the horrible picture of a dead man... ...and now you question every single-a thing we say! WE are the victims here! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">No, you were caught carrying out a plot to swindle hundreds of innocent people.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">...! Hmph! You had to bring that up, ay? It's not fair! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">You 'ave a lot to answer for, Peppino. It is your fault zat we got caught in ze first place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What do you mean by that?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Cavolo! You promised not to say! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">After we 'ad taken all ze money zat day, we should 'ave left ze country. Zat was my plan. I left ze purchasing of ze tickets for ze ferry to Dunkerque to my companion 'ere. But 'e bought zem for ze wrong day.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Oops.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, but is an easy mistake-a to make-a, uh? The first, the thirty-first...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Bof! I 'ave no sympathy for you! We were an 'ole day late for ze boat because of your stupidity! And it's only because of zis, zat ze so-called 'great red-'eaded detective' caught us!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Capo...you know what I think? This is the work of God! Is a holy punishment, ay?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Peppino, for ze last time... ...zis is not 'oly punishment. Zis is 'olly your fault!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Don't blame God for your unholy mistakes. You are makin' me sick wiz anger!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Hmph. Maybe I make-a mistake-a. But when is time to eat-a the pasta, no one is-a faster!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And I've seen the evidence...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>They haven't told us much we didn't already know...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What do you think, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, if it was in the inspector's diary, it seems likely that he must have gone to Lime Street that day. And yet these two both claim they didn't see him...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I have to say... ...they don't appear to be telling lies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, they are experts in deception, don't forget. Sounding plausible is their specialty. They may be lying simply to avoid being implicated in this case as well.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Surely if they were truly experts in deception, they wouldn't have been caught.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Well, yes, you do have a point there...</thought> ...It seems to me like we need more information.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Definitely!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I wonder if I could ask you to examine this identification book very closely... ...Miss Lestrade?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Why Miss Lestrade?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What is your intention here, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Is this really a fake, or is it genuine? That's the question. ...Which we can't answer ourselves.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Don't be ridiculous. No Scotland Yard detective would allow his - or her - identification to be stolen.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gina">That...that... That IS the boss's! ...No question about it.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It can't be!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">As I suspected. The 'undercover detective' who attended the Red-Headed League's enrolment on the day in question... ...was the real Inspector Gregson carrying out an incognito investigation!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zu... Zut aloooooors!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Ordaaar! Ordaaar!</line>
<line speaker="Gina">But...if the boss 'ad 'is identification stolen... ...'e would've reported it straight away. I mean, 'e was always on at me about it. If ya lose summat, report it at once, 'e'd say.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Could it be, then... ...that the inspector was physically unable to report it?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Physically... Ay?! What are you-a saying?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Unable to...? You're, you're not suggesting...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes! It's quite possible that he was killed before he had the chance to report his identification stolen!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">No!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence posits that the victim was killed the day before his body was discovered, at a different location. Do you two...have anything to say about that?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">U! I know-a nothing! U! I done-a nothing! U!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Pull yourself together, Peppino! Mon Dieu! You can behave a little more like a master criminal zan zat, non?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">U! Now I wish I had-a returned to Italia! U!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">S-Stop crying, Peppino, please! Otherwise I...I...</line>
<line speaker="Gina">Lumme! Stop yer whinin' an' start talkin'!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...I believe the court will need to hear your story in considerably greater detail.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">I know-a nothing! U! I done-a nothing! U!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But you will tell everything! ...Or face the worst possible outcome.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ugh... Uuuuuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will dry your eyes and testify again... ...about these identification papers, and the precise circumstances under which you came by them!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">U!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>For crying out loud...</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze, ze truth is, we took 'im prisoner and kept 'im for ze night at our secret 'ideout.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">We took the man's identification from him and shut-a him in the room next to ours!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zere might 'ave been a little tussle, but we did 'im no 'arm. And ze next mornin', we let 'im go.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">He spent-a the night in a nice room! It was-a nothing like prison really! U!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">This, this is outrageous! You imprisoned the man?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But! No! Si! No! It, it was not-a like a prison! He was-a very comfortable and-a calm and-a happy! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">......... It, it was never part of my plan! I swear it!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa! So...so you think it was-a my fault, ay? Just because I got the date of the ferry wrong... by one-a little-a day!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I do not sink it was your fault, Peppino. I know it!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No no no no! Per favore, capo. Is not-a fair.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You shall have plenty of time for squabbling back at the prison, gentlemen.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Uff! I don't believe zis... 'Ow could 'e 'ave been a real detective...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Counsel for the Defence, proceed with the cross-examination!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>So on the day before the incident... ...Gregson spent the night confined in this pair's hideout...</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze, ze truth is, we took 'im prisoner and kept 'im for ze night at our secret 'ideout.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do, do you realise what you're saying?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">You 'ave to believe me! I never intended for zat to 'appen. And I'm sure ze detective did not intend it, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Do you think?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">But, but zere was nothing else I could do!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si! Nothing else! This was-a the first crime for the capo! He was at the end of his-a wits!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I 'ave told you before, Peppino. Zat is not ze way to describe a criminal mastermind!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What about this hideout of yours?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">...An old, empty 'ouse behind ze park on Lime Street.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">We rented the place for-a two days. It was an inspired idea by the capo here.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">An impulsive idea, I would say.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No no no! Not impulsive! Inspired! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">What am I supposed to say to zat, uh, Peppino?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And it was in the house described that you confined Inspector Gregson, was it?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ugh...oui. But you 'ave to remember: I was under ze impression zat 'e was a pretender. Not a real inspector!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That doesn't quite add up, though. If you didn't think the man was a real inspector... ...there would have been no reason to take him prisoner, would there?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Non, you are right. But we couldn't be completely certain.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Even though I didn't sink 'e was a real detective, I, I was too scared to let 'im go zat day, just in case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Too scared? Why?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Because! Why 'ad 'e come to ze park? We didn't know. Zere was a chance zat 'e 'ad seen through my plan.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">And if that was-a the case, he would go straight to the police station to blow-a the whistle on us! Even if he was just-a feigning to be an inspector, he was up to no good, uh? Without-a doubt-a.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I think most people would agree that it's you two who were up to no good.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Well-a...si, you may be right. Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze point is, we were not able to escape from England immediately. Zat is why we 'ad no choice but to take ze man prisoner.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What I don't understand is why the inspector felt the need to show you his identification in the first place.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si! I ask myself the same question!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">We were writing down ze names and addresses of all ze people who we took five shillings from zat day. I have forgotten what name 'e said, but ze address, it startled me.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si si! 'Address: Scotland Yard, Homicide Division,' he said!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">'E probably didn't like your face, Peppino. Anyway, I was not rude. I just politely asked 'im why 'e 'ad said it... ...and zat's when 'e started to say 'e was an inspector. Not long afterwards, 'e took out 'is identification.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>What was Inspector Gregson playing at?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Tell the court what happened next. You took him back to your hideout, you say?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si! We did-a, we did-a!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">We took the man's identification from him and shut-a him in the room next to ours!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That being this identification book here, correct?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si! That is-a the one!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What made you believe that it was a forgery?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">I never seen a real one, of course. But he was so suspicious, this-a man. Allora, I was-a thinking, it must be false! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, it is just as Peppino said. We were convinced it was not genuine.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">And so together, the Hairlarious Brothers, we took-a the man captive!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">All we did was shove 'im inside a locked room. Zen we made preparations to transport all of ze money.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In for a penny, in for a pound...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zere might 'ave been a little tussle, but we did 'im no 'arm. And ze next mornin', we let 'im go.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...what do you mean by 'a little tussle' exactly?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Hm? Bof! It was nothing. Just a minor incident.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">The falso inspector, he was a real piece of-a the work! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What happened?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa! It was a disaster! We give him a nice room, and what does he-a do, uh? In the middle of the night, he tries to escape-a through the ventilatore!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Can you blame him?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">We chased 'im, bien sr. And we caught 'im again.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">...Can you-a blame us?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Wait! You, you didn't... ...shoot the man in your haste, did you?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zut! Who do you sink we are?! Of course not! I simply caught 'old of 'im again and took 'im back to ze room. Zere was really nothing more to it zan zat.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr de Rossi! Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ay?! Me?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Something Mr de Rousseau just said seemed to make you, um... Well, it seemed to make you act even more strangely than usual. What was that all about?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Cavolo! At times like that, you don't-a wanna have the capo after you, believe me! And I speak-a from personal-a esperienza!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Personal experience?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zat is enough, Peppino. Zere is no need to say more.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">The truth is, the night-a before we put the Red-Headed League plan into action, I was-a scared. It was not-a fair to the capo, but...I tried to run away.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a shame you didn't manage it.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But the capo here, he came after me like-a the turbine, uh? And he dragged me back to the house, kicking and-a screaming. I still have-a the bruises to prove it! Ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bruises, you say?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ah...you wanna see, uh? You wanna see my-a fantastico bruises!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zat's enough now, Peppino. No one wants to look at any part of you.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">What-a to do, uh? I-a show you, or I-a don't...? I-a show you, or I-a don't...?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You do! NOW!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Allora, if everybody wants to see, then I-a do it! Ecco! You see? Is still very-a visible, ay?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That, that red ring around your neck? You got that when you were dragged back to the house?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si! The capo, sometimes he is-a very rough! And-</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I said zat's enough! Peppino's neck is nothing to do wiz what we are talking about 'ere. You 'ave my word.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hm, yes... What is your opinion, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>About this red ring around Mr de Rossi's neck? I wonder... Does it matter?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr de Rossi! I'm going to have to ask you... ...to amend your testimony with details about that mark on your neck!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ay, capo? You see? Everyone is interested in what I say, uh?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well. You will amend you [sic] testimony as requested, Mr de Rossi.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si si, if you really want-a to know!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I don't suppose there's any cause for alarm. I'm sure it'll heal up in time.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm not quite sure that's what His Lordship meant, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">So! If you have-a seen enough, then I go back to what I was-a saying before.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the following morning, you let him go, you say?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Correct! And it was an amicable parting. Zere was no trouble.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si si. We shake-a the hands and say let's-a do it again, uh!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not a whiff of perjury here...</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">He tried to escape, but the capo put-a the collare on him and dragged him back...like what he did-a to me, see?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Are, are you saying that red mark was caused by...</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si si! A big collare made from-a the leather!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A leather collar...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Is this true, Mr de Rousseau?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">What? We 'ad a St Bernard at 'ome when I was younger. It is a souvenir from zat time, wiz a very strong chain.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A strong chain?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you put that around your friend's neck?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I'm sorry! I was so angry zat 'e was leaving me alone.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">You did not have to tie the chain to the leg-a of the bed-a, though, uh? I would not have tried to run again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You...you didn't do that to Inspector Gregson as well, did you?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">'Treat-a the people-a equal-a!' Is the capo here's motto, ay?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It's starting to sound a lot more like a prison all of a sudden.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">The capo is-a tough! But the capo is-a rough!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Uuugh... I, I shouldn't 'ave done it...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...the following morning when you released the inspector...</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">He had-a the red ring around his neck just like-a me!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Peppino, s'il vous plat... Leave it now.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Now you know, uh? The capo here, you don't-a wanna tangle with him, ay? But for the inspector, is not so bad...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">He spent-a the night in a nice room! It was-a nothing like prison really! U!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You took away the man's freedom! However comfortable you make it sound, you were still holding him prisoner.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">If you say-a that, then I say-a this: There is something that takes away our freedom too. The lack of-a money! So we are the prisoners as well, uh? All of us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Huh?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No money, no freedom. This is the truth! It-a makes me mad! And it-a makes me sad! What can-a we do?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...well...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If you feel so disenfranchised, take 'money' to court. ...Though it'll cost you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa, there you-a have it! You see? That is why we need the Red-Headed League, to fight for the justice!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm...perhaps he has a point.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">No, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">All we did-a was to give the man a comfortable place to sleep for the night. And you say it was a prison, uh? UH?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Hm...perhaps he has a point again.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">No again, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">You should have heard him-a snoring! Ma dai! If anyone was disturbed, it was us!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Not much to go on, really...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Their testimony does make me wonder, you know. About this pocket watch belonging to the inspector, I mean.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ah yes, the one he treasured so much, apparently.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">If he was confined but not restrained, as the witnesses are implying... ...he would still have been able to wind his watch.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's very true, yes. <thought>So did Inspector Gregson actually die while he was being held captive by these red-heads?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">In which case, is it possible that these two young men are responsible for Inspector Gregson's...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">To be honest...I find that hard to believe. Perhaps we should try to find out exactly what happened.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Very wise, Mr Naruhodo, yes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So the day before his body was discovered, Inspector Gregson was taken prisoner while working incognito...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Non non! It was not like zat! It was 'ardly a prison. It was an...invitation to stay. It was 'omely.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">However you describe it, there's one glaring inconsistency that remains.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What inconsistency is this, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I would ask the court to look closely at this photograph of the victim, Inspector Gregson. You will see...that there is no red ring visible around his neck!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Eh?! But, but that-a makes no sense! It was me who took-a the collare off the man in the morning. And I saw the red bruises on his-a neck, just like I have!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Given that the mark is still clearly visible on this witness's neck... ...we'd expect to see bruising on the victim, who put in the collar more recently than Mr de Rossi!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I-Indeed! That is most peculiar...</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">But what we-a tell you, uh? Uh? We say this...from-a the beginning... Many times! U!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, Peppino is right. Ze man in ze photograph... ...'e is someone different to ze man we 'eld captive zat niiiiiiiiight!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It would appear then, that on the day before the incident... ...the man who visited the park on Lime Street posing as an incognito inspector... ...was not Inspector Gregson at all!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If that's true, however, how do you explain the inspector's identification?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">This is a genuine identification book, issued by Scotland Yard. It's inconceivable that someone could have stolen such an important item from the inspector. The prosecution made that assertion itself!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">And we also know that the inspector had made a note about the Red-Headed League in his diary for that day. Which surely means we can't divorce the two events completely.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The inconsistency noted by the defence is most troubling. If it were the real Inspector Gregson whom these two red-headed gentlemen encountered... ...the fact that no bruising can be seen around his neck defies explanation.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But equally, if they actually encountered an imposter... ...how did that person come to be in possession of the real inspector's identification?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Does the defence have some plausible explanation, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>The whole thing defies explanation.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It is for precisely these occasions that we keep meticulous notes in the Court Record, Mr Naruhodo. Because those are the facts, and the facts cannot lie!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>No, the facts can't lie... ...even when they point to something so incredible, it's almost unbelievable!</thought> Well, My Lord, the true identity of the person who turned up in the park for the Red-Headed League's enrolment... ...is revealed by information in the Court Record, I believe.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Very tantalising, Mr Naruhodo. So, why don't you help us all to see whatever truth it is that you've apparently seen? Who exactly was this 'inspector' that appeared before Mr de Rousseau and Mr de Rossi?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Obviously there's nothing to deliberate here. It was Inspector Gregson himself! There's no other explanation, since he was in possession of genuine Scotland Yard identification!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In that case, I believe I speak for everyone here present when I ask... ...how do you explain the lack of bruising around the victim's neck, which you yourself brought up?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Ah, yes...that is the burning unresolved question, isn't it?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You claim there's nothing to deliberate, Counsel. However... ...I would implore you give your answers a little more thought in future!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It's possible I oversimplified that...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">It seems to me that the lack of bruising around the victim's neck is the hardest discrepancy to reconcile.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, I...think I can see how to tackle this now...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Though it seems incredible, I admit, the undeniable facts point to only one thing: Since no bruising can be seen on the victim's neck... ...the person who these two red-headed men took prisoner that day cannot have been Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">In other words, your whole argument up to now has been a waste of time.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the contrary. I haven't finished.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">There's no bruising on the victim's neck, so the question immediately posed next is... ...who exactly was this man in the park on Lime Street found to be carrying Inspector Gregson's identification?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si... Si! That's-a right! We tell the same story every time: Whoever this man was, the capo dragged him from-a pillar to-a post with the dog collare!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Mon Dieu, Peppino! I was not so 'arsh as you say, uh?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">So who was that-a falso inspector, ay? Who was he?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Clearly the defence has an idea about that. About the true identity of the man these two imprisoned that night...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I must ask the counsel for the defence to elaborate posthaste. Who did the witnesses encounter in the park posing as Inspector Gregson?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Oh really? On what grounds?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...I said it was no secret, but...that part is!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Dear me. If ever a penalty was in order, it's now, I feel.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Like-a the punishment? The capo can lend you his collare if you want, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Perhaps my learned friend needs to experience what it feels like to be dragged around the streets by the neck?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...I'll use my imagination, thanks.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Mr Naruhodo, the red ring produced by the collar is clearly the crux of the matter here...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Yes, the bruising around the neck...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Judge">Goodness me! Isn't...isn't that...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">One of the witnesses who was in the stand in this very courtroom earlier today! A nameless man, whose only occupation appears to be peddling hearsay to passers-by.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What on earth would a street seller be doing with a police inspector's identification papers? Witnesses! Is this the man or not?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">What 'as 'appened to 'is lip?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, this-a man is not for the Red-Headed League, ay? He's-a looking for the Twisted Lip League, no?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Perhaps rather than making such a rash claim next time... you should bite your lip instead.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It seems improbable, yes. But one undeniable fact remains! During his testimony earlier... ...I noted something around the man's neck: a red ring of bruising!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Eh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The defence demands that Mr Gossip be brought back to the stand!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Orrrdaaar! ...Bailiff! Bring the aforementioned witness back into the courtroom! Immediately!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well I never... An undeniable ring of bruising indeed. And identical...to that of the witness beside him!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Now what's going on here, eh? I've always had this, me. It's a birthmark, in't it?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A birthmark, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I assume the reason you've been recalled to the stand has been explained to you?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Aye, um...summat about an inspector again. But I'm telling you, you've got it all wrong as usual.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're denying all knowledge of it?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well of course I am! Are you trying to kill me with all this nonsense, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well...at least you'll have more stories to peddle back on Fresno Street, won't you? Now, we're going to need you to testify again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And you, Mr de Rousseau and Mr de Rossi. I'm sure you'll cooperate, won't you?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Do we 'ave any choice?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">We are in big-a trouble, ay, capo?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That's quite enough dilatory chatter. Proceed with the testimony!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze man who claimed to be an inspector zat day... was definitely not zis man.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Is right, si! You think we would-a forget these grand lips, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I never leave Fresno Street, alright? I've no interest in any Red-Headed League.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would certainly appear that we have the wrong man.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">What 'ave I been telling you, uh? Zere was no need for zis pointless testimony.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">That's right. I'm just a simple pedlar, remember. Fresno Street's all I know. How would I have come by a police inspector's identification book, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes, that's hard to explain, but...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmph. A brief cross-examination, I think, Counsel. Very brief.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh. Isn't there anyone in this courtroom who thinks I might be on to something?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">I stand steadfastly at your side as always, Mr Naruhodo!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Ze man who claimed to be an inspector zat day... was definitely not zis man.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you say. But how can you be quite so certain?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zere is no need to 'urt your 'ands on ze desk, monsieur. Surely ze reason is obvious, non? Because I 'ave never before seen lips like zis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nevertheless! There's a clear red mark around Mr Gossip's neck. And it looks very much like that left behind on the neck of your colleague by your prized collar!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Mon Dieu! Wiz your words, it is like you try to wring my neck!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">It does look very much like-a my neck though, ay?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No no, this is a birthmark, lad. The biggest lips in London and a neck to die for! Aye, they broke the mould when they made me!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">For ze first time in my life... ...I feel lucky to 'ave been born wiz red 'air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And I thought being Japanese made you stand out in London...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you maintain that you've never seen this man before?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, c'est a. I swear to it by ze flames of my 'air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So fierce pride has outgrown the frustration with your hair now, has it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you say. But how can you be quite so certain?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Zere is no need to 'urt your 'ands on ze desk, monsieur. Surely ze reason is obvious, non? Because I 'ave never before seen lips like zis.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Nevertheless! There's a clear red mark around Mr Boone's neck. And it looks very much like that left behind on the neck of your colleague by your prized collar!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Mon Dieu! Wiz your words, it is like you try to wring my neck!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">It does look very much like-a my neck though, ay?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">No no, this is a birthmark, lad. The biggest lips in London and a neck to die for! Aye, they broke the mould when they made me!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">For ze first time in my life... ...I feel lucky to 'ave been born wiz red 'air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>And I thought being Japanese made you stand out in London...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you maintain that you've never seen this man before?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui, c'est a. I swear to it by ze flames of my 'air.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>...So fierce pride has outgrown the frustration with your hair now, has it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Is right, si! You think we would-a forget these grand lips, uh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes, I don't imagine I'll forget those lips in a hurry, either.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">That is what I am-a saying. For some reason, it makes me wanna eat - how did Fabien call it? - an 'clair'. You know, I've never seen the hair as black as-a yours before, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Likewise, I'd never seen red hair like yours until I came to Britain.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, maybe is a nationale trait, uh? Maybe all the people from this-a man's country have-a the grand lips!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">No, lad, I was born right here on Fresno Street. And I've never left.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa! That is-a the problem, si.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you definitely didn't go to the park on Lime Street that day, Mr Gossip?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Now how many times do you want me to say it, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, yes, I don't imagine I'll forget those lips in a hurry, either.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">That is what I am-a saying. For some reason, it makes me wanna eat - how did Fabien call it? - an 'clair'. You know, I've never seen the hair as black as-a yours before, either.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Likewise, I'd never seen red hair like yours until I came to Britain.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, maybe is a nationale trait, uh? Maybe all the people from this-a man's country have-a the grand lips!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">No, lad, I was born right here on Fresno Street. And I've never left.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Uffa! That is-a the problem, si.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So you definitely didn't go to the park on Lime Street that day, Mr Boone?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Now how many times do you want me to say it, eh?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I never leave Fresno Street, alright? I've no interest in any Red-Headed League.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you'd heard of the Red-Headed League, had you?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">You don't get a name like 'Gossip' for nothing, eh? It's my business to know what's going off in town. I sold that tasty titbit to a fair few red-heads that came past me. Just between uz, I even got Sandwich to cough up for it!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well...he does have a very red nose, if that counts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Who knows?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">But as you can see, my own hair's not got a hint of red in it. And in any case, Fresno Street's my patch. You won't catch me sidling off to some other part of town. No sir, not likely!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr de Rousseau!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Uuugh! Ah...oui? Can I 'elp you?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Did Mr Gossip's words just now lead you to remember something relevant, perhaps?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">......... It was ze other day, when I was looking for a place near ze park. A small 'ouse or something.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">To be the headquarters of your Red-Headed League, yes.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I visited an 'ousing agent on Lime Street, and zere I saw 'im. Zis man was paying money to ze agent.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr...Mr Gossip...with a housing agent?!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Oui. 'E 'ad some kind of contract in 'is 'and, and zey were clearly discussing terms.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Bu... No no no! You're mistaken, chum! I've never left Fresno Street, me. Like I said before. You've mistaken me for someone else. Someone with the same face!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No no! The capo is right! I remember it-a too! He was-a paying the man with-a the banknotes!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">With notes?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">L-Like I said, that was... That wasn't me!</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">I was curious why this-a man with the dirty clothes had so much-a money. So I looked at-a the name on the papers.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And what name was written? 'Mr Gossip'?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">No no, this-a man, he lies! He tells you that he has-a no name... ...but in fact his-a name is Hugh Boone, uh? Is better than Mr Gossip, I think, si?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">NOOOOOOOOO!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm, indeed... And it is not the intention of the court to invade the privacy of witnesses. Very well, I shall respect your wishes, sir. The aforementioned name shall be redacted from all court records of this trial. Assuming no objections?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I'm sorry, My Lord, but the defence does object. Because the name just mentioned has a very deep significance to this case!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good gracious! Do, do you similarly object, Prosecutor Asogi?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As it happens, My Lord...that particular name has already been mentioned during today's proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well I never! In what capacity?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Hugh Boone... The name of the leaseholder of the room!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Let me put this very simply! The victim's body was discovered...in your rented room!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I suggest, sir...that you start talking!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">Well...alright... ...I suppose that might be the case, aye.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So your real name is Hugh Boone?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">......... Well just between uz...I don't like to blow me own trumpet, but there's no finer pedlar of titbits in town. So aye, I happen to be able to afford a grubby little room in a falling-down backstreet townhouse.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You do?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">And once every six months, I go and pay the rent to the agent on Lime Street. Aye, I remember now. There were two vulgar red-heads in there last time.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Ay? If either of us is-a vulgar, is not-a me!</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Sink again, Peppino.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Why didn't you bring this up before?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">It's like I told you already... ...I don't like talking about my personal life. I'm a titbit pedlar as far as everyone else is concerned. No fuss.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You will update your testimony to include this most surprising revelation...Mr Boone.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">......... If I must.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So the leaseholder Scotland Yard has been looking for since the body was discovered... ...has been here under our noses all along.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I see...</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">As it happens, after I sold Sandwich that little titbit about the Red-Headed League... ...he went and got himself some red paint from somewhere. God only knows where, mind. But just between uz...he didn't have the gumption to dunk his head in it.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Aye, I rent the room where that fella was found, it's true. For what difference it makes.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...you live in that room presumably, do you?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">No, I don't live there! What do you think? There's no bed, is there? Just a desk.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then...why would you want to rent it?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Well, I...I don't think I should have to say, really.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Then how about the noticeboard in there? Which was covered from top to bottom in confidential documents only the police should have had access to.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Ah...no...that board's not mine. The inspector must have brought it along. It's only the other bits and bobs that belong to me. The desk and the chair and that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Um...people don't generally carry enormous noticeboards around with them... The real question is...why was Inspector Gregson killed there, in your room?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">......... Well obviously, I've not the faintest idea. I mean, it's causing me no end of bother, to be honest.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I [sic] seems to me that Mr Gossip- Sorry, Mr Boone... ...would rather as little is known about his room as possible for some reason.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, it does come across that way. And more importantly... ...knowing that the scene of the crime is actually his room completely changes things. In particular, there's one part of his testimony that's really bothering me now.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's how I'm finally going to undo this man...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">I'm all alone in the world, me. I've no kinfolk or nothing. Why would I be involved in something like that?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You mean you have no family?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">No, none at all. So I spend my days on Fresno Street peddling titbits to passers-by... ...hoping - just between uz, this is - that eventually, someone else with lips like mine will come along.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">I don't-a think so.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">You may be right.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Anyway, that mark on your neck is just too much of a coincidence for us to ignore.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">Well what's a fella to do then, eh? If you don't believe me, we're at an impasse. And there's nothing I can do but flick me lip.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>It looks like I'm not going to get anywhere here unless I can produce some proof.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">You're basically saying I got dressed up and posed as some fancy inspector, aren't you? Well, it's beyond me how you think I could do that.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">Just look at me, eh. Doz it look like I could carry off a disguise with a face like this?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Maybe you could! Say...with a moustache! Or a beard to cover up that lip!</line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">Aye, perhaps. But if I was going to stick some fake facial hair on to cover up this fine specimen... ...I'd end up looking like His Lordship over there, wouldn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">......... ...Pardon? I, I assure you my lips are entirely unremarkable! And I would ask you not to cast such scrutinising looks in my direction, Counsel!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ah! Sorry...My Lord. <thought>My imagination got the better of me there.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, Inspector Gregson did wear a moustache, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You're right! He did! So...perhaps he was hiding something himself...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">He could barely have hidden a crumb in a moustache of that size.</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">And anyway, ze detective we spoke wiz 'ad no facial 'air at all.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, si, the capo is-a right. He was-a clean shaven.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... It certainly seems beyond the realms of possibility that this witness could have disguised himself as the victim.</line>
<line speaker="Gossip/Boone">Aye, it doz and it is!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's the extent of their testimony, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's your feeling, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, what Mr Gossip says is undeniable: It would be all but impossible to hide those lips with any form of disguise.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps, yes... But nevertheless, the mark around his neck is equally undeniable. And it's identical to the one that Mr de Rossi suffered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's true... <thought>But why does this whole disguise idea just keep playing on my mind...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>That's the extent of their testimony, is it?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">What's your feeling, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, what Mr Boone says is undeniable: It would be all but impossible to hide those lips with any form of disguise.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Perhaps, yes... But nevertheless, the mark around his neck is equally undeniable. And it's identical to the one that Mr de Rossi suffered.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's true... <thought>But why does this whole disguise idea just keep playing on my mind...?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">If you have no 'kinfolk' as you put it... ...then explain why it is that among the sparce furnishings, we found this photograph in the room?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Ah!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I presume, as you've been renting the room, that this photograph belongs to you, does it not?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Oh, um...well...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Boone, drop the pretence...and tell the court exactly who you really are!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">I, I don't know what...what you mean. I'm a pedlar! I, I keep telling you so! You really don't need to bother with me. Please, just...just leave it alone!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As the man says... ...leave it alone. Whatever the truth is about this man's life, it has no bearing on this case. Because it's simply not possible that he impersonated Inspector Gregson!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">How can you be so sure?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Just look at the man! No amount of disguise could ever hide those unmissable features!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But what if...we were to look at this the other way around?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Yes, Counsel, what do you mean?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well...there's no denying that Mr Boone's lip is very prominent indeed. But consider the possibility...that his prominent lip is itself part of an elaborate disguise!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Then hiding that prominent feature - in other words revealing his true face... ...would make an utterly impenetrable disguise! Wouldn't you agree...Mr Hugh Boone?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Aaah... AAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Good- Witness! Are you still hiding the truth from this court?!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">If, if that's a disguise, then... ...underneath it, his true identity must be...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes, that's right. There's really only one person he could really be. My Lord! The defence believes it can reveal Mr Boone's true identity to the court!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">No... Please...no...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very well then, Counsel... What is the true identity of this pedlar who goes simply by the name of 'Gossip' on the street?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Without question, My Lord!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But...would it therefore not be the case... ...that those lips are no disguise at all?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAAH! Ugh...I walked right into that one, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid so. And I really can't sympathise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't help being a little curious about how it would feel to have a lip like that, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't dig yourself in any deeper now, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Judge:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's really not much of an exaggeration to say... ...that anybody could be Mr Gossip just by attaching that enormous bottom lip!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If that's what you think... ...then why don't you put on some fake lips and try living as a street pedlar yourself?!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">GAAAAAAAAAH! Ugh...I walked right into that one, didn't I?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">I'm afraid so. And I really can't sympathise.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I can't help being a little curious about how it would feel to have a lip like that, actually...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Don't dig yourself in any deeper now, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Your real name...is actually Mr Vigil, isn't it? Mr Daley Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">YAAAAAAAAAAAAGH!!!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I don't recall that name, Counsel. Who is this Mr Vigil?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a name I encountered yesterday, My Lord. It has to do with a certain client of Mr Herlock Sholmes. A young gentlewoman came to the detective asking him to locate her missing husband. The woman in this photograph, in fact. This is Mrs Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">W-What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">From what I understand, you haven't returned home since the night before the inspector was found dead.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Erm...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But of course on that night, you were being held captive by the two Red-Headed League men.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And last night, you were put up by the prosecution service in preparation for testifying in this trial. Because we'd been led to believe that you, Miss Venus and Mr Sandwich were all homeless. Being important witnesses in this case, we needed to know where we could find you, of course.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And that explains why you've not only been unable to return home, but also unable to contact your wife... ...who's been beside herself with worry, waiting for you at the Vigil residence.</line>
<line speaker="Boone">Now, now just you hold on a minute! I don't have the first idea-</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">What I'm talking about? Really?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">It's a simple enough matter to confirm my suspicions! All we have to do is pull off that disguise!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">N-No... Please!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Bailiff! Bring soap, a sponge and a washbowl at once! Mr de Rousseau and Mr de Rossi, you will restrain the witness!</line>
<line speaker="Boone">UWAAAAAAAAAGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well... ...we are now seeing your true features, I presume?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Lift your head, sir. So the court can see your face.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">It would appear that the defence counsel's assertion was entirely correct. This has all been a very elaborate deception. So, witnesses, tell the court: have you seen this man before?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I, I don't believe it, but...</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Si, there is-a no question. This is-a the inspector we saw in the park!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Extraordinary!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">On the day of the Red-Headed League enrolment... ...the man claiming to be Inspector Gregson who appeared before Mr de Rousseau and Mr de Rossi in the park...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...Was you, disguised as the inspector! Or rather... ...was you posing as the inspector in no disguise at all!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Vigil was formerly employed as the chief warder at Barclay Prison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The chief warder? Then your career had promise. Why, you would quite possibly have become the future governor of the prison. What on earth have you been doing peddling tittle-tattle on Fresno Street?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, it's been ten years since Mr Vigil worked at the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Ten years?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... I'm...I'm really dreadfully sorry about all of this. Yes, it's true... I am Daley Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And you were the chief warder at Barclay Prison ten years ago...? ......... So where did Mr Hugh Boone come from?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Boone is...the other me. It's a name I invented.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Well...evidently there is a great deal under the surface here.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'll...explain everything. I'll tell you just how wretched my life has become.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">As you say, it was ten years ago now that my employment as Barclay's chief warder came to an end. Having left the prison service, I searched for some new occupation by which to earn a wage. But times were hard in London, and I found no suitable engagements at all. In desperation one day, I turned my hand at selling wares on Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But your wife appears to know nothing of this. She still maintains that you are the chief warder at Barclay Prison.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I was utterly determined that my wife should not know of my failings. Which is why I've never told her. I opened an account at the bank under the name of Hugh Boone... ...and I rented the cheapest room I could find on Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The scene of the very crime we're investigating.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">...Yes, that's right. A place from which I could emerge every morning at eight as a squalid pedlar... ...and transform myself back every evening at five into a well-dressed man about town before returning home. That quickly became my daily routine.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I was puzzled by the lack of furniture in the room... ...but that explains it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">But why on earth didn't you just tell us this in the first place?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I have a wife, sir. And two sons. And without wishing to sound self-conceited, they regard me with some pride. I...couldn't bring myself to disappoint them.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So instead you decided to conceal your occupation from them?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">...Yes. I've made such a terrible mess of everything...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Still, one thing doesn't add up. No matter how many 'titbits' of information you could sell to passing gentlemen, even at sixpence a piece... ...you couldn't hope to match the salary you must have commanded as chief warder at the prison.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Very true. To have kept your family in comfort, despite ten years of somewhat misbegotten employment...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... That was all thanks to Inspector Gregson.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha...? Inspector Gregson?! What on earth...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">It was some years after I'd invented Boone and begun my other life as a street seller. He - the inspector, that is - recognised me one day.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Do you mean to say...the victim was an acquaintance of yours?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I knew him from my time working at the prison. When he saw what I'd become, he...was deeply troubled for me and my family. And from that day forward, he visited me on Fresno Street with increasing regularity. Then one day...he asked me if I would carry out a secret assignment for him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">A, a secret...?! What was it?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I was to...impersonate the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">What?! Impersonate him?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">We always met in that little room so the inspector could brief me. 'Visit Orczy's tomorrow and take a statement from the proprietress.' It was always something along those lines. Surveillance work, interviewing people... On those occasions, he would lend me his identification so people would believe who I was. My instructions were to make an impression. To let people know that Inspector Gregson had been at work. And for those services, he compensated me financially.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">A Scotland Yard inspector willingly relinquished his identification into your care with intent to deceive?! That - as I'm sure I need not point out - is a very serious criminal offence.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But why? What was the point of you impersonating him?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I...I truthfully do not know. All I can say... ...is that the inspector warned me on numerous occasions:</line>
<line speaker="Gregson">Now remember, Vigil. I need your solemn word. You don't blab about this to anyone, alright? Ever! Even if... Well, if I end up a croaker.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">In time, he started to bring papers with him to the room as well. It became something of a second office for him.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">So...in fact... ...the person who declared himself to be Inspector Gregson at the park on Lime Street was really....</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes. It was me. Acting on the inspector's orders. As usual, I removed my Boone disguise... ...and then went as instructed to the park, armed with the inspector's identification book. It never occurred to me...that the bruise on my neck might give me away.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well... ...it would seem this confession completely destroys the defence's case.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Explain yourself, Prosecutor Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">My learned friend's assertion was as follows: The victim was killed at another location on the day before his corpse was discovered... ...at the hands of these two Red-Headed League men when they imprisoned the inspector.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">But no! That can't be! After all...it wasn't the inspector who went to the park that day; it was me!</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh goodness...</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Finally, we 'ave clarity. We 'ad nothing to do wiz ze murder of ze inspector. And merci, monsieur de la dfense...for proving it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha... AAAAAAAAAAAARGH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Ordaaaaaar!!! Indeed it would appear that we have reached a de facto conclusion of sorts. These witnesses had no involvement in the murder of the victim... ...as proven, somewhat ironically, by the defence.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Uuugh...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I hereby call an end to the cross-examination.</line>
<line speaker="???"><cutIn type="holdIt">Hold it!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Pardon me, My Lord, but with your permission... ...I would like to pose one further question to the witness.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Kazuma...?</line>
<line speaker="Judge">What question, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">It concerns the events of ten years ago. I believe you would have been present at a very significant execution that was carried out at the time.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Ten years ago...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>The execution of the Professor...Genshin Asogi!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I want to know...exactly what your involvement was.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Oh!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Answer me, man!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">...!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">One moment, Counsel! Is this related to the current case?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... Naturally. It is the prosecution's belief that this case and the events of ten years ago... ...are inextricably linked.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Hmmm... Does the defence concur, Counsel?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Kazuma... You're not yourself. You're not as calm and collected as usual.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Poor Kazuma-sama. No wonder he's acting this way. Mr Vigil's memories of what happened ten years ago... ...would tell the tale of Genshin Asogi's last moments. His own father...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I know. I do understand that. <thought>But even so...</thought> Kazu- ...Prosecutor Asogi.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">...!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Do you genuinely believe... ...that this question requires an answer in order to learn the truth behind Inspector Gregson's death?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I need you to trust me. ...Please.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Very well. Then the defence has no objection.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...I see. In that case, you will answer the question, witness.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... The, the truth is... ...I remember very little of that time.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">You've forgotten?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I'm sorry to say, yes. As I said, I resigned from my role at the prison ten years ago. But for some peculiar reason...my memory of the events leading up to that moment is extremely hazy.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">.........</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Does that not strike you as strange, Mr Naruhodo?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Well, ten years is a long time... ...but to have forgotten the reason why he left such an important job...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes...you're right. <thought>And not only that... ...Mr Vigil's claim contradicts what we already know.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">The human spirit is a fragile thing. It's broken all too easily. Which is why... ...we have a tendency to wrap it up for protection.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Sorry? The, the human spirit...? I'm afraid I don't understand what you mean.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">When we experience pain and suffering that we feel unable to bear... ...we block it out. Obliterate it from our memories. Seal it away. But it never truly leaves us. If the seal is broken, the memories resurface. And when they do...that fragile spirit may finally be crushed.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">But, but I really don't...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">But if it must be crushed, then so be it! Because the truth will not stay buried! It's coming out...one way or another!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... <thought>Right... Now I understand. It's clear what his intentions are. He means to expose the truth...at any cost.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">.........</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Perhaps if I pointed out the contradiction in what Mr Vigil claimed earlier... ...it might cause some crucial memories to return to him. ...But should I? Should I present the evidence or not?</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>I have no idea how this is going to go... ...but this is a court of law and I have a duty to pursue the truth!</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>If it could genuinely crush the man's spirit... ...I can't be responsible for that. I don't have the right.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Susato">Kazuma-sama won't rest until he knows. And this is a court of law. Where nothing is more sacred than the pursuit of the truth.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...! <thought>Susato-san's right. I knew the risks when I took the decision to fight this trial. Whatever the consequences...I can't shy away from my responsibility now.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Vigil! I'd like you to look at this... Evidence that clearly contradicts your version of events!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Leads to:</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Ryunosuke:</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">W-What do you mean to do? The way you're looking at me...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>He claims that he resigned from his job at the prison all those years ago. But we have decisive evidence that says differently.</thought> I'm sorry, I made a mistake. Allow me to present the evidence again.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Just a few moments ago, you made the following statement: 'I resigned from my role at the prison ten years ago.'</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Ah...well, yes...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In other words, you claim to have left the post of chief warder of your own volition.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Well...yes, of course. ...Why?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Tell me... ...do you remember seeing this document before?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">No. No, I don't.</line>
<line speaker="RYunosuke">This is a dismissal notice ordering the immediate termination of a prison staff member's employment.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">A dismissal notice...?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">And the name on the notice...is yours, Mr Vigil.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Wha...? WHAT?! It's...it's...MINE?!</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">So you didn't resign from the prison service at all. For some reason...you were dismissed as chief warder from Barclay.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">No, there's...there's been some mistake. I'm...I'm sure... I'm sure I tendered my resignation! This dismissal notice is nonsense! ...Isn't...it?</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">If you were forcibly dismissed, there must have been good reason. Clearly...you did something. Mr Vigil! It's time to break the seal and have you remember!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">......... According to the few remaining records... ...the final execution that you supervised was on 17th June ten years ago. And on that day, something very serious took place at Barclay Prison.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The 17th...of June...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Was, was that... ...the Professor's execution?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Pro...fessor...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">As you were the chief warder at the time, it stands to reason... ...that you would have been present throughout the proceedings.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">It, it does...sound...familiar...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">And yet! That execution never took place! ...The convict, ostensibly executed earlier that day, later re-emerged from his grave...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The convict...came back to life...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">In the cemetery in the middle of the night. There was a witness.</line>
<line speaker="Susato">However, the witness claims that a moment after he saw the convict clambering out of his grave... ...a gunshot rang out from over his shoulder. And the bullet pierced the Professor's chest...killing him instantly. Those may have been the Professor's actual last moments.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yeees... Yeeeeeesss...</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Seeing as you were in charge of overseeing executions at the time... ...you must know the truth about what really happened! It's in your head! Somewhere deep down!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">.........</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">Well...Chief Warder Daley Vigil? I know there are memories in your head that can explain what happened on 17th June ten years ago. And now it's time...for you to drag them up!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Agh... Aaaaaagh...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr...Mr Vigil...?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... .................. Yes... The whole prison... It was complete chaos... The prisoner escaped... He was killed...in the cemetery... The shocking news ripped through Barclay like a hurricane...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Wha......... WHAAAAAAAAAT?!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">O-Ordaaar! ...Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Do, do you mean to say, Mr Vigil... that your memories of the time have returned?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">My head, it's... It's like some floodgates have been opened. The images... The screams...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Oh...my goodness...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">The papers... There...were reports... Articles...about a man who'd seen a ghost...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Yes. Enoch Drebber.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">But, but surely those reports were exaggerated...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">......... There were traces at the scene...</line>
<line speaker="Susato">Traces of what?</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">In Lowgate Cemetery...at plot number 139... Blood... Lots of blood... That's where the man was buried of course. Obviously...something terrible had happened there.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">The depths of conspiracy and depravity from which this tale is emerging are quite staggering.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I've reviewed the police records from that time extensively. A thorough investigation was conducted by Scotland Yard... ...to ascertain how the convict managed to escape in the first place. And the conclusion reached by the investigating team was... ...that a member of the prison staff must have been involved.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Are you suggesting... ...that a prison warder abetted the man's bid for freedom?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">Yes... Yes, and I...I was suspected of doing it. Of using that mass murderer's execution...as a way to help him escape...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You did what?!</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">I remember now. The horror of it all is coming back to me. One evening a few days after the execution, some detectives came to the prison. I was called to the governor's office at the top of the watchtower.</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">As soon as he told me that,  my mind just went completely blank. And...and the next thing I knew, I...</line>
<line speaker="Vigil">AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Ordaaar! Ordaaar! Bailiff! Fetch a doctor at once! Court is adjourned for today with immediate effect!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">I can't find anything out of place.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That last statement was contradictory in a number of ways, I think you'll find!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">In a number of ways, you say?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">That's right, My Lord. In a number of ways!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Perhaps it would serve you well to concentrate your efforts on one contradiction at a time, Counsel.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... I made a bit of a mess of that. In a number of ways, actually.</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">The witness's last statement is clearly contradictory when you consider this piece of evidence here! Yes! Undeniably!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">You say it's undeniable, Counsel, but I fail to see any contradiction here at all.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... I think perhaps that itself is the contradiction.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Indeed.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Ugh... Time for a rethink...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><cutIn type="objection">Objection!</cutIn></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">My Lord! There are clearly grounds for being suspicious of that last statement!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">I'm sorry, Counsel, but I fail to see why.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, you know...I was just playing devil's advocate!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">...Yes. You do appear to have something of the devil in you, Mr Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke"><thought>Says the man merrily dishing out penalties...</thought></line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Well, Miss Venus?! What do you say?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">I say that'll be six 'undred pennies.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Venus">That's my banter on the street whenever anyone comes along.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">W-Well...this isn't Fresno Street.</line>
<line speaker="Venus">Tsk! Miser!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Gossip! Do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Gossip">I do as it happens! Your timing's perfect. I've just got wind of a juicy tale that'll be right up your snicket. You don't want to let this one slip by, I tell ya. And sixpence is all I ask...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe try Prosecutor Asogi instead.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't want your gossip, Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Sandwich! Do you perhaps have something to fill us in with?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">A w-wise philosopher once said that p-people are nothing more than mindless signposts.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Sorry?</line>
<line speaker="Sandwich">Which means... ...that signposts are n-nothing more than mindless people...if you think about it.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">......... Perhaps mind less about philosophy and mind more about the proceedings?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr de Rousseau! Is something wrong?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I was just considering something.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">About the testimony? Did something that was just said jar with you?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">Non. I was considering my next cunning plan.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Fantastico, capo! The Hairlarious Brothers are-a gonna be back in action, ay?</line>
<line speaker="De Rousseau">I sink my next enterprise will be an exclusive club called...ze Four-Eyed League!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Kindly discuss your upcoming criminal activities once you're back in your cell.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr de Rossi! Do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">Che? What?</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">You looked as though you were thinking of something... whilst eating a mouthful of pasta.</line>
<line speaker="De Rossi">......... Ah, si. I was-a thinking... ...perhaps my hair is this-a colour because I eat too much Bolognese sauce.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...No comment.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">'Scuse me!</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">Mr Boone! Do you have something to say?</line>
<line speaker="Boone">I do as it happens! Your timing's perfect. I've just got wind of a juicy tale that'll be right up your snicket. You don't want to let this one slip by, I tell ya. And sixpence is all I ask...</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">...Maybe try Prosecutor Asogi instead.</line>
<line speaker="Kazuma">I don't want your gossip, Ryunosuke Naruhodo.</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That will do! I believe I have heard quite enough evidence to form an unbiased opinion. As this is a closed trial, the findings of this court will not be disclosed to the public. However, this will be the very last time the Reaper stands in this or any other courtroom.</line>
<line speaker="Ryunosuke">B-But, My Lord! Wait!</line>
<line speaker="Judge">Barok van Zieks, in accordance with the findings of this court, I pronounce you...</line>
<line speaker="Judge">That is all. Court is adjourned!</line>
</xml>