<lyrics>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>If I asked that boy to jump, I know he would</l>
<l>He don't even have to say, it's understood</l>
<l>He treat me nice, he treat me right, he treat me good</l>
<l>Still I get so hesitant, still I get so hesitant</l>
<l>So I took myself where I think I should be</l>
<l>Something told me that it's waiting here for me</l>
<l>Parisian nights, Parisian high, Parisian breeze</l>
<l>Feeding me like medicine, feeding me like medicine, yeah</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>It's so romantic in Paris</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
<l>It's so romantic in Paris</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
<l>Yeah, I already have love in L.A. </l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>If you show me too much love, it makes me leave (Makes me leave)</l>
<l>Guess that's one of many things that's wrong with me (That's wrong with me)</l>
<l>Looking past you when you're right in front of me</l>
<l>I won't do that anymore, I won't do that anymore (Anymore)</l>
<l>Why'd it take so long for me to know this? (Know this)</l>
<l>Scared to put the water with the roses (Roses)</l>
<l>Halfway 'cross the world for me to notice</l>
<l>But I notice, yeah, I notice, yeah</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>It's so romantic in Paris</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
<l>It's so romantic in Paris</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>Je ne voulais pas trouver l'amour</l>
<l>Mais Paris a quelque chose</l>
<l>Qui donne envie d'aimer, d'aimer passionnément</l>
<l>Mon cœur est à toi pour toujours</l>
<l>You will always have my heart</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>It's so romantic in Paris</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. (Already have love)</l>
<l>It's so romantic in Paris (So romantic in Paris)</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it (I know that I try)</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
<l>It's so romantic in Paris, babe</l>
<l>Won't even try to compare it (Won't even try, won't even try)</l>
<l>Thought I was sure that I'd find it (Thought I was sure, I was sure)</l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
<l>But I already have love in L.A. </l>
</section>
</lyrics>
