<lyrics>
<section type="intro">
<l>La-da-da-da, da-da-da (Da-da-da-da-da)</l>
<l>La-da-da-da-da</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>If I told you how much I think about her</l>
<l>You'd think I was in love</l>
<l>And if you knew how much I looked at her pictures</l>
<l>You would think we're best friends</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>'Cause I know her star sign, I know her blood type</l>
<l>I've seen every movie she's been in, and, oh God, she's beautiful</l>
<l>And I know you loved her, and I know I'm butthurt</l>
<l>But I can't help it, no, I can't help it</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>I'm so obsessed with your ex (Uh-huh)</l>
<l>I know she's been asleep on my side of your bed, and I can feel it</l>
<l>I'm starin' at her like I wanna get hurt</l>
<l>And I remember every detail you have evеr told me, so be careful, baby</l>
<l>I'm so obsеssed with your ex (Ah)</l>
<l>Yeah, I'm so obsessed with your ex (Ah)</l>
</section>
<section type="post-chorus">
<l>La-da-da-da, da-da-da</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>She's got those lips, she's got those hips</l>
<l>The life of every fuckin' party</l>
<l>She's talented, she's good with kids</l>
<l>She even speaks kindly about me, ah-ah</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>And I know you love me, and I know it's crazy</l>
<l>But every time you call my name, I think you mistake me for her</l>
<l>You both have moved on, you don't even talk</l>
<l>But I can't help it, I got issues, I can't help it, baby</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>I'm so obsessed with your ex</l>
<l>I know she's been asleep on my side in your bed, and I can feel her</l>
<l>I'm starin' at her like I wanna get hurt</l>
<l>And I remember every detail you have ever told me, so be careful, baby</l>
<l>I'm so obsessed with your ex (Ah)</l>
<l>Yeah, I'm so obsessed with your ex (Ah)</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>Is she friends with your friends? Is she good in bed?</l>
<l>Do you think about her? No? I'm fine, it doesn't matter, tell me</l>
<l>Is she easy-going? Never controlling?</l>
<l>Well-traveled? Well-read? Oh God, she's makin' me so obsessed</l>
</section>
<section type="outro">
<l>I'm so obsessed with your ex (Ah)</l>
<l>She's been asleep on my side in your bed (Ah), woah</l>
<l>I'm so obsessed with your ex (God, she makes me so upset)</l>
<l>I'm so obsessed with your, with your ex</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
