<lyrics>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>Perfect, easy, so good to me</l>
<l>So why's there a pit in my gut in the shape of you?</l>
<l>Distract myself, say it's somethin' else</l>
<l>Maybe I'm just overwhelmed, maybe I'm confused</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>Barely sleep when you sleep next to me</l>
<l>But I keep thinkin' I'll find a cure</l>
<l>I say that I'm fine, I tell you all the time</l>
<l>I've never felt so happy and sure</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>But I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>'Cause it cuts right through to the heart</l>
<l>Yeah, it knows me too well so I got no excuse</l>
<l>I can't lie to it the same way that I lie to you</l>
<l>I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>If I play it, then I'll think too hard</l>
<l>Once you let the thought in, then it's already done</l>
<l>So I lay in your arms and pretend that it's love</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>If I was brave and noble like you</l>
<l>I'd have the nerve to just stop stringin' you along</l>
<l>But I'm not half as decent as you</l>
<l>I'd rather be tied to someone, even if they're wrong</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>I make excuses, my friends know the truth is</l>
<l>I'm not as alright as I claim</l>
<l>I say that I'm fine, I tell them all the time</l>
<l>As they watch all the life fade away</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>Yeah, I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>'Cause it cuts right through to the heart</l>
<l>Yeah, it knows me too well so I got no excuse</l>
<l>I can't lie to it the same way that I lie to you</l>
<l>I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>If I play it, then I'll think too hard</l>
<l>Once you let the thought in, then it's already done</l>
<l>So I lay in your arms and pretend that it's love</l>
<l>Yeah, I lay in your arms and pretend that it's love</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>I pretend that it's love</l>
<l>I pretend that it's love</l>
<l>I pretend that it's love, love</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>'Cause what if I never find anything better?</l>
<l>The doubt always creeps through my mind</l>
<l>So we'll stay together 'cause how could I ever</l>
<l>Trade somethin' that's good for what's right?</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>Oh, I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>It cuts right through to my heart</l>
<l>It knows me too well, I got no excuse</l>
<l>I can't lie to it the same way that I lie to you</l>
<l>I'm so scared of my guitar</l>
<l>When I play it is when I think too hard</l>
<l>I let the thought in, it's already done</l>
<l>But I lay in your arms and pretend that it's love</l>
<l>Yeah, I lay in your arms and pretend it's enough</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
