<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <para num="1">Knowing how to change a tire is a necessary skill for all drivers. If you rely on
        a cell phone to save you in a roadside emergency, there’s always that chance you will forget
        to charge it, be out of range, or leave it at home. Flat tires can happen anywhere, and a
        cell phone is no substitute for knowing how to change a flat tire.</para>
    <para num="2">Thankfully, changing a tire isn’t all that hard! Just adhere to the following
        guidelines to be prepared in case you have a flat.</para>
    <para num="3">
        <heading>ITEMS YOU'LL NEED TO FIX A FLAT TIRE</heading>
        <subheading>These items should have come with your vehicle:</subheading>
        <item xml:id="jack">Jack</item>
        <item xml:id="lWrentch">Lug wrench</item>
        <item xmlid="spare">Fully inflated spare tire</item>
        <item xml:id="manual">Vehicle owner’s manual</item>
    </para>
    <para num="4">
        <body>If you have misplaced any of these items, or if your car did not come with these
            items, you should purchase new ones right away. And be sure you’re regularly inflating
            the spare tire to your vehicle manufacturer’s recommended PSI. You should check the
            spare’s air pressure every time you check your other tires. Remember to check pressure
            every month and before long trips or carrying extra load.</body>
    </para>
    <para num="5">Here are some items that don’t come with your vehicle but that you should stow in
        your trunk or glove box in case you have to change a flat tire: <item>Flashlight with
            working batteries</item>
        <item xml:id="poncho">Rain poncho</item>
        <item xml:id="wood"> Small cut of
                    <mesure><quant>2</quant><unit>"</unit>X<quant>6</quant><unit>”</unit></mesure>
            wood to secure the jack</item>
        <item xml:id="glove">Gloves</item>
        <item xml:id="whWedges">Wheel wedges</item></para>
    <para num="6">
        <heading>HOW TO CHANGE TIRES</heading>
        <body>
            <step num="1">
                <heading xml:id="safeLocation">FIND A SAFE LOCATION</heading>
                <body>As soon as you realize you have a flat tire, do not abruptly brake or turn.
                        <action>Slowly reduce speed</action> and <action>scan</action> your
                    surroundings for a level, straight stretch of road with a wide shoulder. An
                    empty parking lot would be an ideal place. <tip>Level ground</tip> is good
                    because it will prevent your vehicle from rolling. Also, <tip>straight stretches
                        of road are better than curves because oncoming traffic is more likely to
                        see you</tip>. Never attempt to change your tire on a narrow shoulder near
                    oncoming traffic. Keep moving (slowly) until you find a safer spot. While
                    driving on a flat risks ruining your rim, replacing a rim is better than being
                    hit by an inattentive driver. Make sure to <action>consult</action> your owner’s
                    manual and review their specific steps on how to change a flat tire for your
                    vehicle</body>
            </step>
            <step num="2">
                <heading xml:id="hazardLights">TURN ON YOUR HAZARD LIGHTS</heading>
                <body>Your <item xml:id="hazards">hazard lights or <alt>“flashers”</alt></item> will
                    help other drivers see you on the side of the road. To avoid an accident,
                        <action>turn</action> them on as soon as you realize you need to pull
                    over.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="3">
                <heading xml:id="parkingBreak">APPLY THE PARKING BRAKE</heading>
                <body> Once stopped, always use the <item xml:id="parkingBrake">parking brake</item>
                    when preparing to replace a flat tire. This will minimize the possibility of
                    your vehicle rolling.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="4">
                <heading xml:id="whWedges">APPLY WHEEL WEDGES</heading>
                <body><item xml:id="whWedges">Wheel wedges</item> go in front of or behind the tires
                    to further ensure the vehicle doesn’t roll while you fix the <item
                        xml:id="flatTire">flat tire</item>. <tip>If you’re changing a rear tire,
                        place these in front of the front tires. If your <item xml:id="flatTire"
                            >flat tire</item> is at the front, put the wheel wedges behind the rear
                        tires</tip>. Bricks or large stones will work just as well as “real” wheel
                    wedges. Just be sure they’re large enough to stop the car from rolling.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="5">
                <heading xml:id="hubcapRemove">REMOVE THE HUBCAP OR WHEEL COVER </heading>
                <body>If your vehicle has a <item xml:id="hubCap">hubcap</item> covering the <item
                        xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item>, it’s easier to remove the <item
                        xml:id="hubcap">hubcap</item> before lifting the vehicle with the <item
                        xml:id="jack">jack</item>. If your <item xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item> are
                    exposed, you can skip ahead to Step 6. Use the flat end of your <item
                        xml:id="lWrench">lug wrench</item> to <action>remove</action> the <item
                        xml:id="hubCap">hubcap</item>. This will work for most vehicles, but some
                        <item xml:id="hubCap">hubcaps</item> need a different tool to come off.
                        <action> Consult </action>your owner’s manual for proper <item
                        xml:id="hubCap">hubcap</item> or wheel cover removal procedures.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="6">
                <heading xml:id="lugNutsLosen">LOOSEN THE LUG NUTS</heading>
                <body>Using the <item xml:id="lWrench">lug wrench</item>, turn the <item
                        xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item> counterclockwise until you break their
                    resistance. You may have to use force, and that’s ok. Use your foot or all of
                    your body weight if necessary. Loosen the <item xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item>
                    about <measure num="0.25">¼</measure> to <measure num="0.5">½</measure> of a
                    turn, but don’t remove them completely yet. Save that for when it’s time to
                    remove your tire/wheel from the vehicle.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="7">
                <heading xml:id="jackPlace">PLACE THE JACK UNDER THE VEHICLE</heading>
                <body>The right place for the <item xml:id="jack">jack</item> is usually beneath the
                    vehicle frame alongside the tire that’s flat. Many vehicle frames have molded
                    plastic on the bottom with a cleared area of exposed metal specifically for the
                        <item xml:id="jack">jack</item>. To safely lift and avoid damage to the
                    vehicle, follow the instructions for <item xml:id="jack">jack</item> placement
                    in your <item xml:id="manual">vehicle owner’s manual</item>.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="8">
                <heading xml:id="jackRaise">RAISE THE VEHICLE WITH THE JACK</heading>
                <body>To prevent the <item xml:id="jack">jack</item> from settling under the weight
                    of your vehicle and coming off balance, <action>place</action> a small cut of
                        <item xml:id="wood">2x6” wood</item> beneath it before attempting to raise
                    your vehicle. This tactic is especially helpful on asphalt. With the <item
                        xml:id="jack">jack</item> properly positioned, raise the vehicle until the
                    flat tire is about <masure><quant num="6">six</quant>
                        <unit>inches</unit></masure> above the ground.<action> Never put</action>
                    any part of your body under the vehicle during or after raising the vehicle with
                    the <item xml:id="jack">jack</item>.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="9">
                <heading xml:id="lugNutsUnscrew">UNSCREW THE LUG NUTS</heading>
                <body>Now it’s time to <action>remove</action> the <item xml:id="lugNut">lug
                        nuts</item> all the way. Since you've already loosened them, you should be
                    able to <action>unscrew</action> them mostly by hand.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="10">
                <heading xml:id="flatTireRemove">REMOVE THE FLAT TIRE</heading>
                <body><action>Gripping</action> the <item xml:id="flatTire">tire</item> by the
                    treads, <action>pull</action> it gently toward you until it’s completely free
                    from the hub behind it. <action>Set it </action> on its sideso that it doesn’t
                    roll away.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="11">
                <heading xml:id="spareTireMount">MOUNT THE SPARE TIRE ON THE LUG BOLTS</heading>
                <body>Now place the spare on the hub by lining up the rim with the lug bolts. Push
                    gently until the lug bolts show through the rim.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="12">
                <heading xml:id="lugNutsTighten">TIGHTEN THE LUG NUTS BY HAND</heading>
                <body>Put the lug nuts back on the lug bolts and tighten them all the way by hand.
                    Once they are all on, check each one again, tightening as much as possible. You
                    will tighten them with the wrench after lowering the vehicle to the
                    ground.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="13">
                <heading xml:id="lowerANDTighten">LOWER THE VEHICLE AND TIGHTEN THE LUG NUTS
                    AGAIN</heading>
                <body><action>Use</action> the <item xml:id="jack">jack</item> to <action>lower
                    </action>the vehicle so that the spare tire is resting on the ground but the
                    full weight of the vehicle isn’t fully on the tire. At this point, you should
                        <action>tighten</action> the <item xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item> with the
                    wrench, turning clockwise, as much as you can. Push down on the lug wrench with
                    the full weight of your body.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="14"><heading xml:id="lowerCompletely">LOWER THE VEHICLE COMPLETELY</heading>
                <body><action>Bring</action> the vehicle all the way to the ground and
                        <action>remove</action> the <item xml:id="jack">jack</item>. Give the <item
                        xml:id="lugNut">lug nuts</item> another pull with the wrench to
                        <action>ensure</action> they’re as tight as possible</body>.</step>
            <step num="15">
                <heading xml:id="replaceHubcap">REPLACE THE HUBCAP</heading>
                <body>If the <item xml:id="hubCap">hubcap</item> you took from the <item
                        xml:id="flatTire">flat tire</item> will fit your spare, <action>put it in
                        place</action> the same way you removed it initially. If it doesn’t fit,
                    stow it away with the tire when you stow your equipment.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="16">
                <heading xml:id="stowEqipment">STOW ALL EQUIPMENT</heading>
                <body>You have before you a <item xml:id="jack">jack</item>, a <item
                        xml:id="lWrench">lug wrench</item>, <item xml:id="whWedges">wheel
                        wedges</item>, your <item xml:id="flatTire">flat tire</item>, and possibly a
                        <item xml:id="hubCap">hubcap</item>. Don’t forget to put all of them in your
                    vehicle before driving away.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="17">
                <heading xml:id="checkSparePressure">CHECK THE PRESSURE IN THE SPARE TIRE</heading>
                <body>You should <action>check</action>the tire pressure of the spare tire to make
                    sure that it is safe to drive on. “T-Type” temporary spares, also called
                    “mini-spares,” require 60 psi (420 kPa). If the tire needs pressure, drive
                    (slowly) to a service station immediately.</body>
            </step>
            <step num="18">
                <heading xml:id="flatToTechnician">TAKE YOUR FLAT TIRE TO A TECHNICIAN</heading>
                <body>Temporary spare tires aren’t made to drive long distances or at high speeds,
                    so drive cautiously until you’re able to visit a tire technician. A professional
                    should be able to determine whether your tire needs a repair or if it’s time to
                    replace it.</body>
            </step>
        </body>
    </para>
    <para num="7"><heading>HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE TO FIX A FLAT TIRE? </heading>Aside from taking
        your tire to a professional, the above procedure shouldn’t take more than
                <time><quant>15</quant> to <quant>30</quant>
            <unit>minutes</unit></time> to change a tire. Just be sure you don’t leave out any
        steps. It’s beneficial practice changing a tire in your garage or driveway to ensure you’re
        ready to handle this situation if it ever happens to you.</para>
    <para num="8"><heading>A FEW MORE TIPS ON CHANGING TIRES</heading> Knowing how to fix a flat
        tire is great, but regular tire maintenance is even more important. In addition to reviewing
        this guide regularly, remember to do the following: Keep your tires properly inflated Rotate
        your tires according to the manufacturer’s guidelines Monitor for tread wear All of these
        precautions will extend the life of your tires and reduce the likelihood of a flat. While
        there’s no way to prevent flat tires completely, proper care can improve performance and
        ensure your tires last as long as possible.</para>
</root>
