<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Dr. B's plan:
    How to open a new XML document in oXygen 
    Pasting in a blob of text
    Pretty print demonstration! 
    Elements fo  structure
    Attributes: what are they and why use them?
    Self-closing elements!
    Comments (like this!)
-->
<!--I'm typing some text above the root element.
I'm in a meta space that isn't really the XML document.
-->
<!-- type stuff -->
<root><title>Country Loaf (Pain de Campagne)</title>
    <authorInfo><author><name part="first">Deb</name>
            <name part="last">Lindsey</name></author> for <pubTitle>The Washington
        Post</pubTitle></authorInfo>
    <date>SEP 10, 2014</date>
    <para>Washington author Sam Fromartz has been making sourdough variations of this yeast bread
        for years. Here, he adds fermented cider for flavor. A mild beer may be substituted; an IPA
        would be too bitter. The loaf is sized to last a few days.</para>
    <para>The optional tablespoon of water is to compensate for the variable absorption of the rye
        and whole-wheat flours.</para>
    <para>You'll need a colander, a pastry cloth or clean dish towel and a covered cast-iron or
        enameled cast-iron pot.</para>
    <para>Make Ahead: The dough needs four 20-minute rests, plus an 8-to-24-hour stay in the
        refrigerator and a final 1 1/2-hour rise.</para>
    <para>Storage Notes: Store the cooled loaf in a paper bag for a day, and store in a plastic bag
        for a few days after that. Do not refrigerate.</para>
    <servingInfo><heading>SERVINGS:</heading>
        <size type="tested">Tested size: <quantity>10-12</quantity>
            <unit>servings</unit>;</size> makes one 11-ounce loaf 10 to 12 slices</servingInfo>
    <ingredienList>INGREDIENTS <i><measure><quant num="1.25">1 1/4</quant>
                <unit>cups</unit>
                <alt><quant>160</quant>
                    <unit>grams</unit></alt></measure> white bread flour, plus more for dusting</i>
        <i>1/4 cup (38 grams) stone-ground whole-wheat flour</i>
        <i>1/4 cup (32 grams) stone-ground whole rye flour</i>
        <i> 1/2 teaspoon instant yeast or bread machine yeast</i>
        <i>1 teaspoon table salt</i>
        <i>1/4 cup (55 grams) dry fermented cider (may substitute Pilsener beer; see headnote)</i>
        <i>1/2 cup (120 grams) lukewarm water (80 degrees), plus an optional 1
        tablespoon</i></ingredienList> DIRECTIONS Whisk together the flours, yeast and salt in a
    mixing bowl. Combine the cider and water in a liquid measuring cup. Add the liquid to the flour
    mixture; use a spatula or bench scraper or your hand moistened with water to blend them for
    about a minute. The dough should be shaggy yet cohesive. Cover the bowl with a towel; let the
    dough rest for 20 minutes. Moisten your kneading hand. If the dough seems stiff, add the
    optional tablespoon of water. Stretch one edge of the dough (still in the bowl), then press it
    into the center of the bowl. Repeat this about a dozen times, moving clockwise to catch all
    sides of the dough. (This should take 1 or 2 minutes.) Turn the dough over so the seams are on
    the bottom. Cover and let rest for 20 minutes. Repeat the clockwise stretching and folding two
    more times, with 20-minute rests after each. Cover and refrigerate at least 8 hours and up to 24
    hours. The dough should have doubled. If it hasn't, leave it on the counter until it does.
    Lightly flour a work surface. Use a pastry cloth or clean dish towel to line a round colander.
    Dust the cloth with flour. Transfer the dough to the floured work surface. Fold the edges toward
    the center to create a round shape, turning it over so the seams are on the bottom. Let it rest
    for 5 minutes, then transfer to the colander, seam side up. Cover with a towel and let the dough
    rise for 1 1/2 hours. Thirty minutes before baking, place a cast-iron Dutch oven (lid on) or
    enameled cast-iron pot with a lid (on) in the oven; preheat to 475 degrees. Carefully remove the
    hot pot from the oven. Turn the dough out onto the counter so the seams are on the bottom. Use
    kitchen scissors to make 8 snips on the top of the dough in an evenly spaced spoke pattern, each
    about 1/4-inch deep. Lift the dough and carefully drop it into the hot pot. Immediately cover
    with the hot lid. Bake for 30 minutes, then reduce the heat to 450 degrees. Uncover and bake for
    8 to 10 minutes or until the crust is dark brown. Try to minimize the amount of time the oven
    door is open. The bread is done when its internal temperature registers 205 degrees on an
    instant-read thermometer and the loaf sounds hollow when knocked on the underside. Transfer the
    loaf to a wire rack to cool for at least 1 hour before cutting.</root>
