<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>


<metadata><ep><epTitle>'Tis the 30th Season</epTitle><szn>30</szn>x<epNum>10</epNum></ep>












<date>12/10/18</date> <runtime>07:58</runtime></metadata>

Ho, ho, ho!  

<music>♪ ♪  </music>

<stage>SCHOOL BELL RINGS</stage>  

Happy birthday.  

<stage>WHISTLE BLOWS</stage>  

<stage>PLAYING "DECK THE HALLS"</stage>  

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!  

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>  

<stage>GROWLING</stage>   

<stage>GROWLS</stage>   

<stage>SHRIEKING</stage>   

ALL: Merry Christmas!   

- <stage>SNORING, MUMBLING</stage>
- <stage><person>HOMER</person> HUMMING</stage>   

<stage>SIGHS</stage> Another Thanksgiving is in the books.   

Which means Christmas is starting.   

Say, <fam>Lis</fam>, I couldn't help but notice you're holding a piece of paper.   

Oh, this piece of paper?   

Why, it's just my Christmas list, is all.   

What a coincidence.   

I also have my Christmas list right here in my hand.   

Oh, you selfish little gangsters.   

There's always another shakedown, isn't there?   

What do you know, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>? There's only one present on my list.   

My word, that's reasonable.   

I, too, only found one present to be list-worthy.   

Oh, give me the lists.   

<stage><person>MARGE</person> GROANS</stage>   

We already have a TV.   

We've been through ten Super Bowls, XLIV through LIII.   

But our dumb TV is not a smart TV.   

And I just want one other smart thing in this house.   

Yeah, well, we'll think about it.   

<stage><person>BART</person> AND <person>LISA</person> HUMMING HAPPILY</stage>   

I want everything about Christmas to be perfect, but that smart TV the kids want is $ ,   .   

<stage>SCOFFS</stage> That's ridiculous.   

Our TV may not be smart, but it's street smart.   

ANNOUNCER: It's Sprawl-Mart's huge Black Friday sale.   

Jay-G headphones only $  .  .   

Two-piece sofa set only $   .  .   

And this GL    K Smart TV only $   .  .   

GL    K Smart TV.
Where have I heard that before?   

The kids are chanting it nonstop.   

<person>BART</person> AND <person>LISA</person>: GL    K Smart TV.   

- GL    K Smart TV.
- Knock it off!   

ANNOUNCER: Supplies are limited, so be here when the doors open at  :   a.m.!   

Black Friday: like The Purge, but for bargains.   

That's how we get it. We have to go.   

Oh, old TV, you really are dumb.   

You just told us how to replace you. <stage>LAUGHS</stage>   

Why do we have an antenna on an HDTV?   

I thought it looked cool.   

So the customers will be entering from here, here and here.   

Our biggest concern are the cutsies.   

- I hate those n*zi.
- I said "cutsies."   

- You think the n*zi didn't take cuts?
- Oh.   

I leave for Sprawl-Mart now, getting us a good place in line.   

And I go to sleep now, waking up in the middle of the night, rested and ready to relieve you   

- at  :   a.m.
- That's right.   

Godspeed, hot woman.   

<stage>BOTH MOANING</stage>   

I love you, too, <fam>Homie</fam>, but I have to go.   

My tongue is frozen to your zipper.   

Aw, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, great to see you out here.   

You want a Cup O' Noodles to chase away the chill?   

- How sweet.
- It's just water.   

I can't afford the real thing, but if you stare at the label while you drink it, you'd swear there was real chicken powder in there.   

- <stage>SHUDDERS</stage>
- Oh.   

What bargain are you busting down the door for?   

I'm getting a Futon Friend for my granddaughter.   

I want her to remember me as more than just a <fam><person>grandpa</person></fam> who lives at the airport.   

The trick is to carry a piece of empty luggage because then they... they...   

<stage>SOBS</stage>   

<stage>SNIFFS</stage>   

Sorry, Ralphie, it's just too cold.   

Even my blubber isn't helping.   

<stage>SIGHS</stage> Cold in the winter, hot in the summer.   

Why did I grow you?   

Oh, your hands feel cold.
Let me look at them.   

Whoa, that's toasty! Am in Ipanema?   

<stage>VOCALIZING "GIRL FROM IPANEMA"</stage>   

Hmm? Hmm?   

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>   

I can do this. It's  :  .   

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s gonna be here any minute.   

<stage>SNORING</stage>   

<stage>ALARM BEEPING</stage>   

<stage>MUMBLES</stage> What?   

- <stage>MEOWS</stage>
- What the...?   

<stage>MEOWS</stage>    

Ooh, got to relieve <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>!    

<stage>SHUDDERS</stage>    

<stage>GROANS</stage>    

My hands are starting to freeze.    

I hope <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> gets here soon.    

Why are we standing?    

We still have hours before the store opens.    

To keep out the cutters.    

Ow! You're punching me in the back.    

I ain't doin' it.    

It's the baby what's in my belly thrashing about.    

If you go into labor, I'll help you deliver, but then that baby has to go to the back of the line.    

- Yeah!
- <stage>ANGRY CHATTER</stage>    

I know how to hold a baby in. <stage>INHALES</stage>    

Have a safe Black Friday, and welcome to Thunderdome.    

- <stage>GRUNTS</stage>
- <stage>EXCITED CHATTER</stage>    

<stage>DOVE COOING</stage>    

<stage>SHOUTING</stage>    

<stage>WHIMPERS</stage> My hands are frozen, which makes it easier to do this. <stage>GRUNTING</stage>    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

<stage>GASPS</stage> The electronics department.    

I'm going to make it.    

<person>GIL</person>: I'm not gonna make it!    

Is there one drop of humanity in this big-box store?    

<stage>SHOUTING, GROANING</stage>    

<person>MARGE</person>: Don't look, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>. At any other time of year, 

that man's life would be worth more than a TV, 

but not at Christmas. 

<stage>GROANS</stage> Tell my granddaughter I existed.    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

This will help raise the little one.    

<music>♪ Jangle bells, jangle bells ♪    </music>

<music>♪ We gots a TV ♪    </music>

<music>♪ Now the only thing we lack ♪    </music>

<music>♪ Is e-lectricity, hey! ♪    </music>

You did it, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.    

You've given a poor old man the greatest gift of all,    

- a grandchild's love.
- Well, that makes it all...    

I can't leave without one of those.    

I'll give you a hundred bucks for it.    

- Can't say no to that.
- Oh...    

<stage><person>MARGE</person> GROANS</stage>    

<stage>TIRES SCREECH</stage>    

Oh! <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to let you down.    

I'm not mad at you. I won't let myself be mad at you.    

This is Christmas, and Christmas is great for our kids, and I vow on my life to make it a great Christmas.    

I totally agree.    

Now because you've been through so much, let me drive.    

- Let me call you an Uber.
- <stage>GROANS</stage>    

So I'm afraid you won't be getting the smart TV for Christmas.    

We figured.    

Never get your hopes up around here.    

But I promise you, Christmas will be better than ever.    

I'll sweep that up, sweetie.    

<stage><person>MARGE</person> GROANS</stage>    

Your mother froze her fingers trying to get a Christmas gift for you,    

and what were you going to give her?    

- Lanyard.
- Poem.    

I thought as much.    

Well, we're gonna make this Christmas about your mother.    

- But Christmas is for kids.
- Her.    

MONICA <stage>ON VIDEO</stage>: Hi, guys, it's Monica here with five easy hacks for resetting your threshold Christmas caroler.    

Number one, locate the P.I.X. input on the pressure strip.    

I already did that, Monica.    

I think I've got it.    

What if we take Mom on a Florida vacation for Christmas?    

<stage>NORWEGIAN ACCENT</stage>: Hoy, hoy, hoy.    

I ride on a pig.    

Don't forget to leave me porridge!    

Ugh, I've got it set on Norwegian.    

Well, at least we're not planning a vacation at the last second, we're planning at the last minute.    

Can't afford Nine Flags Underwater, Yankees Fantasy Camp, Yankees Suck Fantasy Camp...    

Oh, my God, there's a place we can afford.    

I've never heard of it.    

How can we be sure it's what it seems in the ad?    

That's a good point.
On the other hand...    

only three rooms left!    

And    people are looking at them.    

All right, kids, let this be a lesson.    

You should never succumb to something just because you are pressured to...    

One room left!    

I got it! Full price, nonrefundable! Boom!    

Christmas is on me. Christmas is on me.    

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, darling, remember when we agreed you should take it down a few notches?    

Yeah, the notches.
Always with the notches.    

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, have you considered that we could spend Christmas somewhere else?    

Home.    

If it's not home, it's not Christmas.    

Home, home, home!    

We're gonna have to take her out cold.    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

<stage>MUTTERS</stage>: You're getting one little... sleeve and there you go.    

- Mom?
- Yes, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>? Yes?    

- That's not our cat.
- Damn it.    

<stage>YOWLS</stage>    

Mom, we came to sing some carols.    

And I'll pour the tea.    

<music>♪ Silent night ♪    </music>

<music>♪ Holy night ♪    </music>

<stage>ECHOING</stage>: <music>♪ All is calm ♪    </music>

<music>♪ All is bright ♪    </music>

<music>♪ Start counting backwards from ten to one ♪    </music>

<music>♪ When you wake up ♪    </music>

<music>♪ We'll have Christmas fun... ♪    </music>

Wake up, sleepyhead. <stage>CHUCKLES</stage>    

- We're in Tennessee.
- Tennessee?    

We packed all the luggage ourselves.    

After all that you've been through, this Christmas is about you.    

The warm air helped my hands.    

I like Tennessee.    

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>: That's fantastic.    

However, we just entered Georgia.    

Change the bumper sticker, boy.    

Dirty Birds! You got that right!    

Yeah! Go, area team!    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

<stage>THUNDER CRASHES</stage>    

Enjoying the sunshine?    

That's the Christmas gift we get all year long.    

Can we please get to our room?    

We just drove  ,    miles in four hours.    

Of course.    

And thank you for reminding me why I never had kids.    

Let's go, shall we?    

All of us in this one little room?    

I call sleeping in the bathtub!    

I want to sleep in the bathtub.    

There's no bathtub.
Just a combo shower and toilet.    

We call it a shoilet.    

Well, the fun is outside.    

<stage>THUNDER CRASHES</stage>    



Ooh, that's gonna be a big one.    

Oh, I don't know how we're gonna give you kids a Christmas.    

Dad, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, meet me in the shoilet.    

- <stage>TOILET FLUSHES</stage>
- <catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!    

Let me tell you something about your mother.    

She is always as happy as the saddest one of us.    

I'm not always the saddest one.    

Polar bears are dying.    

<stage>CRIES</stage>: Oh, that's so sad.    

So, rain or shine, we will all have smiles on our faces.    

Her mood will be based on the signals we are giving.    

All hands in.    

Okay, three, two, one...    

ALL: Fake enthusiasm.    

What are you guys doing in here?    

Uh, having a great time.    

That's about to get better.    

- Really?
- <stage>TOILET FLUSHES</stage>    

Who wants room service?    

<stage>TOILET FLUSHES</stage>    

<stage>THEME PARK MUSIC PLAYING</stage>    

This is cool. Cartoon characters no one's ever heard of.    

That's Mulberry Mutt, Tremendous Boar and Thelonious Skunk.    

- Does somebody want a hug?
- No.    

- Oh, I think you do.
- Really, I don't.    

Hug the bull, boy.    

That's right, kid. Legally, you have to initiate it.    

That's so sweet.    

<stage>DOG HOWLS</stage>    

You know, they say whenever you travel, it grows your brain.    

This place is fantastic.    

WOMAN: This place is a dump.    

MAN: I picked it!
If you criticize this place, you're criticizing me!    

WOMAN: Well, in that case, this place is a loser with a gambling problem.    

That's the worst thing the kids could possibly hear.    

MAN: I won once, when I met you.    

- WOMAN: Aw...
- <stage>MOANING</stage>    

WOMAN <stage>GIGGLES</stage>: Come here.    

<stage>LAUGHTER</stage>    

Oh, for God's sake. I'll stop this.    

<stage>LAUGHTER CONTINUES</stage>    

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>    

Get this over with quick!
There's kids next door!    

MAN: There's kids in here, too!    

<stage>LAUGHTER, MOANING CONTINUES</stage>    

<stage>SIGHS</stage>    

Makes you feel kind of lonely, doesn't it?    

- Yeah.
- Well, it all starts with a hug.    

<stage>CHUCKLES</stage> You want a hug?    

Aw...    

<stage>SQUAWKING</stage>    

Oh, boy. You kids are up early.    

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and I are going to engage in perhaps the most popular Florida tradition... complaining to the manager.    

JEANIE: Hey, come on in.    

This place is nothing like it looked on the Internet.    

We can't compete with the big boys.    

Disney's already laying ground for a new Family Guy World.    

<music>♪ Lucky there's a family guy... ♪    </music>

I was the "it" boy in     .    

I don't know when and I don't know how, but I am gonna get you.    

Well, at least something in this place is clean now.    

<stage>SHOUTS</stage> That was the most horrifying ride    

I've ever been on.    

Where's <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>?    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

Oh, this is so much fun.
You know how I love history.    

It's like looking at a rogues gallery of <location>America</location>'s villains.    

According to the soundtrack to Hamilton, you were a real jerk.    

- <stage>g*n CLICKS</stage>
- <stage>SHRIEKS</stage>    

Vice presidents rule!    

Aw. Are you really having a great time?    

Really? Because I sure as heck am not.    

No, I'm FaceTiming <person>Milhouse</person> 'cause it's more fun.    

Whassup?    

<person>Milhouse</person>, give me something.    

I'm trapped in <location>The Hall of Vice Presidents</location>.    

Well, I'm kind of the vice president of us.    

<stage>GROANS</stage> Got to go.    

And we've got to go. Back home.    

We can be in <location>Springfield</location> by Christmas if we can just get our money back.    

Leave that to me.    

<stage>MOANS</stage>    

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>    

I sh*t my best friend in the face.    

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>    

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>    

<stage>SCREAMING ECHOES</stage>    

<stage>"CAROL OF THE BELLS" PLAYING</stage>    

<stage>EXCITED CHATTER</stage>    

<stage>PEOPLE GROANING</stage>    

There it is, the first snow.    

It smells so clean.    

<stage>ALL INHALING DEEPLY</stage>    

<stage>ENGINE SPUTTERING</stage>    

- <stage>ENGINE STOPS</stage>
- <stage><person>MARGE</person> GROANS</stage>    

<stage>WIND GUSTING</stage>    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

Oh, my God.    

<person>Moe</person> serves Christmas dinner to the old and needy.    

Yeah, look, it's the one nice thing I do. Ha.    

Guess old <person>Moe</person>'s got a heart.    

Also, if I turn the rummy away, they might wind up in church.    

That could turn their life around.    

That's bad for business.    

<person>Moe</person>, I never dreamed you were capable of such a sweet thing.    

Oh, no... I beg you, don't make a moment out of this.    

Oh.    

Ha. You missed my tongue there, but, eh, that's all right.    

<stage>"SILENT NIGHT" PLAYING</stage>    

Everyone, please close your eyes.    

Boy, you do the honors.    

Dear Lord, we didn't get the gift we wanted, a GL    K Smart TV.    

The place we went was a dump.    

But isn't Christmas really about being with your family and your bartender?    

We have traveled many miles to learn there's no place like <person>Moe</person>'s.    

Amen.    

If you're not going to buy something, leave.    

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, I disrespected you and I'm sorry.    

I've refunded your money plus $ ,  if you pledge to never come here again.    

And please tell your sister she's pretty.    

Not <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, the baby.    

You can't win in Florida.    

Oh, my God, why don't your batteries die?    

- I have a solar head.
- <stage>GROANS</stage>    

Well, you'll be happy to know we've put the money to good use.    

Now, to celebrate Christmas the way our ancestors did.    

<stage>GASPING</stage>    

You know, there's a real log burning below it, right?    

Yeah, but is it HD?


</txt></xml>