<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>


<metadata><ep><epTitle>E My Sports</epTitle><szn>30</szn>x<epNum>17</epNum></ep>












<date>03/18/19</date> <runtime>15:35</runtime></metadata>

- <stage>WATER SPLATTERING</stage>
- Sorry, Dad, but it looks like I've conquered you at Risk,  

- bankrupted you at Monopoly...
- <person>HOMER</person>: Hmm. Hmm. and aggravated you at Aggravation.  

Well, with you as a daughter, I'm a winner in the game of Life.  

Although, I lost that, too.  

<stage>GRUNTS</stage> Such a good father.   

Everyone is really getting along.   

What the hell is going on?   

There's no <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.   

- You're right.
- Where is he?   

Ladies, relax.   

Remember when I said I'd punish <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> after he got us... banned from the buffet?   

<stage><person>BART</person> CHUCKLES</stage>   

I can't shut it off.   

Someone wedged a seasonal Tuscan focaccia in the lever!   

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>   

Well, <fam>Homie</fam>, whatever punishment you gave him must have worked.   

Yep, tough love. I'm his father, not his best friend.   

He'll hate me now, but someday he'll say wonderful things about me to people on airplanes who just want to go to sleep.   

- That young man will...
- How did you punish him?   

Well, I sat the boy down, looked him straight in the eye, and bought him a top-of-the-line computer gaming rig.   

- You what?
- I get it. You bribed him.   

Stay out of this. I did not bribe him.   

I addicted him to something that will numb his spirit until he's no longer our responsibility.   

Well, it has been pretty peaceful around here.   

k*ll! Die! Die! Get wrecked, newbs!   

<stage>DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING</stage>   

This is General Splattin'. Do you copy?   

- Copy.
- BOTH: Copy.   

Jinx. You me a Coke.   

<stage>GROANS</stage> I'll never be able to pay that bet.   

Focus, <person>Nelson</person>, focus.   

Kite the enemy into a gank.
Squeeze it...   

- on three... two...
- <stage>expl*si*n</stage>   

GG!   

That means "good game."   

It's how the other team lets you know... they surrender!   

<person>HOMER</person>: Mm.   

Now I hit control-six to defile their corpses.   

Haw-haw! Haw-haw!   

- Haw-haw!
- <stage>CHICKENS CLUCKING</stage>   

<stage>DANCE MUSIC PLAYS</stage>   

Civilized annihilation.   

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, the boy just may be learning some life k*ll.   

Mom, do you agree with this?   

I guess so. Your father is showing an interest in <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, which is good.   

Well, if that's how things work, then I'm gonna behave badly, too.   

<stage>BOTH LAUGHING</stage>   

- That's great!
- Sure you are.   

I'll show you! I'm gonna... tear up my homework.   

<stage><person>LISA</person> GROANS</stage>   

I'm really gonna do this. Here I go.   

<stage>GROANS</stage> Actually, this bibliography could be improved.   

<stage><person>LISA</person> HUMMING A TUNE</stage>   

- <stage>TYPING</stage>
- Island of the Blue Dolphins. 

Ibid. Ibid. Ibid. Ibid.   

Op cit. Ibid. Ibid. Ibid.   

Ibid. Ibid. Ibid. 

<stage>SHOWER RUNNING</stage>   

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s been in the shower for an hour.   

<stage>CHUCKLES</stage> With a young man that age, there's only one reason he's in the bathroom that long.   

Skunk sprayed him good.   

Oh, my God, he's playing with himself!   

On that game.   

He's playing that game in the shower?   

We have to stop this right now.   

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, take care of your son.   

Make him quit. <stage>GROANS</stage> Geez.   

Sorry, boy, I have to put my foot down.   

I can't quit now.   

My team's about to compete in a tournament.   

I can't let them down.   

Well, team building is important.   

All right, let yourself go, and your partner will support you.   

<stage><person>LENNY</person> SCREAMS, GROANS</stage>   

Damn you, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!   

Please, Dad, can I play in this one last tournament?   

Sorry, boy, you're through.   

First prize is a thousand bucks.   

You get paid to play video games?   

A thousand bucks.   

- They actually pay you?
- Yes.   

- In dollars?
- Yes.   

- To play a video game?
- That's right.   

- They pay you in cash?
- Yes, yes, yes!   

- How much?
- A thousand!   

All right. Do not tell your mom, but I'm gonna say yes, one last tournament.   

Oh, thank you, Dad.   

Just one thing... they actually pay you?    

Yes!    

A thousand dollars to play video games?    

<stage>DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING</stage>    

Group up.
Time to put these suckers away.    

Oh, yeah, show me some Gs, Odgenville.    

We win! And it's all because I let them do it.    

Now, apparently, the Evergreen Terrors have won, uh, this thing I don't understand at all, but which gave the school new basketball nets.    

Now to hand you your prize money, which is $ ,    cash.    

Let go, Seymour.    

I'm telling myself to.    

I've never held this much money in my hand all at once.    

Let me just, uh... <stage>CHUCKLES</stage> look at it.    

1c1de IS PAINLESS" PLAYS]    

<music>♪ ♪    </music>

PILOT: Uh, welcome to our  -hour-and-  -minute flight 

from Seoul, <location>South</location> Korea to <location>Springfield</location>. 

One brief note: Our in-flight entertainment system 

is not working at all. 

Have a great flight, folks. 

- Also, we're out of almonds.
- <stage><person>HOMER</person> GROANS</stage>    

Zen. Remember your Zen.    

I'm sorry, you're too fat for coach.    

We'll have to put you in first class.    

Thanks to Buddha, I win again.    

Dad, I don't think you've quite grasped the religion.    

Two words: Boo-duh.    

<stage><person>LISA</person> GRUMBLES</stage>    

<stage>SNORING</stage>    

We don't want you anymore. You blew it.    

Your son has a chance to be well-adjusted.    

- <stage>ALL JEERING</stage>
- Yeah, great.    

Wait, I've got a baby daughter.    

Maybe she's good at beach volleyball.    

How old is she?    

- One.
- Too late.


</txt></xml>