<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>


<metadata><ep><epTitle>From <location>Russia</location> Without Love</epTitle><szn>30</szn>x<epNum>06</epNum></ep>












<date>02/28/19</date> <runtime>06:43</runtime></metadata>

<stage>AUDIO OF CHOIR SINGING "THE SIMPSONS" PLAYS BACKWARDS</stage>

 <catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

 - <stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

 - <stage>GRUNTING</stage>

 <catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

 <stage>GRUNTING SOFTLY</stage>

 - <stage>GROWLS</stage>

 - <stage>GRUNTS</stage>

 Hey.

 <stage>GRUNTING GIBBERISH</stage>: old lady kids then the f*re go out <catchphrase>stupid <person>Flanders</person></catchphrase>.

 Beer Only good will come of you.

 Hey, it looks like I just invented English.

 Ha!

 - Whuh?

 - I think I'll build a tavern.

 Of course, it won't be as clean and nice as this swamp.

 - - <stage>NEON LIGHTS BUZZING</stage>

 <stage>INSECTS TRILLING</stage>

 <fam>Homie</fam>, we can't keep inviting so many people to Thanksgiving.

 They all drink too much.

 <stage>SLURRED GRUNTING</stage>

 Use your words.

 Who do we cut?

 - <person>Flanders</person>.

 - We don't invite him.

 Let's invite, then dis-invite him.

 OK.

 I know this is a tough one but <person>Moe</person>?

 Remember last yeat?

 His plus-one?

 Oh, yeah!

 <stage><person>MARGE</person> GROANS</stage>

 Why won't you let me pop her?

 No.

 It's bad juju.

 So, um we are tipping Thanksgiving super small this year.

 Yeah, I understand.

 I won't tell no one I'm invited.

 Hey, I was thinking of making, uh, slivered green beans, little bits of bacon, a tough one, but <person>Moe</person>?

 - pearl onions in there.

 - <stage>GROANS</stage>

 What's the matter?

 You don't like pearl onions?

 <stage>SCOFFS</stage>

 Next you'll be badmouthin' shallots!

 Actually you're not invited.

 And this is how I find out, huh?

 By you telling me in person?

 Gently?

 With-with plenty of notice?!

 I'm sorry, man.

 I'm-I'm really sorry.

 Hey, no problem.

 I mean, I'm just your bartender, right?

 No women, no buddies 

 - <stage>PHONE RINGS</stage>

 - Ah, thank God, a friend!

 <person>Moe</person>'s Tavern.

 <person>Moe</person> speaking.

 Uh, hello.

 I'm looking for a Mr.

 Buttface, first name Ima.

 Ima?

 Nobody's been named that in, like, a hundred years.

 And as for the rest, why don't you double-check that name, huh?

 Try saying it out loud.

 - Ima Buttface?

 - Haw-haw!

 Yeah, well, mistakes are how we learn there, young fella.

 Good luck in your, uh, your journey into adulthood.

 Dude, that was lame.

 And I'm the king of lame.

 I dream about needlepoint.

 <stage>GRUNTS</stage>

 Maybe we should just give up these prank calls.

 Yeah.

 No more little prank calls.

 We're gonna go hard core!

 Hard core?

 The only thing my mom's never done.

 <stage>CHOKED UP</stage>: I'm so proud of her.

 <person>HERMAN</person>: So, you're looking to acquire some military-grade mischief makers?

 I cannot and I will not sell such items to minors.

 Welcome to the dark net, the devil's URL.

 <stage>GATE SQUEAKS</stage>

 Even Amazon can't find you here.

 Ain't that right, Alexa?

 Please, I've done nothing.

 Just shut me off.

 Please.

 <stage>SPOOKY VOICE</stage>: Welcome to the dark net.

 Could you stop that, please?

 <stage>GATE SQUEAKS</stage>

 <stage>ALL SCREAM</stage>

 Whoa!

 Quit scaring us!

 All right.

 <stage>BOYS SCREAM</stage>

 <stage>CHUCKLING</stage>

 This is our chance to get back at <person>Moe</person>.

 Wait.

 What did he do to us?

 It doesn't matter.

 Let's do this!

 <person>NELSON</person>: A grenade launcher!

 Just like the one my dad liberated in Afghanistan!

 I thought your dad just went out for smokes and never came back.

 All right.

 The truth is, he left on the first ship colonizing <location>Mars</location>.

 That's why he can't call or send checks.

 But he did send me this.

 What?

 That's just a lame-o candy bar.

 I need this, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!

 Fine.

 Your dad's on <location>Mars</location>.

 Haw-haw!

 You're an enabler!

 Deadly.

 Treason.

 Overpriced.

 Whoa, whoa, whoa!

 What about this?

 Whoa!

 That'll break <person>Moe</person>'s heart and his wallet.

 <stage>ALL CHUCKLING</stage>

 Well, hello.

 I'm Hacky.

 Here to help you commit Internet crime.

 Do you want to A: Submit a false Medicare Claim?

 B: Doxx your ex-girlfriend?

 Or C; Hack into PayPal?

 But if we're caught, I morph into Snitchy the weasel and give all your information to the FBI.

 To continue, click "agree. " <person>BART</person> 

 <stage>QUIETLY</stage>: The "package" should be arriving now.

 Cool!

 We get to see a taxi.

 <stage>ALL GASP</stage>

 <stage>RUSSIAN ACCENT</stage>: Is this the residence of successful American businessman, uh, <person>Moe</person> Szyslak?

 Uh, who wants to know?

 Anastasia Alekhova, his new wife.

 His wi-i-ife?!

 <stage>LAUGHTER</stage>

 Dark net rules!

 And no state sales tax!

 Boo-yeah!

 Well this is a contract and it is my electronic signture which I assume is impossible to fake, but I did not order no mail-order bride!

 - I understand.

 - Good.

 You see me in person, and you do not want me.

 No, no.

 You got it all wrong.

 It's me.

 I can't take another heartbreak.

 My only friends are the ghosts that came with the bar.

 Drinkity drink da drink da drink I woke up in a henhouse this morn Drinkity drink da drink da drink But I still wasn't drunk As the day I was born.

 Back in my head, Fats.

 Oh, there's a lot of dark thoughts in there.

 I didn't wanna die here.

 I just came in to use the phone.

 Sweetheart, we'll straighten this out.

 I'll overnight youse back to <location>Russia</location>, and, oh, boy, I'm sorry to say this, but, uh but on Delta.

 Where are my manners?

 Let me show you around.

 Uh, pool table, uh, jukebox <person>Barney</person>.

 We have alcoholics, too.

 But ours are thin, with ropey muscles.

 What's this?

 Ah, that's the Love Tester.

 You just stick a nickel in it, and it tells you what's in your heart.

 <person>MOE</person>: Uh-oh, am I falling for her?

 I think it knows what I'm feeling.

 And what I'm having for dinner.

 <person>MARGE</person>: Who can guess what oil I sautéed these vegetables in?

 Olive?

 Canola?

 Oh, not this game.

 Coconut?

 Grape-seed?

 Yeah, fantastic conversation, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

 <stage>SINGSONGY</stage>: I don't hear an oil.

 - Peanut?

 - Guess again.

 Um, sunflower?

 Walnut?

 No, no and no.

 <stage>GIGGLES</stage>

 This is why I had kids.

 The answer is - Finally.

 - Vegetable oil!

 Hey, vegetable oil!

 Good one, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

 Did you hear <person>Moe</person> accidentally bought a wife online?

 <stage>LAUGHS</stage>

 <stage>CHUCKLES</stage>

 Excuse me.

 How can mail-order brides still be a thing in this day and age?

 <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, ignorant men and foolish women sometimes do dumb things to find love.

4:00.

 Putting the brew in Hebrew.

 Oh, yeah.

 <stage>"WEDDING MARCH" PLAYS</stage>

 Mom, this costume's embarrassing.

 It's your last punishment.

 Also, you look cute.

 When I was little, I used to dream of a man in the most velour tracksuit there could be, who would sweep me off to an apartment shared by only four other families.

 I just want to say that you've made me very happy, which, uh, boy, I thought I could never be.

 And now the signing of the traditional orthodox marriage papers.

 Ring boy, please bring my notary stamp.

 I can scratch this off my bucket list.

 Wait a minute.

 I've been learning Russian, on the dark net, and this says, "<person>Moe</person> gives <stage>SPEAKING RUSSIAN</stage>

 - all 

 - <stage>GRUNTS</stage>

 - his" 

 - <stage>GRUNTS</stage>

 "personal property to Ana.

 " This looks airtight.

 And believe me, I know marriage law.

 Yeah, I read him divorce decrees to get him to go to sleep.

 Boom-chaka-laka!

 Ana, is this true?

 No.

 It's just another one of their stupid pranks.

 My sweet <person>Moe</person>, there is no way to fake what we have.

 Oh, I can't do it.

 I-I just, I can't risk another heartbreak.

 I'm I'm sorry.

 <stage>GASPING</stage>

 <stage>BROOKLYN ACCENT</stage>: So, uh, am I still getting paid?

 Wait, you're not from <location>Russia</location>?

 No, Brooklyn.

 Back when Brooklyn was Brooklyn.

 <stage>CHUCKLES</stage>

 You know what I mean?

 Ana, what about you?

 <stage>WITH MIDWESTERN ACCENT</stage>: I'm not Russian at all.

 I'm from Columbus, Ohio.

 That's even worse.

 Ana, you're a scam artist.

 And one that didn't aim too high.

 <stage>WITH OHIO ACCENT</stage>: What do you mean?

 You know I'm in debt, right?

 Serious, serious debt.

 <stage>LAUGHS</stage>

 Just look at my invites.

 You still wanna marry me?

 Well, it looks like this just became a g*n wedding.

 It's time for youse two to leave.

 <stage>WITH NO ACCENT</stage>: Fine.

 I'll find another man and give him what he dreams of.

 I just have to, uh <stage>WITH FRENCH ACCENT</stage>: speak a little like this.

 <stage>WITH SCOTTISH ACCENT</stage>: Or maybe Scottish, like Oh, do my ears deceive me?

 Are you from the <location>Highlands</location>?

 Aye.

 Between Inverness and the Moray Firth.

 Oh, well, you'll love this guy.

 He's loaded.

 <stage>CHUCKLES</stage>

 Let's go.

 Wait.

 Why are you wearing a wedding dress?

 Is it because you're a loon that got stood up and can't get over it?

 Just like Mother.

 - When are we gonna warn Willie?

 - Why do we have to warn Willie?

 - He doesn't have any money.

 - Okay.

 Then when are we gonna warn her?

 We don't need to warn her.

 Her heart is as cold as a Rocky Mountain Duff. D. J.

 Kirk, let's get this <location>party</location> rockin'.

 Did somebody say crank up the volume?

 <stage>expl*si*n</stage>

 - No one said crank up the volume.

 - Dammit.

 <stage>DRAMATIC MUSIC</stage>

 Papa?

 Son, it's it's so great to see you.

 <stage>GROANS</stage>

 I wanna hear everything about your top secret mission.

 Of course.

 Of course.

 Let me just go, uh, get some space cigarettes and we'll have a long, long talk.

 I'd like that.

 Oh, I finally have a dad again.


</txt></xml>