<lyrics>
<section type="intro">
<l>Ooh-ooh-ooh</l>
<l>Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>Brown guilty eyes and little white lies, yeah</l>
<l>I played dumb, but I always knew</l>
<l>That you talked to her, maybe did even worse</l>
<l>I kept quiet so I could keep you</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>And ain't it funny how you ran to her</l>
<l>The second that we called it quits?</l>
<l>And ain't it funny how you said you were friends?</l>
<l>Now it sure as hell don't look like it</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>You betrayed me</l>
<l>And I know that you'll never feel sorry</l>
<l>For the way I hurt, yeah</l>
<l>You talked to her when we were together</l>
<l>Loved you at your worst, but that didn't matter</l>
<l>It took you two weeks to go off and date her</l>
<l>Guess you didn't cheat, but you're still a traitor</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>Now you bring her around just to shut me down</l>
<l>Show her off like she's a new trophy</l>
<l>And I know if you were true, there's no damn way that you</l>
<l>Could fall in love with somebody that quickly</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>And ain't it funny? All the twisted games</l>
<l>All the questions you used to avoid</l>
<l>Ain't it funny? Remember I brought her up</l>
<l>And you told me I was paranoid?</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>You betrayed me</l>
<l>And I know that you'll never feel sorry</l>
<l>For the way I hurt, yeah</l>
<l>You talked to her when we were together</l>
<l>Loved you at your worst, but that didn't matter</l>
<l>It took you two weeks to go off and date her</l>
<l>Guess you didn't cheat, but you're still a traitor</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>(Ah-ah-ah)</l>
<l>God, I wish that you had thought this through</l>
<l>Before I went and fell in love with you</l>
<l>(Ah-ah-ah)</l>
<l>When she's sleepin' in the bed we made</l>
<l>Don't you dare forget about the way</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>You betrayed me</l>
<l>'Cause I know that you'll never feel sorry</l>
<l>For the way I hurt, yeah</l>
<l>You talked to her when we were together</l>
<l>You gave me your word, but that didn't matter</l>
<l>It took you two weeks to go off and date her</l>
<l>Guess you didn't cheat, but you're still, you're still a traitor</l>
<l>(Ah-ah-ah)</l>
<l>Yeah, you're still a traitor</l>
</section>
<section type="outro">
<l>Ooh-ooh-ooh</l>
<l>God, I wish that you had thought this through</l>
<l>Before I went and fell in love with you</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
