<lyrics>
<section type="intro">
<l>Ah</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>Made it clear when you told me (Ah-ah)</l>
<l>Don't know why, but you gotta be lonely (Ah-ah-ah)</l>
<l>Say it's hard, but you make it look easy (Ah-ah)</l>
<l>So I'm tryin' to live in reality (Ah-ah-ah-ah)</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>Decompressin', tryna ease the tension, but you</l>
<l>Got me stressin', feelin' like I need to call when</l>
<l>You sneak up on me, tell me that you miss me in your life</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
<l>You say that you need to be alone</l>
<l>But night and day, want me at your beck and call</l>
<l>You say you know that you might be crossin' a line</l>
<l>Wastin' all our time</l>
<l>To think that we could be casual</l>
<l>You're not my friend and, baby, you never were</l>
<l>Why the fuss if you say you just wanna be mine?</l>
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>Tell me, what's gonna happen</l>
<l>When it's you and me in a room, but you know you can't have it?</l>
<l>Oh, I'll be laughin'</l>
<l>When you say that you really have changed</l>
<l>Finally found your way</l>
<l>'Cause I'm close to your face (Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah)</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>Double-checkin', did I get the message in the way</l>
<l>You intended? Got me second-guessin' when you</l>
<l>Sneak up on me, tell me that you need me in your life</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
<l>You say that you need to be alone</l>
<l>But night and day, want me at your beck and call</l>
<l>You say (Uh) you know (Yeah) that you might be crossin' a line</l>
<l>Wastin' all our time</l>
<l>To think that we could be casual</l>
<l>You're not my friend and, baby, you never were</l>
<l>Why the fuss if you say you just wanna be mine?</l>
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>You say that you need to be alone</l>
<l>But night and day, want me at your beck and call</l>
<l>You say you know that you might be crossin' a line</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
<l>You say that you need to be alone</l>
<l>But night and day, want me at your beck and call (Want me at your beck and call)</l>
<l>You say you know that you might be crossin' a line</l>
<l>Wastin' all our time (Time)</l>
<l>To think (Think) that we could be casual</l>
<l>You're not (Not) my friend (My friend) and, baby, you never were</l>
<l>Why (Why) the fuss (Fuss) if you say you just wanna be mine?</l>
<l>I can't read your mind</l>
</section>
<section type="outro">
<l>Ha-ah-ah-ah, la, mm-mm</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
