<lyrics>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>I have nightmares each week 'bout that Friday in May</l>
<l>One phone call from you and my entire world was changed</l>
<l>Trust that you betrayed, confusion that still lingers</l>
<l>Took everything I loved and crushed it in between your fingers</l>
<l>And I doubt you ever think about the damage that you did</l>
<l>But I hold onto every detail like my life depends on it</l>
<l>My undying love, now, I hold it like a grudge</l>
<l>And I hear your voice every time that I think I'm not enough</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>And I try to be tough, but I wanna scream</l>
<l>How could anybody do the things you did so easily?</l>
<l>And I say I don't care, I say that I'm fine</l>
<l>But you know I can't let it go, I've tried, I've tried, I've tried for so long</l>
<l>It takes strength to forgive, but I don't feel strong</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>The arguments that I've won against you in my head</l>
<l>In the shower, in the car, and in the mirror before bed</l>
<l>Yeah, I'm so tough when I'm alone, and I make you feel so guilty</l>
<l>And I fantasize about a time you're a little fuckin' sorry</l>
<l>And I try to understand why you would do this all to me</l>
<l>You must be insecure, you must be so unhappy</l>
<l>And I know, in my heart, hurt people hurt people</l>
<l>And we both drew blood, but, man, those cuts were never equal</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>And I try to be tough, but I wanna scream</l>
<l>How could anybody do the things you did so easily?</l>
<l>And I say I don't care, I say that I'm fine</l>
<l>But you know I can't let it go, I've tried, I've tried, I've tried for so long</l>
<l>It takes strength to forgive, but I don't feel strong</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>Ooh, do you think I deserved it all?</l>
<l>Ooh, your flowers filled with vitriol</l>
<l>You built me up to watch me fall</l>
<l>You have everything, and you still want more</l>
</section>
<section type="outro">
<l>I try to be tough, I try to be mean</l>
<l>But even after all this, you're still everything to me</l>
<l>And I know you don't care, I guess that that's fine</l>
<l>But you know I can't let it go, I've tried, I've tried, I've tried for so long</l>
<l>It takes strength to forgive, but I'm not quite sure I'm there yet</l>
<l>It takes strength to forgive, but</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
