<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>The Crepes of Wrath</epTitle><szn>01</szn>x<epNum>11</epNum></ep>
<stage>FADE IN</stage></metadata>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks in through the main door, eating a candy bar and carrying his skateboard.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Froggie, I'm home!

He makes his way up the stairs and throws off his backpack and several other objects on the floor as he goes to his room. His room is a complete mess. A green frog sits inside a glass jar on a dresser.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hi, little fella. Got some nice juicy flies for you.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> drops a single fly into the can and the frog eats it.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> looks over the great mess in the hallway.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Geez, Louise. Look at this mess. I told that boy a billion times to pick up his jun---.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> accidentally steps on <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s skateboard and he's sent flipping and rolling down the stairs. He screams the whole way down, cursing a bit as well.

<stage><person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL</stage>I like to play with you. I like to play with you.

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(gasps)</stage>: My back. There goes my back again.

<stage><person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL</stage>I like to play with you. I like to play with you. I like to play with you. I like to play with you.

<location>Santa's Little Helper</location>, the family dog, walks in. <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> grunts as he tries to get up.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Go get help, Dog.

The dog instead starts licking <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

<stage><person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL</stage>I like to play with you. I like to play with you.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A much later time. <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> is still on the floor in pain. The dog sleeps on his stomach. The battery of the doll is dying.

<person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL <stage>(dying out)</stage>: I like to play with you. I like to play with you.

<fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> crawls over <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s head.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>. My poor back.

<fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> takes out her pacifier and sticks it into <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s mouth.

<stage><person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL</stage>I like to play with you. I like to play with you.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

Even later. <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> now sleeps on the floor near <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s head. The doll is still alive.

<stage><person>KRUSTY</person> DOLL</stage>I like to play with you. I like to p--. I like to play---.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam> and <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> walk in and gasp.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Dad!

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, what happened?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, the boy. Bring me the boy.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam> stomps into <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s room and yells at him.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, if you had cleaned up your room when I asked you to, your father's trick back would still be aligned. So you'll pick up this mess right now!

She leaves and slams the door. <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> begins throwing objects into his closet, muttering under his breath.
<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Clumsy <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>. Everything's always my fault. If he'd just watch where he was going.
He discovers a pink box under his bed and shakes it.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hello, what have we here?

He opens it and gasps.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>A cherry b*mb! I thought I blew all you guys up.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The playground on <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s school. Kids play marbles, ride around on swings, and jumprope.

PRINCIPAL <person>SKINNER</person> walks around enforcing the rules.
<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>People, people, no rough-housing on the monkey bars. You there, tuck in your shirt. Watch it, I saw what.

<person>Skinner</person>'s mother, <location>Agnes</location>, walks behind him.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>You certainly have done awfully well for yourself, Spanky.

<person>SKINNER</person> <stage>(quietly)</stage>: Mother, please don't call me Spanky on school grounds.
Nearby, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> holds the cherry b*mb in front of <person>Milhouse</person> and several other friends.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Wow! A cherry b*mb!

<stage>LEWIS</stage>What are you gonna do with it, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Watch out, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>. It's <person>Skinner</person>!

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Uh-oh.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> hides the cherry b*mb and the boys form a line.

<stage>ALL</stage>Good morning, Mr. <person>Skinner</person>!

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Morning, boys.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>Why haven't you introduced me to your students, Spanky?

The kids laugh at <person>Skinner</person> until he gives them a mean look.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>Well?

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Mother, I would like you to meet...<person>Milhouse</person>, Lewis, Richard, and <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> Simpson.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>This is the <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> Simpson you're always talking about?

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Mm-hmm.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>But he looks so sweet.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>I am, ma'am.

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Simpson! Let's move on now, Mother, shall we?

He leads her away.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Bye, Spanky.

They all snicker and once again stop when <person>Skinner</person> looks back.

FADE TO BLACK

FADE IN

The boys stand in the bathroom.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>So, you're gonna flush it?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>What can I say? I've got a weakness for the classics.

He flicks open a lighter.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Outside, <person>Skinner</person> and <location>Agnes</location> walk in the hallway.

<stage><location>AGNES</location></stage>I think I need to make a stop at the little girls' room.

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Okay, Mother. This way.

He opens a door for her and she goes in.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> drops the flaming b*mb into a toilet and flushes it.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Ha ha, so long, sucker!

He stands back and an expl*si*n is heard on the other side. Water begins coming out of the toilets like a geyser.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

In the hallway, <person>Skinner</person> hears the screaming of his mother.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

12 months a year. At least you get the summer off.

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Mhm-hmm.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> discuss as they make their way down the stairs.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>And I get to take a plane there, wouldn't I, Mom?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Yes, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Wow! And one back?

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>Mm-hmm.

They walk into the living room.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Well, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> seems very enthusiastic about the idea.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and <person>Skinner</person> bounce off and give each other high-fives.
<person>HOMER</person> +<stage> <person>SKINNER</person></stage>Yes! Whoo, baby! Way to go! Bon voyage, boy!

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

An airplane sits on a runway. Near it, the Simpsons clan say their goodbyes. <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> kisses <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Goodbye, my special, my special little guy. You will write us, won't you?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>All the time.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>What do you know about <location>France</location>?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>I know I'm going and you're not.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>I'm gonna miss you, son. And listen, while you're seeing all those great sights, always remember that you're representing your country. I guess what I'm saying is...don't mess up <location>France</location> the way you messed up your room.

They shake their hands.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Okay, Dad.

A flight attendant walks over to them.

<stage>FLIGHT ATTENDANT</stage>Is one of you going to be on the charter flight?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Yes, sir.

<stage>FLIGHT ATTENDANT</stage>Mm-hmm. Come along.

He yanks <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> away.

<stage>SIMPSON FAMILY</stage>Goodbye, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>. Bye. Be good. We'll miss you.

They wave as <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> is thrown into the plane.

He sits in the middle of several passengers.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A new airfield. A subhead says: "<location>Tirana</location>, <location>Albania</location>".

A family kisses their son goodbye <stage>(the foreign exchange student)</stage>. His mother and father do the same things as <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> and <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> did, just in Albanian.

2: Ah, Maurice. Once the American boy arrives, your days of back-breaking labor will be over.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and his buddy arrive.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Eww. What a dump.

He stares sadly.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A plane flies over another airport. <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, and <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> stand on a platform.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>You know, in <location>Albania</location>, the unit of currency is called the lek...

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><stage>(laughing)</stage> You gotta be kiddin'. The lek.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> continues reading from her book.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>And the national flag is a two-headed eagle on a red field.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Give me the old stars and stripes.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>And the main export is furious political thought.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Political what?

<stage>ANNOUNCER</stage>Trans. <location>Albanian Airlines</location>, flight number two, <location>Tirana</location> to <location>Springfield</location>, is now arriving.

The plane stops in front of them.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> stands in front of the two men. As we soon come to know, their names are Cesar and Ugolin. Ugolin is skinny and Cesar is fat and wears a French cap.

<stage>UGOLIN</stage>Welcome to your new home.

<stage>CESAR</stage>Escape is impossible. My name is Cesar. This is my nephew, Ugolin. You may find life here at the chateau hard, but if you shut up and do exactly what we say, the time will pass more quickly.

<stage>UGOLIN</stage>He's right, you know.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Well, okay, sir.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The airplane door opens and the Albanian boy walks off to meet the Simpsons.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Adil?

<stage>ADIL</stage>Mother?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Well, I guess for the next few months, yes, I will be your mother.

<stage>ADIL</stage>And this must be <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> and <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>.

He shakes their hands.

<stage>ADIL</stage>And you must be my new father, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

He hugs <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and kisses him twice on the cheeks.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Affectionate little Albanian, isn't he?

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Cesar opens <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s suitcase and takes out a camera and another object.

UGOLIN <stage>(in French)</stage>: Cesar, look! We are rich.

They inspect a pair of underwear and a <person>Krusty</person> the Clown T-Shirt.

CESAR <stage>(in French)</stage>: These won't fit us, but we can sell them.

<stage>UGOLIN</stage>And a red hat for you, Maurice.

He places <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s cap on the mule's head.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hey, come on, guys. Quit being so grabby?

They both growl in anger.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Sorry, man. Be my guest.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of <location>Springfield Elementary</location> School. Inside, <person>Skinner</person> makes a presentation on Adil. All the students gather in their seats.

<stage><person>SKINNER</person></stage>You may find his accent peculiar. Certain aspects of his culture may seem absurd, perhaps even offensive. But I urge you all to give little Adil the benefit of the doubt. In this way, and only in this way, can we hope to better understand our backward neighbors throughout the world.

The students clap as Adil stands up on the podium.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Thank you, Principal <person>Skinner</person>. Thank you, fellow students. Although I have only been in your country a few days, I have already found Americans to be most...trusting. Although, officially, I am required to hate you, I want you to know I do not feel it in my heart.

The students clap.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

Ugolin walks along a wheat field, whistling a tune. Cesar and the mule follow close behind.

<stage>CESAR</stage>Hurry up, boy. My grapes are waiting for their water.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> tiredly carries several pails of water on a stick behind them.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of the Simpsons house in the evening. <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> and Adil talk at the dinner table.

<stage>ADIL</stage>How can you defend a country where 5% of the people control 95% of the wealth?

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>I'm defending a country where people can think, act, and worship any way they want.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Can not.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Can too.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Can not.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Can too.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Please, please, kids. Stop fighting. Maybe <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>'s right about <location>America</location> being a land of opportunity, and maybe Adil has a point about the machinery of capitalism being oiled with the blood of the workers.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Your father is right. We should not fight. Friends?

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Well, okay.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Well, now that that's settled, I'll just clear the dishes.

<stage>ADIL</stage>No, no, Mrs. Simpson. You have been oppressed enough for today. I will clear the dishes.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh. Okay.

Adil walks off into the kitchen.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>DId you see that? You know, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, this is the way I've always wanted it to be. We've become a fully functioning family unit. We've always blamed ourselves but I guess it's pretty clear which cylinder wasn't f*ring.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Your paper-thin commitment to your children sends shivers down my spine! May I be excused?

She storms off.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, she's just jealous. She'll get over it. And if she doesn't, we can always exchange her.

He laughs as <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> looks angrily at him.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Just kidding.

DISSOLVE TO;

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and his French buddies eat under a low light.

UGOLIN <stage>(in French)</stage>: Mmm. Good sausage.

CESAR <stage>(in French)</stage>: Yes. Pass me the wine.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Can I have something to go with my turnip?

<stage>CESAR</stage>Quiet! When you work like a man, we will feed you like one.

<stage>UGOLIN</stage>Now go to sleep!

He points to a stack of hay.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks over, but before he can, the mule plops down on it.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hey, hey, come on. Move it pal.

<stage>CESAR</stage>You leave Maurice alone. The floor is good enough for you. You go to sleep there.

He points and <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> trudges over to a dark corner as they eat and joke. He lies down.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of the Simpsons house. In <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s room, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> tucks Adil in.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Nice and cozy, Adil?

<stage>ADIL</stage>Yes. Thank you, Father.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Look, Adil, you can call me Dad.

<stage>ADIL</stage>All right, Dad.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Aw! You called me Dad.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Dad, do you think I could come visit you at <location>the nuclear power plant</location>?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>You wanna see where I work?

<stage>ADIL</stage>Oh, yes, very much.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> has tears in his eyes.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>None of my biological kids ever wanted to see me at work.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Then I can go?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Well, I'll have to pull a few strings with the boys in security, but sure you bet.

The boy smiles evilly.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Excellent.
<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Cesar holds a bundle of grapes in front of <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage>CESAR</stage>Now watch me. You grab the grape between your thumb and forefinger and gently twist it off and drop it in the bucket. Now you do it.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> plucks one off and drops it.

<stage>CESAR</stage>Very good. Now do it a million times.

It is revealed that they're in the middle of a gigantic field.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of the <location>Springfield</location> Power Plant. Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> shows Adil a box of donuts.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>See these? American donuts. Glazed, powdered, and raspberry filled. Now how's that for freedom of choice?

<stage>ADIL</stage>Dad, do you think I might see your plutonium isolation module?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Dee....uh...maybe. Hold on a second.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> walks over to his buddy <person>Lenny</person>.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Hey, <person>Lenny</person>.

<stage><person>LENNY</person></stage>Hmm?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Does this place have one of those plutonium isolation deals?

<stage><person>LENNY</person></stage>Yeah, over in sector 12.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Sector 12?

12. Come along, Adil.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> picks off the remaining grapes off their vines. The bucket is close to full. He takes the last one, looks around, and puts in his mouth. Udolin slaps him on the back and the grape flies out.

<stage>UDOLIN</stage>Ungrateful swine! We give you food, we give you shelter, and this is how you repay us!

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and Adil walk among the nuclear materials and machines, both dressed in safety suits. Adil takes pictures with his camera.

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(laughing)</stage>: Heh, heh, heh, you little shutterbug.

They walk into a restricted area where Adil prepares to take a picture of the plutonium. <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> suddenly pops into view.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Cheese!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> blocks every sh*t Adil takes, preventing him from getting anything.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, wait a minute.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> takes off his mask and Adil tries again to take a picture.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> stands in a large wooden bowl, stomping the grapes with his feet. Cesar and Ugolin lie in the shade with Maurice the mule.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Stupid grapes. Bunch of creeps! I hate <location>France</location>!

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> continues stomping as we...

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of the Simpsons house during evening. Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> lie in bed. A picture of Adil has been hung on the wall.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>You sure have taken a shine to little Adil.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Well, he sure makes life a lot easier around here. You have to admit that.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Well, okay, I will...if you admit you love <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Okay, okay, I love <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>. Well?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>What?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Well?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh, Adil's a very sweet boy.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Darn tootin'.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s room, where a wire hangs out the window. It leads to the tree house, where Adil listens and transmits Morse code while looking at the photographs. He inserts a photograph and speaks into a microphone.

14 Rue Voltaire". It is smudged by the rain. <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks along the street, shivering and freezing.

A man dressed in a blue suit with an umbrella walks around the corner.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>You're a policeman, aren't you?

<stage>MAN</stage>Excusez-moi. Je ne parle pas Anglais.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>But you gotta help me. These two guys I'm staying with, they work me day and night. They don't feed me. They make me sleep on the---

The man takes out a role of candy.

<person>BART</person> <stage>(coughing)</stage>: I --- I don't want a piece of candy. I need your---.

He reluctantly swallows what the man gives him.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Come on, Mister, can you help me?

The man speaks more French and <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks away.

2: The Sparrow!

In the treehouse, Adil fumbles with the microphone and it tumbles out onto the roof.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Adil! Oh, there you are!

<stage>AGENT</stage>Get him!!

The agents topple <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> as they rush to the treehouse.

DISSOLVE TO;

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s savior giving a speech to several reporters with cameras.

Cesar and Ugolin are led out of the chateau.

<stage>POLICEMAN</stage>From now on you will be doing all your winemaking in prison.

The reporters begin taking pictures of them.

CESAR <stage>(in French)</stage>: And all because we participated in a student exchange program.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Au revoir, suckers!

A French version of the magazine Newsweek is shown, with <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> on the cover and the headline "Vive le <person>bart</person>!!".

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A policeman presenting <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> with a medal. He is kissed by a woman <stage>(presumably a queen or similar)</stage>.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

The agent holding Adil in front of a plane. The Simpsons stand nearby.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>So he's going to prison?

<stage>AGENT</stage>Uh...no. We've arranged an exchange for one of our own men caught in <location>Albania</location>.

Another child is led off the plane.

<stage>CHILD</stage>So, Sparrow, we meet again.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Yes, sometimes I think I am getting too old for this game.

<stage>AGENT</stage>Okay, kids, let's hurry it up.

<stage>ADIL</stage>Goodbye, Simpsons. Thank you for your hospitality. I hope this experience will not sour you on the student exchange program.

Adil is <location>lead</location> onto the plane.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Goodbye Adil.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Have a nice trip.

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(sadly)</stage>: Goodbye, Adil. I'll send you those civil defense plans you wanted.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

An airplane rolls out on the runway.

<stage>FRENCH ANNOUNCER</stage>Air <location>France</location>, flight diz neuf cent quatre-ving huit, <location>Paris</location> to <location>Springfield</location> is now arriving.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks out of the open door holding all sorts of souvenirs.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Look, Mom. There he is!

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, my baby boy. Welcome home.

They hug.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hey, where's the big guy?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>He means me. Hey, boy.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hey, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>He brought us gifts. His first unselfish act.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and the family in the kitchen, discussing.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>So, basically, I met one nice French person.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, I have something to say that's gonna bother me if I don't say it. It's good to see you.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Same here.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>I'd love a glass of that wine <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> brought us.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> tries to open the bottle.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Sorry, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>. Some wiseguy stuck a cork in the bottle.

<person>BART</person> <stage>(in French)</stage>: My father. What a buffoon.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>You hear that, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>? My boy speaks French!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> bites off the cork and spits it out as CREDITS APPEAR and we FADE OUT.

CREDITS GO.
</txt></xml>