
<?xml-model href="../../../../../OneDrive/Desktop/Untitled1.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml>
    <txt>
        <metadata><ep><epTitle><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s Night Out</epTitle><szn>01</szn>x<epNum>10</epNum></ep>
<date>05/21/98</date> <runtime>02:15</runtime></metadata>

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

We begin with an outside sh*t of the house.

Inside, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> hums as she brushes her teeth.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>So how was the office birthday <location>party</location>?
It turns out <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> is right behind her.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, it was delightful.  The frosting on the cake was this thick.

He holds out two fingers and shows her the size.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>And Eugene Fisk -- my poor sucker of an assistant -- didn't know the fruit punch was spiked and he really made an ass of himself putting the moves on the new girl in <location>Valve Maintenance</location>. <stage>(laughs)</stage>.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Does this girl like him?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>I have to warn you, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.  I think the poor young thing has the hots for yours truly.

He taps her jokingly on the shoulder and chuckles.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>. 

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Just keeping you on your toes, baby.

239 pounds.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Two hundred and thirty nine pounds!  Oh, I'm a blimp!  Why are all the good things so tasty?  From now on, exercise every morning.

He starts doing weak arm exercises when <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> grabs him around his neck.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>You're not a blimp, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.  You're my big, cuddly teddy bear.

They kiss.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> looks at a fitness advertisement.  It shows a small, scrawny guy being transformed into a tough, muscular, fit guy in a before and after picture.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Aw, baloney. 

He looks next a X-Ray TV glasses ad.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Yeah, right.

Next up is a hyp-no Coin.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Oh, give me a break.

He looks down at a "Genuine spy Camera" Ad.  A slogan beneath it says "Just like the C.I.A. uses!!!"

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Wow, cool, man!

He cuts the ad out.  He grabs a hammer and breaks his piggy bank <stage>(which already has cracks from previous beatings)</stage> to collect several coins.

He slides everything into an envelope, runs out, and drops it into a mailbox.

FADE OUT

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

A sh*t of the house.  A subhead says "Six months later".

Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> gargles some kind of mouthwash in the bathroom.  He stands on the scale and looks down.  He spits out the mouthwash.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh no!  Two hundred and thirty nine pounds?  I'm a whale!  Why was I cursed with this weakness for snack treats?

He looks at himself in the mirror.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Well, from now on, exercise every morning, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

Once again, he starts doing weird exercises when <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> walks in from behind.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Ooh.  Don't strain yourself, dear.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Good idea, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

He stops.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>By the way, this Friday night I'm gonna be attending a little get together with the boys at work.  Eugene Fisk is marrying some girl in <location>Valve Maintenance</location>.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, is this some kind of stag <location>party</location>?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>No, no, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.  It's gonna be very classy.  A tea-and-crumpets kind of thing.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> begins shaving.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Hmm.  Eugene Fisk.  Isn't he your assistant?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>No!  My supervisor.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Didn't he used to be your assistant?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Hey, what is this, the Spanish Inquisition?!

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Sorry, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> watching TV on the family couch.  <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> reads a book as the doorbell rings.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Uh-oh, it's the "fe-mailman".

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Female carrier, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> opens the door.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Lady, where's my spy camera?

<person>BART</person> +<stage> LADY MAILMAN</stage>Where's my spy camera?

<stage>LADY MAILMAN</stage>Every day for the last six months---

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Where's my spy camera?  Where is my spy camera?

<person>BART</person> +<stage> LADY MAILMAN</stage>Where's my spy camera?  Where's my spy camera?!

<stage>LADY MAILMAN</stage>Here's your stupid spy camera!

She shoves a small box into his chest.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Oh.  Thanks, ma'am.

He shuts the door on her and begins opening the box on the floor.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Whoa, man.  Look at the size of this thing.  I wonder if it really works...

He stares it and takes a picture of himself.  Looks fine.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Cause I got a lot of spying to do.

He looks mischievously upstairs.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> exercising in the bathroom.  <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> opens the door and snaps a picture.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!  What are you doing?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Sorry, Dad.  The answer to that is top secret.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> runs out as <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> grumbles.  <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> proceeds to the parent's bedroom where a sound of a razor is heard.

He peeks in and takes a sh*t of <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> shaving her armpits.   Ugh.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Ooh.  Oh, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>What?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Go take some wildlife pictures or something.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

A bunch of bushes from which <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> emerges.  He takes a picture of a d*ad rat or another animal that has been run over and has tire tracks on it.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s room, where <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> has his shorts down and his camera behind him.  <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> walks in.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Mom, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> was taking a picture of his butt.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> quickly fastens his shorts as <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> walks in.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Oh, sure.  Like I'm really gonna take a picture of my butt.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh, stop it, you two.  And put on some nice clothes.  Since it's just the four of us tonight, we're having dinner at the Rusty Barnacle.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Yay, fried shrimp!

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Aw, mom, can't we just grab a burger at--?  Only four of us?  Who escaped?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Your father.  He's having a boy's night out.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> being poured a mug of beer.  <person>Lenny</person>, <person>Carl</person>, and a bunch of coworkers sit nearby.

Eugene's father makes a speech.

EUGENE'<stage>S FATHER</stage>Just as I was asking myself "Where did my seven year old boy get the money for a father's day present?", I opened the box.  And inside was little Eugene's baseball glove.  He had given me the one thing that mattered most to him in the whole world.  Eugene, when I see you -- the one thing that matters most to me in the whole world -- married tomorrow, I'm going to know just how you felt that day.

<stage>EUGENE</stage>I love you, Dad.

EUGENE'<stage>S FATHER</stage>I love you, son.

The two hug.  Everybody continues drinking.  Smoke fills the air as well.

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(bored)</stage>: Where am I, the planet Cornball?

<stage><person>CARL</person></stage>Hey, don't worry, things are gonna pick up once the entertainment gets here.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Ooh, entertainment.

<stage>OTHER PERSON</stage>Yes, sir.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and <person>Lenny</person> clink their glasses.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The Rusty Barnacle, where a waitress dressed like a pirate leads a couple to a table.

On the other side, the Simpsons sit with their pirate waiter.

<stage>WAITER</stage>Ahoy, I spy the children's menu.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Ahoy, this place bites.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage>WAITER</stage>So what's it gonna be, me little bucko?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hmm, let's see.  This evening I shall go for the squid platter.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Ew.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>With extra tentacles, please.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.  Excuse me, sir, the <location>party</location> next door seems to be a little raucous.  Could you please ask them to quiet down a little bit?

<stage>WAITER</stage>Aye, aye.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> fills out a service questionnaire.  He checks "Poor" for all the categories.

The waiter walks over to the loud room and walks in.  Inside are <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and the rest of his buddies.

<stage>WAITER</stage>Hey, try to keep it down, guys.  Okay?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Hey, shut up.

GROUP <stage>(singing)</stage>: Open the door and lie on the floor said Barnacle Bill the sailor.

Back at his table, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> looks over at a sign above him that says "Cod Platter - $4.99.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hmm...

He re-arranges the letters so they spell "Cold Pet Rat".

The waiter sets a dish down for <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

<stage>WAITER</stage>Here you go.  There you are.  For the baby.

He sets down individual plates.

<stage>WAITER</stage>And one squid platter, extra tentacles.

He sets the plate down, smiling.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s face turns green in disgust.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, quit fooling around and eat your dinner.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>Yeah, eat it, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Ugh, may I please be excused for a minute?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Okay, but don't dawdle.  Your food will get cold.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Inside the office, where <person>Carl</person> stands near Eugene.  Both he and his father look depressed.

<stage><person>CARL</person></stage>Okay, Eugene.  One last taste of bachelor freedom.

<person>Lenny</person> turns on a boombox and middle eastern music plays.

<stage><person>LENNY</person></stage>Presenting, <location>Princess Kashmir</location>, queen of the mysterious <location>East</location>.

A stripper waltzes in and starts dancing for the men.  Everybody barks and cheers her on.

<stage><person>LENNY</person></stage>Now this is what I call a <location>party</location>.

EUGENE'<stage>S FATHER</stage>How do I tell you this, my boy?  We're in hell.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Heh, heh, look at him squirm.

<stage>STRIPPER</stage>You care to dance?

<stage>WORKER</stage>She wants you, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

<stage><person>LENNY</person></stage>Go for it, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

<person>Lenny</person> pushes <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> on top of the table as she giggles.  The two start dancing, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> slightly nervous at first.

<stage>WORKER</stage>Shake his buns.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> walks out of the bathroom and hears the noises coming from the other room.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>I'm sorry, I don't usually laugh like this.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> peeks in and gasps.  <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> doesn't see him.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Ay <catchphrase>caramba</catchphrase>.  Wow, man.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> takes out his handy dandy little camera and snaps a sh*t.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, this is the most fun I've ever had in my life.

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

A sh*t of the outside of <location>the Springfield Elementary School</location>.

2: The subtle gray tones recall the work of Helmut Newton.

<stage>MARTIN</stage>Who's the sexy lady, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Beats me.  But the gay dancing with her is my pop.

<stage>ALL</stage>Wow!

STUDENT 3: He brings to mind the later work of Diane Arbus.

<stage>MARTIN</stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, I'd really appreciate a print of your masterwork.

<stage>STUDENTS</stage>Yeah.  Me too.  Come on.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Sorry, guys.  No can do.

<stage>STUDENTS</stage>Oh.

<person>Milhouse</person> comes in from the side.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Come on, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.  You're gonna make me a print, aren't you?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Will you swear not to let another living soul get a copy of this photo?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Ok.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Cross your heart and hope to die?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Yep.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Stick a needle in your eye?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Yep.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Jam a dagger in your thigh?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Yep.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Eat a horse manure pie?

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Yep.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Well, okay.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<person>Milhouse</person> sits with another kid in the library.  He taps him with his elbow.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Psst, look what I got.

<stage>KID</stage>Whoa, I gotta have a copy of that.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Sorry.

<stage>KID</stage>Aw, come on.

<stage><person>MILHOUSE</person></stage>Well, okay.

The two walk over the copy machine and <person>Milhouse</person> puts a coin in.  A copy slides out.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The playground, where <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> hangs upside down on his feet. Another boy walks over.

<stage>BOY</stage>Hey, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.  How come <person>Milhouse</person> gets a copy of your girlie picture and I don't?  I thought I was your friend too.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Well, okay.

The two run over to the copy machine and make a copy.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

Inside a classroom, the boy hands over a copy to another classmate sitting in front of him.

Soon, there is a whole stack of copies being printed and a group of kids take one off of a pile.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

A father holds the picture in front of his son.

<stage>FATHER</stage>Son, why are you wasting your time with this sleazy trash?

<stage>SON</stage>Sorry, Dad.

The son walks away in shame as the father laughs.

<stage>FATHER</stage>Wait till I show the guys at work this little doozy.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

The photo emerges out of a fax.  A man picks it up and speaks on the phone.

MAN <stage>(laughs)</stage>: Mike, this is Al.  Just wanted to thank you on the "informative memo" you faxed me.  Whoops, here comes the boss.  Gotta go.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<person>Reverend Lovejoy</person> sits at his desk when his assistant walks up.

<stage>ASSISTANT</stage><person>Reverend Lovejoy</person>, your wife confiscated this from one of the boys in the choir.

Lovejoy looks at it and gasps.

<stage>LOVEJOY</stage>Why this sheep has strayed from my own flock.  His name's---

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<person>Smithers</person> and <person>Burns</person> in their office.  <person>Smithers</person> holds the same photo.

<stage><person>SMITHERS</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson, sir.   A low-level employee in sector 7-G.

<stage><person>BURNS</person></stage>Simpson, huh?  A family man?

<stage><person>SMITHERS</person></stage>Wife and three kids, sir.

<stage><person>BURNS</person></stage>I'd like to see our self-styled Valentino tomorrow morning, <person>Smithers</person>.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

A group of women in a gym stare at the picture taped to the wall.  It shows an arrow to <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s belly and says: "Watch Out!!! Bathing Suit Season is Coming!".

They all snicker as <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> walks up.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>What are we laughing at?

She gasps and rips the picture off the wall.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>An outside sh*t of the <location>Kwik</location>-E-Mart.

Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> takes out a donut from a shelf.  He heads over to <person>Apu</person>.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>One glazed and one Scratch-N-Win, please.

<stage><person>APU</person></stage>You look familiar, sir.  Are you on the television or something?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Sorry, buddy.  You got me confused with Fred Flintstone.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> scratches his lottery card.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Ooh, Liberty Bell!  Another Liberty Bell!  One more and I'm a millionaire.  Come on, Liberty Bell, please, please, please, please, please, please.

He scratches it and it turns out to be a grape.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage> <catchphrase>Doh</catchphrase>!  That purple fruit thing.  Where were you yesterday?

Another customer walks into the store.

<stage>CUSTOMER</stage>Hey, hey, lookin' good.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>What do you want, pal?

A young boy on a skateboard calls him over.

<stage>SKATEBOARD BOY</stage>Hey, mister.  Do dee do do do dee do do.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Well, a "do dee do dee do" to you too, pint size.  Jeez, you got a lot of nutcases in here.

<stage><person>APU</person></stage>Oh, sir, I've seen things you can't imagine.

A construction worker or plumber or something of that short yells to him as <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> leaves.

<stage>CONSTRUCTION WORKER</stage>Hey, hey, hey!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>I hear ya, buddy.  Whew.  Full moon.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> stops his car at a stoplight.  Nearby, a convertible stops and three girls start laughing at him and waving.

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(chuckles)</stage>: Hmm.  Still got it.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> parks the car and turns off the engine.  He whistles as he makes his way to the front door.  He walks in and gaps as <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> slams the picture into his face.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>What is the meaning of this?!!

<person>HOMER</person> <stage>(stammering)</stage>: Meaningless, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.  Don't even attempt to find meaning in it.  There's nothing between me and <location>Princess Kashmir</location>.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Princess who?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Hey, my photo.

<person>MARGE</person> +<stage> <person>HOMER</person></stage>Your photo?!

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Uh-oh.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><catchphrase>Why you little</catchphrase>---!

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Why you big---!

She grasps <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> around the neck and chokes him.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, go to your room.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>I'm out of here.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Look, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, honey, baby, doll.  I---.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, I don't even want to look at you right now.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>What are you saying, honey?

She points out to the street.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>But where will I sleep?

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>My suggestion is for you to sleep in the filth you created!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Would a <location>motel</location> be okay?

She slams the door shut on him.  <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> walks sadly away when the door opens behind him.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, I knew you'd come to your--.

A suitcase hits his face and <fam><person>Marge</person></fam> comes out.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Here, if you have any soul left, you'll need these.

She hands him a box of tissues as she sheds a tear.  Clothes are strewn all around them.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>I know I will.

She goes back into the house and shuts the door.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> sheds several tears as we...

FADE TO BLACK

<stage>FADE IN</stage>

An outside sh*t of <person>Moe</person>'s.  Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> sniffles as he drinks a beer and talks with <person>Moe</person>.  A sign above him says "Ladies Night - Unescorted Ladies Drink Free".

<stage><person>MOE</person></stage>What's the matter, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?  Hottest ladies' night in months and you're not even checking out the action.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, <person>Moe</person>.  My wife gave me the old heave ho because of some lousy picture.

<stage><person>MOE</person></stage>What, this one?

He points to a copy framed on his wall.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><catchphrase>Doh</catchphrase>!

<person>Barney</person> leans over.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>So, uh, where are you staying tonight, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><location>Motel</location>, I guess.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>Oh no, no pal of mine is gonna stay in some dingy flophouse.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<person>Barney</person> opens a door and he and <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> enter his apartment.  It's a complete mess.  There are clothes, wrappers, magazines, and empty beer bottles all over the floor.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>If you get hungry in the middle of the night, there's an open beer in the fridge.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> looks out a window.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Look, <person>Barney</person>.  See the row of tiny lights up there?  The middle one is my house.  Someone must have left the porch light on.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>Hey, that's rough, pal.

<person>Barney</person> dials a telephone.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>Hello, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.  You left your damn porch light on!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><person>Barney</person>!

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s not made of money, you know.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> steals the phone.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Who is this?

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>Don't listen to him, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.  He's--

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage>Oh, it's you.

She hangs up.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, you're overwrought.  Why don't you unwind a little bit?  <location>Party</location> down the hall.  You know, this apartment complex caters to upscale young singles like me.

He burps loudly.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>No, <location>Barn</location>.  I just want to crawl into bed.

<stage><person>BARNEY</person></stage>Suit yourself, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.  Nighty-night.

<person>Barney</person> walks out as <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> opens up his suitcase.  He sighs.

DISSOLVE TO;

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> lying on a coach and a table, his eyes open.  Music and laughter come from next door.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam> and the kids eating breakfast in the kitchen.

<stage><person>LISA</person></stage>I wonder when Dad's coming home.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam> looks over at her, a slightly sad look in her eyes.

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

An outside sh*t of <location>the Nuclear Power Plant</location>.

Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> drinks a cup of coffee.  <person>Smithers</person> comes on the announcement system.

<stage><person>SMITHERS</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson.  <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson.  Report at once to Mr. <person>Burns</person>' office.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, no.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> sitting in front of <person>Burns</person> in his office.

<stage><person>BURNS</person></stage>What in blue blazes do you think you're doing, Simpson?
<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>What do you mean, sir?

<person>Burns</person> holds up the photo.

<stage><person>BURNS</person></stage>I mean this.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> gasps.

2: Oh, that's a good idea.  Uh, but April's over at Foxy Boxing tonight.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> is yanked.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> talking with another manager, from the third club.

MANAGER 3: Just let me say that it is an honor to have <location>Springfield</location>'s number one swinger here with us to---

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Forget that.  I'm teaching my boy a lesson.  Is she here or not?

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> desperately tries to get a look but can't.

MANAGER 3: Uh, try <location>Mud City</location>.

<stage>CUT TO</stage>An outside sh*t of <location>Mud City</location>.  Inside, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> speaks on the phone.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage><fam><person>Marge</person></fam>!  <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>!  We're gonna try one more place, <location>the Sapphire Lounge</location>.  <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!  I said look at the floor!

<stage>DISSOLVE TO</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s car sliding up into the parking lot of <location>the Ye Old Ramp Inn</location>.

Inside, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> and <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> walk along several performers.

<stage>PERFORMER</stage>He really loves me---

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>There she is.  Hey, Princess.  It's me, the guy from the snapshot.

He walks over to her.  She is dressed like an angel and quite embarrassed.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Oh.  Oh, hi.

<stage>STAGE MANAGER</stage>Places, ladies, places.  Can I get just a little cooperation?  It's show time.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Look, I'm here because I want to apologize for treating you like an object.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Uh-huh.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>I also want my boy to find out that you're more than just a belly.  I want him to meet the women behind all the spangles and glitter and find out that she has thoughts and feelings too.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Oh, well, okay.  But can we make it quick?

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Nice to meet you, ma'am.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Could you tell him a little bit about yourself?

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Well, uh, my real name is Shawna Tifton.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Uh-huh.

Suddenly, the platform she's on begins rising.  This is some kind of play or performance in the inn...and <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s part of it!

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>My pet peeve is rude people.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Uh-huh.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>And my turn-ons include silk sheets and a warm fireplace.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Thank you very much, ma'am.  We'll be on our---.

He turns around and slips off the edge.  He hangs on with one hand.  It turns out to be a cage of some sort.

In front of the curtain, performing for the audience, is a singer.

<stage>SINGER</stage>I've heard them say so often
They can love their wives ooh
But I think that's just foolish
Men must have hearts...made of stone
Now my heart is made
Of softer stuff

Behind the curtain, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> still hangs nervously.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>Cool, man.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Get out of my cage.  My boss will freak out.

She begins trying to hit his fingers with her shoes, hoping her hands will slip.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Oh, no!

<stage>SINGER</stage>A pretty girl can't look my way without...

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Don't!  Don't!

She continues trying to tap him.

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage>Don't!  No.

<stage>PRINCESS</stage>Get out.  Get out of here.  Get your hands off.

She hits him in the face several times and he screams.

<stage>SINGER</stage>

A new romance...
Oh, I could love a million girls
And every girl a twin...

The curtain rises behind the singer and the show begins with the females dancing.  The audience cheers wildly.

<stage>SINGER</stage>Oh, I could love a Chinese girl, an Eskimo, or---

Princess finally hits <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and he's sent falling down to the stage.  He crashes to the steps and rolls down, much to the surprise of the audience and the dancers.  <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> looks attentively at every hit.

SINGER <stage>(silently)</stage>: Get off of my stage, fat boy.

<stage>AUDIENCE MEMBER</stage>Hey, it's the guy from the picture!

2: This is my Suzie.

AUD. MEMBER 3: Oh, she's so cute.  Here's mine.

<stage>SINGER</stage>You know, my mom sounded a little down the other day.  I'd better give her as call.

<stage><person>MARGE</person></stage><fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

<stage><person>HOMER</person></stage> <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

She is in tears as they run at each other.  <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> swings her around and hugs her.  They kiss on the stage.

<stage><person>BART</person></stage>All right, folks.  Show's over.  No more to see, folks.  Come on.  Only sick people want to see my folks kiss.
FADE OUT

CREDITS BEGIN

THE END
</txt></xml>