<xml>
<episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 102 

<title>THE SERIES HAS LANDED</title>

<author>Ken Keeler</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Fry, Bender and Leela sit around 
a big green table facing a big screen which Farnsworth stands 
in front of.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
As new employees I'd like your opinion 
on our commercial. I paid to have it 
air during the Superbowl.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Not on the same channel, of course.</speak>

<info>He puts a tiny video into the VCR and the commercial appears 
on the screen. A man is sat in his office and a huge green horrible 
gelatinous blob with three eyes is in front of him.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Interplanetary deliveries - what a 
headache!</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Uh... <info>(shouting)</info> I'm not Evans!</speak>

<info>Horrible Gelatinous Blob turns to the camera.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
When those other companies aren't brave 
or foolhardy enough to go, trust Planet 
Express for reliable, on time delivery.</speak>

<info>As the announcer speaks the Planet Express ship streaks across 
the screen being chased by spaceships shooting lasers at it. 
A man runs across an ice world with a parcel while at the same 
time being bombed. He delivers the parcel and is snatched by 
a gigantic vulture. Back in the office Evans lifts up a parcel.</info>

<speak who="EVANS">
Here's your package, Mr. Horrible Gelatinous 
Blob.</speak>

<info>He eats Evans anyway.</info>

<speak who="EVANS">
Thank you, sir!</speak>

<info>The Planet Express logo - a simplified picture of the ship flying 
across a white circle with "Planet Express" written around it 
- appears on the screen.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Planet Express: Our crew is replaceable. 
Your package isn't.</speak>

<info>The bird is still carrying the man and squawks. The commercial 
ends.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Are there really giant birds like that?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No, no! That was all just special effects! 
Now let's have breakfast. I hope everyone 
likes eggs.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Kitchen. Farnsworth opens a box of eggs. 
They are giant bird eggs. One hatches and the bird inside tries 
to eat him. He hits it with a frying pan.</info>

<info>Opening Credits. Caption: In Hypno-Vision.</info>

<info>Outside Planet Express. A Jamaican man with dreads crosses the 
street. He is wearing a green suit and glasses. He unlocks the 
door and turns the open sign around from "Sorry, We're Closed" 
to "Sorry, We're Open".</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express. Meeting Room. Fry, Bender, Farnsworth 
and Leela are sat around the table. Fry pours some cereal into 
a bowl, Bender relaxes and Leela looks at a clipboard.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm never going to get used to the 31st 
century.  Caffinated bacon? Baconated 
grapefruit? Admiral Crunch?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well, if you don't like that try some 
Archduke Chocula.</speak>

<info>She holds up a box of the cereal. Enter the Jamaican man with 
a large crate.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah, Hermes! Crew, meet Hermes Conrad. 
He manages my delivery business, pays 
the bills, notifies next of kin, what 
have you.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Someone come and dropped this package 
through the slot last night. Now which 
one of you is the captain?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, my! I haven't picked a new captain 
yet. It's always so hard to choose.</speak>

<info>He looks around the table. Fry is so enthusiastic he doesn't 
manage to swallow his spoonful of cereal completely and milk 
dribbles down his chin.</info>

<info>Farnsworth looks at Bender who drinks back a bottle of beer 
and belches a flame. He looks at Leela. She has already signed 
Hermes' clipboard and she salutes to him.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hmm, you!</speak>

<info>He points at her. Fry groans.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Hermes' Office. Hermes sits at his desk facing 
Leela. He slides a sheet of paper to her.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
OK, Captain, this is just a standard 
legal release protecting Planet Express 
from lawsuits in the event of the unforeseen.</speak>

<info>He hands Leela a piece of paper.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(reading)</info> Death by airlock failure.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Mmm.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(reading)</info> Death by brain parasite.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Yeah.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(reading)</info> Death by sonic diarrhoea?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(chuckling)</info> Oh, you don't want that!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Look, I don't know about any of your 
previous captains but I intend to do 
as little dying as possible.</speak>

<info>She puts the form on the desk and Hermes chuckles again. He 
slides it back to her.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Sign the paper!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Corridor. Farnsworth and Fry stand next to a 
door.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Now Fry, before you go into space you'll 
need to see our staff doctor. I should 
warn you though, he's a little unusual. 
<info>(whispering)</info> He wears sandals!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Zoidberg's Office. The doctor, a red 
alien creature is sat in his chair with is feet on the desk. 
Behind him is a chart of a human's internal organs - pinned to 
the wall upside down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hi -- eurgh!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dr. Zoidberg, this is Fry, the new delivery 
boy. He needs a physical.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Excellent, excellent!</speak>

<info>He clacks his claws. Fry is not so sure.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You'll be fine.</speak>

<info>He turns to leave but looks back with a worried look on his 
face.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Now open your mouth and let's have a 
look at that brain.  No no no no no 
not that mouth!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I only have one.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Really?</speak>

<info>He takes a small card out of his pocket and looks at it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, is there a human doctor around?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Young lady, I'm an expert on humans. 
Now pick a mouth, open it and say... 
What? My mother was a saint! Get out!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth is unscrewing Bender's 
head from his body. With them is Leela and a young Asian woman 
wearing a pink jumpsuit.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dear Lord, Bender, you're filthy.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah, like you don't have crap in your 
neck!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth puts Bender's head down on a table and turns to the 
girl.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Amy, why don't you give his body a going 
over with the cleaning pick?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
OK. Does it hurt when I go like this?</speak>

<info>She pokes Bender's neck but hits Leela in the eye instead.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
A little.</speak>

<info>Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, the doctor says I'm as healthy 
as a crab. Can I go into space now?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
As soon as we finish cleaning Bender. 
Oh, and Fry, this is our intern, Amy 
Wong. She's an engineering student of 
mine. <info>(whispering)</info> I like having her 
around because she's the same blood 
type as me.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey! You're the unfrozen guy! From the 
20th century, right?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(chuffed)</info> Last time I checked.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hang on. Amy Wong? Of the Mars Wongs?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Look. We're not as rich as everybody 
says.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh-huh! What sorority do you belong 
to?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(ashamed)</info> Kappa Kappa Wong.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, rich girl. Look over here! It's 
me, Bender. I'm being entertaining. 
<info>(singing)</info> La la la look at my head. 
It's all painted look at my head! I 
got a big old head, hey! Ho! <info>(talking)</info> 
Alright, show's over, I'm tired.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah, to be young again. And also a robot! 
Now as I recall you youngsters have 
a package to deliver.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Finally! Come on Bender, let's mosey!</speak>

<info>He picks up Bender's head and throws it to his body. It misses 
the catch and Bender's head falls on the floor.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nice catch, idiot!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. The crate is being loaded into the ships 
cargo bay on a magnetic winch. It is addressed to Luna Park.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So where are we going anyway?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nowhere special. The moon.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The moon? The moon moon? Wow! I'm gonna 
be a famous hero just like Neil Armstrong 
and those other brave guys no one ever 
heard of!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, I love stuff like the moon! Can 
I come, Leela?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well...I guess so. Just be careful. 
I'd like to hold off any major screwups 
until at least my second day as captain.</speak>

<speak who="FANSWORTH">
Nothing will go wrong.  <info>(whispering)</info> 
If something goes wrong bring back the 
blood.</speak>

<info>Ships Cockpit. Bender and Amy are sat on the couch. Leela sits 
in the pilot's seat while Fry sits in a chair beside her. She 
presses some buttons.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. The tilting mechanism comes 
out of the floor and pushes the ship into its 45-degree launch 
position.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. The hangar roof slides open.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Fry scoots his chair over to Leela.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Can I do the countdown?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Huh? Oh sure, knock yourself out.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ten......nine --</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK we're here!</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(awestruck)</info> Eightsevensixfivefourthreetwooneblastoff!</speak>

<info>The ship cruises towards the moon and flies through a hole in 
a dome on the surface.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Luna Park. The ship lands.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Leela takes the keys out of the ignition 
and Fry gets out of his seat and heads for the door.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hurry up, I wanna see the moon!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Relax, its open till 9.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. Fry stands on the bottom step.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's one small step for Fry --</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
And one giant line for admission!</speak>

<info>The man is standing in a long queue for the Luna Park, a huge 
Disneyland-like place with moon-themed rides.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow!  Um, can I have cuts?</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Hmm -- No!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Fry runs in.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You're not gonna believe this but they 
landed an amusement park on the moon!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Guh! It's the happiest place orbiting 
Earth.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Lets go, already!</speak>

<info>They walk towards the door but Leela is blocking it.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, we have a crate to deliver.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Let's just dump it in the sewer and 
say we delivered it.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Too much work. Lets burn it and say 
we dumped it in the sewer.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, if everyone's finished being stupid 
--</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I had more but you go ahead.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
We'll deliver that crate like professionals 
and then we'll go home.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But I've never been to the moon before.</speak>

<info>Leela sighs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Alright. We'll deliver that crate like 
professionals...and then we'll go ride 
the bumper cars.  Amy, why don't you 
help Fry hoist down the crate. Then 
lock up when you're done. Just be careful.</speak>

<info>She hands the keys to Amy.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Aye, aye, Captain! I mean only one eye. 
I mean, yes, sir, um, ma'am!</speak>

<info>Ships Cargo Bay. Fry stands next to the crate by the open bomb 
bay doors while Amy stands at the magnetic winch control station.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Clear?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Clear!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Ready to hoist?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ready!</speak>

<info>Amy presses a button and the winch drops and hits her on the 
head.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Ow!</speak>

<info>The magnetic forces pull the keys out of her pocket. She tries 
again and the winch picks up the crate. The keys slip off the 
winch and through a hole in the crate.</info>

<info>Outside Luna Park Receiving Depot. Fry wheels the crate towards 
the room on a trolley. Amy follows.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
My first space delivery.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Luna Park Receiving Depot. A lazy man named Sal is sat 
at a desk with his feet up. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, greetings, Moon Man, we come in 
peace. I am Fry from the planet Earth.</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
Wise guy, huh? If I wasn't so lazy I'd 
punch you in the stomach.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But you are lazy, right?</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
Oh, don't get me started.</speak>

<info>Luna Park: Moon Street USA. The crew walk past a band of bandbots 
that are shaped like musical instruments, past a Moonvenirs stall. 
Bender stops and takes a bottle out of his chest cabinet and 
a mascot with a huge flat moon shaped head runs up behind him.</info>

<speak who="CRATER FACE">
Hi, I'm Crater Face! Welcome to Luna 
Park. I'll have to confiscate your alcohol, 
sir.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Better mascots than you have tried.</speak>

<info>He finishes the bottle and jabs it in Crater Face's eye making 
it look like a scene from A Trip To The Moon. He leaves..</info>

<speak who="CRATER FACE">
At least I still have my self respect!</speak>

<info>He chuckles to himself then cries.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. At a souvenir stall they merchandise such as "I'm 
With Stupid On The Moon" t-shirts, "My Other Car Is A Porsche 
- On The Moon" bumper stickers and "What Part Of MOON Don't You 
Understand?" fridge magnets. Leela scoffs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Who buys this trash?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Idiots who need gifts for other idiots.</speak>

<info>Fry emerges from around the corner wearing one of the t-shirts 
and carrying magnets.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, I got you guys refrigerator magnets.</speak>

<info>He puts one on Bender's head causing Bender's pupils to dilate 
and an electrical surge in his head. He starts waving his arms 
around in a panic.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Get it off! Get it off! Get it -- uh 
oh!  <info>(singing)</info> How many roads must a 
man walk down, before you... <info>(talking)</info> 
Keep those things off of me! Magnets 
screw up my inhibition unit!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So you flip out and start acting like 
some crazy folk singer?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes. I guess a robot would have to be 
crazy to wanna be a folk singer.</speak>

<info>He gazes upwards sadly.</info>

<info>Luna Park: Whalers Of The Sea Of Tranquility. The gang float 
through an It's A Small World After All-like ride passing by 
robotic whalers.</info>

<speak who="WHALERBOTS">
<info>(singing)</info> We're whalers on the moon,

We carry a harpoon,

But there ain't no whales so we tell our tall tale

And sing our whaling tune!

</speak><info>A Whalerbot tilting on a barrel waves to Bender.</info>

<speak who="WHALERBOT">
Bender, hey, Bender! Over here!</speak>

<info>Bender covers his face and turns away.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, jeez, I went to high school with 
that guy!</speak>

<info>Luna Park: Goophy Gopher Revue. The audience sit patiently for 
the show to begin.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Monsanto presents: The Goophy Gopher 
Revue!</speak>

<info>On a small stage several robotic gophers pop out of crater-shaped 
holes.</info>

<speak who="GOPHER #1">
Why does a moon rock taste better than 
an Earth rock?</speak>

<speak who="GOPHER #2">
Because it's a little meteor!</speak>

<info>The gophers laugh.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This is weak!</speak>

<speak who="GOPHER #1">
Address all complaints to the Monsanto 
Corporation.</speak>

<info>Luna Park. The crew get some candy floss from an Orlon Candy 
stall and carry on walking around the park. Fry looks unhappy.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What's wrong, Fry?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I don't know. This place is great and 
all but its just so artificial. The 
gravity, the air, the gophers. You might 
as well stay on Earth.  That's what 
I came to see! I wanna go out there 
and jump around like an astronaut. Screw 
this phoney stuff!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
But the phoney stuff is what's fun. 
It's boring out there.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah! You're the kind of guy who visits 
Jerusalem and doesn't want to see the 
Sexeteria!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Maybe I should take Fry on the Luna 
Rover ride. You get to wear a space 
suit and drive around on the surface. 
And the line's short because it's educational.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I don't care how educational it is. 
Let's do it!</speak>

<info>He runs off with Leela. Bender raises his bottle.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting)</info> Next year in Jerusalem!</speak>

<info>Luna Park: Destination Moon. Fry and Leela sit in a moon buggy 
wearing orange spacesuits.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Finally! Get ready for some serious 
moon action.</speak>

<info>They go through some doors.</info>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
<info>(voice-over)</info> The story of lunar exploration 
started with one man. A man with a dream.</speak>

<info>The ride continues to a room with animatronic versions of the 
leads from The Honeymooners.</info>

<speak who="RALPH KRAMDENBOT">
One of these days, Alice. Bang! Zoom! 
Straight to the moon!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wow, I never realised the first astronauts 
were so fat!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's not an astronaut, it's a TV comedian. 
And he was just using space travel as 
a metaphor for beating his wife.</speak>

<info>Luna Park Arcade. Amy is playing Virtual Virtual Skeeball, a 
virtual version of Virtual Skeeball. She just sits in a chair 
wearing a VR helmet.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Wow! I could swear I was really playing 
virtual skeeball!  Hm?</speak>

<info>She takes the helmet off.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Look, it's that crate we were gonna 
throw in the sewer.</speak>

<info>He points to Sal who is emptying the crate into a claw machine 
using a robot arm around his waist. They watch as the ship keys 
fall out of the crate and into the machine. Amy gasps.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
The keys to the ship!  They must have 
fallen into the crate! Leela's gonna 
kill me!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nah. She'll probably make me do it.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Mister? Could you please get those keys 
out for me?</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
What do I look like? A guy who's not 
lazy?</speak>

<info>Amy gets a coin out and plays the game. The claw grabs the keys 
but drops them on the way back up and she curses in Chinese.</info>

<info>Luna Park: Destination Moon. The moon buggy continues across 
lunar terrain, boxed in with poorly constructed walls with stars 
painted on them.</info>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
<info>(voice-over)</info> No one knows where, when 
or how Man first landed on the moon...</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I do.</speak>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
<info>(voice-over)</info> ...but our fungineers think 
it might have happened something like 
this:</speak>

<info>A prop of a lunar landing module opens up and Whalerbots file 
out of it.</info>

<speak who="WHALERBOTS">
<info>(singing)</info> We're whalers on the moon,</speak>

<info>Goophy Gophers pop up from craters.</info>

<speak who="GOPHERS">
<info>(singing)</info> We carry a harpoon,</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> ...and sing a whaling tune. 
We're whalers on the moon...</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's not how it happened.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, really? I don't see you with a fungineering 
degree! p></speak>

<speak who="FRY">
This is stupid. I'm taking this thing 
out to the real moon.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, no. This is my first mission and 
I'm not gonna let us get in any trouble. 
Besides, the car's on a track.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Not for long!</speak>

<info>He grabs a harpoon, throws it in front of the buggy and derails 
it. It drives over a whalerbot and out onto the open lunar surface.</info>

<speak who="WHALERBOT">
Ooh aah! I died doin' what I loved.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. Fry drives the car around grinning.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, you're on the surface. Now I'll 
give you 10 minutes. Then you'll get 
bored, turn around and apologise for 
being such a jerk. Agreed?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Agreed.  Yee-haw! Woo! Yeah! Crank up 
the radio!</speak>

<info>He turns the radio on.</info>

<speak who="WHALERBOTS">
We're whalers on the -</speak>

<info>He turns it off straight away.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry drives around another crater.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yee-haw!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Time's up. Make a U-turn at the next 
crater.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No not yet. How 'bout we go look for 
the original moon landing site?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's crazy! It's been lost for centuries!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well I'm feelin' lucky!  Uh... I'm ready 
to go back now.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
We're gonna die! It's every man for 
himself!  Help me, Leela!  You did it! 
We're safe!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No. Now we're gonna die.</speak>

<info>The gauge on the oxygen canister reads nearly empty.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's every man for himself.</speak>

<info>He tries to run off but chokes himself on the oxygen pipe from 
his helmet.</info>

<info>Luna Park: Arcade. Amy is still trying to get the keys but the 
claw drops them again. Enter Bender with a small doll.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, look what I won from a tourist's 
pocket!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Shut up. You're distracting me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Come on, it's just like making love. 
Y'know: Left, down, rotate 62 degrees, 
engage rotor.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I know how to make love!</speak>

<info>The claw drops the keys again. Amy sighs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Here, let me do it.  Ah, lousy arm. 
Must be rigged!  That's her, officers! 
Uh, that's the woman who programmed 
me for evil!</speak>

<info>He runs off with his extended arm trailing behind him and the 
Moon Patrol chase him.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Lunar Park Dome. The Moon Patrol officers throw 
Bender outside the dome and close the doors behind him.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah, well, I'm gonna go build my own 
theme park, with blackjack and hookers. 
In fact, forget the park!</speak>

<info>Lunar Surface. An exhausted Fry and Leela continue their journey 
back to the park.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(gasping)</info> I'm sorry, Leela, I can't 
go on any further. Just leave me to 
die in that barn over there.</speak>

<info>Leela gasps. Fry is pointing to a farm in a dome.</info>

<info>Cut to: Farmyard. Fry and Leela run in and take off their space 
helmets, panting.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Thank God!</speak>

<info>Behind them a gun cocks. They turn around and see a farmer. 
He has a buck tooth and a cap that says "The Moon Shall Rise 
Again".</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
Trespassers, eh?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, sir. We're amusement park patrons.</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
Ooh, that's a wicked sinful place. Tilt-a-whirl's 
OK, but the rest is mighty wicked.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Our car broke down and we're out of 
oxygen. Can we borrow some?</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
Huh, borry? Looky here, city girl, oxygen 
don't grow on trees. You'll have to 
earn it doing chores on my hydroponic 
farm. You can go back to your precious 
theme park at sun up.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I guess we could do chores for a few 
hours.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, night lasts two weeks on the moon.</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
Yup. Drops down to -173!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Fahrenheit or Celsius?</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
First one, then th'other. And them spacesuits 
ain't a-heated so you ain�t goin' nowhere 
til sunrise. You can sleep in the barn. 
Just don't be a-touchin' my three beautiful 
robot daughters. Y'hear?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Robot daughters?</speak>

<info>He points to his robot daughters outside the house.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
This here is Lulabelle 7.</speak>

<speak who="LULABELLE 7">
Yoo-hoo!</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
Daisy-Mae 128K.</speak>

<speak who="DAISY MAE 128K">
Yoo-hoo!</speak>

<speak who="FARMER">
And the Crushinator.</speak>

<info>The Crushinator is a huge pink thing with tracks instead of 
legs.</info>

<speak who="CRUSHINATOR">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> Yoo-hoo.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whoa!</speak>

<info>Barn. Fry and Leela are milking some cows.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I told you to turn around and go back 
to the park. But oh, no, the park was 
too phoney. We had to see the real moon.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And it was great! We got to see craters 
and rocks and that one incredible rock 
that looked like a crater and, and these 
fellas.</speak>

<info>He pats the cow, which isn't a cow but some sort of insect-bovine 
creature called a buggalo.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, face it. The moon is a dump. It's 
a boring dried up wasteland. And the 
only reason anybody ever comes here 
is for the tacky little amusement park. 
Can't you just accept that?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I guess I can't.</speak>

<info>They hear a shot from outside. They look through the transparent 
barn doors and see Bender running out of the farmhouse.</info>

<info>Cut to: Farmyard. The farmer chases him out of the house waving 
his rifle.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
I'll learn ye to sleep with my robot 
daughters!</speak>

<info>Bender runs into the barn.</info>

<info>Cut to: Barn. He leans against the transparent door. Outside 
the farmer reloads his gun.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
He'll never find me in here.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, Bender. You didn't touch the Crushinator, 
did you?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Of course not. A lady that fine you 
gotta romance first.</speak>

<info>Another gunshot smashes the barn door behind Bender. Bender 
legs it while the farmer reloads. Fry and Leela follow him through 
another door. They pick up their helmets as they run.</info>

<info>Cut to: Farmyard. They grab some oxygen tanks and get into the 
moon buggy.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. The buggy speeds away from the farm. 
The farmer, in a spacesuit but with his cap sat on top, Lulabelle 
7 and Daisy-Mae 128K run after them. The farmer fires a shot 
at them and misses.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
Oh, no you don't! C'mere Crushinator.</speak>

<info>Crushinator drives out of the farm and pulls up beside him.</info>

<speak who="CRUSHINATOR">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> Yes, Pa.</speak>

<info>She transforms into a car. The farmer and his other two daughters 
get in and drive after Fry, Leela and Bender. They chase the 
crew around past craters and through ravines. The farmer takes 
a shot at the crew and narrowly misses them. The crew round a 
corner and find their way blocked by a rock bridge.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's too low.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hang on. Hang on. Jump.  Hold on to 
your helmet!</speak>

<info>They jump the gorge, flying over crocodiles with space helmets 
and land safely on the other side. They all cheer and then a 
wheel falls off the buggy. The Crushintor approaches the other 
side and stops. The farmer climbs out and slams the door.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
God darn, it Crushinator, jump!</speak>

<speak who="CRUSHINATOR">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> No, Pa. I love him.</speak>

<info>The farmer takes his hat off and jumps on it, groaning. Leela 
looks at the broken wheel and Fry sees a huge shadow approaching.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, cool! Dark side of the moon!</speak>

<info>Leela gasps.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nightfall's coming.  Hurry, before we 
freeze.</speak>

<info>The flee from the shadow.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What do you mean "we", mammal?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. He watches the crew 
through a telescope.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, dear! I really ought to do something. 
But I am already in my pyjamas.</speak>

<info>He falls asleep and starts snoring.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. Fry and Leela are panting.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We can't outrun it forever.</speak>

<info>Fry sees something.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Over there! Look! It's the moon landing 
site! We found it!</speak>

<info>They run towards it. Leela climbs the ladder and pushes over 
the hatch.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Quick, get in.</speak>

<info>Fry sees the American flag.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's that flag from MTV! And Neil Armstrong's 
footprint!  Hey! My foot's bigger! Leela, 
isn't this the greatest thing you've 
ever seen?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, look around. It's just a crummy 
plastic flag and a dead man's tracks 
in the dust.  Now get in here before 
you freeze.</speak>

<info>Fry sighs and climbs the ladder.</info>

<info>Cut to: Apollo 11 Lander. Leela helps him in.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. She closes the door just as Bender arrives.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, no room for Bender, huh? Fine! I'll 
go build my own lunar lander, with blackjack 
and hookers. In fact, forget the lunar 
lander and the blackjack. Ah, screw 
the whole thing.</speak>

<info>He walks off.</info>

<info>Apollo 11 Lander. Leela reads the oxygen gauge.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well if the oxygen holds out we might 
live long enough to starve to death.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Look, Leela, I'm sorry. I never should 
have dragged you out here.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's right, you shouldn't have. I 
still don't get what the big attraction 
is.</speak>

<info>Fry sighs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I never told anybody this but a thousand 
years ago I used to look up at the moon 
and dream about being an astronaut. 
I just didn't have the grades. Nor the 
physical endurance. Plus I threw up 
a lot and nobody liked spending a week 
with me.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
A week would be a little much.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The moon was like this awesome, romantic, 
mysterious thing, hanging up there in 
the sky where you could never reach 
it, no matter how much you wanted to. 
But you're right. Once you're actually 
here it's just a big dull rock. I guess 
I just wanted you to see it through 
my eyes, the way I used to.</speak>

<info>Leela looks through a window. She sees the Earth.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, look. It really is beautiful. I 
don't know why I never noticed before.</speak>

<info>Bender runs towards the capsule.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. The farmer is chasing him in a weird 
thing with spikes.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
Had to come back for the Crushinator, 
eh, robot? Well I got you this time.</speak>

<info>The spikes get closer to Bender. The Planet Express ship swoops 
in above them. The magnetic winch lowers towards Bender.</info>

<info>Cut to: Apollo 11 Lander.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's Amy! We're saved!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Amy? Where'd she learn to operate the 
controls like that?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Amy is operating the winch expertly, 
having had practice at the Luna Park with the claw game. The 
toys from the game are piled up in the corner.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. The winch is getting closer to Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Not the magnet! No! No! Nooo --  Uh-oh!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Amy cheers.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lunar Surface. Bender kicks his legs and waves his arms 
around as he flies away from the farmer attached to the winch.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> She'll be comin' round the 
mountain when she comes,

She'll be comin' round the mountain when she comes --

<info>(talking)</info> I'll kill you Amy!

<info>(singing)</info> She'll be comin' round the mountain,

She'll be comin' round the mountain,

She'll be comin' --

</speak><info>He slams into the side of the lunar lander and it takes off. 
The farmer watches the ship fly away and takes off his space 
helmet and jumps on it.</info>

<speak who="FARMER">
Aww, dang it!</speak>

<info>He starts to choke then collapses. He reaches over to the helmet 
and puts it back on and breathes. Bender, still attached to the 
side of the lander, carries on singing.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> She'll be riding six white 
horses when she comes,

She'll be riding six white horses when she comes -

<info>(talking)</info> Hey, I'm pretty good!

<info>(singing)</info> She'll be riding six white horses...

</speak><speak who="LEELA">
So, Fry, was the real moon anything 
like the moon you used to dream about?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, close enough!</speak>

<info>THE END</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well I'll shoot her with my ray gun 
when she comes,</speak>

Yes, I'll shoot her with my ray gun when she comes,

Yes, I'll shoot her with my ray gun,

Oh, I'll shoot her with my ray gun,

Yes, I'll shoot her with my ray gun when she comes,

When she comes!

I'll be blastin' all the humans in the world,

I'll be blastin' all the humans in the world,

I'll be blastin' all the humans,

I'll be blastin' all the humans,

I'll be blastin' all the humans in the world,

In the world!

<info>(shouting)</info> One more time!
</xml>