<xml>
<episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 109 

<title>HELL IS OTHER ROBOTS</title>

<author>Eric Kaplan</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Condemned By The Space Pope.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. Fry, Leela and Bender are sat waiting for 
a Beastie Boys gig to start.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This is awesome! I've been waiting a 
thousand years to see a Beastie Boys 
show.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Can I get anybody a beer?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Sure!</speak>

<info>Bender opens his chest cabinet and uses his antenna to pump 
some beer into a cup. He hands it to Fry and Fry takes a gulp.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Ladies and gentlemen, here to lay down 
some old, old, incredibly old school 
beats: The Beastie Boys!</speak>

<info>A man wheels the Beastie Boys' heads in jars onto the stage. 
The crowd cheers. Some guys in black suits grab the jars and 
dance around. The Beastie Boys perform Intergalactic.</info>

<speak who="BEASTIE BOYS">
<info>(singing)</info> Well now don't you tell to 
smile

You stick around I'll make it worth your while

Got numbers beyond what you can dial

Maybe it's because I'm so versatile

Style profile I said

It always brings me back when I hear Wu Child...

</speak><info>Leela looks at her wrist thing.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Impressive. They're busting mad rhymes 
with an 80% success rate.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I believe that qualifies as ill. At 
least from a technical standpoint.</speak>

<info>Fry is standing away from them.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Will you guys shut up! I'm trying to 
look cool.</speak>

<info>He attempts to dance.</info>

<speak who="BEASTIE BOYS">
<info>(singing)</info> ...known for the Flintstone 
Flop

Tammy D gettin' biz on the crop

Beastie Boys know to let the beat...

</speak><speak who="MIKE">
Drop!  Ow! How's it going?  Enjoying 
the show? Ow!  <info>(shouting)</info> Don't forget 
to pick up a T-Shirt!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! An old-fashioned mosh pit! Come 
on guys. Tonight we're gonna party like 
its 1999...again.</speak>

<info>The Beastie Boys start to perform Super Disco Breakin.</info>

Beastie Boys <info>(singing)</info> Well it's 50 cups of coffee and you know 
it's on

I move the crowd to the break of break of dawn...

<info>Fry and Bender get into the mosh pit. Leela gets bumped around 
and doesn't look like she is enjoying herself.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Ow! Hey, watch it!</speak>

<info>She elbows someone in the face, kicks someone else, punches 
someone else the does a full circle flying kick and knocks everyone 
around her over.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The crowd are sat in their seats again.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, these guys rock harder than ever!</speak>

<info>The Beastie Boys sing Sabotage.</info>

<speak who="MIKE"><info>(SINGING)</info>
Oh my...</speak>

<speak who="MCA"><info>(SINGING)</info>
...it's a mirage...</speak>

<speak who="AD ROCK"><info>(SINGING)</info>
...tellin' you all it's a...</speak>

<speak who="AD ROCK"><info>(SINGING)</info>
Sabotage, yeah!</speak>

<speak who="MIKE">
Peace, we out!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers and the Beastie Boys are wheeled out. Fry cheers. 
Enter a Fender amplifier who recognises Bender.</info>

<speak who="FENDER">
Hey, Bender!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, Fender! Man, I haven't seen you 
since high school. You still workin' 
at Jack In The Box?</speak>

<speak who="FENDER">
Not anymore, baby. I'm with the band!</speak>

<info>Backstage. The Beastie Boys are getting head massages.</info>

<speak who="MIKE">
Aw! Oh, yeah!</speak>

<info>Enter Fender, Bender, Fry and Leela.</info>

<speak who="FENDER">
Hey, fellas, hey. I want you to meet 
my friends Bender, Fry and Leela.</speak>

<speak who="AD ROCK">
Y'know we're, really not that interested 
in meeting them.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! I love you guys! Back in the 20th 
century, I had all five of your albums.</speak>

<speak who="AD ROCK">
That was a thousand years ago. Now we 
got seven.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Cool! Can I borrow the new ones? And 
a couple of blank tapes?</speak>

<info>Fender turns his volume down and turns to Bender.</info>

<speak who="FENDER"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
Hey, Bender, why don't we ditch these 
organ sacks and hit the real party?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Count me in! I'm gonna drink til I reboot!</speak>

<info>Room. Fender presses a button, a door slides open and in the 
room are three robots hooked up to an electricity thing. It shocks 
them and they groan.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, what kinda party is this? There's 
no booze and only one hooker.</speak>

<speak who="FENDER">
Don't be a drag, man. We're jacking 
on!  Aww yeah!  Wanna jolt?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh hey, I'm no square but isn't that 
counter-indicated by my operations manual?</speak>

<info>The other robots laugh.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Counter indicated!</speak>

<speak who="FENDER">
Come on, Bender, grab a jack. I told 
these guys you were cool.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, if jacking on'll make strangers 
think I'm cool, I'll do it!</speak>

<info>He takes the plug and sticks it in his head. He goes crazy and 
starts to hallucinate. Sitar music plays. He falls onto a circuit 
board. Then he flies around a molecule and eats the electrons. 
He eats the proton and starts giggling. He dances with an electric 
eel. Fender takes the plug out.</info>

<speak who="FENDER">
Easy, baby. You don't wanna get hooked 
on this stuff.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Eh, no need to worry. I don't have an 
addictive personality.</speak>

<info>He smokes a cigar, gulps down some beer and jacks on again.</info>

<info>New New York Street. The next day Fry and Bender walk around 
a slum. Hobos sleep in the travel tubes and windows are boarded 
up. Bender wears shades.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey uh Bender. What are we doing in 
this bad neighbourhood?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Shut up, square!  I'll just be a minute!</speak>

<info>Fry leans against a lamppost and whistles.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Three hours later Bender comes out. He walks weirdly 
and groans. He falls over, rolls off the pavement and lands face 
down in the gutter. A Preacherbot walks by and sees him.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
Wretched sinner unit! The path to robot 
heaven lies here......in the Good Book 
3.0.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey! Do I preach to you when you're 
lying stoned in the gutter? No! So beat 
it!</speak>

<info>Preacherbot tuts and walks off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Who was that guy?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yo mama! Now shut up and drag me to 
work!</speak>

<info>Fry drags Bender by his legs.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Hermes addresses the staff with 
a chart.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Our electric bill's climbing faster 
than a green snake up a sugarcane. Obviously 
someone round been wastin' a whole heap 
a juice! Probably you!</speak>

<info>He points at Zoidberg.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Me?</speak>

<info>Enter Fry and Bender.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Good morning, Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
None of your business, get off my back!</speak>

<info>He runs into the restroom.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
What's his problem?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
If I didn't know better I'd almost think 
he was abusing electricity.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender? No way!  I definitely would've 
noticed something.</speak>

<info>Leela gets up and knocks on the restroom door.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, why are you spending so much 
time in the bathroom? Are you jacking 
on in there?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No! Don't come in!</speak>

<info>Enter Farnsworth with a box.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news, everyone! Today you'll be 
delivering a crate of subpoenas to Sicily 
8, the Mob Planet!</speak>

<info>Bender returns.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright, let's get to work! I'll be 
out in a second.</speak>

<info>He runs back into the bathroom.</info>

<info>Ships Cockpit. The crew have made the delivery and are returning 
to Earth.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I know Big Vinnie said he was giving 
me the kiss of death but I still think 
he was gay.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Did he use his tongue?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
A little.  You OK, Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
None of your business! Get off my back!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh oh. There seems to be some sort of 
electrical disturbance in the Coalsack 
Nebula.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
A what kind of disturbance?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Electrical. Anyway it's going to take 
some careful piloting to avoid it.</speak>

<info>Bender sneaks out of the cockpit.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. Bender opens the door and steps out. He 
edges his way around to the engines and pushes them so the ship 
flies straight towards the nebula. He laughs insanely.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Leela is struggling with the controls.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We're out of control. We're heading 
straight into the electric field!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What's happening? I-I feel weird!</speak>

<info>The electricity has made his hair stand on end.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. Bender stands on top of it in front of 
the gun turret, waving his arms.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Come on universe you big, mostly empty 
wuss! Gimmie all the juice you got! 
Oh, mama!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Bender sits atop the ship, melted to 
it. Amy drills him off with a jackhammer. He slides down the 
front of the ship and lands on the floor. Farnsworth, Leela and 
Hermes stare at him. Bender looks up at them.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What?</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Bender has been repaired and a 
crate of spare robot legs and thighs is on the floor next tot 
he table.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, we didn't mind your drinking, 
or your kleptomania, or your pornography 
ring.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
In fact, that's why we loved you.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
But this electricity abuse crossed the 
line. You almost killed us.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And you made me feel like a jerk for 
trusting you. Just like when my friend 
Richie swore he wasn't taking drugs 
and then he sold me my mom's VCR and 
then later I found out he was taking 
drugs. You make me ashamed to be your 
friend.</speak>

<info>Bender sighs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You're right. I'm a lost cause.</speak>

<info>He walks out.</info>

<info>New New York Street. Bender walks past Sparky's Den sadly. He 
hears an organ play behind him and looks across the street to 
the Temple Of Robotology.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Maybe there's another way.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Temple Of Robotology Roof. Bender plugs himself into 
the neon sign and jacks on.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, yeah, that's the good stuff.  <info>(crying)</info> 
What am I doing? What have I become? 
Huh?</speak>

<info>He looks down though the roof and sees a sermon.</info>

<info>Cut to: Temple Of Robotology.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
I see a lot of fancy robots here today. 
Made of real shiny metal. But that don't 
impress the Robot Devil, no, sir!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
No, sir!</speak>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
'Cause if you're a sinner, he's gonna 
plug his infernal modem in the wall, 
belchin' smoke and flame. Amd he's gonna 
download ya straight to Robot Hell!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Straight to hell!</speak>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
So I ask ya: Who will stand up and be 
saved? Who? Who?</speak>

<info>The glass roof gives way and Bender falls through and lands 
in front of Preacherbot.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(weakly)</info> Me.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Hermes addresses the crew.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
And as a further cost-cutting measure, 
I have eliminted the salt-water cooler.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
This is a witch hunt!</speak>

<info>Enter Bender wearing a bow tie.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Oh, what a beautiful morning, 
oh what a beautiful day! <info>(talking)</info> Greetings, 
friends. Don't we all look nice today?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Great he's whacked out on electricity 
again.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No, I'm whacked out on life. My friends, 
I found religion.</speak>

<info>The crew stare, shocked.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Religon? Is this another scam to get 
free yarmulkes?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Give him a break, Fry. If this helps 
Bender clean up his act then I think 
we should be supportive.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, yeah.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Oh, yes!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh, yeah.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wonderful. Then you'll all come to my 
exceedingly long, un-air-conditioned 
baptism ceremony!</speak>

<info>The staff murmur.</info>

<info>Temple Of Robotology.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
We are gathered here today to deliver 
brother Bender from the cold, steel 
grip of the Robot Devil unto the cold, 
steel bosom of our congregation.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
Tell it, Preacher!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #3">
That equals true.</speak>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
Brother Bender, do you accept the principles 
of Robotology on pain of eternal damnation 
in Robot Hell?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes, I do.</speak>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
Then I will now baptise you.  Press 
any key to continue.</speak>

<info>Bender presses a button and he is lifted and baptised in a barrel 
of High Viscosity Baptismal Oil. Preacherbot welds the symbol 
of Robotology - a resistor symbol - to Bender's chest.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, while you're at it, could you touch 
up this seam?</speak>

<info>He raises his arm. Preacherbot welds the seam. Bender giggles.</info>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The crew are dressed up.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
This is unbelievable. The old Bender 
never would have taken us out to dinner.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
The old Bender's gone. He won't trouble 
you anymore.</speak>

<speak who="WAITER">
Would monsieur care to see the wine 
list?</speak>

<info>Bender shreds the wine list and hands it back to the waiter.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
No poison for us, thanks. I'll stick 
with good old mineral oil.  Ah! Functional!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The food arrives.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Mon, I'm hungrier than a green snake 
in a sugar cane field!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Friends! Friends! Surely you're not 
going to eat before we say Robot Grace? 
In the name of all that is good and 
logical we give thanks for the chemical 
energy we are about to absorb. To quote 
the prophet Jerimatic: 1000101010101...</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The crew have given up and are anxiously waiting 
for Bender to finish.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
...0010110012. Amen.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Does that mean we can eat now?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes.  But first, since I love you all 
so much, I'd like to give everyone hugs. 
Come here, Fry!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, uh, but I don't want to.</speak>

<info>Bender hugs Fry.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mmm! Mmm! Fry, you're my friend!  C'mon, 
everyone line up for a hug. Let's tear 
down some emotional walls.</speak>

<info>The others edge their seats away.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Bender sticks something to the ship.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What are you doing to my ship?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sanctifying it!  There! That ought to 
convert a few tailgaters.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender's stupid religion is driving 
me nuts.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Amen.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
If only he had joined a mainstream religion 
like Oprah-ism or Voodoo.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
We've got to get the old Bender back.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And I think I know a way to do it. We 
have to reacquaint him with a little 
thing called "sleaze".</speak>

<info>Atlantic City Street. The ship lands in a car park.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The crew have taken Nibbler with them and they walk 
down the street.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I can't believe somebody hired an interstellar 
spaceship to deliver a package to Atlantic 
City. What are we delivering anyway?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, this.</speak>

<info>He pulls some mints out of his pocket.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Where are we delivering it to?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh, here.</speak>

<info>She takes the mints and puts them in a mailbox.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Another job well done. Now back to the 
office for an enjoyable evening of fasting 
and repentance.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, Bender. So long 
as we're here why don't we take in some, 
exotic dancing!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey, great idea!</speak>

<info>Bender turns around. He is standing outside a club called Power 
Strip. He gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
But, those girls don't wear cases. You 
can see their bare circuits.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Come on, it'll be fun! Maybe we could 
even drink a little fortified wine.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What?" Drinking wine is a sin. Even 
if it is deliciously fortified.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey, Bender, looks at that woman's purse. 
It's hanging by a spaghetti strand.</speak>

<info>Bender zooms in but pushes his eyes back in again.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Thou shalt not snatch.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And there's Hookerbot 5000. She's got 
a heart of solid gold!</speak>

<speak who="HOOKERBOT">
Hey, sailing unit!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Stop tempting me! For once in my life 
I have inner peace.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Pfft, that's for losers. C'mon, sin 
your heart out.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Go nuts.</speak>

<speak who="HOOKERBOT">
Live a little.</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Could you hold my purse for a minute?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Go for it, Bender. You know you wanna!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well...</speak>

<info>Power Strip. Bender dances with the Stripperbots and laughs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm the greatest.  Woo-hoo!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Look's like we got the old Bender back!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You know it, pork pie! Except for one 
thing.</speak>

<info>He rips the Robotology symbol off his chest and throws it over 
his shoulder. It sinks into a dish of stuff and beeps and glows.</info>

<info>Trump Trapezoid. Bender entertains three Fembots in the jacuzzi 
in his hotel room.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Y'know, as a major Hollywood director 
I'll be holding auditions tonight for 
my next movie. And even though you're 
all young and naive, I think you might 
just have what it takes.  Hey! I'm trying 
to score here! Can't you read the "Do 
Not Disturb" sign?  No! No!</speak>

<info>A pitchfork comes through the door and knocks him out.</info>

<info>Robot Hell. Bender wakes up. The Robot Devil welcomes him. He 
is a huge red robot with a tail and other things you might associate 
with the devil.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Greetings, Bender! Welcome to Robot 
Hell.</speak>

<info>Bender screams.</info>

<info>Trump Trapezoid. The next day Fry and Leela are in Bender's 
room. There are scorch marks where Bender fell and he has been 
dragged out of the room.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What in hell happened to Bender?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well he didn't check out. The ashtray's 
still here.  Look, Nibbler's caught 
the scent of vodka and motor oil! Go, 
boy. Follow that stench.</speak>

<info>The run out of the room.</info>

<info>Robot Hell Tunnel. Bender is chained to a cart and the Robot 
Devil stands behind him with a whip. The cart rolls down a track.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm hallucinating this, right?</speak>

<info>The Robot Devil whips him.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
No, Bender. Robot Hell is quite real. 
Here's our brochure.</speak>

<info>He hands Bender a brochure entitled Hell Is Other Robots.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
But I don't belong here. I don't like 
things that are scary and painful.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Sorry, Bender, you agreed to this when 
you joined our religion. If you sin 
you go to Robot Hell - for all eternity.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aww, hell - I mean heck!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
It's alright, you can say that here.</speak>

<info>Outside Reckless Ted's Funland. Fry and Leela look up at the 
sign.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait! I remember this place. They shut 
it down after all those people caught 
salmonella from the flume ride.</speak>

<info>Nibbler leads Fry and Leela to a ride called The Inferno.</info>

<info>Cut to: The Inferno. They open the door and look around.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hmm. Look! It's the symbol of Bender's 
old religion.</speak>

<info>Fry presses the symbol and the crazy mirror beside it slides 
upwards. Behind it is Robot Hell.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Unbelievable. It's an actual, factual 
Robot Hell.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Who would've thought hell would really 
exist? And that it would be in New Jersey!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Actually --</speak>

<info>A trap door opens beneath them and Nibbler watches them disappear 
down a twisting fun slide. They scream as they fall.</info>

<info>Robot Hell: Level 1.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
We know all your sins Bender and for 
each one we've prepared an agonising 
and ironic punishment. Gentlemen?</speak>

<info>A band of Hellbots start to play. Bender knows what is coming.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw crap, singing. Mind if I smoke?</speak>

<info>He lights a cigar but Beezlebot takes it from him and stubs 
it out on his chest. Two little robots throw him a hat and cane.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Cigars are evil

You won't miss 'em,

We'll find ways to simulate that smell,

What a sorry fella,

Rolled up in smoke like a panetela,

Here on level 1 of Robot Hell!

</speak><info>Bender falls through a trapdoor.</info>

<info>Cut to: Robot Hell: Level 2. He lands next to a card table. 
He picks the cards up and takes one from his chest cavity.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Gambling's wrong and so is 
cheating,

So is forging phoney IOU's,

Let's let Lady Luck decide,

What type of torture's justified,

I'm pit boss here on level 2!

<info>He spins a wheel that Bender is strapped to. Luck decides to 
deep fry Bender.</info>

<info>(talking)</info> Ooh! Deep fried robot!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Just tell me why.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Please read this 55-page warrant.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> There must be robots worse 
than I.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> We've checked around, there 
really aren't.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Then please let me explain,

My crimes were merely boy-ish pranks.

</speak><speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> You stole from boy scouts, 
nuns and banks!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Ah, don't blame me blame my 
upbringing!</speak>

<info>He steals Beezlebot's wallet.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Please stop sinning while 
I'm singing!</speak>

<info>He pulls Bender's arm off and kicks him through a hole.</info>

<info>Cut to: Robot Hell: Level 5. Bender lands in front of the Beastie 
Boys. The Robot Devil picks Bender up by the leg and shakes him. 
Hundred of CDs fall out of his chest cabinet.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Selling bootleg tapes is wrong,

Musicians need that income to survive.

</speak><speak who="BEASTIE BOYS">
<info>(singing)</info> Hey, Bender, gonna make some 
noise,

With your hard drive scratched by the Beastie Boys!

That's whatcha whatcha whatcha get on level 5!

</speak><info>Cut to: Robot Hell Slide. Fry and Leela slide further down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> I don't feel well.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> It's up to us to rescue him.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> Maybe he likes it here in 
hell.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> It's us who tempted him to 
sin.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> Maybe he's back at the motel.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> Come on, Fry, don't be scared,

I'm sure at least one of us will be spared,

So just sit back, enjoy the ride.

</speak><speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> My ass has blisters from the 
slide.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Elevator. Bender and the Robot Devil plunge into Hell. 
The Robot Devil takes stuff out of Bender's chest cabinet.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
<info>(singing)</info> Fencing diamonds,

Fixing cockfights,

Publishing indecent magazines...

<info>He kicks Bender out of the elevator.</info>

You'll pay for every crime,

Knee-deep in electric slime,

You'll suffer 'til the end of time,

Enduring torture's most of which rhyme,

Trapped forever here in Robot Hell!

<info>The music ends and the show finishes with a fireworks display.</info>

<info>(talking)</info> Of course that's just for starters.</speak>

<info>Fry and Leela fall from the slide screaming and land behind 
Beezlebot. They see him and gasp.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, are you alright?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No! Oh they're tormenting me with up-tempo 
singing and dancing.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Alright, Beelzebot, what'll it take 
to get our friend back?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Sorry, but I hold all the cards here. 
There's nothing I can do. Now, if you'll 
just sign this fiddle contest waiver.</speak>

<info>Fry takes the pen but Leela stops him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wait. What fiddle contest?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
The Fairness In Hell Act of 2275 requires 
me to inform you that if you can best 
me in a fiddle contest, you win back 
Bender's soul. As well as a solid gold 
fiddle.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wouldn't a solid gold fiddle weigh hundreds 
of pounds and sound crummy?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Well it's mostly for show.</speak>

<info>He picks up the fiddle and it glints in the light.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> Do you know how to play 
the fiddle?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(whispering)</info> No, do you?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> No, but I used to play 
the drums. They're sorta similar. <info>(talking)</info> 
What happens if we lose?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
You'll only win a smaller, silver fiddle. 
Also I guess I'll kill one of you, uh, 
him.</speak>

<info>He points at Fry. Fry gulps.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We'll do it.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Very well, then. Beat this.</speak>

<info>He plays a tune and uses his tail as an extra arm.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, we're boned.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Your turn.  Ha!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Time for the drum solo!</speak>

<info>She beats the Robot Devil over the head with the violin and 
he squeals like a little girl.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Run!</speak>

<info>They do. Hellbots and flying bugbots chase them. The bugbots 
shoot laser rings at them. Bender grabs a pair of a bugbots wings 
and flies in and grabs Fry and Leela who are swarmed by a crowd 
of Hellbots with pitchforks. Bender ascends and heads for small 
hole in the roof.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
Stop them! They cheated!</speak>

<info>A bugbot shoots three laser rings at the trio. Two miss but 
one catches on Bender's antenna, forming a halo. The Hallejulah 
chorus plays and they get closer to the hole. Hellbots pull chains 
to close the hole.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hurry, Bender!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I could if you'd drop the stupid gold 
violin!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, sorry.</speak>

<info>She drops it. It hits Beezlebot on the head. He squeals and 
Fry, Leela and Bender escape through the hole.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outisde The Inferno. They cheer.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Don't worry, guys, I'll never be too 
good or too evil again. From now on, 
I'll just be me.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh, do you think you could be just little 
less evil than that.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I don't know. Do you think you could 
survive a 700ft fall?</speak>

<info>Fry chuckles.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Good old Bender!</speak>

<info>THE END</info>

<info>The Beastie Boys perform a remix of the theme 
over clips from the episode.</info>

<speak who="BEASTIE BOYS">
Yeah, Yeah! This one goes out to my 
man, Bender</speak>

Sending this one out, special dedication

To all my peoples in the robot homeworld

Yeah, yeah! Big up with the professor

My man Dr. Zoidberg

I'd like to shout out - a personal shout out to Leela

Fry! My man Bender

Nibber, Nibbler, in the house

Big shout out to all the Futurama
</xml>