<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 208 

<title>XMAS STORY</title>

<author>David X. Cohen</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Based On a True Story.</info>

<info>Catskills Ski Lodge. The whole Planet Express staff are on a 
ski holiday. The room is packed with people waiting for a show.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Ladies and gentlemen: Conan O'Brien's 
head.</speak>

<info>The audience cheer.</info>

<speak who="O'BRIEN">
Thank you, thank you. Let's get started. 
Max, play me over.  Looks like someone 
forgot to feed Max.  So, people are 
getting pretty worried about this Y2K 
problem, huh?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No. they fixed that 900 years ago.</speak>

<speak who="O'BRIEN">
Just bear with me, sir. Anyway, I'm 
walking to work this morning--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I doubt it!</speak>

<speak who="O'BRIEN">
Listen, pal, I may have lost my freakishly 
long legs in the war of 2012 but I've 
still got something you'll never have: 
A soul!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Eh.</speak>

<speak who="O'BRIEN">
And freckles!  Well, I'm out of material. 
You can catch me next week at the Andromeda 
Chuckle Hut. Enjoy your breakfast.</speak>

<info>The audience applauds.</info>

<info>Mountains. The staff are geared up for skiing. They walk away 
from the lodge.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah, lets face it: Comedy's a dead art 
form. Now tragedy ...  ... That's funny!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Come on, everyone. Perhaps some skiing 
will help us forget the mouldy old antics 
of Conan O'Brien.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Great idea!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
We can only hope!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry and Leela are on the ski lift.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This snow is beautiful. I'm glad global 
warming never happened.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Actually it did. But thank God nuclear 
winter cancelled it out.</speak>

<info>The lift tips them off and they ski over to Bender.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hi!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Enough of your mindless chitchat, let's 
get going.</speak>

<info>Hermes and Zoidberg are on the ski lift but it isn't moving.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Jah damnit! We're stuck.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
At least you're not cold blooded!</speak>

<info>He puts a glove over his mouth.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Sweet lion of Zion! Look at the Professor 
go.</speak>

<info>He points at Farnsworth who is skis well. He is actually asleep.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry and Leela ski.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Look out! We're heading straight for 
those trees!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah, yeah, relax. Trees down.</speak>

<speak who="TREES">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> Trees down.</speak>

<info>The trees go down and Fry and Leela ski over them.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Cool. Hey what do you do if you want 
the trees up?</speak>

<speak who="TREES">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> Trees up</speak>

<info>The trees go up and one takes Fry with it. He is stuck at the 
top of one.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(hoarse)</info> Trees down!</speak>

<speak who="TREES">
<info>(mechanical voice)</info> Trees down.</speak>

<info>They go back down and Fry gets buried under the snow with one. 
Bender speeds past on a snowboard. He is wearing a red and blue 
hat and has a cigar in his mouth.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Lookin' good, meatball!</speak>

<info>A man skis alongside Bender.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Excuse me, sir, you're snowboarding 
off the trail.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Lick my frozen metal ass.  Uh-oh!</speak>

<info>He falls over the edge of a cliff and screams as he falls towards 
a frozen lake. Children skate on the ice. Bender plummets straight 
through the surface. The ice around cracks and the children fall 
in. They scream.</info>

<speak who="CHILD">
<info>(shouting)</info> Mommy!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg skis with his feet on one ski and his claws on another. 
He comes to a stop at the bobsled run. Hermes is in a bobsled 
car and Fry stands behind him.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You, a bobsledder? That I'd like to 
see!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Listen, you filthy crab, a thousand 
years ago there was a legendary team 
of Jamaican bobsledders.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yup, I remember. They came in last at 
the Olympics then retired to promote 
alcoholic beverages.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
A true inspiration for the children. 
Um, a little help please?  <info>(screaming)</info> 
Nooo!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg laughs, slips, falls and slides down the track after 
Hermes. Fry laughs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, what the hell!  Ow!</speak>

<info>Catskills Ski Lodge. Amy is chats up a man in a cast.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
You poor man. What happened to you?</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Well, there I was on the triple diamond 
slope, when suddenly--</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, excuse me.  Hello there.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth skis into the lodge and wakes up to discover a bronze 
medal around his neck.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wha?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The staff all sport various injuries and sit around 
a blazing fire with their feet up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah! Nothing like a warm fire and a Super 
Soaker of fine cognac.</speak>

<info>He squirts some into his mouth.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, it really puts you in the Christmas 
spirit.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
What-mas?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Christmas. You know? X-M-A-S.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, you mean Xmas. You must be using 
an archaic pronunciation. Like when 
you say "ask" instead of "aks".</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Xmas, huh?  Y'know this'll be my first 
Xmas away from home.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey, hey. Let me aks you something: 
Would it cheer you up if we went and 
cut down an Xmas tree?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah! An old-fashioned Xmas tree!</speak>

<info>Forest. Fry seems disappointed that Xmas trees are palm trees.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey! These aren't Xmas trees!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Eh wha?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
They're supposed to be some kinda, you 
know, pine tree.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Pine trees have been extinct for 800 
years, Fry. Gone the way of the poodle 
and your primitive notions of modesty. 
Ah! Brisk!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
This isn't the way Christmas is supposed 
to be.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
There, there.</speak>

<info>He leans against Fry and pats his shoulder.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Everything's changed.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's not true.</speak>

<info>She swings an axe and a laser on the end cuts through a palm 
tree. It falls.</info>

<info>The ship flies across New New York with the Xmas tree tied to 
the roof. It lands in the Planet Express hangar.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. Zoidberg puts down a box marked 
"Xmas Decorations" and cuts the tape with his claw. Bender rocks 
back and forth in a chair with Nibbler on his lap.</info>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SINGING)</info>
Xmas tree oh Xmas tree! Bah boo bee 
boo bah bee boh.</speak>

<info>Leela sits on the arm of a couch in front of the fire and Fry 
sits next to her on the couch. The Xmas tree is in the middle 
of the room. Farnsworth leads a string of lights around the bottom 
of the trunk. Amy takes a star out of a box and uses a jet pack 
to get to the top of the tree. She hits her head on the ceiling.

<speak who="AMY">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(nostalgic)</info> Every Christmas my mom would 
get a fresh goose for goose burgers 
and my dad would whip up his special 
eggnog out of bourbon and ice cubes. 
This dumb holiday just makes me think 
of all the things I left behind. Let's 
just stop talking about Xmas.</speak>

[Enter Hermes with some envelopes.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Happy Xmas, Xmas people! Xmas cards 
have arrived! Xmas!  Amy, there you 
go, Fry, Professor, Zoidberg, a mighty 
haul for Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes! I got the most! I win Xmas!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
And last, but not least, the sweet flower 
of the office: Me. Hermes Conrad.</speak>

<info>Leela is disappointed. Bender looks at his card. On the front 
is an ASCII Xmas tree.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hmm.  Ah, a picture of my mommy.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Huh? What's this?  A card from my cousin 
Zoidfarb.  Instead of "Claus" he writes 
"Claws"! Now that's humorous. Today's 
comedians could learn from this card.</speak>

<info>Leela watches the others. She sighs and walks out.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. Leela opens her locker and gets 
out a photo album. She looks at photos of her childhood. One 
shows her as a baby in an area marked "Abandoned Property". Another 
shows her outside the Orphanarium, smiling. Children point at 
her and laugh. Another shows her at her senior prom with no date. 
She closes the album and a tear falls onto it.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What's the point of Xmas when everyone 
you know died a thousand years ago? 
I'm the lonliest person on Earth.  Hey, 
Leela, how 'bout a little sympathy here, 
huh?  Yoiks! What was that about?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Fluh! She's an orphan.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes, and the only one of her species 
in all the known universe. What a lonely 
life.</speak>

<info>He walks off shaking his head.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
My God! Poor Leela.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(upbeat)</info> Hey, buddy, heard you needed 
cheering up! Well old Bender'll make 
you laugh.  Look at me look!  Oh, man, 
I gotta work on my act!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry has taken off his jacket.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I feel like a rat. Here I am whining 
like a pig while all along Leela was 
lonely as a frog. I could kick myself.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I'll do it for you.</speak>

<info>She kicks him in the shin.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow! Thanks.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You should be ashamed of yourself, Fry. 
You'd have to be blind not to notice 
that Leela's a cyclops.</speak>

<info>He is actually talking to Hermes.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Fry's over there, man.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh?</speak>

<info>He adjust his glasses and looks around the room. Bender sits 
in a chair with his feet up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Xmas Eve; Another day where I accomplish 
nothing.</speak>

<info>He slurps brandy and turns the TV on to the news.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
The holiday season is a time of celebration 
for most. But it is also a time to remember 
the tragic suffering of the less fortunate.</speak>

<speak who="MORBO">
Earthlings do not yet know the meaning 
of suffering.</speak>

<info>He cackles. Linda chuckles.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
Earlier today I visited a shelter for 
down-and-out robots.  Homeless robots, 
too poor to afford even the basic alchohol 
they need to fuel their circuits. Is 
there anything sadder? Only drowning 
puppies. And there would have to be 
a lot of them.</speak>

<info>Bender heads for the door.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Where are you going, Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
To volunteer at a liquor kitchen for 
homeless robots.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Yeah, right! As if you ever did anything 
charitable.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm very generous. What about that time 
I gave blood?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whose blood?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Some guy's.</speak>

<info>He leaves.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I've got to do something to show Leela 
how sorry I am.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
So what's the problem? Just get down 
on your claws and do the apology dance.</speak>

<info>He starts scuttling and singing.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So it's left, left, right-- Wait! I 
have a better idea! I'll go out and 
get her the perfect Xmas present. Something 
so great she'll never want to be unhappy 
again.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Just be back by sundown, mon.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
We'll see. I like to haggle.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You can't stay out on Xmas Eve. You'll 
be killed!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Say what?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good Lord! He doesn't know about Santa 
Claus.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I know about Santa Claus.</speak>

<info>He winks.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Back in 2801, the Friendly Robot Company 
built a robotic Santa to determine who'd 
be naughty and who'd been nice and distribute 
presents accordingly. But something 
went wrong.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! 2801! Anyway...</speak>

<info>He turns to leave.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wait, you fool! Due to a programming 
error, Santa's standards were set too 
high and he invariably judges everyone 
to be naughty.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
If he catches you after dark, he'll 
chop off your head and stuff your neck 
full of toys from his sack of horrors.</speak>

<info>Fry gulps.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Nice meeting you.</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. Bender is dressed as a homeless robot, 
wearing a torn woollen hat and fingerless gloves. He walks into 
Our Motherboard Of Mercy Liquor Kitchen.</info>

<info>Cut to: Our Motherboard Of Mercy Liquor Kitchen. Bender is greeted 
by the Preacherbot.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
Welcome, brother! May the blessings 
of the season be upon you.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah, yeah, amen. Listen, I'm one of 
those lazy homeless bums I've been hearing 
about. Could you point me to the free 
booze.  Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!</speak>

<info>Alien Overlord &amp; Taylor. The department store advertises and 
Xmas Sale with "3% Off".</info>

<speak who="FRY">
There's this girl who I really like 
but she thinks I'm a jerk. Can you help 
me?</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN #1">
Yeah, there's a suicide booth in the 
food court. Though there's a line this 
time of year.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, I need to get her a gift. And I 
need it before sundown.</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN #1">
Well, you can't go wrong with something 
traditional.  A Surface-to-Santa rocket 
launcher. It comes with three jolly-seeking 
missiles.</speak>

<info>Fry laughs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's funny!</speak>

<info>A missile points itself at Fry.</info>

<speak who="SALESMAN #1">
Careful, sir!</speak>

<info>Our Motherboard Of Mercy Liquor Kitchen. Bender is finishing 
off his seventh bowl of liquor.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, yeah! You filthy hobos sure kow 
how to live.  Hey, chief, someone's 
stealing your handkerchief full of crap.</speak>

<info>The robot turns around and Bender steals his bowl. A little 
robot with a leg missing holds out a bowl to the Preacherbot.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Excuse me, sir? Might I have a sip of 
booze?</speak>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
I'm sorry, Tinny Tim. Seems we ran out 
early tonight.</speak>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
I understand.</speak>

<info>He turns, coughs, and limps away.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
My God! That poor kid!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<info>Joe's Ark Pet Store.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You're the last store open. I need something 
for my friend Leela.  Just give me your 
best animal.</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN #2">
Best? Well that's a matter of opinion. 
I personally like the Electric Snail.</speak>

<info>He picks up the snail in a jar. It's shell sparks with electricity.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's a stupid animal. You're stupid! 
I said I want the best one. Now which 
costs more? The parrot or the Stink 
Lizard?</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN #2">
The lizards are a buck each, the parrot 
is $500.</speak>

<info>Fry whistles.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's a hell of a good parrot. Although, 
I could get 500 lizards for the same 
price. Girls like swarms of lizards, 
right?</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN #2">
Sir, the store is closing in two minutes.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright, I'll take the 500 lizards. 
No, wait, yes. No. Yes. Yes. Yes! The 
parrot!</speak>

<info>The parrot squawks.</info>

<info>Outside Joe's Ark Pet Store. Fry walks away with his parrot 
and the shop closes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, I spent every penny I had but 
I bet Leela's gonna love you.  Hey, 
you're quite the talker, aren't you? 
Shut the hell up!  Ow!  Stupid bird! 
I know where you live.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. Amy ties a ribbon around an present. 
She holds the knot with her finger and Zoidberg cuts off the 
excess. On the other side of the room, Farnsworth and Hermes 
play chess naked. Enter Leela.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey, it's Leela.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Sorry I stormed out before. I didn't 
mean to ruin everyone's Xmas.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Huh? You were gone?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's just that I get tired of Fry always 
only thinking of himself.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I hear that! I aks him to set the table. 
Instead he goes out to buy you a present. 
Selfish dog.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wait! You mean he's still out? His life's 
in danger!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Why?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm telling you why. Santa Claus is 
coming to town!</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. The parrot flies towards a tall building 
with a large digital clockface. Fry looks up at it from the street.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright, bird, you thought you could 
beat me in a game of wits. But you just 
met your equal.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Building. Fry opens a hatch and steps out onto 
the clock face. He drops the cage and gulps. The parrot edges 
away from him. He steps closer to it. The parrot moves to the 
very edge.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Aha! Cornered!</speak>

<info>He leaps for the bird but it flies away before he can get a 
hold of it. He loses his balance and falls. He grabs onto the 
2 on the clock. It changes to a 3 then a 4. He falls a little 
further. It changes to a 5, a 6 and then a 7. With nothing to 
hold onto he falls. Leela grabs him from a hatch.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hi there!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela! Oh, my God! You saved my life. 
I am gonna get you so many lizards.</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. Fry and Leela walk out of the building.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
You didn't need to buy me a present, 
Fry.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I just wanted to do something to make 
you happy. I mean, I miss my family 
but you never even had a family.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's OK. You're lonely and I'm lonely. 
But together we're lonely together.</speak>

<info>They hold hands.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Merry Xmas, Leela.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Merry Xmas.</speak>

<info>A huge shadow creeps over them followed by two loud bangs. They 
turn around.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, boy! It's Santa!</speak>

<info>Santa's eyes turn around 180-degrees, making him look angry.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Ho, ho, ho!  You've been very naughty, 
Fry and Leela. I checked my list.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well check it twice!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
I perform over 50 mega-checks per second. 
You're both naughty for disregarding 
each other's feelings.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
But we set things right. Fry even risked 
his life to get me a present.</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
But what about your other co-workers? 
Did either of you ever stop to think 
about Dr. Zoidberg's feelings?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No! I swear!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
Santa has something very special in 
his sack for you two!</speak>

<info>Fry smiles. Santa pulls out a laser gun and shoots them. They 
scream and run away.</info>

<info>Outside Hattie's House. Bender and some other robots are singing 
carols.</info>

<speak who="ROBOTS">
<info>(singing)</info> So lock the door and hit the 
floor,

'Cause Santa Claus comes tonight.

</speak><info>Hattie claps.</info>

<speak who="HATTIE">
Go away!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Whoa, hold on! How about inviting us 
in for a traditional glass of hard cider?</speak>

<speak who="HATTIE">
Oh, alright. But just one glass!  (from 
inside) OK, that's enough.  I said that's 
enough!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(from inside)</info> Get her purse!</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. Fry and Leela are still running from 
Santa. They jump to the ground and Santa swoops over them in 
his sleigh, turns around and heads back towards them.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Please let us live! We'll put out milk 
and cookies for you!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
You dare bribe Santa? I'm going to shove 
coal so far up your stocking you'll 
be coughing up diamonds!</speak>

<info>He throws a bauble-bomb at Fry and Leela. They run into an alcove 
and it explodes. Santa flies his sleigh around ready for the 
kill. Leela tries a door but it's locked.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We're trapped.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I never thought it would end this way: 
Gunned down by Santa Claus. Honestly, 
I didn't see it coming!</speak>

<info>Santa gets closer. Fry and Leela crouch down in a corner.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Goodbye, Fry.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Goodbye, Leela.  Hey, look: We're under 
the mistletoe.</speak>

<info>Leela looks up and they both look at each other. They move towards 
each other to kiss.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Your mistletoe is no match for my T.O.W. 
missile!</speak>

<info>He shoots at them. Fry and Leela scream. The parrot flies in 
front of the alcove and gets hit by the missile and explodes. 
Feathers flutter down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, you're present may need some assembly.</speak>

<info>Elsehwhere, Bender and the other robots are carrying lots of 
stuff.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> On the 4th day of Xmas I stole 
from that lady.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
<info>(singing)</info> Four family photos.</speak>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
<info>(singing)</info> Three jars of pennies.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
<info>(singing)</info> Two former husbands.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> And a slipper on a shoe tree.</speak>

<info>He throws the slipper down the sewer. Raoul waves through the 
gate.</info>

<speak who="RAOUL">
Oh, thank you!</speak>

<info>Fry and Leela come running down the street.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Help!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(shouting)</info> Somebody help us.</speak>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
It's humans. Shall we mug them, robot 
sir?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No, wait, I know these guys. They got 
nothing.</speak>

<info>Bender runs towards Fry and Leela. Santa flies over them.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Ho ho ho!  You've been very naughty, 
Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What? Me? I didn't do nothing. You're 
thinking of the kid.</speak>

<info>He points at Tinny Tim.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
My God, Bender! Framing an orphan? That's 
so naughty I'll have to add it to my 
list right now.  Framing ... I-N-G ... 
... an ...</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. Amy, Hermes, Farnsworth and Zoidberg 
are sat under the Xmas Tree exchanging gifts.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Amy, this is for you: A set of combs 
for your beautiful hair.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, that's so sweet. But I sold my hair 
to a wigmaker so I could buy a set of 
combs for Hermes.</speak>

<info>She pulls her hat off revealing she is bald.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Oh, the irony. I sold my hair so I could 
buy this third set of combs for Zoidberg.</speak>

<info>He pulls his hat off. He is also bald.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Thank you. These'll come in handy for 
my new hair.  Finally I look as pretty 
as I feel!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting; from outside)</info> Help!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(shouting; from outside)</info> Help!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting; from outside)</info> Help!</speak>

<info>The staff look through the window. Fry, Leela and the robots 
are still being chased by Santa. They run towards the Planet 
Express building.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, dear. They'll be killed on our doorstep. 
And there's no trash pickup until January 
3rd.</speak>

<info>Enter Fry, Leela and the robots. There is a crash on the roof.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Sweet manatee of Galilee! He's on the 
roof!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Quick! The armour-plated chimney cover! 
Push! Push!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Use teamwork!</speak>

<info>The chimney is nearly covered when Santa sticks a candy cane 
through a gap and rolls the cover back. The crew gasp. Santa 
and the reindeer fly in.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!</speak>

<info>Hermes dives behind the sofa.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
You've all been very naughty. Very naughty 
indeed. Except you, Dr. Zoidberg, this 
is for you.</speak>

<info>He hands Zoidberg a gift.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
A pogo-stick!</speak>

<info>He giggles and bounces around the room.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
As for the rest of you, I'm going to 
tear off your skin like wrapping paper 
and deck the halls with your guts.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah? Well I don't believe in Santa 
Claus. Come on, everybody, if you don't 
believe in him he can't hurt you.  Ow! 
God! The pain!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
Ho ho ho! Time to get jolly on your 
naughty asses!</speak>

<info>He laughs maniacly.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Watch out! His belly is shaking like 
a bowl full of nitro-glycerine!</speak>

<info>A reindeers nose beeps and flashes red.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Rudolph's nose!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> He's gonna blow.</speak>

<info>Everyone screams. Zoidberg cuts a wire hanging from the Xmas 
tree.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Aha!</speak>

<info>The wire falls and electrocutes Santa. Leela kicks him and the 
rest of the staff use the Xmas tree to push him and his sleigh 
into the chimney. The robots cover it with the armour-plated 
cover. The reindeer beeps faster and the cover rocks as Santa 
explodes.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. Santa, the sleigh and the reindeer 
fly upwards away from the building.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The Planet Express crew, LaBarbara 
and the homeless robots are sat around the table talking.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes, good thing I got us out of that 
one!</speak>

<info>Bender brings a covered plate in from the kitchen.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Xmas dinner, everyone.</speak>

<info>He pulls the cover off. The dinner is the exploded parrot.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, Bender? Where did you get that bird?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I found it lying in the street, like 
all the food I cook. Dig in, everyone.</speak>

<info>He cuts a piece off and puts it on Tinny Tim's plate.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Thank you, sir.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You got the toenail!  Oh!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Look, the food isn't what's important.</speak>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
I'm so hungry.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The important thing is we're all together 
for Xmas. And even though I'm surrounded 
by robots and monsters and old people, 
I've never felt more at home.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSOWRTH">
Hear, hear! Now let's all of us shut 
up and sing!</speak>

<info>They gather around a piano.</info>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(SINGING)</info>
He knows when you are sleeping.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH"><info>(SINGING)</info>
He knows when you're on the can.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA"><info>(SINGING)</info>
He'll hunt you down and blast your ass 
from here to Pakistan.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG"><info>(SINGING)</info>
Oh.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES"><info>(SINGING)</info>
You'd better not breathe, You'd better 
not move.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SINGING)</info>
You're better off dead, I'm telling 
you, dude.</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(SINGING)</info>
Santa Claus is gunning you down!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers. Farnsworth takes off his lab coat, exposing 
himself again.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Merry Xmas, everyone!</speak>

<info>He joins the others at the piano and it snows again outside.</info>

<info>Closing Credits. A version of We Wish You A Merry Christmas 
plays. Santa and his reindeer fly by.</info>

SANTA
I'll be back. Back when you least expect 
it: Next Xmas! Ho ho ho!</xml>