<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 210 

<title>PUT YOUR HEAD ON MY SHOULDER</title>

<author>Ken Keeler</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Not Based On The Novel by James Fenimore 
Cooper.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. On the TV the heads of George Washington 
and Abraham Lincoln sit on podiums in front of a red curtain.</info>

<speak who="LINCOLN">
Four score and 1145 years ago our forefather's 
foreheads conceived a new nation.</speak>

<speak who="WASHINGTON">
And this Presidents' Day we honoureth 
those values that my body fought and 
died for.</speak>

<info>Behind the heads the curtain opens and reveals a car showroom. 
The salesman, a robot called Malfunctioning Eddie, points to 
a car.</info>

<speak who="MALFUNCTIONING EDDIE">
Values like this brand new Plymouth 
V'Ger! Hi, I'm Malfunctioning Eddie 
and I'm malfunctioning so badly I'm 
practically giving these cars away!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey, let's go car shopping! My parents 
promised if I got all B's they'd buy 
me a bar. And I got all C's!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mind if I tag along? I gotta bring my 
ass in for servicing.  The recall notice 
says it could burst into flames in a 
low-speed collision.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No wonder you've been staying at the 
back of conga lines lately.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'll get my coat. Let's go, Bender.</speak>

<info>She taps his ass with a rolled-up newspaper and it bursts into 
flames. Amy, Fry and Leela recoil in horror.</info>

<info>Malfunctioning Eddie's Showroom. A man with an accent introduces 
himself to Amy.</info>

<speak who="VICTOR">
Hello, I am Victor and I know many things 
about the art of unloading fine cars 
on beautiful women.</speak>

<info>He kisses her hand.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh-huh. Now tell us she's witty and 
sophisticated.</speak>

<speak who="VICTOR">
Ah-ah-ah! A gentleman always sells a 
lady a car first.  This is the Beta 
Romeo. Yes, the Beta Romeo. Note the 
cross-your-heart seat belt which protects, 
lifts and separates.</speak>

<info>At the coffee machine Fry pours himself a cup. A salesman puts 
his hand on his shoulder.</info>

<speak who="SALESMAN">
Spotted her the minute you walked in, 
didn't you, sir? She's a real beauty.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yup, she's beautiful coffee alright.</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN">
No, the Ford Thundercougarfalconbird! 
Nothing makes you feel more like a 
man than a Thundercougarfalconbird. 
So how much were you thinking of spending 
on this Thundercougarfalconbird?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Sorry, I'm not here to buy.</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN">
I understand and it's wonderful you 
don't care whether anyone questions 
your sexual orientation.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I care! I care plenty! I just don't 
know how to make them stop!</speak>

<speak who="SALESMAN">
One word: Thundercougarfalconbird!</speak>

<info>Amy and Victor are now sat in the Beta Romeo.</info>

<speak who="VICTOR">
The luxurious seats are stuffed with 
eagle down and the dashboard inlaid 
with the beaks of a thousand eagles. 
Also, there are some eagles under the 
floorboards.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
That's an awful lot of eagle.</speak>

<speak who="VICTOR">
Yes, and yet--</speak>

<info>He sighs.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
What's wrong?</speak>

<speak who="VICTOR">
It is just, the luxury edition has so 
much more eagle. It saddens me to think 
of you missing out.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, don't be sad. My parents are paying 
and they're incredibly rich.</speak>

<info>Victor raises his right eyebrow and pushes it down again with 
his finger.</info>

<info>Service Department. Bender is lying down on a raised platform 
and a mechanic drills into his back, causing him pain. The mechanic 
lowers him to the ground and he gets up.</info>

<speak who="MECHANIC">
I installed shock-absorbing bumpers 
to reduce the risk of catastrophic butt 
failure.</speak>

<info>Bender turns around and gasps at what he sees grafted to his 
butt.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You, sir, have defaced a national treasure! 
I demand you restore my buttocks to 
their former glory.</speak>

<info>He gets back onto the platform.</info>

<speak who="MECHANIC">
Alright. But sooner or later that ass 
is gonna blow. And when it does, I just 
pray you're not moonin' someone you 
care about.</speak>

<info>Malfunctioning Eddie's Showroom. Amy and Leela look under the 
bonnet of the Beta Romeo's.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Smeesh, Leela! This car has everything 
a beautiful woman like me needs. Victor 
said so.</speak>

<info>Victor chuckles.</info>

<speak who="VICTOR">
<info>(to himself)</info> No dog food for Victor 
tonight.</speak>

<info>Leela closes the bonnet.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, the sticker says 55,000 but we'll 
only go as high as say--</speak>

<info>Amy puts her hand in the air.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
60,000!</speak>

<info>Leela sighs.</info>

<speak who="VICTOR">
Oh, I will have to ask my manager.</speak>

<info>He walks into Malfunctioning Eddie's office.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Amy, you don't go up from the sticker 
price.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I thought it was an auction.</speak>

<info>Through the office window, we see Victor say something to Eddie. 
Eddie smiles and they both dance. Victor comes back out again.</info>

<speak who="VICTOR">
He is not too happy.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I'm sorry. 80,000?</speak>

<info>Eddie's head explodes.</info>

<info>New New York City Street. Amy and the others drive back to the 
Planet Express building. Outside, she prepares to park the car.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Uh-oh. I'm terrible at parallel parking.</speak>

<info>The car moves into a space sideways then shunts two cars in 
front and behind it.</info>

<info>Planet Express Corridor. Fry and Leela walk past Hermes' office.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(from inside)</info> And now you're asking 
for a day off? Get out of my and my 
sight!  You're bogarting my patience.</speak>

<info>The door opens and Hermes walks out.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hermes. Who were you yelling at?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Myself. I asked myself a Valentine's 
Day off. But I was in no mood for any 
of my shenanigans.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Valentine's Day's coming? Oh, crap! 
I forgot to get a girlfriend again. 
Well since neither of us has a date, 
why don't we...</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You just assume I can't get a Valentine's 
date?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Shall we say 8 o'clock?</speak>

<info>Enter Amy.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey, I'm taking my new car out for a 
spin to Mercury. Anybody wanna come?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, OK. What's the weather like?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
The usual: Boiling lead, oceans of lava.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So, what? Shorts?</speak>

<info>Amy's Car. They drive across the Mercurial surface listening 
to music.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Boy, this A.C. is incredible!  I'd better 
turn on the heater too.  <info>(shouting)</info> 
Boy, this heater is incredible! I'd 
better turn up the A.C. some more.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Hey, how about some icy margaritas?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Yeah!  We're slowing down!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Don't worry. I'll hit the 
fuel guzzler!</speak>

<info>She presses a button and the car accelerates.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Who wants pop-tarts?  Uh-oh!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
It's OK, I have an emergency phone.</speak>

<info>She picks up a make-up case and applies blusher to her cheeks.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What are you doing?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Spluh! It's a video-phone.  Lucky I'm 
a member of the Astro-Afro-Antarctico-Amer-Asian 
Auto Association.  Hello? Septuple-A?</speak>

<info>The sun beats down on the planet. Beads of sweat pour down Fry's 
face. He leans back over the seat and pulls the hood over the 
car.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Phew!</speak>

<info>Amy finishes her call and sighs.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
It'll be a couple hours. Oh, I'm gonna 
get sweat on my sweat-suit.</speak>

<info>She pulls the zip on her top down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, tell me something: You've got all 
this money, how come you always dress 
like you're doing your laundry?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I guess 'cause my parents keep telling 
me to be more ladylike.  As though!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I've been there. My folks were always 
on me to groom myself and wear underpants. 
What am I, the Pope?</speak>

<info>Amy laughs.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah, and if you were the Pope they'd 
be all, "Straighten your Pope hat," 
and, "Put on your good vestments".  
You know, Fry, its nice to find someone 
I can talk to about stuff, and junk.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, it's like we feel the same way 
about junk and stuff, or, whatever.</speak>

<info>He smiles. She smiles back.</info>

<info>Mercury Surface. Later, the sun is setting and the AAAAAAA recovery 
truck arrives. A man gets out and sees the car hood is steamed 
up. He laughs, rubs off the condensation and peers inside. Amy 
and Fry hold a set of cards. The man sighs with disappointment.</info>

<info>Cut to: Amy's Car. The recovery truck tows it.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
So while they're towin' us, you wanna 
do it?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah.</speak>

<info>They kiss and disappear below the seats. The man laughs again.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The next morning the crew are 
gathered around the table while Hermes presents an important 
chart to them.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Which concludes the summary of the movie 
I saw last night. Now, any old business? 
Any new business?  Anyone spend the 
night together? </speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yep.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Kind of.</speak>

<info>Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Oh, my God!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
We ran out of fuel on Mercury and one 
thing led to another.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And it led there again when we got home.</speak>

<info>He and Amy chuckle.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Congratulations, Fry, you snagged the 
perfect girlfriend. Amy's rich, she's 
probably got other characteristics.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender! Romance isn't about money.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, so it's just coincidence that Zoidberg 
here is desperately poor and miserably 
lonely? Puh-lease!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
For your information, it's because he's 
hideous.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg sighs.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Well I think Amy and Fry go together 
like a lime and coconut.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Do I hear wedding bells?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What? No!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Really? Oh, dear.</speak>

<info>He pats the side of his head. Zoidberg sighs.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You're both very lucky. I'd pay anything 
to end my miserable loneliness. If only 
I weren't so desperately poor.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wait. You mean people will pay good 
money for romance? Hmm. I think I have 
a scheme so deviously clever that I--</speak>

<info>Courtroom. The judge bangs his gavel.</info>

<speak who="JUDGE">
$500 and time served.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Stupid anti-pimping laws.  Well, pay 
the man!</speak>

<info>He struts out. His two Hookerbots follow him.</info>

<speak who="HOOKERBOT">
Bender, honey, we love you!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Shut up, baby, I know it!</speak>

<info>Planet Express Corridor. Bender hammers a sign on a door that 
has "Bender's Computing Dating Service. Discreet And Discrete" 
written on it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah, computer dating. It's like pimping 
but you rarely have to use the phrase 
"upside your head".</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, this is stupid. Why would anyone 
come to you for romantic help?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey! Don't make me go upside your head!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Zoidberg's Office. Zoidberg files his claws 
while Hermes knocks on the supply room door.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(shouting)</info> Fry! Amy! Put your pants 
back on; I need a stapler.</speak>

<info>He struggles to open the locked door. Zoidberg blocks his way.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Stop! Stop! If you interrupt the mating 
dance the male will become enraged and 
maul us with his fearsome gonad.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Supply Room.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(whispering)</info> It's working, they think 
we're making out.  Wait, why aren't 
we making out?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I 'unno.</speak>

<info>They kiss and drop to the floor.</info>

<info>Planet Express Corridor. Outside the lounge, Larry, Lou and 
the saleswoman from Alien Overlord &amp; Taylor queue to use Bender's 
dating service.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Lounge. Bender has set up his dating 
service at the table and is about to interview a client.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
OK, Mister...?</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Uh, Smith! Zapp Smith. Uh, Brannigan.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Just check off the things you're looking 
for in a love partner.</speak>

<info>He hands Zapp a sheet of paper.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Let's see ... Oh, yes!  Yes, definitely. 
Oh, I'd like some of that.  Mmm, I'll 
just have everything on the menu.</speak>

<info>He punches out the rest of the holes and hands it back to Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now to run it through our high speed 
romance-a-logical data-fier.  Say hello 
to Miss Right!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Hello!</speak>

<info>He rubs the paper against his chest.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Supply Room. Amy and Fry finish making out. 
Fry gasps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! We're great kissers!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah! Hey, later, you wanna drive out 
to Europa? We could have a picnic and 
spit watermelon seeds at Jupiter.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, yeah! I used to spit at stuff back 
in the 20th century. Ah, it's cool how 
we sort of think exactly alike, and 
junk.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah. Y'know, Fry, I really like hanging 
out with you.</speak>

<info>Fry is shocked.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Leela welds a section of the ships cargo 
lift while Fry paces backwards and forwards.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Everything was going great. Then all 
of a sudden, she's talking about hanging 
out. Hangin out? She's getting way too 
serious. I'm not a one woman man, Leela.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You'll be back to zero soon enough.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Don't you get it? She's smothering me.</speak>

<info>Amy walks past.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Hi.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You see? You see? Now she's bothering 
me when I'm at work.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry--!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm doing my job -- there's Amy. I spend 
a few hours selecting a candy from the 
machine -- there's Amy. I wake up the 
morning after sleeping with Amy -- there's 
Amy!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I think you're over reacting.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Am I? <info>(shouting)</info> Am I? <info>(talking)</info> Face 
it, I'm a prize catch.  I mean, I'm 
pulling down delivery boy money.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, she's pulling down billionaire 
trust-fund money.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Then she wants me as a trophy husband. 
Leela, you gotta come to Europa with 
us, I can't be alone with her.</speak>

<info>Amy arrives with a picnic basket.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
So, ready for a secluded picnic with 
just you and me?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, you know who loves secluded picnics 
with just you and me?  Uh, Dr. Zoidberg.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg, scavenging through a dustbin, looks up.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Did someone say something about a free 
hot meal?</speak>

<info>Amy's Car. The car flies past the Monolith from 2001: A Space 
Odyssey and drives across the icy surface of Jupiter's moon while 
Zoidberg eats the contents of the picnic basket.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Mmm, I haven't eaten since Tuesday! 
Bird eggs, animal slices ...  ... dry 
woven reeds!  All gone! Can I drive?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No. So, Fry, you busy tomorrow? I got 
two tickets to the big ape fight.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Jeez, we're already planning to spend 
Valentine's Day together. Isn't that 
enough?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
OK, sure. What do you wanna do for Valentine's 
Day?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, so all of a sudden we're spending 
Valentine's Day together?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
But you just said--</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's it, Amy, we have to talk. Zoidberg, 
you drive.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Wahoo!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Amy's Car. The car tips as they change places.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(from inside)</info> Pardon me, excuse me.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Amy's Car. Zoidberg is at the wheel while Fry and Amy 
are in the back.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ah, I'll just turn the wheel to maximum 
fastness!</speak>

<info>He turns it. Amy screams.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Amy, you know how at first you like 
chocolate but then you start to get 
tired of it because it always wants 
to hang out with you?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Huh? You don't like chocolate?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Look, could chocolate just let me finish?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Vroom vroom! And the winner of the big 
car race is: Hot Rod Zoidberg!</speak>

<info>He mimes a crowd cheering.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Amy, what I'm trying to say is, I think 
maybe you and I should stop--</speak>

<info>Something in the front snaps. Zoidberg has pulled the wheel 
off.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Uh-oh. Here, you drive!</speak>

<info>He offers the wheel to Fry. The car spins out of control, hitting 
chunks of ice. It heads straight for a huge mountain of ice. 
Fry screams and the car crashes.</info>

<info>Europa Surface. Fry was out cold but comes to. Zoidberg looks 
over him.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Fry? Are you alright?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow! My head is killing me. What happened? 
Was anybody hurt?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
No, no, no, no, no, of course not. Nobody 
but you. I'm afraid your body was badly 
damaged in the crash.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
How badly?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
That's it over there.  Don't worry, 
I managed to keep your head alive with 
some quick surgery.</speak>

<info>Fry moves his eyes up and down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Where is it?</speak>

<info>Zoidberg points.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
There.</speak>

<info>Fry turns to his right and sees Amy's head. Zoidberg has grafted 
his head onto her left shoulder.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Looks like we'll be spending a lot more 
time together, Fry!</speak>

<info>Fry screams.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth and Zoidberg inspect 
Fry's body. Leela tuts.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
This sort of thing always happens with 
office romances.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Don't worry, Fry, we'll have your body 
all fixed up in a few days.  Upsy daisy!</speak>

<info>He walks out of the room, hitting the body on the walls on the 
way out. Fry whimpers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, Amy, I'll try not to interfere 
with your life too much.</speak>

<info>Amy seems to pick her nose.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Fry!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ooh, sorry. I guess I control that arm.</speak>

<info>He waves the arm around and hoots.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
So, what was it you wanted to talk about 
before we crashed anyway?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, that.  Maybe we'd better talk in 
private. <info>(whispering)</info> I'll meet you 
in the closet.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Supply Room.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Amy, I really like you, as a friend. 
But I think we're spending too much 
time together.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You're breaking up with me?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I just think we should start seeing 
other people.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
But, I was really having fun.  If that's 
how you feel.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm sorry, but it is.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Well, whatever. Hey, listen, as long 
as we're not seeing each other, you 
mind if I ask someone else out for Valentine's 
Day?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Huh?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I mean, unless it would make you feel 
bad, being a third wheel.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, I can get a date too. Now that 
I'm single, I'll attract all sorts of 
women!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
With my body I think you might only 
attract one sort of woman.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(happy)</info> Oh! <info>(disappointed)</info> Oh!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Bender drinks from a bottle. Leela sits 
down and plays with his "Dating Consultant" nameplate nonchalantly.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
So, how's business?</speak>

<info>Bender opens his chest cabinet, revealing a huge pile of money. 
He pulls out a $500 note.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Are you familiar with my friend Al Gore? 
I'm tellin' ya, losers get really desperate 
around Valentine's Day.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah, it's pathetic alright!  How much?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
500 bucks.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Done.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Zapp Brannigan OK?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
600.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. Enter Leela who sees Fry and 
Amy playing table tennis. Fry sees Leela.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, hey, Leela, uh, can I talk to you 
for a minute?  In private?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, no problem.</speak>

<info>She puts her fingers in her ears and sings to herself in Chinese.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This is an emergency. Amy made Valentine's 
plans with some goon and I'm gonna be 
stuck there, lonely and miserable. Will 
you be my date, please?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You're too late, Fry. I'm sharing Valentine's 
Day with a very special man. He's not 
Zapp Brannigan or anything!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Then I have no choice but to do something 
so pitiful and embarrassing that I'm 
ashamed to tell you about it.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender's in his office.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Thanks.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Amy is still singing while Fry does 
business with Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I got your hook-up, Fry. Now my usual 
fee's 500 bucks, but seeing as how it's 
you, I'll need it in advance.</speak>

<info>Amy's Apartment. Amy dresses herself while Fry "helps".</info>

<speak who="AMY">
OK, Fry, we're done putting on the bra.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Why exactly did you shave your legs 
anyway? Are you expecting something 
to happen with your Valentine's date?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
What business is it of yours?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And another thing: You're using an awful 
lot of make-up there.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
This is deodorant.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What does it do?</speak>

<info>The doorbell rings. Amy reaches for her dress.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(shouting)</info> C'mon in, Gary! I'll just 
be another 20 minutes.</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
<info>(from outside)</info> I'll be waiting.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
20 minutes? You're practically ready 
now!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah, but it's good to make them wait 
a little.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, God, it's true!</speak>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. Amy, Gary and Fry sit at a table. Fry 
eats a hamburger.</info>

<speak who="GARY">
That dress looks great on you.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(simultaneously)</info> Thanks.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(simultaneously)</info> Thanks.  Where is she?</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
I must say, Amy, you're all made up, 
just like Fry's date. Get it?</speak>

<info>Amy shakes her head.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Mm-mm.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I've got a date. She'll be along any 
minute.</speak>

<info>Enter Bender with a old woman.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry, look who I found! It's Petunia, 
your dream girl!</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
How's them eats?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh--</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Don't mind if I do.  Kids'll be hungry.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(whispering)</info> She seems a little old 
for me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
She is well-travelled. And I don't mean 
she travels a lot!</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Wheels fell off my house.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now how about a rose for the lady? Five 
bucks a pop!</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
I'll take one.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, yeah? Well I want one too.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Eight bucks.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But you just said--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Demand suddenly skyrocketed, you all 
saw it.</speak>

<info>On another table, Leela sits alone. She sighs. Bender arrives.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Leela, meets your future husband Sal.</speak>

<info>Sal is wearing blue overalls and has a cigarette in his mouth. 
He cringes.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
Nice eyeball, eyeball.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nice ass, ass.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooh, sparks! <info>(whispering)</info> Buy her a 
rose, I guarantee she'll put out!</speak>

<info>Sal considers then sits down.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
Eh, I'll take my chances.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Bender's other clients are also there. Larry eats 
from Hattie's fork and Zapp makes a toast with his woman who 
has a five-o'clock shadow.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Cheers!</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Cheers!</speak>

<info>Fry and Petunia don't seem to be gelling.</info>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
So tell me about your prospects. You 
a good gambler?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, ma'am I--</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
What's your game? Bingo? Keno? Wait 
a minute! You don't have your own body.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, but I control this arm.</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Slots player, huh? Sorry, but I think 
I can do better.</speak>

<info>She gets up from the table.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait, come back, uh, darling.</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Can't, hon. I gotta catch my bus back 
to Nutley. I'd kiss you goodnight but 
I lost my teeth pulling out a stump.</speak>

<info>She walks towards the exit.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
So anyways, Leela, I'd love to take 
a whack at ya but that 10:15 to Nutley 
ain't goin' nowheres without yours truly 
behinds the wheel.</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Excuse me, did you say "10:15 to Nutley"?</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
Why, yes I dids.</speak>

<info>They stare into each others eyes and passionately kiss. Leela 
turns to Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> Bender! Did you just round 
up our dates at the bus station?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Of course not.</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
Anybodys else for Nutley?</speak>

<info>Bender's customers get up and head for the door. Zapp's date 
also leaves.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Baby, wait! You didn't show me your 
surprise.</speak>

<info>Gary has his arm around Amy.</info>

<speak who="GARY">
<info>(whispering)</info> You know what I'd like 
to do...?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, jeez, get a room!</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
Maybe later.</speak>

<info>Fry is shocked.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, I have an idea: Let's all go out 
for ice cream.</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
Actually, I thought Amy might like to 
come back to my place for coffee.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I don't really like coffee.</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
Neither do I.</speak>

<info>Fry is shocked again.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Ooh, I feel a little tipsy!</speak>

<info>Fry is shocked again.</info>

<speak who="GARY">
Let me pick up the check.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Nooo!  That's it I'm gettin' the hell 
outta here.  Ooh! Ow!</speak>

<info>Leela hears Fry and walks to their table just as Amy and Gary 
are about to leave.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Why, if it isn't my favourite head on 
Amy's body: Fry.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, Leela!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
We were just on our way out.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nonsense, the evening's young. So, Gary, 
what do you do for a living?</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
I'm a banking industry regulator.</speak>

<info>Amy sighs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Really? Y'know I heard that banking 
industry regulations are really very 
simple.</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
Oh, no, that's not true. You see, modern 
banking regulations are a product of 
five different regulatory traditions. 
Six if you wanna get technical.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, I do.</speak>

<speak who="GARY">
It all began in 1410 when a number of 
noblemen convened...</speak>

<info>Fry and Leela look at each other.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
Thank you.</speak>

<info>They smile.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Zoidberg finishes stitching 
Fry's head to his neck.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
There you are, good as new. Except for 
your dorsal fin, I'm afraid I couldn't 
find it after the crash.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Can I live without it?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
If you call that living.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I still don't understand why you wouldn't 
let me graft a laser cannon onto your 
chest. To crush those who disobey you. 
But I guess we're just two different 
people.</speak>

<info>He and Zoidberg leave.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So, uh, thanks for the ride, Amy. And 
I hope there are no hard feelings about 
your date, or stuff.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
It's OK, I had fun. And if I ever feel 
lonely I can just look over at this 
disfiguring scar and think of you.</speak>

<info>They smile. Amy leaves. Fry sighs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, anyway, it's nice to have my own 
body back.</speak>

<info>He yawns, stretches and pats his chest. He looks down and sighs. 
Enter Leela and Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
So how's the old corpse? Everything 
hooked up OK?</speak>

<info>Fry stands up.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Seems to be. My neck's just a little 
tender.  Ow! Cool!  Ow! Listen, Leela. 
Thanks for rescuing me last night.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Anytime. I actually enjoyed hanging 
out with you.</speak>

<info>Enter Bender, counting his profits.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yep, everything worked out great thanks 
to good old Bender.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Come on! It's not like you intentionally 
set us up with bad dates so we'd spend 
Valentine's Day together.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Didn't I, Leela? Didn't I?</speak>

<info>He winks and a heart wipe closes the scene but opens up again.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
No! You didn't! You just corralled a 
bunch of stiffs at the bus station and 
pocketed our money!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
True. But in the end, isn't that what 
Valentine's Day is really all about?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I guess so.  Watch the neck! Watch the 
neck!</speak>

<info>He kicks Bender's ass and sparks start coming out of it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
My ass! My beautiful ass!</speak>

<info>It explodes.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>