<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 212 

<title>RAGING BENDER</title>

<author>Lewis Morton</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Nominated For Three Glemmys.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Most of the staff are sat around 
the table.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news, everyone. I've taught the 
toaster to feel love.  And Hermes returns 
from his vacation today.</speak>

<info>Enter Hermes. There is a Brain Slug attached to his head. It 
is a small green blob with one eye and two antennae. Hermes has 
a glazed expression. The others seem oblivious.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> Good morning, people.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, Hermes!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hello!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Good to see you.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yo!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
My man!</speak>

<info>Hermes sits down.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
So how was the Spleef Nebula?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> The flight had a stopover 
on the Brain Slug planet. Hermes liked 
it so much he decided to stay of his 
own free will.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hermes has all the fun. Wait a second! 
He's got a Brain Slug on his head!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> Shh! You're gonna get us 
all assimilated!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(whispering)</info> Just act normal and switch 
to a garlic shampoo.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> On to new business. Today's 
mission is for all of you to go to the 
Brain Slug planet.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What are we going to do there?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> Just walk around not wearing 
a helmet.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Sounds great, Hermes! Whatever you say. 
<info>(whispering)</info> Let's ditch him and go 
to the movies!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, yeah!</speak>

<info>The others agree.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'm seeing a movie with friends!</speak>

<info>They get up and leave. Hermes starts droning.</info>

<info>Outside Loew's Aleph-0 Plex. Some of the movies showing are 
It Came From Planet Earth, Shaft On Africon-9 and When A Man 
Loves A Smizmar. The gang look at some others that are advertised 
outside. Fry points at a Galaxy Wars poster.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Cool, let's see this one!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nah. I'm not in the mood for a historical 
documentary. I've heard good things 
about Quizblorg, Quizblorg.</speak>

<info>She points to a poster which features two smartly-dressed green 
blobs picnicking on green grass.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Guk! I hate subtitles. Alien films are 
so pretentious.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Fellows! Fellows! How about a film we 
can all enjoy? Planet Of The Clams. 
It's about an upside-down world where 
lobster is slave to clam.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Who invited you? Let's just see All 
My Circuits: The Movie.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, I wanna see that.</speak>

<info>The others agree.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Good point, Bender.</speak>

<info>Loew's Aleph-0 Plex Refreshments. A robot with flashing zits 
stands behind the counter.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll take a small Slurm.</speak>

<speak who="REFRESHMENTBOT">
For only 25 cents less, you can get 
a super-small.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, OK.  Oh, man!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, gimmie a large diet malt liquor 
and a popcorn with extra motor oil.</speak>

<info>The robot pumps oil onto the tub of popcorn.</info>

<info>Loew's Aleph-0 Plex Auditorium. Farnsworth is sat in the front 
row.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Down in front!</speak>

<info>The others are sat a few rows back. An old-fashioned black and 
white newsreel starts.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Glagnar's Human Rinds presents: This 
Week In The Universe.</speak>

<info>The titles come on and show a biplane flying around a galaxy.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(sarcastic)</info> Ooh, this is real futuristic!</speak>

<info>The guys from Mystery Science Theater 3000 are sat at the other 
end of the row.</info>

<speak who="CROW T">. ROBOT
Shh! Don't talk during the movie.</speak>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
This week in the universe: New New 
York mayor C. Randall Poopenmeyer opens 
a new tube line to alleviate rush hour 
traffic.  Dateline: Paramecium Homeworld. 
Newly-crowned Miss Universe Glady's 
Lennox entertains troops fighting to 
wipe out the human race.  Go get 'em, 
boys!  And in the world of Ultimate 
Robot Fighting, the Masked Unit wins 
his championship bout against Gorgeous 
Gonks by technical melting.</speak>

<info>The Masked Unit throws the other robot to the canvas and melts 
him using eye lasers. Bender waves his arm in the air.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting)</info> Go Masked Unit!  Uh, hey, 
buddy! Yo!  You mind taking your head 
off?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
I'm sorry, sir, but I need it to watch 
the movie.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Just ask Flabby over here to describe 
it to you later.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Sir, she is as the factory made her.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well they should have stopped making 
her about halfway through.</speak>

<info>A "Not Suitable For Aliens From Planet M-14" restriction comes 
up on the screen. Two three-eyed, three-legged aliens grumble 
and leave. The opening credits roll with a Bond-esque theme and 
titles complete with naked Fembot silhouettes and guns. Credits 
like "Directed by Directing Unit 4", "Written by Writing Unit 
5 and Writing Unit 12 &amp; Joe Eszterhas" come up. A Fembot dives 
off the end of a laser barrel.</info>

<speak who="FEMBOT">
Whee!</speak>

<info>A wipe opens on Calculon sitting in an office.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Well, that finishes this paperwork. 
Calculon Enterprises.</speak>

<speak who="MONIQUE">
Calculon, a fight scene has broken 
out at the special effects warehouse. 
Come quickly before a fiery explosion 
chases someone down a hallway.</speak>

<info>Two laser blasts hit a building behind her. Calculon hangs up.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
I have no choice but to--</speak>

<info>The scene freezes.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
If you want Calculon to race to the 
laser gun battle in his hover-Ferarri, 
press 1. If you want Calculon to double-check 
his paperwork, press 2. Enter now.</speak>

<info>"1. Violent Lasergun Battle" and "2. Tedious Paperwork" appear 
on screen. Confused, Fry presses "1" on his chair.</info>

<speak who="CHAIR">
You have pressed 2.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No I didn't!</speak>

<speak who="CHAIR">
I'm almost positive you did.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Night has fallen outside. Calculon is checking his 
paperwork.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Add in the carryover from form 16A, 
then deduct line 2B...</speak>

<info>Bender kicks the back of the robot's chair.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Pardon me, sir. But you seem to be inadvertently 
kicking my seat.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(mocking)</info> "Pardon me, sir. But you seem 
to be bleh bleh..."</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Yes, that's the gist of what I said. 
Would you mind?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sure thing, pal.</speak>

<info>He carries on kicking the chair.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Uh, sir?</speak>

<info>Bender flicks a kernel at the robot's head then turns around.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(fake shocked)</info> Who threw that?!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT">
That's it! Sir, I challenge you to fisticuffs!</speak>

<info>Bender laughs as the robot transforms into what a muscular robot 
would look like if they had muscles.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, I'm boned.</speak>

<info>The robot shoots laser beams from his eyes at Bender. Bender 
ducks out of the way and the laser beams hit his seat. Other 
people run, screaming as the movie jams and the lights come back 
on.</info>

<speak who="HATTIE">
Let's all go to the lobby!</speak>

<info>Bender, still clutching his popcorn, runs from the robot as 
it tramples down seats. Bender runs across the front row of seats, 
past Farnsworth who hasn't moved, and stops when he reaches a 
wall. He drops his popcorn. The robot's voice is much deeper.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
I'm gonna open a pile whup-ass on you!</speak>

<info>He steps forward and slips on the motor oil and falls to the 
ground. He groans and shuts down. The others gather around. Leela 
gasps.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, do you know who that was?</speak>

<info>She opens a panel in the front of the robot. It is the Masked 
Unit.</info>

<speak who="MAN #1">
Cripes! The Masked Unit! You knocked 
him out cold.</speak>

<info>The others gasp and murmur.</info>

<speak who="MAN #2">
I'm impressed.</speak>

<info>Flabby puts her arms around Bender. A man wearing a brown suit 
and a red tie with extremely bushy eyebrows pushes through the 
crowd. His name is Abner Doubledeal.</info>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Son, I'm the commissioner of Ultimate 
Robot Fighting. I'm a connoisseur of 
jerks like you who pick fights in movie 
theatres and you're the biggest I've 
ever seen.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You should see me at funerals.</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Kid, I want you in the Ultimate Robot 
Fighting League.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ultimate Robot Fighting? Sounds pleasant! 
I'll do it.</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers and waves.</info>

<speak who="FLABBY">
My hero!</speak>

<info>She kisses him. Farnsworth still hasn't moved and wipes his 
eyes.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Aw. They don't make movies like this 
anymore.</speak>

<info>He blows his nose.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The staff are gathered around 
Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm gonna be the greatest Ultimate Robot 
Fighter ever. Float like a floatbot, 
sting like an automatic stinging machine!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Bender, you can't be an Ultimate Robot 
Fighter. It's the most brutal form of 
competition in the galaxy!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It is?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
There are no rules. Two robots enter, 
one robot leaves. Then later the other 
robot leaves after being declared the 
winner.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, did I mention the crippling, agonising 
pain? I'm pretty sure I did. Oh, yes, 
definitely.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Crippling pain? That's not covered by 
my insurance fraud! Count me out.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No! You've got to do it. I don't care 
how suicidal it is.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey! How come when I wanna do fun stuff 
that'll kill me you're against it?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
This is more important than that marble-eating 
contest, Fry! It's about pride. Let 
me tell you a story from my childhood.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh, again with the orphanarium!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
When I was growing up at the orphanarium, 
I got picked on a lot...</speak>

<info>Flashback: A teenage Leela and some teenage boys are dressed 
in martial arts uniforms.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(voice-over)</info> ...My only outlet was Arcturan 
Kung Fu.</speak>

<info>Teenage Leela takes on two guys and floors them. Her teacher, 
a green alien called Fnog watches.</info>

<speak who="FNOG">
Excellent. Bill, Keith, you will go 
to Junior Championships. Bill, congratulate 
Keith when he regains consciousness.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
But, Master Fnog, I can beat these dorks 
with one eye closed.</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
Perhaps. But there is more to winning 
than beating your opponent. You lack 
the will of the warrior.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What do you mean? Watch this!</speak>

<info>She kicks Bill in the stomach.</info>

<speak who="BILL">
<info>(crying)</info> Ow!</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
No girl has the will of a warrior. You 
have the will of a housewife or, at 
best, the schoolmarm.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's it. I'll take you on right now.</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
Very well. But, you see, I have the 
will of the warrior. Therefore, the 
battle is already over. The winner? 
Me!  Rematch? You lose again! Had enough? 
I thought so!</speak>

<info>He and the other guys laugh.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I lost my chance to be a champion. I 
won't let you throw away yours.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Leela's right! I don't wanna end up 
a loser like her. Count me back in!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The table, chairs and water cooler have 
been pushed to the window side of the room so there is an open 
training area for Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Let's see what you got. Touch your toes.</speak>

<info>Bender reaches down but struggles. His torso snaps off at his 
waist and the top half of his body falls to the floor. He tries 
to reach his toes but is too far away.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Still ... can't ... reach!</speak>

<info>Montage: Leela does a flying kick and indicates for Bender to 
try. He kicks his leg and it extends and wraps itself around 
his neck, choking him. Next, Bender does one-armed press ups, 
first with his left arm, then his right, and then with neither. 
A car jack comes out of his chest and pushes him up and down. 
He stands up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Let's commence preparations for rumbling!</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. The bleachers are packed for RobotMania 
XXVII. Leela rubs Rust-Oleum onto Bender's shoulders. The referee 
is an alien shaped like one of Kif's species but has black and 
white stripes running down his body.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
Ladies and gentlemen and smizmars, welcome 
to tonight's main event. In this corner, 
from Mom's Friendly Robot Factory in 
America's heartland, Mexico: Bender! 
And in this corner, from and made of 
Parts Unknown: The Clearcutter!</speak>

<info>The Clearcutter is a lumberjack robot with an axe on the end 
of one arm and a chainsaw on another. The other Planet Express 
staff are sat with Bender's fans.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Bender rules!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> I got you an official Bender 
hat.</speak>

<info>He takes a Brain Slug out of his jacket and hands it to Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! Thanks, Hermes!  I-- Hey! Cut that 
out!</speak>

<info>He hands it back. The fight bell rings.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You can't hit what you can't see!</speak>

<info>The Clearcutter kicks Bender against the ropes. He bounces back 
and the Clearcutter hits him with the axe. He throws Bender down 
and Bender groans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Get up, Bender. You can't quit every 
time you get an axe in the back.  Or 
a drill through your face. Now quit 
scratching your axe-hole and get out 
there.</speak>

<info>Bender stands up again. The Clearcutter leans on the ropes, 
making them tense. He then cuts through the post and is catapulted 
towards Bender. Bender tries a flying kick. His leg wraps around 
his neck and the Clearcutter hits his footcup. The Clearcutter 
sparks and his head explodes, followed by the rest of his body. 
Bender looks at the flaming wreckage.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Huh?</speak>

<speak who="REFEREE">
And the winner is ... Bender!</speak>

<info>He holds up his severed arm. Bender takes it and puts it back 
in its socket. The crowd cheers.</info>

<info>Locker Room. Doubledeal walks in with Bender. Bender has a plaster 
over the hole in his head.</info>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Nice work out there, kid.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Y'know, I think I he might be dead. 
I took a life!</speak>

<info>He cheers. Enter the Clearcutter, all in one piece.</info>

<speak who="CLEARCUTTER">
Hi, boss. Yo, dude!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, he's not dead. What's up with that?</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
What, you didn't read the pamphlet? 
Ultimate Robot Fighting's a scam, kid. 
It's rigged.  It's a secret so keep 
it under your head. But the most popular 
robot always wins.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You mean I'm not a great fighter? I 
just won 'cause I'm popular?</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Bingo!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Woo-hoo! I'm popular!</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
In fact, you're more than popular; You're 
pure lowest common denominator.</speak>

<info>Bender does a victory dance.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Go Bender! Go Bender! Go Bender!</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. Another fight.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
Presenting Bender the Offender!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm just an ex-con trying to go straight 
and get my kids back.</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
Versus: Billionairebot!</speak>

<info>Billionairebot laughs in a snooty way. He wears a top hat and 
monocle and cash is built in to his hands. The crowd boos. The 
fight starts. Bender takes Billionairebot's watch from his pocket 
and wraps it around him, trapping his arms. He picks up a barrel 
from outside the ring with "Very Poor" written on it and puts 
it over Billionairebot. The crowd cheers.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
Versus: The Foreigner!</speak>

<info>The stereotypical Spanish robot turns to the crowd.</info>

<speak who="FOREIGNER">
I'm not from here! I have my own customs! 
Look at my crazy passport!</speak>

<info>While he isn't looking, Bender grabs him from behind and stuffs 
the Earth flag in his mouth and kicks him out of the ring.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
Versus: The Chain Smoker!</speak>

<info>The robot looks like a cigarette machine. The crowd boos.</info>

<speak who="CHAIN SMOKER">
I love smoking. And after I win the 
fight I'm heading straight to your favourite 
restaurant.</speak>

<info>He blows smoke over the crowd. Bender takes a chair out of his 
chest cabinet and hits him with it then smokes a cigar.

[Planet Express: Lounge. Leela sits impatiently on the press 
bench tapping her foot. Bender walks in wearing a furry coat 
and with his arms around two Fembots.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You know, I'm also an Ultimate Robot 
Lover.</speak>

<info>The Fembots giggle.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender! You're three hours late. You 
can't give up on your training now after 
both of us worked so hard.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What do you mean, "we"?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I said "us".</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, Bender the Offender doesn't need 
you. Bender the Offender doesn't need 
anybody!</speak>

<speak who="FEMBOT #1">
What about us, Mr. The Offender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well obviously I need floozies! Let's 
roll!</speak>

<info>They walk out.</info>

<info>URFL Building: Doubledeal's Office. Bender walks in with the 
Fembots. Doubledeal is there along with Billionairebot, the Chain 
Smoker and the Foreigner.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Howdy, chief. For my next bout, what 
do you say I fight these two bimbos 
in some mud?</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Actually, we've decided to go in a different 
direction.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What if I told your we wouldn't be fighting 
in the conventional sense?</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Bender, your popularity is slipping.</speak>

<info>He holds up a chart with a red line pointing down.</info>

<speak who="FOREIGNER">
Sales of your Bender Brand French milk 
bath soaps are down 20%.</speak>

<info>Bender takes one and sniffs it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Those morons! I said pea berry, not 
sandalwood!</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Damnit, Bender! If you can't move sandalwood, 
you don't belong in this league! That's 
why you're gonna lose next week's title 
match.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But the crowd loves me.</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Perhaps. But let's see how they feel 
about your new persona: The Gender Bender.</speak>

<info>He holds up a pink tutu with "The Gender Bender" written on 
it.</info>

<speak who="BILLIONAIREBOT">
You'll be the most unpopular robot fighter 
since Sergeant Faeces Processor.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, yeah?  Well what if I don't let 
the new guy win?</speak>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Then he'll just have to beat you the 
old-fashioned way: To death!  Melissa, 
send in the new kid.</speak>

<info>A shutter door slides open. A huge robot, covered in spikes, 
enters via the wall.</info>

<speak who="DESTRUCTOR">
I am Destructor!</speak>

<info>He laughs maniacally. Bender puts the tutu on.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(squeaky)</info> See you at the fight.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Bender is sat on the couch with the 
others around him.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
So then I said, "See you at the fight". 
And that's the story.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, I thought Ultimate Robot Fighting 
was real, like pro wrestling. But it 
turns out it's fixed, like boxing.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's one thing to win a fixed fight 
-- there's dignity in that. But to lose? 
And in this atrocity? I can't do it! 
Leela, you gotta train me to win.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No way! If you wouldn't take my help 
when you didn't need it, why should 
I give it to you now when you do need 
it?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
What the hell are you talking about?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I don't know. But I'm not helping.</speak>

<info>She turns on the TV. Bender the Offender is standing on top 
of the world with the Earth flag waving behind him.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
You loved him as Bender the Offender! 
Now get ready to hate him as he threatens 
your sexuality in his new persona ... 
The Gender Bender!</speak>

<info>The picture is replaced with Bender in the tutu wearing a wig. 
He is lying on a bed kicking his legs back and forth and holding 
a pink phone.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm a real toughie!</speak>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER">
Squaring off this Sunday versus Destructor!</speak>

<info>The picture is replaced with Destructor talking into a red phone.

<speak who="DESTRUCTOR">
I will destroy you!  And stop calling 
me!</speak>

[The camera pans down to his feet where Master Fnog is standing.</info>

<speak who="FNOG">
I am Destructor's trainer, Master Fnog. 
My pupil will be victorious for he has 
the will of a warrior!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Not Fnog! Bender, let's hit the gym. 
I'm gonna teach you to fight like a 
girl!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(determined)</info> I'll put on my tutu!</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. Thousands have turned out for the championship 
bout where there is "no" gambling. The crowds cheer as Howard 
Cosell's voice introduces the fight.</info>

<speak who="COSELL">
Hello and welcome to a remarkable championship 
bout. Destructor, a robotic armoured 
tank whose very use at battle has been 
ruled a war crime versus, Gender Bender, 
who wears a pink tutu.  This is Rich 
Little imitating Howard Cosell, here 
at ringside with George Foreman. George, 
a word in edgewise?</speak>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
This could be the most one-sided fight 
since 1973 when Ali faced an 80-foot 
tall mechanical Joe Frazier. M-My memory's 
not what it used to be but I think the 
entire Earth was destroyed.</speak>

<speak who="LITTLE">
Interesting, if true. The Vegas odds 
tonight stand at an unprecedented 1000-0: 
A bet of $0 on Bender pays $1000 if 
he wins. Still, very few takers.</speak>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
It's not-not a smart bet.</speak>

<info>In the ring, Fnog does some last-minute training with Destructor. 
Bender punches the pads on Hermes' hands while Leela reads through 
the script.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
According to the script, you're supposed 
to prance out and tickle him with your 
fairy wand. Instead, I want you to prance 
out and kick his head off!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Got it. Large kickle, hold the tickle!</speak>

<info>He throws some kicks and kicks off Hermes' Brain Slug.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Thank God I'm free of that nightmare!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sorry, buddy. Here you go!</speak>

<info>He puts it back on top of Hermes' head.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> Thank you. It was cold 
down there on the floor.</speak>

<info>Amy, Zoidberg and Farnsworth are sat in the bleachers.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Here, Professor, I got you a programme.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, good. Just let me put on my reading 
glasses.  Why, Zoidberg, there's a lovely 
photo of you in here.</speak>

<info>The bell rings and the referee's mic drops into the ring.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
In this corner, the confused young robot 
with the golden curls weighing 525lbs: 
The Gender Bender!</speak>

<info>The crowd boos.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Boo!</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Get that hippie out of the ring!</speak>

<speak who="REFEREE">
And in these two corners, weighing 400 
tons, the gizmo from Pismo ... Beach, 
Destructor!</speak>

<info>Destructor bangs his knuckles together. Leela rubs Bender's 
shoulders and Fnog arrives.</info>

<speak who="FNOG">
So, we meet again. Most amusing: Girl 
who acts like fighter training fighter 
who acts like girl.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Keep laughing, Fnog!  Ready, Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I was born ready! Gimmie the bell!  
Did you hear a noise?  Final boarding 
call for flight 406, non-stop service 
to pain.  Now boarding standby passengers--</speak>

<info>Destructor punches him in the head, knocking him flat against 
the floor. He tries to crawl away but Destructor grabs his legs 
and hits him against the floor. The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
This seems like as good a time as any 
time to bring up my new grill for no 
reason.  With its patented design, the 
fat drains directly into my mouth.</speak>

<info>Destructor carries on killing Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(weakly)</info> Fry! Throw in the towel!  For 
God's sakes, Fry!</speak>

<info>Fry turns around. There is a Brain Slug on his head. He drones.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(monotonous)</info> That's exactly what I was 
thinking.</speak>

<info>Destructor stands Bender on his feet and punches him in slow-motion 
� la Raging Bull.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(weakly)</info> Mommy!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, Fnog, that's enough. Call him off. 
Fnog?  Hmm.</speak>

<info>Destructor stamps on Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Why won't anyone help me?</speak>

<info>Leela follows the cable under the ring. Fnog is watching Destructor 
on a screen and is controlling him with a VR suit.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
So, once more we meet again.</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
Huh?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You didn't train Destructor. You're 
just controlling him like a puppet. 
I mean, cheating in a fake fight. That's 
low!</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
Better than being a girl. Like you. 
You're a girl!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(ironic)</info> Oh, right. Girls lack the will 
of the warrior!</speak>

<info>She kicks him about. In the ring, Destructor starts mimicking 
Fnog's moves, holding his arms up to defend himself from no one. 
Bender gets up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Huh? It's bendering time!  Take this. 
And this!</speak>

<speak who="FNOG">
You were an excellent student.  Too 
bad I was a lousy teacher!</speak>

<info>He fights back. Destructor copies and beats up Bender some more.

<speak who="BENDER">
I think you misunderstood the concept 
of "bendering time"!</speak>

[Fnog has Leela on the floor.</info>

<speak who="FNOG">
See you in girl hell. I'll be in boy 
hell -- much nicer!</speak>

<info>He punches. Leela grabs his wrist and stops Destructor's punch. 
She looks at the screen and slams Fnog's fist into the ground. 
Destructor's fist comes through the canvas and knocks him out.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yes!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes!  Oh!</speak>

<info>The referee counts him out and the bell dings.</info>

<speak who="REFEREE">
And the winner is Destructor!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="LITTLE">
I've not seen a spectacle of this nature 
in all my years impersonating a sportscaster.</speak>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
It sure was some fight. Interesting 
side note: As a head without a body, 
I envy the dead.</speak>

<speak who="LITTLE">
No argument here.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The bleachers have cleared. The Planet Express staff 
crowd around Bender who has been flattened.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender? How did the fight go? I heard 
somebody got flattened!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Fry, where's your Brain Slug?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth picks up the limp alien from the floor.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Poor little guy starved to death.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm proud of you, Bender. Sure, you 
lost. You lost bad. But the important 
thing is I beat up someone who hurt 
my feelings in high school.</speak>

<info>She chuckles.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm in tremendous pain here.</speak>

<info>Doubledeal pushes through.</info>

<speak who="DOUBLEDEAL">
Great job, kid. You lost and you made 
it look almost half real. I want you 
to have this card good for 10% off at 
Bed Bath &amp; Beyond.</speak>

<info>He puts it in Bender's chest cabinet and leaves.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes! I'm the greatest! The greatest!</speak>

<info>He groans. Leela rolls him up and she and Fry carry him off.</info>

<speak who="LITTLE">
And so ends the chronicle of one of 
the greatest ever to play the sport.</speak>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
And he didn't look half bad in the tutu.</speak>

<speak who="LITTLE">
That he did surely not.</speak>

<speak who="FOREMAN">
What?</speak>

<info>THE END</info></xml>