<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 217 

<title>BENDER GETS MADE</title>

<author>Eric Horstead</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Simulcast On Crazy People's Fillings.</info>

<info>Outside Mmm TV Studio. There is a large sign on the door with 
a picture of Neptunian chef Elzar and "Elzar Live! Now Taping." 
Smartly dressed people walk through the VIP Entrance and Fry, 
Bender and Leela walk through the P Entrance, which is just a 
normal door right next to the VIP Entrance.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mmm TV Studio. At the back of the room people sit in 
bleachers. Fry, Bender and Leela take a seat at a table near 
the front.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow! I'm finally gonna see my favourite 
chef, TV's Elzar. Oh this is the greatest 
nanosecond of my life. No, this one 
is - no, this one. Wait...that one was 
slightly worse. Ah, so far so good on 
this one.</speak>

<info>The lights dim and Bender squeaks. A drum roll rolls and spotlights 
fly around the kitchen studio at the front.</info>

<info>The audience applauds and Bender leaps up cheering.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah!  Alright! Yeah baby!</speak>

<info>Elzar takes off the jetpacks and shakes the cheering audiences 
hands.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Elzar!  Alright!</speak>

<info>Bender block Elzars path.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Elzar, you're my god. Please sign this 
sketch I drew of you.</speak>

<info>He holds up a crude picture of himself staring lovey-eyed at 
a Elzar. Elzar takes it stamps it. Bender takes it back and reads 
it. "I'll Sign This For $50.00. x___"</info> <info>(crying)</info> Oh Elzar, bless 
you!

<info>He hugs Elzar who struggles to get out of his grip.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Now, this is why I prefer your non-stick 
robots.</speak>

<info>The audience laughs and Elzar tickles Bender with an electric 
whisk. Bender chuckles and lets go of Elzar. Elzar runs to the 
front of the room.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(disappointed)</info> Oh.  <info>(normal)</info> Alright, 
yeah!  <info>(quietly)</info> Alright, yeah!</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey, I hope you folks like Cajun food. 
'Cause today we're making Elzar's down-home 
Neptune-style gumbo. Now, step one. 
You'll wanna boil some oysters in a 
pot of down-home Neptune-style gumbo.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(loudly)</info> Boiled? Interesting.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> Bender, please try to be 
a little quieter.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No, you shut up.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Of course, every now and then you'll 
wanna knock it up a notch with a blast 
from your spice weasel.  Bam!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh yeah, bam it again Elzar. Knock it 
up another notch!</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Jeez, who let this guy through the metal 
detector?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Come on you wimp. Work that weasel. 
Quit holding out on us.</speak>

<info>Elzar sighs.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
If you promise to stop interrupting 
alright. Against my will, I'm gonna 
knock it up another notch.</speak>

<info>Bender takes a camera out of his chest cabient.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I gotta get this notch-up knocking on 
film.  Hey Elzar, think fast.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
What, huh?</speak>

<info>The flash goes off and Elzar blasts the spice weasel straight 
into Leela's eye.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Ow! My eye! I'm blind!</speak>

<info>The crowd gasps and murmurs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Bam!</speak>

<info>An ambulance speeds through the streets of New New York and 
stops outside the Taco Bellevue Hospital.</info>

<info>Cut to: Taco Bellevue Hospital. Paramedics run in with Leela 
on a hover-bed. In a cubicle a small doctor examines Hattie.</info>

<speak who="HATTIE">
Tell me doctor, how's my cyst?</speak>

<info>The doctor is a near dead ringer for Gidget the Taco Bell chihuahua.</info>

<speak who="HATTIE">'S DOCTOR
Grande.</speak>

<info>Taco Bellevue Hospital Eye Clinic. While a doctor examines Leela's 
bloodshot eye, Zoidberg dressed in scrubs talks to Fry.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I don't like the look of this doctor. 
I bet I've lost more patients than he's 
even treated.</speak>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
OK. What does this look like?</speak>

<info>He holds up a picture of a blob to Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Um...a grey-ish blob?</speak>

<info>And it is.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Right.  And this one?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Um...a grey-ish blob?</speak>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Not as right that time. It looks like 
you might have some mild corneal irritation.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Nice try little boy. You might have 
your textbook knowledge and your real 
diploma but I have more skill in my 
little claw than you have in your whole 
carapace.</speak>

<info>He screams and clacks his claws at the doctor.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
You seem a bit tense.  Here try these.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Sure, butter me up with candy. But it 
won't work sonny!  <info>(dazed)</info> Why always 
the fighting?</speak>

<info>He walks away and the doctor turns to Leela.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Your eye just needs some rest. You'll 
have to wear this patch for about a 
week.</speak>

<info>He puts a black eye patch over Leela's eye and she groans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
A week? What do you think Dr Zoidberg?</speak>

<info>Zoidberg, still dazed, clacks his claw past his face.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(dazed)</info> Clack.</speak>

<info>Taco Bellevue Hospital Waiting Room. Amy and Bender pace around. 
The doors open and Leela and Zoidberg walk in. Leela holds onto 
Zoidberg's arm...</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(dazed)</info> Thanks for the help Leela.</speak>

<info>He sits down. Fry joins Amy and Bender.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Leela, we're right here.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm not deaf. I just have to wear this 
stupid eye patch. Does it look stupid?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No. In fact, it looks so nice I think 
I might get one too.</speak>

<info>He gestures an emphatic "no" to the others. Enter Elzar.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's Elzar again! Oh my God I'm so excited 
I wish I could wet my pants.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Leela, please, let me make this up to 
you. You and your friends are all invited 
to my restaurant tonight. I'm gonna 
bam you up a dinner you'll never forget.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(cheering)</info> Alright!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(cheering)</info> Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(cheering)</info> Hooray for blindy!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh God. I'm coming dowwwn!</speak>

<info>Outside Elzar's Fine Cuisine. A couple fly in on jetpacks and 
the valets take them and fly away.</info>

<info>Cut to: Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The whole crew are out for the 
evening. Waiters hold plates piled high with food.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Folks tell the neighbours to watch your 
mouth 'cause your tastebuds are going 
on vacation. I made you each your own 
special meal so dig in!</speak>

<info>A waiter puts a plate in front of Hermes and he gasps.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
It's the biggest Jamaican platter I've 
ever seen. Jerk chicken, jerk beef, 
jerk pork. Is there any meat this man 
can't jerk?</speak>

<info>Zoidberg looks at his plate.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
The king crab is to die for! Look, a 
tiny edible crown!</speak>

<info>He eats it.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
What's it made of?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG"><info>EATING</info>
Wood!</speak>

<info>Bender eats his food. Whatever it is it's burning. Fry has a 
burger.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh Fry, you gotta try this sterno-nicoise!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No thanks. That's robot food.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's so good. Oh just try a little!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No really I don't -  Mmm!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You doing alright over there Leela?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh yeah, this salad's fantastic.  So 
fresh.</speak>

<info>She eats it.</info>

<info>Outside Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The couple from earlier have finished 
their meal and the valets return their jetpacks.</info>

<info>Cut to: Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The crew have finished their meal 
too. Hermes pushes his empty plate away, sighs and pats his stomach. 
Farnsworth wipes his mouth and Bender opens his door and burps.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh my. That steamed carrot was a bit 
spicy for me.</speak>

<info>Elzar walks in behind him with a tray of chocolates.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Everybody enjoy their dinner?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Are you kidding me?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Uh-huh.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
God, yes Elzar.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Well, I enjoyed cooking for you. And 
just to make everything completely square, 
I want you to have these complimentary 
after-dinner chocolates.</speak>

<info>The crew takes the chocolates. Underneath is a piece of paper.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
What's this under the chocolates?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Yeah, you take care of that whenever 
you want.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Hey.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
A bill?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You're charging us? After you blinded 
me?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey I made you a nice meal. This ain't 
a charity.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
$1200?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Holy Zombie Jesus!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
We don't have that kind of money. Especially 
not Zoidberg.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
They took away my credit card.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
OK OK wait. I know how to take care 
of this, no problem.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. URL puts some cuffs on Leela. The rest of the crew 
are cuffed too.</info>

<speak who="URL">
You deadbeats are under arrest. It's 
a stone cold shame.</speak>

<info>Fry picks his nose.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
He's making a break for it. Get him!</speak>

<info>He and URL draw their lightsabers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
No, I was just picking my nose.</speak>

<speak who="SMITTY">
He's picking his nose. Get him!</speak>

<info>He and URL bash Fry around the head.</info>

<info>Outside Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The crew file out of the restaurant 
into the police van.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
The old dine-and-dash huh? My daddy 
owned a restaurant and it's punks like 
you who kept it from going regional. 
That's why I became a cop.</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Now it's payback time. Aww yeah.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Please don't hit me. I'm brittle.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey wait a second. I've got the perfect 
solution.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Listen to the smart robot.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I love cooking and Elzar's ass likes 
getting kissed right?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
No question.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
So, how 'bout I work part time at the 
restaurant to pay off our debt?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
I don't know. I usually hire people 
who are a little less unbearable.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Oh, Bender's a model employee.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
He's so polite.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And hard working.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
He's made of candy.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
OK, fine, I'll give it a shot.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(cheering)</info> Alright!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(cheering)</info> Yes!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hot diggety!</speak>

<info>Smitty and URL take their cuffs off.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
You'd better keep your nose clean.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That'll be easy. I never wear the damn 
thing.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Hermes addresses the crew at the 
morning meeting.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Ah. Time for my precious 10am meeting. 
Where in Legoland is Leela?</speak>

<info>Leela walks in with Nibbler on a lead.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm here and I'm getting along just 
fine thank you. My walk to work today 
just took a little longer than usual. 
Nibbler took me through the zoo for 
some reason.</speak>

<info>Nibbler coughs up some antlers. Leela sits down on Zoidberg 
and he groans.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Leela, a little help is nothing to be 
embarrassed about. Like, maybe I could 
do your makeup.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I don't need help. For you information 
I did this all by myself.</speak>

<info>She turns around. The other side of her face is messed up with 
squiggly lines of lipstick and mascara everywhere.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You look beautiful. Incidentally, my 
favourite artist is Picasso.</speak>

<info>Enter Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, I'm off to work at the restaurant. 
One of you will have to fill in for 
me while I'm gone.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Better yet, I'll build someone to fill 
in for you.  Some kind of gamma powered 
mechanical monster, with freeway on-ramps 
for arms and a heart as black as coal...</speak>

<info>He walks out the door. Bender turns to the rest of the crew.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, if that new give can't handle 
thing, gimmie a call.</speak>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine Entrance. Elzar empties the cash from the 
till into his pockets. Bender walks in covered in grease and 
wearing an apron.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm done siphoning out the grease trap. 
I think I need a mint.  So uh, what 
job do I move up to? Pastry chef? Saucier? 
Soup guy?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Bam!</speak>

<info>He holds up a plunger and Bender takes it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(muttering)</info> Bam yourself!  <info>(talking)</info> 
Hey, who are they?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Let's just say they're very good customers 
and I'm not answering anymore questions.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Are they the robot mafia?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Yes.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The waitress shows the Mafiabots 
to their table.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
You call this a table? You call this 
a table? I wouldn't hit a guy over the 
head with this table.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
You hear that? The Donbot don't like 
it. I oughta clamp you - you wanna be 
clamped?</speak>

<info>He shows her his clamps and she flinches. The second mobbot, 
Joey Mousepad, pulls him away.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
Whoa whoa, calm down Clamps.  The boss, 
he likes a wall up which his back can 
be put against. Such as like this there.</speak>

<info>He points at a table with a family already sitting at it.</info>

<speak who="WAITRESS">
But that table's already -</speak>

<info>Enter Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, let me bus that for you gentlemen. 
No, what I meant to do was...</speak>

<info>He slides the plates off the table and they fall to the floor 
and break.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Oh!</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
I can't believe this!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mind your own business and get out!</speak>

<info>The family storm out and Bender kicks the plates around some 
more.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Huh. I like this guy's lack of style.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The mobbots are sat at their table.</info>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
...So I finally get this guy a pair 
of cement shoes which he likes, 'cause 
they're lighter than his lead ones.</speak>

<info>Bender hands them their change on a tray and starts to leave.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey. You think this computes over here? 
Where's all my change? I gave you a 
hundred.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No you gave me a fifty.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Oh no I didn't.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah you did.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Hey, you tryin' to steal from the Donbot?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm tryin' but he's not makin' it easy.</speak>

<info>Clamps and Joey stand up and Bender steps back. Donbot starts 
to laugh. Clamps and Joey join in.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Get a load of the ball bearings on this 
guy, huh. I like you kid. Here's something 
for your trouble.  <info>(whispering)</info> It's 
money.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow thanks.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey, you earned that 50 bucks.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You gave me a twenty.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
I did?  Oh I'm sorry I meant to - hey 
wait a minute.  I got a good feeling 
about you. Say, you wanna work for me 
as a hired goon?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Are you kidding? I've always wanted 
to break into gooning!  <info>(shouting)</info> Hey 
Elzar, I quit.</speak>

<info>Alley. Bender is with the mobbots. Donbot holds up a 3.5" disk.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
We're gonna try you out with a little 
delivery job. It's for a uh, private 
lottery that we run.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow, you guys run numbers?!</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Well, nothing fancy. Just ones and zeros 
mostly.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Just take this disk over to the pool 
hall and give it to Sammy "The Mechanical 
Bull" Gravano. And watch out for the 
cops.</speak>

<info>Bender takes the disk.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's just what my mom used to tell 
me.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Little Bitaly Street. Bender walks out of the alley 
and into a street fair. Robots play hoopla and they all win and 
cheer. A heliumbot blows up a balloon, twists it into a human 
shape and gives to a kidbot. Bender stops by an OI"L"-AD"E" stall 
run by Tinny Tim with certain letters turned backwards. He downs 
a glass.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's some fine oil-ade son. We could 
use a man like you in the Robot Mafia 
which I'm sorta in.</speak>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
You flatter me kind goon. But I'm only 
programmed to sell oil-ade and write 
in cute backwards letters like on the 
sign here.</speak>

<info>Bender is about to take about to take another sip when he sees 
something across the street.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw crap, the cops.</speak>

<info>Across the street, Smitty and URL are dressed in civilian clothes 
but still wearing their police helmets. They read a "Non-Police 
News" newspaper.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Seen any suspicious activity?</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Nope. But check out today's Marmaduke. 
Solid!</speak>

<info>Smitty looks across the road.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Hey. It's that skell from Elzar's.</speak>

<info><speak who="URL"> speaks into his wrist communicator.</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Undercover pursuit in progress...baby.</speak>

[They cover their faces with their newspapers and follow Bender 
who cheerfully whistles. Smitty drops his paper and grabs Bender's 
arms.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Gotcha!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What seems to be the problem officers? 
Was I speeding?</speak>

<speak who="SMITTY">
We'll decide what you were doing after 
an illegal search.</speak>

<info>URL snaps on some gloves and feels inside Bender's chest cabinet. 
Bender giggles.</info>

<speak who="URL">
He's clean.  Smells nice too.</speak>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Better than me?</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Aww yeah.</speak>

<info>They leave and Bender looks across the street. Tinny Tim stands 
on the steps of Pat's Pool Hall; Rich Beginners Welcome. The 
door opens. Tinny Tim holds out the disk to a robot.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Courtesy of Mr Bender.</speak>

<info>The robot takes it and closes the door. Tinny Tim winks and 
waves some money at Bender. Bender thumbs ups. The mobbots come 
around the corner.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Nice job Bender, you passed the test. 
You wanna joi me, Clamps and Joey Mousepad 
at out uh, social club tomorrow night?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, I'd rather plan some fellonies.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Oh. Then we should meet at our Mafia 
crime headquarters.</speak>

<info>Fronty's Meat Market. On the front of the building a sign states 
that it is "Not A Front Since 2997." Inside Bender looks around 
and opens a freezer room door.</info>

<info>Cut to: Freezer Room. Donbot sits on several block of ice with 
Clamps and Joey to either side. Meat carcasses hang on hooks 
around them and a trembling robot stand in front of them.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Donbot, I beg you, I can't make this 
week's loan payment. Look into your 
hard drive and open your mercy file.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
File not found.  Let that be a warning 
to you.</speak>

<info>The robot gets up and puts on his hat.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Thank you Donbot.</speak>

<info>He leaves and Bender walks in.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Joey, Clamps, Donny B!</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey listen Bender. We got a big score 
planned but uh, we need some muscle.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
A little of this huh?</speak>

<info>Joey punches his door.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
Ho ho, this guy's an ox! He's got oxon-like 
strength! Hey, he needs a nickname right? 
Let's call him Clamps.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Clamps? That's my name you numbskull! 
Don't make me clamp you one!</speak>

<info>He clacks his clamps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
How 'bout "Blotto"? It's witty, it's 
got street cred. Plus I can keep my 
monogrammed slippers.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Good thinking! Hey hey! Now, this score 
ain't gonna be no cake walk in the tea 
park alright, there may be some death 
killing.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
It's gonna be clamp this, clamp that, 
bada-climp, bada-clamp.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
What d'you think Blotto? You in?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's funny. Until now I always wanted 
to be a gangster...so the answer's yes.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Hey hey! Way to go way to be way to 
shoot!</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Now since we're committing crimes that 
may be against the law, I suggest you 
have an alibi.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
An alibi huh?</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. The ship is on it's launching mechanism 
preparing to be raised into the launch position.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Corridor. Outside Bender's and his quarters, 
Fry holds a tray with two sundaes on it. Bender groans from inside.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
But we're about to take off. We gotta 
eat our blastoff sundaes.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Fry and Bender's Quarters. Bender isn't inside. Instead 
he has hooked up a tape-reel machine to play over and over.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>FROM OUTSIDE</info>
OK you stay in bed. I'll eat yours.</speak>

<info>The tape rewinds.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Leela, still wearing her eyepatch, feels 
for a button. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender's sick.  Need any help taking 
off?</speak>

<info>Nibbler sniffs at the sundae.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm fine thank you. A real pilot can 
navigate by feel alone.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. The hangar doors half open and 
the ship blasts through them, leaving a hole in them.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Meeting Room. Hermes and Zoidberg turn 
around at the table and see the hole in the doors and the rubble 
on the hangar floor.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
That's coming outta your pay!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg bursts into tears.</info>

<info>Mafiabot Ship. Joey Mousepad drives. Bender walks in with a 
pot of food and puts it on a table which Donbot and Clamps are 
sat at.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You know the secret of traditional robot 
cooking? Start with a good high-quality 
oil...then eat it. So whats this big 
score anyway?</speak>

<info>He ladels some oil into Donbot's dish.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
We're heisting a shipment of Zuban cigars.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Zubans? Those are the finest cigars 
in the universe. I can stink up a hole 
maternity ward with one of those things.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Yo there's our pigeon now. Let's shoot 
bullets out of our guns.</speak>

<info>Bender drinks a ladelful of oil and looks out through the windscreen 
and squeals. The Planet Express ship flies ahead of the Mafia 
ship. He spits out the oil for a very very very long time.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The mobbots have their guns ready. Bender looks 
out the window biting his nails with fear.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Alright, here's the battleplan: We shoot, 
they surrender, we go aboard, somebody 
does some clamping then we heist the 
cigars and go home.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And all without killing anyone.  This 
gang's got some fresh new ideas. I admire 
that.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Oh, we'll kill 'em alright.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
We got 'em heavily out-clamped. They 
won't know what clamped 'em!</speak>

<info>Bender gulps.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Nibbler gobbles some food from his dish 
and Fry leans back on his seat looking through the window.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow, it's too bad you can't see Leela 
'cause theres a cool ship out there 
shooting at somebody.</speak>

<info>The orange laser bolts hit the ship and it shakes and knocks 
Fry and Leela off their chairs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm taking evasive action.</speak>

<info>She his sitting on the other side of the cockpit holding Nibbler's 
bowl instead of the wheel.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, Leela?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Stop bothering me Fry, I need full concentration.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Mafiabot Ship. Clamps and Joey Mousepad stand 
on the portside of the ship firing lasers from their tommyguns. 
The Planet Express ship turns wildly away.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Laser Turret. Fry returns fire and misses. The 
front of the Mafiabot ship opens and missile comes flying out 
of it. Fry squeals and pulls a string.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Fry has rigged up the strings to turn 
the wheel. He turns the ship starboard and missile flies away 
from the ship and explodes.</info>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Missile evaded.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Eyesight is for chumps.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Mafiabot Ship. Donbot drives and Bender stands next 
to him tense.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Their desire to keep living shows me 
no respect. Hey Blotto, roll down the 
window and start shooting.</speak>

<info>He hands him a tommygun.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Um, uh, um.  <info>(fake hurt)</info> Ooh ow! He 
got me! Ow, what a shot that guy is.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Leela stops turning her new wheel.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wait. Why do the raised letters that 
normally say "Turnmaster Steering company" 
say "Nibbler"? Oh no!</speak>

<info>She throws the dish down and makes her way over to the pilot's 
seat.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Laser Turret. Leela takes control of the ship 
and it jerks sideways. She crackles onto a screen.</info>

<speak who="LEELA"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
I'm back at the wheel Fry. Everything's 
under control.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Great, great. The one time I forgot 
to buy flight insurance.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Mafiabot Ship. The Planet Express ship turns 
around and heads for the mobbot's ship. Joey screams.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
They're coming straight towards our 
proximity. Maybe you should give 'em 
the clamps Clamps.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Gee you think? You think that maybe 
I should use these clamps that I use 
every day at every opportunity? <info>(shouting)</info> 
You're a freaking genius you idiot!</speak>

<info>The Planet Express ship flies by and Clamps grabs it's tail 
fin. On the fin is a sign that clearly says "Fuel Line. Do Not 
Clamp." Clamps ignores it and clamps the fuel line. The ship's 
engines shut down.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Fry slides down the turret access ladder 
and runs into the cockpit.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
The engine's stalled. I'm trying the 
manual fuel pump.</speak>

<info>She pumps Nibbler's eyestalk up and down. The doors opens and 
Fry screams. The three Mafiabots are standing in the doorway.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hello, we're the Robot Mafia. The entire 
Robot Mafia. We're here to steal your 
cigars.</speak>

<info>Leela gets up and points at something that isn't a Mafiabot.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
You'll never get away with this.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Unless you let us live. Then you'll 
get off scot free.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Joey, Clamps, hurry and blindfold them 
before they see us some more.</speak>

<info>Clamps blindfolds Fry and Joey points at Leela.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
Hey boss, looks like somebody beat us 
to it.</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'll assume that's a joke at my expense. 
Well, who's laughing now? Heyya!</speak>

<info>She kicks Fry in the face and he groans and falls over. Joey 
holds her.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey where's Blotto? He should be here 
learning the trade.</speak>

<info>Bender peers in through the doorway.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Corridor. Bender opens his chest cabinet and 
turns a voice modulator knob from "Robot" to "King," making him 
sound like a posh snob.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Bender wanders in.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sorry I'm tardy old bean, I was just 
enjoying a rather tasty watercress sandwich.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey. He's more classy than I realised. 
Tie up the prisoners.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Capital idea old sport.  I say, get 
the hell off me!</speak>

<info>Leela leans over to Fry.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> That guy sounds familiar.</speak>

<info>Bender puts a bucket over Nibbler and brick on top. He stands 
up and his antenna hooks onto Leela's patch and pulls it off.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
My word, what have we -  Uh, nothing 
to see here old girl.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Hey boss, this here crew list lists 
a robot on this crew here.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Alright. I want you to find him and 
plug him. Then unplug him.</speak>

<info>Fry and Leela gasp.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
No!</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
I got a little surprise in store for 
that guy. The clamps! Eh?</speak>

<info>He laughs and turns to leave.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh wait, old...spice. Let me have a 
go at this mechanised chap. I can be 
quite the rough customer.</speak>

<info>He walks out.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Corridor. He disappears into his and Fry's quarters.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(whispering)</info> Oh no, poor Bender.</speak>

<info>The sound out metal smashing metal comes from the quarters. 
The real Bender laughs.</info>

<info>Cut to: Fry and Bender's Quarters. Bender sits reading Somewhat 
Fantastic Sci-Fi. He hits himself on the head with a frying pan.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(fake voice)</info> ...Take that you twit. 
<info>(normal voice)</info> No! Stop it!</speak>

<info>The tape starts to rewind and Bender hits the machine with the 
frying pan, breaking it.</info>

<info>Ship's Cargo Bay. The Mafiabots have installed a linkway from 
the Planet Express cargo bay to theirs. Bender carries the last 
crate towards the linkway.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
That's the last of 'em.  Alright now 
let's Mafia things up a little.  Joey, 
burn down the ship. Clamps, burn down 
the crew.</speak>

<info>Bender runs back in and talks like he's from New York.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, hey Donny, baby, gimmie a chance 
here huh? Yous guys skidaddle. Let me 
take care of the doity woik.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Hey, I like your attitude. And your 
latest accent. Keep it up and I might 
just get you your own pair of clamps 
huh?</speak>

<info>He pats Bender's cheek and leaves.</info>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
<info>(muttering)</info> He's gonna get clamps? Clamps 
clamps......clamps clamps!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Phew.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. The Mafiabot ship flies away. Nibbler 
squeaks from under the bucket. Fry and Leela are still tied up.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela, we may not have much time left......so 
let's spend all of it reminscing about 
Bender. He was like a big computer than 
ran on magic.</speak>

<info>Bender sits down, ties his arms up behind the chair and clears 
his throat.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, help! Help!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You're OK!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes I am. Having just this minute regained 
consciousness.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I've got an idea. Hold still.  It's 
about to break, yes, yes!</speak>

<info>Bender's arm drops off.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(cheering)</info> Alright!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah it broke alright</speak>

<info>Outside Planet Express. Leela has crashed the ship into the 
tower, making the building look more like Planet Hollywood than 
Planet Express.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Meeting Room. The crew are all assembled.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm telling you, Leela was cool, she 
was in command, and when she kicked 
people it hurt. It really hurt.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well, this is the big moment. It's finally 
time to take my patch off.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'll handle the snipping. Afterall I 
do have the proper equipment.</speak>

<info>He ignores his claw and uses some scissors to cut the patch 
off. Leela sees a shape come into view and gasps.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I think it's Blotto. That gangster I 
saw when my patch fell off.  Professor? 
Where were you at 10pm last night?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Where am I now?</speak>

<info>The doorbell rings and Bender goes to answer it.</info>

<info>Outside Planet Express. He opens the door and gasps when he 
sees Tinny Tim.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
So they sent a helpless child to kill 
me? Well I'm not going out without a 
fight.</speak>

<info>He kicks Tinny Tim's crutch away and he hops around without 
it.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Fine kick sir. But I'm actually here 
to deliver your cut from the cigar heist.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh sweet legal tender!  Kid, tell the 
Donbot I'm quitting organised crime. 
From now on I'll stick to regular kind.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The ship is back in the hangar. 
Bender sits down with a cigar in his mouth. He takes the cash 
out of his chest cabinet. Fry sighs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's funny Bender. With you sick and 
Leela blind only I know what really 
went on out there. Maybe someday I'll 
tell you the whole story.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And maybe someday I won't listen.</speak>

<info>He starts to eat his cash again.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>