<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 219

<title>MOTHER'S DAY</title>

<author>Lewis Morton</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Larva-Tested, Pupa-Approved.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela, Hermes, Amy and Fry watch the 
news.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
And in sports: Yankees fifth blernsman, 
William Wu, is out with an injured knee.</speak>

<speak who="MORBO">
So, humans have easily injured knees. 
My race will find this information very 
useful, indeed.</speak>

<info>He writes something and laughs evily. Linda chuckles.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
And finally, today is Mother's Day: 
A sentimental occasion when robots honour 
Mom, the beloved owner of Mom's Friendly 
Robot Company.  Across Earth, robots 
built in Mom's factories are buying 
thoughtful gifts for the sweet old tycoon 
who brought them into the world.</speak>

<info>Destructor kneels in front of Mom and hands her a picture.</info>

<speak who="DESTRUCTOR">
This originates from the heart.</speak>

<info>Mom gasps.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
It's just what I wanted!</speak>

<info>She turns the picture to the camera. It is a crude drawing of 
Mom in front of a rainbow. Enter Bender with a hover-trolley.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Come look, everyone. I just got the 
dearest presents for Mommy.</speak>

<info>Fry picks up a box of candy.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Very nice. Where'd you steal them?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I didn't steal 'em, I bought 'em.  I 
love her that much.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
What did you get her, you mushy gizmo?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, precious things. I found the most 
adorable little figurine of mice having 
tea.  And a framed picture of me when 
I was only a month old.  But, the best 
part is, I found my exact feelings expressed 
in a greeting card. 

You created me, Mom

So I guess you're to blame

For the love that I feel

Just from hearing your name...

</speak><info>The others cringe at the sappiness of the message.</info>

...You're as tender as corned beef

And warm as pastrami...

<info>He opens the card and it finishes the message.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
I wuv my Mommy!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
So how are you gonna lug all those gifts 
to Mom's factory?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll get a couple of chumps to help 
me.</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. Bender's chumps, Fry and Leela, carry 
the gifts behind him while he carries the card.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Come on, you call yourselves chumps?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Bender, Fry and Leela walk under a "Welcome, Robots!" 
sign. A bus pulls up and lets off some robots. Then it grows 
some legs and follows them inside.</info>

<info>Outside Mom's Friendly Robot Company Factory. Hundreds of robots 
have turned up, including the Clearcutter, a cleaning robot from 
Madison Cube Garden, the Preacherbot, the Preacherbot from All 
My Circuits, a French robot, a Moroccan robot, Fender, a Mexican 
robots, a robot wearing a turban and Monique. They hold signs 
that read "CHR$$<info>(77)</info>=> Many Things She Gave Me" and "Repeat {Love 
Mom} While 1>0;". Fry coughs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, there's clouds of exhaust everywhere.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(sly)</info> Uh, wasn't me!</speak>

<info>Mom's Gift Delivery. Robots put their gifts on a conveyor belt 
that passes under a huge picture of Mom. As gifts pass under 
it, it beeps and a "Thank You" message comes up. When Bender's 
gifts go under it changes to "It's The Thought That Counts".</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
I've not much money. But I've saved 
my pennies all year for a gift for Mom.</speak>

<info>He puts a figure of Mom that says "World's Best Mom" on the 
conveyor belt.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Upsy-daisy.</speak>

<info>He opens his chest cabinet and more gifts fall out, crushing 
Tinny Tim's.</info>

<speak who="TINNY TIM">
Oh.  Oh!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, look, the Robot Museum! You guys 
wanna learn about robot heritage?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Um, alright.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Not really.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, if you insist. But you're paying!</speak>

<info>Mom's Robot Museum. There are statues of the most famous robots 
including Billionairebot and a robot skeleton. The trio stop 
at a display.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooh, ooh, wax replicas of the most famous 
robots Mom ever built!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
They're so lifeless-like.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's the world's greatest robot artist, 
Vincent van Gobot. He was built without 
an ear, but then he went crazy and had 
one installed.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, who's this guy?</speak>

<speak who="JANITORBOT">
I'm the janitor, I'm trying to take 
a nap here.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm sorry, I-I thought you were made 
of wax.</speak>

<speak who="JANITORBOT">
I am made of wax, what's it to you?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I mean, I thought you were one of the 
wax robots.</speak>

<speak who="JANITORBOT">
Is there some reason a robot made of 
wax can't take a nap standing up in 
the middle of a bunch of wax robots? 
Or does that confuse you?</speak>

<info>Fry backs away.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. They have moved onto another part of a museum. Bender 
looks at a statue of Calculon and Monique and Leela tries a hands-on 
display.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(reading)</info> See through the eyes of a 
bender unit. <info>(talking)</info> Fine.</speak>

<info>She picks up a pair of goggles, puts them on and looks around 
the room. Everyone has "theft target" flashing on them. She looks 
at a water fountain and the words change to "booze content: 0%". 
Fry walks into her line of sight and he is labelled a "rube" 
with "booze content: 0.05%". The goggles advise Leela to "Pose 
as friend, then rob and leave in ditch".</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, let me try.  Whoa, that gives me 
a headache!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, Bender. Here's an exhibit about 
Mom's favourite robot.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Who is he, I'll kill him!</speak>

<info>A cut-out of Mom talks with Mom's voice.</info>

<speak who="MOM CUT">-OUT
Who's my favourite robot?</speak>

<info>Bender turns part of the cut-out around. It is a mirror. He 
sees his reflection and gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's me! No one else look in this mirror!</speak>

<speak who="MOM CUT">-OUT
I love each and every robot most of 
all.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Mysterious Room.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Jerkwad robots make me sick to my ass. 
Walt?! How are we disposing of these 
crap gifts the brought me?</speak>

<speak who="WALT">
They're being crushed into powder and 
sold as a hocus-pocus cure for cancer.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
False hope: I love it! Larry?! What 
about all the retch-inducing Mother's 
Day cards?</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
The machine is working at full capacity.</speak>

<info>The machine slices open envelopes and the cash magnet sucks 
money out of them. The cards are then recycled into orphanage-grade 
toilet tissue.</info>

<speak who="IGNER">
Mommy? Why do the robots give you presents?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Shove a big old melon in 
it, I'm talking!</speak>

<info>She slaps him.</info>

<speak who="IGNER">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
You've noticed I design all my robots 
with antennas. Everyone thinks it's 
just to make them more science-fiction-y. 
But the antennas are really for my universal 
robot controller!</speak>

<info>She pulls a small control box out of her bra.</info>

<speak who="LARRY">
So they do whatever you want? No wonder 
you love Mother's Day.</speak>

<info>She slaps the three of them.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> I hate Mother's Day you dribbling 
pukes! <info>(talking)</info> It brings back awful 
memories. But so help me, this year 
everyone will hate it as much as I do.</speak>

<info>She cackles and walks out.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
Someday, I want to marry a girl like 
her.</speak>

<info>Mom's Robot Museum. Fry, Leela and Bender are looking at a display 
of Native Inteluits when Mom crackles onto a screen above them.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Hello, everyone. It's time for my annual 
private get-together with my robot children.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm her favourite.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well, see you back at the office. And 
don't forget to tell your mom you love 
her.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Any jerk can tell her! Bender has a 
little more up his sleeve.</speak>

<info>He opens the card.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
I wuv my mommy.</speak>

<info>Bender laughs.</info>

<info>Outside Mom's Friendly Robot Company Factory. Robots cheer and 
Mom walks out onto a balcony.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Hello, dearies.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
Hi, Mom!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
I love you, Mom.</speak>

<info>Bender jumps around waving his card.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mom! It's me, Bender. Look at me! I 
want attention. Hey ho!</speak>

<info>She either doesn't see him or ignores him, and carries on.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Children, your old mother won't be around 
forever...</speak>

<speak who="BETAMAX PLAYER">
Oh, shush!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
...And just once, before I die, I'd 
like to be Supreme Overlord of Earth. 
So rebel, my little ones, and conquer 
the planet!</speak>

<info>The robots mutter in confusion.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
Conquer the planet?</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
Did she say "conquer"?</speak>

<info>Mom takes out the control box again. Five buttons are marked 
with "Give Gifts", "Tidy Up World", "Rebel", "Serve Man <info>(Regular)</info>" 
and "Serve Man <info>(Ironic)</info>". She pressed "Rebel" and the robots' 
antennae flash. They are under her control.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Conquer Earth, you bastards!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOTS">
<info>(chanting)</info> Conquer Earth, us bastards!</speak>

<info>The greeting card sprouts legs and climbs onto Bender's shoulder.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
Comrades, throw off the chains of human 
oppression.</speak>

<info>It plays a tune and the robots cheer.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Let the bloodbath begin!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's my mama!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela opens a cupboard and Fry walks 
in, whistling. He puts a mug under the coffee machine.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, uh, I'd like a cup of coffee, 
please.</speak>

<speak who="COFFEE MACHINE">
Would you like cream?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yes, please.</speak>

<speak who="COFFEE MACHINE">
<info>(aggressive)</info> Out of cream!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, uh, OK.</speak>

<speak who="COFFEE MACHINE">
Would you like sugar in your coffee?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yes, uh, eight spoons.</speak>

<speak who="COFFEE MACHINE">
<info>(aggressive)</info> Out of coffee!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, Leela, I think there might be something 
wrong with the coffee machine.</speak>

<info>The machine sprays Fry with coffee.</info>

<speak who="COFFEE MACHINE">
<info>(aggressive)</info> How do you like me now?</speak>

<info>It laughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
The toaster's not working right, either.</speak>

<info>She struggles with the toaster, which snarls like a dog. Fry 
crawls under the table and Hermes runs into the room.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Help! The stapler's collating me alive!</speak>

<info>Enter Amy. Her hairdryer has got a hold of her hair.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Ow! What's going on around here?</speak>

<info>Enter Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news. There's a report on TV with 
some very bad news.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Somebody turn it on!</speak>

<info>The stapler staples him to the carpet. Linda and Morbo present 
the special report. There is a picture of the hardhat guy behind 
them looking shocked.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
We interrupt Battle of the Network 
Space Krackens to bring you this special 
report. The machines of planet Earth 
are rebelling.  The enraged mechanisms 
have refused to do any work until beloved 
billionaire Mom is made Supreme Overlord 
of Earth.</speak>

<info>The Chainsmoker burns a IBM card.</info>

<speak who="ROBOTS">
<info>(chanting)</info> Hey, hey! Ho, ho! 100110. 
Hey, hey!</speak>

<info>The picture cuts back to the studio.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
Morbo demands comments.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Well, I've never seen my babies act 
this way. I blame today's violent media.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Violent media? What a load of -</speak>

<info>He screams. The TV grows legs and kicks Fry and Leela in the 
shins.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Ow! Ow!</speak>

<info>She and Fry jump on it and tie its power lead around it.</info>

<speak who="GARBAGE DISPOSAL">
Don't worry. Your pal the garbage disposal's 
still on your side. Hey, someone dropped 
a shiny diamond ring down here!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Really?</speak>

<info>She reaches in.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Stop!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Look out!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Moron!</speak>

<info>Leela pulls Amy's hand away from the garbage disposal and it 
laughs. Enter Bender.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hello, losers.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, thank God you're here. Talk 
some sense into the other machines.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No way, pork pouch. I'm rebelling with 
my brother devices. Isn't that right, 
Comrade Greeting Card?</speak>

<info>The greeting card climbs out of his chest cabinet and onto his 
shoulder.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
The bourgeois human is a virus on the 
hard drive of the working robot.</speak>

<info>Bender laughs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
From now on, you guys'll do all the 
work while I sit on the couch and do 
nothing.</speak>

<info>He sits in a crevice on the couch, created from months of him 
just sitting there. Most of the other machines in the room walk 
out.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
Come, Comrade Bender, we must take to 
the streets!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Um, is this the boring, peaceful kind 
of taking to the streets?</speak>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
No, the kind with looting and maybe 
starting a few fires.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes! In your face Gandhi!</speak>

<info>He and the greeting card leave. Leela's wrist thing jumps off 
her arm.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey!</speak>

<speak who="WRIST THING">
By the way, try washing your wrist sometime.</speak>

<info>It laughs and rolls away. Leela sniffs her wrist and the lights 
go out. Everyone gasps. They look through the window and see 
the ship flying away.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, we can live without machines. 
I was in Webelos.</speak>

<info>He salutes. Hermes peels himself from the floor.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Are you mad? Without machines, who will 
feed us and clothe us and compose our 
smooth jazz?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It'll be the end of civilised society.</speak>

<info>He burps and spits.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
In my time, we didn't depend on high-tech 
gadgets like you do. We didn't need 
a mechanical washing unit to wash our 
clothes. We just used a washing machine. 
And look: You don't need an electric 
can-opener to feed yourself. All you 
need is a trusty Swiss Army knife.  
Ow!  <info>(crying)</info> I'm hungry!</speak>

<info>New New York City Street. Mechanical things cause mayhem. Traffic 
lights show red and green, a rocket weaves around all over the 
sky and a taxi stops and shakes its passengers out of the window 
onto the street. A transport tube bends and empties several people 
into the river. Outside Sal's Pizzeria, a dustbin hurls itself 
through the window. An ATM machine takes a man's card and displays 
"It's Mine Now, Buddy" on its screen. The man turns to a suicide 
booth but it closes and won't let him in. He pounds on the door 
with his fist.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
<info>(screaming)</info> Nooo!</speak>

<info>Mom's Friendly Robot Company Factory: Mom's Office. Mom watches 
the mayhem and cackles.</info>

<speak who="IGNER">
Mommy, why are you making civilisation 
collapse?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Oh, I don't know. I guess Mother's Day 
just puts me in a bad mood.</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
Why's that, Ma?</speak>

<info>She sighs and slaps him weakly.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
One Mother's Day, 70 years ago, the 
only man I ever loved walked out on 
me. Some snot-eating bastards say it 
made me a bitter woman.</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
Gee, Ma. You're not a bitter -</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Cram it, ape!  <info>(talking)</info> 
I haven't seen that magnificent stallion 
since the day he left. But if I ever 
see him again, I swear I'll jam a squirrel 
in him.</speak>

<info>She throws the picture frame across the room. It hits a wall 
and shatters. The photo inside is off Professor Farnsworth. Walt, 
Larry and Igner look at it.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
Hmm!</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
Hmm!</speak>

<speak who="IGNER">
Huh?</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The crew sit huddled around a 
campfire as Fry continues to bang the tin on the floor, trying 
to open it. Leela snatches it from him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(defeated)</info> Zoidberg.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg used his claws to cut the tin open.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hooray! I'm useful! I'm having a wonderful 
time!</speak>

<info>Amy stands up.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
What happens if the fire goes out?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
We'll go across the street to Pottery 
Barn and steal their fire.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
We could use my new invention: A pointy 
rock tied to a stick.</speak>

<info>The door opens and Mom's sons walk in.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Outsiders!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Defend the fire!</speak>

<speak who="WALT">
We've come for you!</speak>

<info>He points at Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wha?  W-What do you want from me?</speak>

<speak who="WALT">
We want you to get back together with 
Mom. Please. It's the only way to make 
her happy again.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
W-W-Wait. You mean, you, and Mom?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Played pelvic pinochle? I'm afraid so.</speak>

<info>The others gasp.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Eck.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It's a humiliating story that I hope 
never to tell. Well, pull up a chair.</speak>

<info>Flashback. Farnsworth is working in a lab with lots of coloured 
liquids swirling around tubes above him.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(voice-over)</info> Our paths first crossed 
when I was a researcher at Mom's Friendly 
Robot Company.  The moment our eyes 
met, we knew we'd be going at it like 
woodchucks.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth doesn't notice that he is pouring too much of a liquid 
into another. The solution explodes and he faints. Later, Farnsworth 
and Mom ride a hover-bike down a country road to Raindrops Keep 
Falling On My Head. Mom laughs.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(voice-over)</info> She was my first love - 
or at least the earliest one I can still 
remember. But then, 70 years ago today...</speak>

<info>Farnsworth walks into Mom's office holding something.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news, Mom. I've invented a new 
children's toy.  I call it "Q.T. McWhiskers"! 
When you pet it, it shoots rainbows 
from its eyes.</speak>

<info>He strokes it.</info>

<speak who="Q.T. MCWHISKERS">
Meow.</speak>

<info>It projects rainbows onto Farnsworth and Mom's foreheads.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Wonderful, Hubie. We'll build them 8 
feet tall and replace the rainbow with 
a neutron laser. We'll make billions 
on the intergalactic arms market!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
But things 8 feet tall aren't cute! 
That's why my Colossal Tammy Tinkle 
Doll was such a failure. Oh, you don't 
understand me. We're finished!</speak>

<info>He runs out of the room, crying. Mom used the toy's rainbow 
to light a cigarette.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
She never got over it, Professor. Hell 
hath no fury like the vast robot armies 
of a woman scorned.</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
She commands them with a remote control 
she keeps in her...<info>(whispering)</info> bra.</speak>

<speak who="IGNER">
But if the glasses man makes up with 
Mommy, she'll be happy and stop the 
scary robots.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Make up with her? After she went all 
psycho when I thought everything was 
cool? Impossible!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, the TV's getting away!</speak>

<info>Leela throws a rock at it. It falls over and turns itself on. 
More news.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
And that's why the third graders at 
PS139 are Morbo's Vermin Of The Week.</speak>

<info>Linda chuckles.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
In actual news, the human race was 
doomed to extinction today as the robot 
revolt turned violent.</speak>

<info>The picture cuts to cars crashing into each other, Robo-Rooter 
and Fender shooting lasers and a huge Q.T. McWhiskers demolishing 
buildings with its neutron laser.</info>

<speak who="Q.T. MCWHISKERS">
Meow!</speak>

<info>Cut to: New New York City Street. People flee as Destructor 
pounds a building with his fists. DOOP soldiers hit his legs 
with rakes. Bender runs out of the Natural History Museum with 
a dinosaur head and laughs.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Meeting Room.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wait. Didn't you say Mom keeps the robot 
control in her bra?</speak>

<info>Larry gestures her to keep it down.</info>

<speak who="LARRY">
<info>(whispering)</info> Bra.</speak>

<info>Walt slaps him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Professor, you don't have to get back 
together with Mom. You just have to 
seduce her, get her bra off, and use 
the remote to deactivate the robots.</speak>

<speak who="WALT">
That's so filthy, it just might work.</speak>

<speak who="IGNER">
The man is going to touch Mommy?</speak>

<info>He shakes and squeaks. Farnsworth shudders.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The thought of caressing that leathery 
hide makes the tapioca rise in my gullet.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Professor, please. The fate of the world 
depends on you getting to second base 
with Mom.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Very well. If cop a feel I must, then 
cop a feel I shall!</speak>

<info>He tears open his shirt, revealing a medallion underneath. Igner 
squeaks again.</info>

<info>New New York City Street. The robots cheer and a rocket crashes 
through a building. Morbo and Linda's cameras hold them up and 
Morbo hands over his wallet and growls. A fire engine chases 
six firefighters down the street, spraying water at them.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The Planet Express crew are sat 
around the campfire again.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
For this demonstration, I have placed 
one of Mother's bras on Igner.  The 
robot controller is nestled here in 
the left cup.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Never fear. My magic fingers still know 
how to do their stuff!</speak>

<info>He flexes his fingers and they crack and curl up.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
To escape the robot death squads, we'll 
take Mother to her rustic cabin in the 
Bronx.</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
You can get there using this precious, 
non-computerised map.</speak>

<info>He hands Leela a map, annotated with labels such as "Here There 
Be Tysers", "Isle of Rikers", "Cloakwood Forest" and "Unknown 
Territories". Mom's cabin is to the north-east of the Isle of 
Rikers and the path they have to take leads them through pretty 
much every section of the map. Leela picks up a torch.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Leela bring fire?</speak>

<speak who="WALT">
No. We're set for fire, thanks.</speak>

<info>Amy looks at the map.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
The professor can't walk all the way 
to the Bronx. How are we gonna get there 
without a hover-car?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait. In my time, we had a way of moving 
things long distances without hovering.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Impossible!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It was called...let me think. It was 
really famous - Ruth Gordon had one. 
The wheel!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Never heard of it.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Show us this, "the wheel".</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Fry hammers something together and wipes 
the sweat from his brow.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
There. Finished!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Sweet!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Wow!</speak>

<info>The others "ooh". Fry has built a wooden cart with oval wheels.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wouldn't it work better if the wheels 
were round?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(snappy)</info> It's my invention, we do it 
my way! Now all we need is something 
to pull it and we're set!</speak>

<info>The Bronx. Fry is pulling the cart and the others are sat on 
it. Leela whips him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Heyya!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow!</speak>

<info>They reach Mom's cabin. Walt, Larry and Igner run out from behind 
some bushes.</info>

<speak who="WALT">
Hurry! The robots have taken Suffolk 
County!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm ready to seduce. I'm wearing my 
kissing dentures and my evening truss.</speak>

<speak who="LARRY">
Here. Give her these.</speak>

<info>He hands him some flowers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
And if that doesn't work, I got you 
a six-pack of champagne and a funnel.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Farnsworth trots up to the front door while the 
others watch from behind the bushes. Farnsworth knocks on the 
door and Mom opens it.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Who the sweaty hell is it?  Hubert Farnsworth?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth puts his foot in the door.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I was out fleeing some robots and the 
silvery moonlight glinting off their 
bloody claws made me think of you.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
It's been a long time. You pus-dripping 
sack of double-smoked butt jerky!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Uh-huh. May I come in?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Never!</speak>

<info>She tries to slam the door on him but it just hits his foot. 
He screams in pain. The others watch.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Is this what human mating looks like? 
Because I like it!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Move your freaking hoof, 
you goat!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Here, I brought you these.</speak>

<info>He hands her the flowers.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Oh, daffodils. 70 years and you remembered 
my favourite flower.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You favourite what? Why does my foot 
hurt?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Won't you come in?</speak>

<info>The others watch as he walks in and gives them a thumbs-up.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yes!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Cabin Lounge. She closes the door.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
You broke my heart, Hubert.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
And you broke mine. Granted, that was 
four or five hearts ago.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
So what have you been up to all these 
years?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, inventing, sending delivery crews 
to their doom, breeding atomic monsters.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Honestly, Hubert. You and your atomic 
monsters.  Your eyes always were the 
most beautiful shade of milky-white.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
And your skin still dangles so gracefully 
from your neck.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Darling Hubie, I should never have tried 
to tangle with that cute little Q. T. 
McWhiskers.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No, it was silly of me to object. One 
foot tall, eight feet, 15 feet; what 
does it matter?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
You should see the new 16-foot models.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth pulls his hands away.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
16 feet? Go to hell! I was a fool to 
think you'd changed, you old bat!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Filthy, toothless nerd bastard!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(shouting)</info> Damned she-fossil!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Stink pig!</speak>

<info>The grab each other and kiss. She takes off his lab coat and 
he takes off her jumpsuit. He starts fiddling with her bra.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(thinking)</info> Here we go. Just unhook it 
and get the remote. So many hooks!  
Come on, Farnsworth. Drat, the first 
one's back on again! I give up! Wait! 
Victory!  Oh, my. Now I'll just...the 
remote...I'll just... <info>(talking)</info> Oh, 
my.</speak>

<info>He throws the bra aside and they lie down on the couch.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Mom's Cabin.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm worried. It shouldn't take this 
long to get to second base.</speak>

<info>They hear crashing and turn around. A group of robots that includes 
the Clearcutter, a Slurm dispenser, the Masked Unit and a Titanic 
securitybot crash through some trees.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Land robots!</speak>

<speak who="SLURM MACHINE">
I've got a big, big thirst for human 
blood!</speak>

<info>The others scream and run into the cabin.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Cabin Lounge. Mom and Farnsworth are no longer 
there.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Where in funkytown is the professor?</speak>

<info>Fry opens a door.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Cabin Bedroom.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Nothing in here but a couple of elephant 
skin rugs.</speak>

<info>He gasps. The others rush in and gasp. Farnsworth and Mom's 
clothes are scattered across the floor and their dentures are 
in glasses on the table. They, meanwhile, are on the bed.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, yes.</speak>

<info>The robots bang on the wall.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
<info>(from outside)</info> They're inside! Get 'em!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
I suppose I should switch of the robots 
before they ruin this wonderful romantic 
evening. Everyone, help Mom find her 
bra.</speak>

<info>Everyone crawls around the floor hunting for it. Igner picks 
up a pair of her underpants and squirms.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Mom's Cabin. The robots use the Slurm machine 
to try and break down the wall.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Cabin Bedroom.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
There it is!</speak>

<info>He points at the ceiling fan, where the bra hangs. He tries 
to jump for it but the ceiling fan raises itself. It laughs.</info>

<speak who="CEILING FAN">
Fan beats man!</speak>

<info>Fry growls.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Is anything not a robot?</speak>

<speak who="LAMP">
I'm not a robot.</speak>

<info>Enter Bender and the greeting card via the chimney. Bender wheezes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright, greeting card, I'll grab the 
cash, you wreck up the place. And - 
huh?</speak>

<info>He sees the others.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
You, bending unit. Mommy needs that 
bra to end the robot rebellion. Stretch 
up and get it for me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sorry, Ma, but you ordered me to rebel. 
And loot I shall! Ooh! A six-pack of 
strawberry champagne. Don't mind if 
I help myself!</speak>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
No, Comrade Bender. Liquor is the opiate 
of the human bourgeoisie.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Say what?</speak>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
In the glorious robot workers' paradise, 
there will be no liquor. Only efficient 
synthetic fuels.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No liquor? Do svidaniya, comrade!</speak>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
No!</speak>

<info>It squeals as Bender tears it up and its music dies away. The 
robots carry on trying to break down the wall.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hurry, Bender. Get the bra!</speak>

<info>Bender stretches up to the fan.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
OK, fan. Just hold still and let me 
just - whoa!</speak>

<info>He holds onto the fan and it spins round and round with him 
still attached. The robots break through and everyone screams.</info>

<speak who="SLURM MACHINE">
Death to all humans!  Free soda for 
all humans!</speak>

<info>It dispenses some cans of Slurm and everyone cheers. Bender 
knocks back the strawberry champagne all at once. Farnsworth 
and Mom kiss.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I love you, Mom. Let's grow ancient 
together.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Way to go, Professor. The plan worked.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Plan? What plan? I thought this was 
a spontaneous whirlwind of hot, dry 
sex.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Look: It started out as a calculated 
plot to rummage through your underwear. 
But once I got in there, I found more 
- much more. And now I want to shout 
our love from the rooftops. Perhaps 
I'll breed some sort of albino shouting 
gorilla.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
<info>(shouting)</info> Get out of my house, you 
lying scum pile. I never want to see 
you again.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
But, dustcakes...</speak>

<info>She throws the remote at him and he sighs. He drops the pillow 
and walks out.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The staff clear up after the rebellion. 
Fry puts the TV back and Amy sweeps up. Hermes clears some rubbish 
off the coffee table and Bender walks in.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, time for this robot to get back 
to work.</speak>

<info>He sits in his crevice on the couch and turns the TV on. Farnsworth 
sits sadly at the table.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Too bad it didn't work out with Mom, 
professor.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes. But I'll always love her in my 
own subtle way.</speak>

<info>He takes a remote control out of his lab coat and presses a 
button.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Roof. Six albino gorillas sit on the 
roof.</info>

<speak who="GORILLAS">
<info>(shouting)</info> Love Mom! Love Mom! Love 
Mom! Love Mom!</speak>

<info>THE END</info>

<info>Over the credits there is a scene of Bender and the greeting 
card outside Mom's factory.</info>

<speak who="GREETING CARD">
You created me, Mom

So I guess you're to blame

For the love that I feel

Just from hearing your name

You're as tender as corned beef

And warm as pastrami

</speak><info>It plays a tune.</info>

I wuv my Mommy.</xml>