<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 306

<title>BENDLESS LOVE</title>

<author>Eric Horsted</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Torn From Tomorrow's Headlines.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. The hangar doors are open and the launching 
mechanism raises the ship into the launch position.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. The crew are sat at their stations.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Guidance system?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Online.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Autopilot?</speak>

<speak who="AUTOPILOT">
Present.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dark matter indicator?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Making the noise.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
All systems operational. Let's rock!</speak>

<info>She pushes the gear lever forward.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Hangar. The engines fire up.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. The ship takes off and the engines 
suddenly shut down. The ship falls onto the road and the landing 
gear pops out. Motorists honk their horns as the crashed ship 
causes a traffic jam.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Fry, Bender, Zoidberg and Hermes 
sit around the table. Leela stands holding a thick folder.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Gentlemen, I've completed my report 
on the crash.</speak>

<info>She drops the thick file onto the table and everyone stares 
at it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Whoa! I'm not reading that crap. Summarise 
it in one word.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Sabotage.  This is a normal L-unit. 
Without it, space travel is but the 
fevered dream of a madman.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yep.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Of course.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Doy!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
It's an important unit.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And this, my friends, is the L-unit 
I just removed from the ship.</speak>

<info>She pulls a sheet off an L-unit. It is straight. Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That doesn't look like an "L" at all. 
Unless you count lowercase.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You know we don't!</speak>

<info>He slaps Fry and he groans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Whoever did this was strong. This is 
340 pounds of Tonka-tough steel.</speak>

<info>Bender stands at her side and picks up the L-unit.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hmm. It should look like this.  But 
instead it looks like this.</speak>

<info>He straightens it again.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Who would do a thing like that?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Who could do a thing like that? And 
by "that", I mean this.</speak>

<info>He bends the L-unit back and forth repeatedly.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Well, gang, it looks like we have another 
mystery on our hands.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I'd better make a chart of the suspects. 
I'll begin by drawing a line with my 
straight-edge.  Sweet lampre of Santa 
Fe! My edge has been bent!</speak>

<info>Amy walks in wearing Mars University sweats.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(crying)</info> My javelin too! It's ruined. 
Now we'll never beat Jupiter State.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
My slinky!  My cuddly, little pet slinky!</speak>

<info>He cries. Farnsworth walks in. He has been bent forward so his 
back is horizontal and his face is pointing downwards.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
What's all the hubbub?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
My God! Even the Professor's been bent.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
That you for your sympathy, talking 
square of linoleum.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll get you fixed up.  That's fine.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Wait a minute. Bender? What did you 
just do to the Professor?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I bent him.</speak>

<info>More gasps.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Aha!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Bender!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
J'accuse!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, I see. A bunch of stuff gets bent 
so it must be the robot designed for 
bending.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I know how to settle this: We'll check 
last night's surveillance tapes.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Huh?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
What tapes?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Surveillance?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You've seen me naked?</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Surveillance Room. Hermes presses a button and 
a panel in the wall slides up, revealing several screens and 
rows of tapes. Hermes runs his finger across the tapes.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Ah. Last night's tape. It was right 
next to Bathroom Bloopers 4.</speak>

<info>Bender takes the tape and puts it in the VCR. On the screen 
Farnsworth snores in his apartment lounge. Owls wander out of 
an owl hole and start pecking the floor.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
See? Nothing. Told you, losers.</speak>

<info>Bender walks in on the screen with his arms outstretched.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait! There on the screen. It's that 
guy you are.</speak>

<info>Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm sleepwalking.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth watches a little TV monitor attached to his head.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dear God! We've got robots on the ceiling.</speak>

<info>On the screen Bender mumbles in his sleep. He bends a column 
and the staff gasp. Then he bends a sofa cushion, a plant and 
eventually Farnsworth, who groans but remains asleep. Bender 
turns around and bends the camera. The picture cuts to static.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You weren't sleepwalking. You were sleep-bending!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
This is quite a shock. On the other 
hand, it's not surprising in the least. 
After all, I've been bending since the 
day I was built.</speak>

<info>Flashback. Large robotic arms assemble a bending unit on a conveyor 
belt.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(voice-over)</info> I was born on an assembly 
line in the bad part of Tijuana.</speak>

<info>A robotic arm selects a bending unit head from a box filled 
with other robot heads, including Flexo's. It screws the head 
onto the body and Bender opens his eyes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mama.  Hooray! I graduated! Time to 
bend around Europe for a few months, 
then get a job bending.</speak>

<info>He bends his diploma.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
You remember your own birth?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sure. It was only four years ago.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You're only four years old?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Precocious little scamp, ain't I?</speak>

<info>He takes a puff from a cigar.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hmm. Bender must have a pent-up need 
to bend that's not being satisfied by 
his bend-free lifestyle.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Then he can't stay here. He's a menace 
to every straight person in the company. 
Go satisfy your bend lust and don't 
you come back to work until you do.</speak>

<info>He puts his hand up and tips backwards.</info>

<info>Outside Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. Robots have formed a picket 
line outside.</info>

<speak who="ROBOTS">
<info>(chanting)</info> No more bending, no more 
work. Give us a raise, you big fat jerk.</speak>

<info>Sal leans out of a window.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
<info>(shouting)</info> Nevers!</speak>

<info>A car pulls up next to the robots and Joey Mouse Pad leans out. 
He whistles to them.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
Yo! The Mafia supports you. But don't 
tell no one. Spread the word.</speak>

<info>He leans back in.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mafiabot Car. Clamps and Donbot are with Joey.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
As the duly-elected mobsters of this 
union, it's our duty to support the 
struggle of these proud, lazy slobs.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
Yeah, but what if management remains 
intragnizent?</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
From the context it is clear what you 
mean. In that case, Clamps may have 
a little surprise for them.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
The clamps!  <info>(unsure)</info> Right?</speak>

<info>Donbot nods and Clamps laughs maniacally.</info>

<info>Outside Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. Bender arrives and sees 
the robots.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw, no! A strike? Now I'll never get 
to bend anything. Oh, woe is Bender.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
Hang tough, brother. Management refused 
our demand to switch casual Friday to 
Monday.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What?!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
And now they're hiring scabs at ten- 
times the normal wage.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ten-times normal wage?  I'll give those 
jerks what for!</speak>

<info>He walks straight through the fence towards the factory and 
the robots cheer him on.</info>

<info>Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. Bender shakes Sal's hand.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
Welcomes aboard, scab.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Great to be here.</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
Come on. I'll introduces you to your 
scab co-workers you'll be scabbing with. 
This heres our scab foreman.</speak>

<info>The bending unit turns around.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Flexo?</speak>

<speak who="FLEXO">
Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, sorry you got sent to that South 
American Turkish prison instead of me 
on account of mistaken identity.</speak>

<speak who="FLEXO">
You bastard! They treated me like an 
animal and that's what I became!  Nah, 
you're alright. Good to see you, buddy!</speak>

<info>They high-five.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
And heres another scab what also works 
here: Angleyne.</speak>

<info>Bender gasps and stares at the Fembot, blurry eyed. She is thin 
and has blonde hair.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Hello.</speak>

<info>Angleyne smiles.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
Hey, yous guyses wanna move that things?</speak>

<info>Robots move a pane of frosted glass from in front of Angleyne, 
revealing her to be more heavily-built than Bender thought.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(more sexfully)</info> Hello!</speak>

<info>Angleyne laughs croakily then coughs.</info>

<info>Outside Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. The robots still march 
and chant.</info>

<speak who="ROBOTS">
<info>(chanting)</info> Give us a raise you big fat 
jerk.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. A girder drops into Flexo's 
hands.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
<info>(from outside)</info> Nevers!</speak>

<info>Flexo bends the girder and moves it aside. Bender stands in 
front of him and bends a girder. Angleyne bends wires into wire 
coat hangers. Bender gazes at her and sighs. A girder hits him 
on the head.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ow!  Um. Hi, Angleyne. Whatcha up to?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Making hangers. Guidance counsellor 
said I had a knack for it.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's cool, that's cool. So, um, uh, 
I was wondering if, y'know, it's cool 
if not, but, what are you doing after 
work?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
What I always do. Jack squat.</speak>

<info>Bender chuckles.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Me too.  Man, we have a lot in common, 
huh?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well we are made of virtually identical 
components.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Are you sure? Maybe I should 
sneak a peek at your access panel.</speak>

<info>Angleyne holds up a leaflet.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Hey, according to the scab handbook 
that's extremely inappropriate banter. 
<info>(sexfully)</info> And that's just the way I 
like it.</speak>

<info>Bender smiles.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Hermes tries to straighten his straight 
edge. Behind him the ship is a battered mess.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Haile H. Selassie!</speak>

<info>He bends it straight. Beside him, Zoidberg has re-curled his 
slinky, though it doesn't really look right.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
There, little friend. Good as new.</speak>

<info>He strokes it and puts it atop a pile of books he has arranged 
like stairs. He nudges the slinky and it flops down the books 
and bursts into flames. Zoidberg groans and bursts into tears.</info>

<info>New New York City Street. Fry and Farnsworth walk down the rough 
street. Farnsworth is looking upwards and doesn't notice how 
bad the street and its inhabitants are.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
What an exquisite day. That azure sky, 
the verdant treetops.  Those delightful 
birds with their chirp, chirp, chirp 
and their tweet, tweet, splat.</speak>

<info>They pass a dog leaving its mark on a fire hydrant and two hookers 
wearing jet packs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Professor, I've never seen you so cheerful. 
What the hell's wrong with you?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hmm. I'm not quite sure. Perhaps seeing 
things from a new perspective has reminded 
me of life's beauty. Or perhaps my new 
posture is causing blood to pool in 
the back of my brain, resulting in a 
mild delirium. Incidentally, you have 
a dime up your nose.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I wish! It's a nickel.</speak>

<info>Outside Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. A new day dawns and Bender 
passes the picket line wearing a hardhat and carrying a lunchbox. 
He waves his fist.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Union forever! Lousy scabs! They can't 
do those things! Et cetera!</speak>

<info>Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I bet watching me bend girders like 
this turns your legs all rubbery.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well my legs are made of rubber.  And 
anyway, I am just as strong as you are, 
Mac.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, yeah?  Prove it.  Here, let me help 
you.</speak>

<info>He puts his arms around her and together they bend the girder 
into a heart shape. A few bars of Unchained Melody play as they 
gaze into each other's eyes. They lean in and kiss, and sparks 
fly.</info>

<info>Montage: Bender and Angleyne date to American Breed's Bend Me, 
Shape Me. At a fairground stall, Bender tries to knock down a 
pile of bottles with a ball but repeatedly misses. Angleyne looks 
away in dismay so Bender throws the ball at the man in the stall, 
knocking him out. He takes a big stuffed pig and gives it to 
Angleyne then steals the man's wallet and they run off. Later, 
they enjoy a boat ride on a lake. Bender's detached arms row 
the boat and he and Angleyne cuddle. Still later, they ride a 
tandem through the park. Fry scoots alongside them using the 
Professor as a bicycle and Hermes and Zoidberg hold some tape 
at the finish line. Fry and Farnsworth get ahead and Bender takes 
a stick out of his chest cabinet and puts it between the spokes 
of Farnsworth's wheel, causing him and Fry to fly through the 
air. They land in a lake and Bender laughs as he and Angleyne 
cut through the tape.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Farnsworth, Leela, Fry, Zoidberg, 
Amy and Hermes sit around the table. For some reason everyone 
except Farnsworth is tied to their chair and Leela's ponytail 
points to her right.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
My new bent outlook has completely re-energised 
me. I'm even dating a young Brazilian 
retired actress.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright!</speak>

<info>Amy cheers.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Some say I'm robbing the cradle but 
I say she's robbing the grave.</speak>

<info>Bender wanders in sideways. It turns out the meeting table has 
been stuck to the wall so Farnsworth can see everyone eye-to-eye.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Howdy, doodies. What's new?</speak>

<info>He uses his suction feet to walk up the wall and sit in an empty 
chair.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I was just regaling your former co-workers 
with a tale of bedroom antics, the likes 
of which--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah, yeah! Big whoop! No-one cares. 
I got Bender-related news. I'm in love 
and I'm taking all my friends out to 
celebrate.</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Let's get liquored up!</speak>

<info>Bender walks down to the floor and everyone else falls out of 
their seats and land in a pile on the floor.</info>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The evening's special is blackened leftovers. 
The crew sit around a table and Farnsworth leans against it with 
his legs behind him.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey, look at this crowd. You guys gotta 
try the pasta. It's got a real nice 
profit margin. Bam! So, special occasion 
tonight?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, Elzar, you'll never guess what's 
happened?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Bam?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I met the most dynamite ladybot.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey, that's terrific. To celebrate, 
I'm gonna stick seven copies of my latest 
cookbook on your bill.</speak>

<info>He holds up his book, Three More Recipes and leaves.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Bless you, sir.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
So, Bender, tell us about this new girlfriend 
of yours.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I intend to. Through the lost art of 
the toast.  To Angleyne, she's got it 
all. Looks, charm and the love of a 
fabulous bending robot.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
She sure does.</speak>

<info>He points across the room. Bender turns and gasps. Flexo and 
Angleyne sit at a table laughing.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Flexo!</speak>

<info>He picks up a baguette and tries to break it. Elzar walks past 
at the back of the room.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
<info>(shouting)</info> Careful, that's a week old!</speak>

<info>Bender grunts and the stick breaks, then his arms fall off. 
He reattaches them and mutters to himself.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I finally meet a nice girl with a pair 
of legs that don't quit unexpectedly 
and that jerk Flexo steals her away? 
It's time to kick some shiny, metal 
ass.  You degenerate hussy! I'm disappointed 
in you too, Angleyne.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Bender, it's-it's not what you think.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, God! Then it's worse than I think.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Now look, there is no reason to be upset. 
Flexo and I are divorced.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Div-- Huh?</speak>

<speak who="FLEXO">
We're just havin' dinner 'cause we wanna 
stay friends.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, I knew that. What I'm actually outraged 
by is your choice of wine. Really, it's 
the steward's fault.</speak>

<info>He smacks a passing steward.</info>

<speak who="STEWARD">
Excellent choice, sir.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Bender paces backwards and forwards 
muttering to himself. Fry and Leela sit on the couch and Farnsworth 
leans against it. Leela reads a book.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(muttering)</info> That Flexo, I'm knockin' 
him right on his butt. I can't believe 
this.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Obsessing won't help, Bender. Take a 
lean back and enjoy life.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I can't. My Fembot may be in love with 
another Manbot.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well talk to her. Tell her about your 
feelings in an open an honest way.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah. Either that or be a man.</speak>

<info>Fry's and Bender's Lounge. At dusk, Bender paces around the 
apartment while Fry trims a plant into the shape of the Planet 
Express ship.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
OK, I've constructed an elaborate lie: 
I'll call Angleyne while pretending 
to be Flexo, arrange a date, show up 
disguised as him and catch her two-timing 
me with myself.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's thinkin' like a man.</speak>

<info>Bender picks up the phone and dials.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(disguised voice)</info> Hello? This is Flexo.</speak>

<info>Outside The Hip Joint. A taxi flies towards the club and Bender 
gets out. It's Robot Nite and designated device drivers drink 
free. Bender opens his chest cabient and sticks a goatee to his 
chin.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now we'll see who loves whom.</speak>

<info>He cackles and walks in.</info>

<info>Cut to: The Hip Joint. Bender looks around and sees Angleyne 
at the bar.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, hot stuff.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Hey, Flexo.  So since when do you go 
to bars on work nights? It's not like 
you at all.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nonsense. It's exactly like me. Flexo: 
The fun loving love machine Fembots 
love to love. Hey, barkeep, I'll have 
a Fuzzy Navel and she'll have the girliest 
drink in the house.</speak>

<speak who="BARTENDERBOT">
Two Fuzzy Navel's comin' up.</speak>

<info>Bender takes a wad of cash out of his chest cabinet.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I hope they can make change for a fortune.</speak>

<info>He tosses the cash over the bar. On the other side of the bar 
the Mafiabots watch him.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
Yo. Get an eyeload of that filty scab 
with the beard flashing his filthy scab 
money. It's an insult to you, boss.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Yeah. That cash oughta be slushin' my 
fund and kicksing my back.</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
I'm greasing up my whoozits!</speak>

<info>He squirts oil on his clamps.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Whoa, whoa, Clamps, not yet. Let's just 
keep an eye on him and see if he does 
it a couple more times.</speak>

<info>Bender and Angleyne drink.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You're lookin' good to Flexo tonight.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Quit makin' with the googly eyes. You 
know that I'm in love with Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Bender? That walking wuss factory?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well he may be a walking factory but 
believe me he is no wuss. Now look. 
You and me are through. I told you that 
when I divorced you.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But going through a divorce together, 
you can't tell me that didn't bring 
us closer. Care to dance?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
You know I love dancing but you always 
hated it.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
In that case it's something I've always 
wanted to make up to you.  Hey, scratchmo. 
How 'bout dropping me and the lady some 
rump-rattling beats?</speak>

<info>He takes out his cash and throws it at the DJbot. The Mafiabots 
watch.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
I had hoped that by the second time 
he flashed his cash my rage would have 
subsided. Sadly that has not happened.</speak>

<info>Clamps sharpens his clamps. Bender and Angleyne dance with the 
other robots.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
You used to be so inflexible, Flexo. 
You have really loosened up!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I recently upgraded my funk card. C'mon!</speak>

<info>He dances.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Alright!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
C'mon now, what's new!  Ew!</speak>

<info>He wipes it on his casing.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Flexo? What-What's going on?</speak>

<info>Bender laughs weakly and puts the goatee back on his face.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Um...</speak>

<info>He grabs Angleyne and tilts her back and she laughs.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Flexo!</speak>

<info>The robots dancing on the platforms start to fall apart and 
they rain on Bender and Angleyne.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Bender and Angleyne sit at a table as the janitor 
sweeps the robot parts off the empty floor.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
So the moral of the story is: If you 
want it to stay sunk, tie a weight to 
it!</speak>

<info>They laugh.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
<info>(laughing)</info> You always were a kick in 
the teeth, man.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw, shucks, thunder-buns! You make me 
feel like a million volts.</speak>

<info>Angleyne sighs and stirs her finger around the rim of her glass.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Flexo, Flexo, Flexo. I'm starting to 
remember why I fell for you in the first 
place.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(thinking)</info> So, she's falling for Flexo, 
eh? I'd better seduce her a little more, 
just to be sure.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well, it's late. I should get home to 
my trailer.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll walk you out. After all, a true 
gentleman tends to his date's every 
need.  Tiparillo?</speak>

<info>Outside The Hip Joint. Bender and Angleyne walk out smoking 
their cigars. Bender hands a valet some money.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Here you are, my lad. Bring the lady's 
car around in the finest way possible.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Mafiabot Car. The mobbots watch.</info>

<speak who="JOEY">
He's flashin' his cash loaf again.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
How many times is that? Two or three?</speak>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Three.</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Alright. That's the necessary number 
of times. That scab's gonna have a little 
on-the-job accident.</speak>

<speak who="JOEY">
With all due respect, Donbot, I don't 
think we should rely on an accident 
happening. Let's kill him ourselves.</speak>

<info>Donbot groans.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside The Hip Joint. Angleyne stands by her car.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well, goodnight. I-I had a great time.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
How 'bout a lift? To your place.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
What?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Admit it. You felt something for me 
tonight. And by me I mean Flexo.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Hey look, I had fun but--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
But--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Buuut?</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
<info>(gasping)</info> But...  Huh? Bender! You tricked 
me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's right, baby. I ain't your lover 
boy, Flexo, the guy you love so much. 
You even love anybody pretending to 
be him.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Well maybe I love you so much I love 
you no matter who you're pretending 
to be.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, how I wish I could believe or understand 
that! There's only one reasonable course 
of action now: Kill Flexo.  Ow!</speak>

<info>He takes Angleyne's car and flies away. She runs after him to 
the edge of the platform.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
<info>(screaming)</info> Nooo!</speak>

<info>Curvetti Bros. Bending Plant. Flexo hums as he bends girders. 
Bender walks in and pushes Flexo.</info>

<speak who="FLEXO">
Thanks, I appreciate that.  Nah, I'm 
joshing you. That was quite annoying.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You call yourself divorced? You're making 
a mockery of one of our oldest institutions.</speak>

<speak who="FLEXO">
What?</speak>

<info>Bender punches him and they start fighting. In a control room 
above, the mobbots watch. Clamps operates a set of controls that 
hold a huge unbendable girder above the factory floor.</info>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Alright, boss, give the word and I'll 
drop this unbendable girder. Clamp, 
clamp, ka-bamp!</speak>

<speak who="DONBOT">
Remember, only kill the one with the 
beard. That other filthy scab we got 
nothing against.</speak>

<info>Clamps moves the girder and Flexo pushes Bender against a wall. 
Bender opens Flexo's door and punches the roof of his chest cabinet. 
Flexo groans.</info>

<speak who="FLEXO">
That's low!</speak>

<info>Angleyne runs around the corner.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Please stop! I'm not worth it!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Probably not. But I love you And I'm 
gonna kick his ass 'til I win you back.</speak>

<info>He pushes Flexo into the middle of the room and Clamps moves 
the girder again. Flexo starts choking Bender.</info>

<speak who="DONBOT">
<info>(from control room)</info> OK, Clamps. Now!</speak>

<info>The girder drops and Bender and Flexo fall to the floor. Angleyne 
screams and the mobbots look through the window.</info>

<speak who="CLAMPS">
Ooh, that's gotta clamp!</speak>

<info>Flexo has been crushed under the girder. Angleyne kneels by 
him.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
Flexo? Are you OK?</speak>

<speak who="FLEXO">
Yeah, never better.  Nah, I'm yankin' 
your chain, I'm dying.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
You can't die. Tonight Bender showed 
me that I love you.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But, I love you.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
I know and I care for you too. But I 
could never love anyone as much as you 
made me realise I love Flexo.</speak>

<info>She hugs Flexo and cries.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
But ... but ...  I love you so much, 
Angleyne, I want you to be happy no 
matter what.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
What, what are you saying?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm saying I've got an unbendable girder 
to bend.</speak>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
You can't bend that girder. It's unbendable!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well I don't know anything about lifting, 
so that just leaves us the one option.</speak>

<info>He grunts as he tries to bend the girder. He stops and takes 
some BENDGAY out of his chest cabinet. He rubs it on his hands 
and arms and tries bending again. Oil dribbles down his forehead, 
his door pops off and his antenna explodes but he finally manages 
to bend the girder away from Flexo's head. Flexo waddles out 
from under it and shakes Bender's hand.</info>

<speak who="FLEXO">
Thanks, buddy. Another year under that 
and I'd have been a goner.</speak>

<info>Angleyne hugs Bender.</info>

<speak who="ANGLEYNE">
I'll always remember this, Bender.</speak>

<info>She hugs Flexo and Bender wipes a tear away from his eye.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> Me too. Me too. <info>(talking)</info> Jerk.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The staff sit around the table.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
So Flexo and Angleyne had sex right 
there on the factory floor? Well, at 
least you got bending out of your system.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes. I won't be up to bending again 
for a long, long time.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Perhaps it's your outlook that needs 
a good bend. A 90-degree bend to a place 
where happiness is perpendicular to 
wonderment.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Professor, we're all sick of your upbeat 
attitude.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I'll say.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Believe it.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Nonsense. It's just like in the song 
I wrote:

<info>(singing)</info> We all need a new angle on life,

You gotta bend away all your trouble and your strife,

</speak><info>Leela sighs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, you've gotta help us.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I try to get out but they keep pulling 
me back in.</speak>

<info>He stands up and rolls up his sleeves.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(singing)</info> You gotta dangle,

Have a new angle,

Wangle a new dangle on life.

</speak><info>Bender bends him and he screams. He has bent right over backwards.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
No, Bender! The other way.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I like him better this way.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm sad now.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Eh, it's fine.</speak>

<info>THE END</info>
</xml>