<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 307

<title>THE DAY THE EARTH STOOD STUPID</title>

<author>Jeff Westbrook &amp; David X. Cohen</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: 80% Entertainment By Volume.</info>

<info>A planet, Tweenis 12 hangs in the void of space. Glowing cracks 
start to appear on the surface. There are several explosions 
and the planet explodes, the shockwave and debris flying out 
in all directions. A group of glowing, flying brains fly away 
from what is left of the planet. A caption tells us Tweenis 12 
was one day's brain flight from Earth.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. The Planet Express staff are at a pet show. 
There are stalls selling cream, Soylent Chow, Kibbles 'n' Snouts 
and flea collars for giant fleas. Leela carries Nibbler and a 
big purple bag over her shoulder.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Is Nibbler stoked for the big pet show?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
He ought to be with all the strict training 
I've been putting him through.  Nibbler: 
Roll over and you get a ham.  Roll over. 
Roll over for the ham.  You are so adorable! 
Who wants a ham?</speak>

<info>He takes it and swallows it whole. Farnsworth reads a pamphlet.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Zooka barooka! First prize is $500 and 
a year's supply of dog food!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">"$500", you say?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">"Dog food", you say?</speak>

<info>He licks his tendrils.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The sheep herding trial has begun. A collie herds 
four sheep into a pen and the staff watch from the bleachers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, that's dog's gonna be hard to beat. 
Look at him bring in the sheep! One 
sheep, two sheep......three sheep.</speak>

<info>He falls asleep on Farnsworth's shoulder. Farnsworth carries 
on eating his popcorn.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
The dog's good, but our real competition 
is the Hypno-Toad.  Your turn, Nibbler, 
honey. Herd those sheep!</speak>

<info>Nibbler scurries towards the bleating sheep and the crew eagerly 
watch.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Come on, Nibbler!</speak>

<info>They cringe as Nibbler eats the sheep. He coughs up the bells.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ma'am, I have a late entry.  My hard-shelled 
wooping terrier, Mr. Zoidberg.</speak>

<info>He whips Zoidberg and he woops. He whips him again and Zoidberg 
woops and waves his claws in the air.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The crowds cheer for Zoidberg and Bender. Zoidberg 
scurries through a tunnel with Bender whipping him as he goes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Faster! Faster.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg woops. He comes out of the tunnel, jumps on to a balance 
beam and somersaults across it. Bender hits him again.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Suck in that gut! You wanna be spayed?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Zoidberg stands on a table and a judge inspects 
him. He looks in his mouth and then tickles his arm. Zoidberg 
laughs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Silence, you cur! Puff out that brisket!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Zoidberg does a Spanish flamenco for the judges 
in the talnt competition and Bender watches from ringside.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I should be weeping! I'm not weeping!</speak>

<info>He chases Zoidberg and the judges look at each other and shrug.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry, Amy and Farnsworth wander around the rest of 
the arena and pass Glab with a unicorn-cat. Fry sees what looks 
like an invisible-dog-leash and laughs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I love these things!</speak>

<info>It's a real invisible dog and it bites Fry's ankle. He screams. 
Nibbler is being inspected by the judge.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Shake paws, Nibbler. Come on, shake. 
He might be a little hungry. Shake, 
boy. Usually he's had more ham by now. 
Shake!</speak>

<info>Nibbler chirps and sees a kid with a pig-shaped balloon. He 
licks his lips and jumps onto the balloon, biting into it. It 
bursts and flies towards the ceiling. Nibbler falls from it and 
lands in a bowl of cream. The cream splashes over people and 
cats jump on them, making the people scream.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The awards ceremony begins.</info>

<speak who="JUDGE #1">
Third prize, a party-sized keg of guinea 
pigs, goes to Dave Spiegel and his owner, 
Fluffers.  Second prize, this lovely 
afghan made from an Afghan, goes to 
Bender and his wooping terrier.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Second place?  That's a fancy word for 
losing.  You didn't stick your landing!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Forgive me, my friend.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Never!</speak>

<info>He whips him again.</info>

<speak who="JUDGE #1">
And before we announce the winner we 
have a special award for a first-time 
contestant: Miss Leela and her mystery 
pet, Nibbler!</speak>

<info>Leela gasps. The crowd applauds.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Me? Award? Him? Me? Good?</speak>

<speak who="JUDGE #1">
That's just the kind of eloquence you'd 
expect from the owner of Dumbest Pet 
in Show.  And the grand prize winner......the 
Hypno-Toad.  All glory to the Hypno-Toad.]</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Most of the staff are sat around 
the conference table. Nibbler is asleep in Leela's arms. She 
sighs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Maybe they're right. Maybe Nibbler is 
dumb.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Don't listen to them, Leela. People 
said I was dumb, but I proved them.</speak>

<info>Enter Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news, everyone. We were supposed 
to make a delivery to the planet Tweenis 
12 but it's been completely destroyed.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Why is that good news?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
They paid in advance.</speak>

<info>Comic twang. Bender bangs his chest.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Excuse me.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
This is mighty strange.  First, the 
civilisation Space Rome collapsed, then 
Don Martin 3 went caflooie and now Tweenis 
12.</speak>

<info>The three holographic planets are replaced with red X's.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Looks like this planet is next in line.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's Earth.  The planet we live on.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'd hate to be those guys.</speak>

<info>Nibbler starts sniffing. He jumps off Leela's lap and starts 
whimpering.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
What's got into him? He's twitching 
like Zoidberg when someone mentions 
the word "food".</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What now?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. Nibbler jumps out of a window.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(shouting)</info> No! Nibbler, come back!</speak>

<info>Alley. Night has fallen. Leela enters the alley carrying another 
joint.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Too bad Nibbler's not around. I guess 
I'll have to eat this raw, dripping 
ham by myself.  Nibbler?  Nibbler, you're 
scaring me.  Nibbler?!  Am I going crazy? 
Have my years of wild hedonism finally 
caught up with me?  Nibbler, help! Don't 
leave me here.  Uh, Nibbler? Could you 
scooch the seat up just a little bit?</speak>

<info>The next morning, the brains fly over New New York, turning 
buildings a glowing blue with some weird rays. Seven brains converge 
on the Planet Express building and turn it blue.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Lounge. Bender sits on the couch mumbling 
and the room glows blue around him. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela back yet?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry, help me! My heart stopped beating!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You don't have a heart; you're a robot.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sure...right. Robot!  Oh, Fry! My skin's 
all dry and clanky.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well, yeah. Robots are made of metal.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Am I a robot?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, if this is some kind of scam, 
I don't get it. You already have my 
power of attorney.</speak>

<info>He walks off towards the meeting room.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry!  My skin!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth has his head between 
the balls of a Newton's Cradle.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ow. Ow. Ow.  I'm a genius. Ow. Ow.</speak>

<info>Fry leaves without saying anything.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Zoidberg's Office. Zoidberg is crouched on the 
examination table. He sticks one of his tendrils out and trys 
to clack it with is claw. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Dr. Zoidberg? Why is everyone acting 
so weird?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Zoidy want balloon! Want balloon now! 
Zoidy want go outside!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(angry)</info> I just let you back in!</speak>

<info>Nibbler's Ship. The ship flies through the vacuum of space. 
The ship is so small that Leela is squashed into the back. The 
whole top section is a transparent dome. Part of Leela's ponytail 
is caught in it and it blows in the wind outside.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
This is unbelievable. I thought you 
were a furry little moron. But here 
you are flying an adorable spaceship. 
If only you could talk.  Wait! I understood 
that!  You say you're transmitting your 
thoughts directly to my brain.  You 
say those awful flying brains are making 
everyone on Earth stupid?  Oh, stupider. 
And you go on to say that we're headed 
for your home planet where your race 
has lived since the beginning of the 
universe?  So, how did the universe 
begin?  Then the meaning of existence...? 
So every religion is wrong!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Hermes stands in the emergency 
chemical burn shoulder with his mouth wide open, letting the 
water run into it. The door is open and there is a puddle of 
water on the floor. Fry closes his mouth and pushes his head 
forward.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Lounge. Bender, Zoidberg, Amy and Farnsworth 
stare open-mouthed at the TV. The TV that isn't on. Fry sits 
on the couch and turns it on. Morbo spins around in his chair 
and Linda watches. He falls off and she laughs.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
You fell!  Hi! Today, some bad things 
happened. One bad things was a train 
got crashed in New Jersey. Wanna see? 
People won't be late for work though, 
because the governer lady says, (deeper 
voice) "I'm sending in more trains!"</speak>

<info>A train crashes into the wreckage and commuters run onto it.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Go!</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Wait for me! Wait for me!</speak>

<info>The picture returns to the studio.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
Morbo can't understand his TelePrompTer. 
He forgot how you say that letter that 
looks like a man with a hat.</speak>

<speak who="LINDA">
It's a "T". It goes "tuh".</speak>

<speak who="MORBO">
Hello, little man. I will destroy you!</speak>

<info>Fry turns the TV off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, even the news monster is acting 
strange. What are we gonna do?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Duh, I know! Let's play the lottery!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No. Let's buy internet stock!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
On margin! Zoidy wanna buy on margin!</speak>

<info>Hermes is wrapped in a towel on the other side of the room and 
holds a piece of wood in front of his face.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Look at me! I'm invisible!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a minute! I know what's going on 
here. You've all become idiots!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, let's all join the Reform Party!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Oh, yeah!</speak>

<info>They run out.</info>

<info>Nibbler's ship flies towards a planet called Planet Eternium 
which lies at the exact centre of the universe. The continents 
are shaped like love hearts. It lands outside a building called 
the Hall of Forever, ten miles west of the exact centre of the 
universe. The main part of the building is a dome with an eyestalk 
on top of it. Either side of the dome are two "Rosetta Stone" 
obelisks with both alien languages carved onto them.</info>

<info>Hall of Forever. Nine of Nibbler's race sit on raised chairs 
in a dark chamber. Enter Nibbler and Leela.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
Welcome back, Lord Nibbler, Ambassador 
to Earth, homeworld of the pizza bagel.</speak>

<info>Nibbler speaks plain English with a deep voice.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Thank you. I bear many receipts for 
reimbursement.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
The four welcomes of friendship to you 
as well, Leela. We shall manipulate 
your mind so we appear to be speaking 
your language. Do not be afraid, my 
child.</speak>

<info>She pulls the hood of her robe off her head. Her eyestalk has 
a little orange bow tied around it.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm not afraid.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Uh, good. Good.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
So, your real name is Lord Nibbler? 
That's a coincidence.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
That name is for your sake. In the time 
it would take to pronounce one letter 
of my true name a trillion cosmoses 
would flair into existence and sink 
into eternal night.</speak>

<info>Leela laughs and pinches Nibbler's cheek.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, you're all so cute!</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
No, we are not.  We Nibblonians are 
an ancient and powerful race. Behold. 
When the universe was forged in the 
crucible of the big bang, our mighty 
race was already 17 years old.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aww!</speak>

<info>Fiona growls. The hologram changes and shows a rocky planet 
with a lightning storm overhead.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
For the first millisecond of time, things 
were OK. But then there arose a terrible 
enemy: The Brain Spawn.  Ever since, 
we have waged unceasing war against 
these dreadful --</speak>

<info>A Nibblonian chef opens a door into the chamber.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLONIAN CHEF">
Lunch is ready.</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
Then let the feast of a thousand hams 
begin.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Hall of Forever. Chewing and eating noises come 
from inside and the Nibblonians burp.</info>

<info>Cut to: Hall of Forever. Leela is sat on the floor tickling 
Ken and Fiona like cats.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
So why are these Brain Spawn attacking 
Earth, Nibbler?</speak>

<info>Above Nibbler is a hologram of the Brain Spawn flying around 
New New York.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
The Brain Spawn hate all consciousness. 
The thoughts of others screech at them 
like the forced laughs of a billion 
art house movie patrons.</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
Thus, they travel from world to world 
making everyone stupid in order to wipe 
out all thought in the universe.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wipe out all thought? My God! They're 
like flying televisions.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
And even we are powerless to stop them, 
fearsome though we are.</speak>

<info>She purrs.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
There is but one being that can resist 
them. A child of destiny whose bizzare 
brain wave pattern makes him immune 
to the Brain Spawn attack.  He is the 
hope of the universe.  The fate of your 
world - perhaps all worlds - rests in 
his special mind.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Now, when you say "special"...</speak>

<info>Planet Express Balcony. Fry stands on the balcony looking at 
the carnage. Buildings burn in the distance, ships fall from 
the sky and cars crash in the street. A man crashes his car into 
a lamppost, opens the dome and slumps over dead. Fry picks up 
a bullhorn and talks into the wrong end.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Attention New New Yorkers. Stop acting 
so stupid!</speak>

<info>A bird lands on the other end and squawks into it. Fry screams 
and falls over.</info>

<info>Nibblonian Ship. The large circular ship orbits the Earth and 
is flanked by lots of smaller ships.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
Nibblonian fleet holding at perimeter 
of moron zone, formerly known as "Earth".</speak>

<info>The command centre of the ship looks like the Enterprise bridge 
from Star Trek, albeit a lot more pink. Ken, Fiona and Nibbler 
all sit on one big love-heart-shaped chair in the middle of the 
room.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Why would Fry be immune to the flying 
brains? Because he doesn't shower?</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
The Brain Spawn suppress intelligence 
by attacking the delta brain wave. Every 
animal and robot in the universe generates 
this wave, as do certain trees.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Fry, however, does not.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Somehow he has cobbled together a random 
assortment of other brainwaves into 
a working mind.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Like a prom dress made from carpet remnants.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Yes, like your prom dress.</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
The Brain Spawn are commanded by a giant 
evil brain with a gooey centre of pure 
hate.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Only Fry, with is superior, yet inferior 
mind, can approach him. You must tell 
him to disable it. We will do the rest.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You can count on me.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
No we can't. Once on Earth, you will 
be too stupid to remember the message.</speak>

<info>Ken nods.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
That's why we wrote it down for you.</speak>

<info>He pins the note to the front of Leela's top.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
We've also prepared a bag lunch and 
some mittens.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic. Hermes, Zoidberg, Amy and Farnsworth 
are lined up on the couch and Bender stands nearby. In front 
of them, Fry has set up a classroom situation. He has written 
"Fry's Dumb School" on a blackboard and there is a cardboard 
box in front of it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Time to re-educate you duncebags. We'll 
start with US presidents.  This is our 
first president, George Washington. 
Let's review. Who was our first president?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Umm...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
A pickle jar?</speak>

<speak who="WASHINGTON">
Thomas Jefferson?</speak>

<info>There is a screeching sound from outside. Leela crashes through 
the window in Nibbler's ship. It glides to a halt and she steps 
out of the smoking wreckage.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela! I've been so worried. Are you 
a bonehead?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I...have to tell...must...important...something...</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whoa, whoa! Slow down. You're going 
a mile a minute.</speak>

<info>Leela sees the note on her top, takes it off and hands it to 
him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
This! You for this!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Thanks!</speak>

<info>He blows hit nose on it, screws it up and throws it in the fire.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
No!  Ow! Fire hot.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The professy will help!  Fire indeed 
hot!</speak>

<info>Fry looks around and tips the water from Chest A. Arthur's jar 
over the professor's arm. Arthur's head falls out too and lands 
on the floor.</info>

<speak who="ARTHUR">
Oh! Chester A. Arthur fall down.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Brain. Brain make people dumb.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, Leela. Brain make people smart.</speak>

<info>He taps his head. Behind him, two Brain Spawn appear in the 
broken window. Leela growls and turns him around. He sees the 
brains and screams.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
You go fight biggest brain of all.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Even bigger than those? Holy nuts! Where 
is it?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I 'unno!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hm. A giant brain is basically a giant 
nerd. And where would a giant nerd be? 
The libary!</speak>

<info>Outside New New York Public Library. Fry and Leela run up the 
steps and two Brain Spawn fly in and block their path. Fry forces 
them out of the way.</info>

<info>New New York Public Library Corridors. Fry and Leela run past 
a librarian trying to push a book onto a bookshelf sideways. 
They run past Reference Books, Books on Tapeworm and Stephen 
King: A - Aardvark. They come to a stop outside Ancient Literature. 
From behind the door there comes a purple glow. Fry pushes the 
door ajar.</info>

<info>Cut to: New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. A huge 
brain hovers over a table reading books.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Pathetic human race. Arranging their 
knowledge by category just made it easier 
to absorb. Dewey, you fool: Your decimal 
system has played right into my hands! 
What do you want?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm here to kick your ass.</speak>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Wishful thinking. We have long since 
evolved beyond the need for asses.  
Odd. My stupefaction field is having 
no effect on your ability to think.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's right. And I think you'll find 
that a little knowledge is a dangerous 
thing!  OK, better think of a new plan. 
Come on, Fry, think!  Thinking...thinking...</speak>

<info>There is a buzzing sound and the brain shivers.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Oh! Stop that!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey! Thinking hurts him. Maybe I can 
think of a way to use that.  Aha! Prepare 
to be thought at. Leela, give me a topic.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Duh...</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Seriously, I can't think of anything. 
Gotta find something to make me think. 
<info>(reading)</info> Hardy Boys. <info>(talking)</info> Too 
easy. <info>(reading)</info> Nancy Drew. <info>(talking)</info> 
Too hard. Aha! Perfect! Bonfire of the 
Vanities!</speak>

<info>He reads it and the buzzing returns. The brain sinks into the 
corner of the room.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
No! It's unbearable!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside New New York Public Library. The Brain Spawn 
outside drop like flies.</info>

<info>Cut to: Nibblonian Ship. The Nibblonians watch this on a screen.</info>

<speak who="FIONA">
The brains are weakening.  Nibblonians 
to Nibble stations. Prepare cuddle bug 
for deployment in 40 nibblets.</speak>

<info>Nibbler sighs.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Sometimes I fear we are cute.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Oh, niggle-snoosh!</speak>

<info>New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. The Big Brains 
purple glow has turned green. It groans as Fry carries on reading.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Take that! And that! This sentence I 
don't understand but take this one!</speak>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
You have not won yet.  Each book in 
this room is a gateway to a mental realm 
and I shall take you there and imprison 
you forever.</speak>

<info>It envelopes a book and Fry and Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Icky!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Herman Melville's Moby Dick. Leela and Fry are on a 
dinghy in the middle of the ocean.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Where are we?</speak>

<info>They look around and see Captain Ahab and Queequeg on the boat 
with them.</info>

<speak who="AHAB">
A gold doubloon to the man who first 
spies the white whale.</speak>

<info>The Big Brain rams the side of the boat from the water.</info>

<speak who="QUEEQUEG">
Big whale over there.</speak>

<speak who="AHAB">
I saw it first!</speak>

<info>He pockets the gold and gives a shifty look. Fry is about to 
harpoon the brain when Queequeg grabs his arm.</info>

<speak who="QUEEQUEG">
Wait! That no white whale. It grey, 
pink-y whale!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Queequeg, let go of me! I have to kill 
it!</speak>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Farewell! You will all be trapped in 
this dense, symbolist tome forever!</speak>

<info>It dives.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Follow him! It's our only way out!</speak>

<info>He dives in, followed by Ahab, Queequeg and Leela.</info>

<info>Cut to: New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. Fry 
and Leela struggle in the purple glow. The Brain picks up another 
book.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mark Twain's The Adventures Of Tom Sawyer. Tom Sawyer 
is painting the fence and the characters from Moby Dick are with 
Fry and Leela.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Excuse me, have you seen a giant brain?</speak>

<speak who="TOM SAWYER">
Yep. I let him help me whitewash Aunt 
Polly's fence.</speak>

<info>He pushes open the gate, revealing the Brain wearing a straw 
hate and painting the fence.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Tom Sawyer, you tricked me. This is 
less fun than previously indicated. 
Let this corny slice of Americana be 
your tomb for all eternity.</speak>

<speak who="TOM SAWYER">
Please, no!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Come on!</speak>

<info>They chase the Brain.</info>

<info>Cut to: New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. The 
Brain picks up another book.</info>

<info>Cut to: Jane Austen's Pride And Prejudice. Fry is at a staely 
banquet.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Mr. Fry, Mama tells us you're quite 
the oddity; a bachelor at your age.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Tou think I'm an oddity? Wait'l you 
see --</speak>

<info>A door opens.</info>

<speak who="BUTLER">
Presenting the most eligible landowner 
in all Hertfordshire, Mr. Brainly.</speak>

<info>Enter the smartly-dressed Brain.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
I'm a gigantic brain!</speak>

<info>There is general murmuring from the people.</info>

<speak who="MAN #1">
I say!</speak>

<speak who="MAN #2">
Most ungentleman-like!</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Mr. Brainly, what news have you of the 
London season?</speak>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
Well...</speak>

<info>Fry grabs Tom Sawyer's bucket.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, Brain-y, think fast!</speak>

<info>He throws the whitewash at it.</info>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
I always think fast.</speak>

<info>The whitewash hits it and it screams.</info>

<speak who="AHAB">
The whale! He be white now!</speak>

<info>He and Queequeg throw harpoons at it and it screams. Ahab breaks 
off his wooden leg and hits the Brain with it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela, I've got an idea. Stay here with 
Queequeg.</speak>

<info>He jumps out of the window. Leela looks at Queequeg and twiddles 
her hair.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Is there Mrs. Queequeg?</speak>

<info>Cut to: New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. Fry 
pushes and sturggles and breaks free of the Brain's glow.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yes! I'm free!  Alright, Brain. Get 
ready for some electroshock treatment!</speak>

<info>He smashes the bulbs and swings on the light towards the Brain. 
He misses it by a mile and slams into a bookcase on the other 
side of the room. He falls to the floor and it falls on him, 
crushing him. Leela is freed from the purple glow. She sees Fry 
choking and screams.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, don't die! Wake up!  <info>(screaming)</info> 
Nooo!</speak>

<info>The Brain laughs. The bookcase and Fry's dead body fade away. 
Leela is kneeling in the middle of the room. The Brain is still 
laugh. She looks around and hears Fry's voice. He is writing.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela cried for her lost love as Fry 
lay dead under the heavy bookcase. The 
Big Brain laughed in triumph......Then, 
for no reason, he left Earth forever. 
The end.  There!  Now he's trapped in 
a book I wrote: A crummy world of plot 
holes and spelling errors.</speak>

<speak who="BIG BRAIN">
The Big Brain am winning again. I am 
the greetest!  Now I am leaving Earth 
for no rason!</speak>

<info>It squeezes through the window.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside New New York Public Library. The Nibblonians 
watch and cheer.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
The Big Brain is defeated. Let what 
must be done be done.</speak>

<info>The Nibblonian soldiers eat the other brains that have fallen.</info>

<info>Cut to: New New York Public Library: Ancient Literature. Leela 
shakes her head as her intelligence returns.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Me...feel...a bit better in cognitive 
faculties.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I did it!  And it's all thanks to the 
books at my local library.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The rest of the staff sleep as 
Hermes points to a chart showing the increase in employee sleep 
during meetings.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
<info>(voice-over)</info> And so life returned to 
normal. Or as normal as it gets on this 
primative dirtball inhabited by psychotic 
apes...</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Fry reads "Fry Tricks The Brain" to 
Farnsworth who dismisses it.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
<info>(voice-over)</info> ...Thanks to the effect 
of the brain rays, the people of Earth 
had no memory of what had transpired, 
except Fry. And no one believed him 
or cared what he had to say...</speak>

<info>Leela's Quarters. Leela lies on her bed stroking Nibbler, who 
is back in his cape.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
<info>(voice-over)</info> ...I, meanwhile, returned 
to my post, ever vigilant, lest Earth 
again come under Brain attack. And when 
that day comes, God help us. God help 
us all.</speak>

<info>Leela picks him up.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Time for a diapee change!</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
<info>(voice-over)</info> End transmission.</speak>

<info>THE END</info></xml>