<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 310

<title>LUCK OF THE FRYRISH</title>

<author>Ron Weiner</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Broadcast Simultaneously One Year 
In Future.</info>

<info><info>(Old New York; The Past)</info> Brooklyn Pre-Med Junior Hospital. A 
woman is in labour in a delivery room. Her husband sits in the 
corner reading Cold Warrior magazine. They are Fry's parents.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Push Mrs Fry, push!</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
You can do it honey! Squeeze one out 
for America!</speak>

<info>He goes back to reading his magazine.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Hey keep it down it's the 
9th inning!</speak>

<info>She holds a portable radio to her ear.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Swing the bat you bum!</speak>

<info>The doctor lifts up a baby. It cries.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
It's a boy. And look at that red hair.</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
You sayin' my son's a commie?</speak>

<info>Mrs Fry cheers.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
This is the happiest day of my life!</speak>

<info>The doctor puts the baby on her lap.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Here's your baby ma'am.</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Yeah OK thanks.</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
So, what should we name him?</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Uh, you pick. I picked dinner last night.</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Well, I was thinking Philip. After those 
screwdrivers?</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
That's a fantastic idea. More morphine 
please.</speak>

<info>Hospital Room. Mr Fry puts Philip in a bed and introduces his 
brother to him.</info>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Look Yancy, its your baby brother Philip.</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
I wanna be named Philip! Me Philip! 
Me Philip!</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Son your name is Yancy, just like me 
and my grandfather and so on. All the 
way back to minuteman Yancy Fry, who 
blasted commies in the American Revolution. 
Philip, until I find a suitable model 
of an ICBM you'll have to make do learnin' 
to fear this toy spacecraft.</speak>

<info>He turns the mobile on and leaves. Philip laughs as the mobile 
turns around. Yancy snatches away the rocket.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Mine! Mine!</speak>

<info>Philip starts crying. Yancy throws the rocket out the window.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present (i.e. The Future)</info>) The Planet Express 
ship flies down to Earth and lands in the car park outside Flushing 
Downs.</info>

<info>Flushing Downs Stands. The horse race starts and the crew stand 
up and cheer.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> C'mon!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
<info>(shouting)</info> Baby needs a new pair of 
shoes!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
To hell with your spoiled baby, I need 
those shoes!</speak>

<info>The horses cross the finish line.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No fair! You changed the outcome by 
measuring it.</speak>

<info>He tears up his slip. Fry looks through some binoculars.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
How'd you do Fry?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll tell you when my horse finishes...bad.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Flushing Downs Luxury Box. Mr and Mrs Wong and Amy stand 
talking in the box while a classy orchestra plays for them.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
In today's field we own four horses 
and two jockeys.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
We just put our best jockey out to stud 
Amy, he's perfect for you!</speak>

<info>The very short jockey strolls up behind Amy.</info>

<speak who="JOCKEY">
Hey baby, ever do it in a suitcase?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Flushing Downs Stand.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooo look! It's the centaur race!</speak>

<info>The bells rings and the centaurs start running around the track, 
horsewhipping themselves as they go. Fry crosses his fingers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Come on, come on! Hey Leela, how 'bout 
a kiss for good luck?  I meant tongue 
luck.</speak>

<info>The centaurs cross the finish line.</info>

<info>Fry groans.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I am so unlucky! I've run over black 
cats that were luckier than me.</speak>

<info>Flushing Downs Horse D'Oeuvres Stand.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Get your piping hot horse burgers, horse 
fries, horse cake and shakes. We got 
tongue straight from the horse's mouth.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hmm.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
It all sounds good.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
All our horses are 100% horse fed for 
that double juiced in horse goodness.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'll have a cholesterol free omelette 
with horse beaters.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
And you sir, how can I horse you?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I'll have a horse coke.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Horse Pepsi OK?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Neigh.</speak>

<info>Flushing Downs Stables. Bender sneaks in disguised as a horse. 
He innocently whistles and injects a horse with Comatonin. It 
yawns. Bender chuckles. The jockey runs in behind him.</info>

<speak who="JOCKEY">
Hey what are you doing?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
This.</speak>

<info>He injects the jockey and he falls over asleep.</info>

<info>Flushing Downs Stand. Bender is back with the group. Fry prays.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Dear Horse God, I know I don't usually 
pray to you, sometimes I doubt you even 
exist. But if you're willing to grant 
me luck, please, stamp your hoof once. 
Come on number six move it!  Don't 
do that! What are you -  Man it's contagious!</speak>

<info>The one horse that started the race gallops over the finish 
line.</info>

<info>Bender's slip flashes. He has won $2500. He cheers.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
That'll teach those other horses to 
take drugs!</speak>

<info>Fry tears up his slip.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's it! You can only take my money 
for so long before you take it all, 
and I say enough.  I've got one dollar 
left, and this one I'm holding onto! 
Oh no you don't!  I may not know much 
about horses but I know a lot about 
doing anything for one dollar!  If you 
think bad luck can defeat me then you 
don't know my name is Philip J -</speak>

<info>He reaches over to the wire with the rake but it electrocutes 
him. He pulls the rake away and breathes a sigh of relief. Then 
he gets struck by lightning and falls.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Flushing Downs. Fry has landed upside down in 
a dustbin and is smoking from the lightning strike. The Horse 
D'Oeuvres man comes outside through a door carrying a bucket 
of horse leftovers.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
That is one unlucky guy!</speak>

<info>He pours the bucket over Fry and leaves.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Past)</info> Basketball Court. 12 year old Fry dribbles 
the ball where Yancy can't get to it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Kareem's got the skyhook but Philip 
J. Fry's got the spacehook!</speak>

<info>He throws the ball but it bounces off the basket. Yancy chases 
after it and dribbles it back to the basket.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Yancy drives, he goes up with his patented 
spacehook!</speak>

<info>He throws the ball and it goes through the hoop.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey. That's my patented spacehook! You 
stole it!</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
You're not the president of it!</speak>

<info>He points at the ball and Fry runs to get it. He looks across 
at the grass next to him and sees something growing there. A 
seven leaf clover. He picks it up.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Holy camolie! A seven leaf clover!</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
<info>(shouting)</info> I'm dying of old age!</speak>

<info>Fry tucks the clover into his sweatband and dribbles the ball 
back onto the court. He shoots, Yancy jumps to get the ball but 
misses and the ball goes through the hoop. Fry cheers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Phil wins! Yancy's fans are stunned! 
There'll be no celebration at the Yancy 
dome!</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Lucky.</speak>

<info>Fry takes the clover out from his sweatband and gawps at it.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present)</info> Planet Express: Meeting Room. The crew 
are gathered around the table. Fry is nearly bald from the lightning 
strike and Bender whistles while he counts his winnings.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well someone's in a good mode.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Let's just say I lucked out at the track! 
Also I rigged one race.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Pah. I'd have won a lot of money too 
if I still had my lucky seven leaf clover. 
Plus I'd still have my hair.</speak>

<info>Enter a Hairbot which has replacement hair for the crew growing 
on it.</info>

<speak who="HAIRBOT">
I got your page Mr Fry, your new hair 
is ready!</speak>

<info>He takes the hair off his head and puts it on Fry's head. Fry 
shuffles it into place.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
So whatever happened to this seven leaf 
clover?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I hid it in a secret hiding place who's 
location I never told anyone. Not even 
Scruffy.</speak>

<info>Scruffy leans against the doorframe suspiciously and walks out.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
So the clover is still in the hiding 
place maybe?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey yeah! Maybe it is still there! Underground 
in the ruins of Old New York. Helping 
some ant defeat another ant or helping 
some piece of dirt turn it's luck around.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dirt doesn't need luck.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm going down there to get my clover 
back. Now some of the tunnels have metal 
bars so I'll need someone who's good 
at bending. Leela how 'bout you?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Sure I'll do it.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Like hell you will. Bending's my middle 
name.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It is?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yep. My full name is Bender Bending 
Rodriguez</speak>

<info>Street. In the middle of the road Fry lifts a PJ's manhole cover.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Here's the entrance.  From this moment 
on I declare my bad luck officially 
over.</speak>

<info>The ladder gives way beneath him and he plummets into the darkness 
then lands in a heap. Bender and Leela peer into the hole.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
He was fun.</speak>

<info>Ruins Of Old New York. Fry, Bender and Leela walk down a deserted 
ruined street. Leela holds up her wrist thing.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well if we get bored I've got Tetris 
on this thing.</speak>

<info>The crew come to the edge of a cliff top and ahead of them are 
lots of ruined buildings.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Look, up ahead.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Old New York. The city that inspired 
a casino in Las Vegas.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. They continue walking down a street.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! We've got Manhattan all to ourselves! 
I can finally do all the crazy stuff 
I always dreamed of doing!  Howard Stern 
s overrated!  Uh, oops!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
New York is so burned.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And remember when Mayor Giuliani cracked 
down on jaywalking?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well Rudy, how'd you like this action?</speak>

<info>He walks across the road and a huge lizard flattens him.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Past)</info> New York Street. A bunch of guys dressed 
in late 80s crap stand around. Fry and Yancy are with them.</info>

<speak who="GUY #1">
As you know the big breakdance is Saturday. 
So if we wanna win those Jam Master 
J autographed parachute pants our crew 
has to pop, lock and bust the freshest. 
Noticwably F.A.T., drop us a beat.  
Name?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Cosmic F.</speak>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Style?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Outer space.</speak>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Special moves?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The moonwalk...the robot...the zero 
G!</speak>

<info>He steps back and Yancy steps forward.</info>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Name?</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Cosmic Y.</speak>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Style?</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Uh, deep space!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Deep space??</speak>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Special moves?</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
The spacewalk...</speak>

<info>He copies Fry's moonwalk.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey!</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
...The robot...</speak>

<info>He copies Fry's robot.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
The robot? That's similar to mine!</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
The zero G!</speak>

<info>He copies Fry's zero G.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What are you doing? You totally ripped 
off my routine.</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
You callin' me a biter?</speak>

<info>Noticeably F.A.T. stops beating and everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Why do you always have to steal everything 
from me Yancy? Find your own life and 
live it.</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Stop illin'! Word!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well I'd like to see you try and steal 
this. the septuple head spin.</speak>

<info>Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
He's just scratching. No one's ever 
done more than a quadruple.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh yeah? Noticeably F.A.T., rewind the 
tape.</speak>

<info>And he does. Fry pulls the clover out of his shoe and tucks 
it into the sweatband on his head. He does the head spin.</info>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Crazy sucker!</speak>

<speak who="GUY #2">
Phil, you're hot!</speak>

<speak who="NOTICEABLY F">.A.T.
That was ice cold bro!</speak>

<speak who="GUY #1">
Fry if I ever see you try anything that 
crazy again, this crew might just have 
some new parachute pants!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers and Fry gawps at the clover again.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Stop hogging the clover.</speak>

<info>He struggles to get it from Fry. Fry pushes him away and runs 
away. Yancy chases him.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present)</info> Ruins Of Old New York. Fry gets up off 
the road and dusts himself off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright team, let's go find that clover!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Which way to your house? The sign says 
we're at 71st street.</speak>

<info>Fry looks at the sign.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
71st street? Hmm, never heard of it. 
Downtown could be in any direction.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No sweat, we'll just take a spin on 
the B-train!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ruined Station. Bender attaches himself to the train 
tracks and electricity shoots through him and he giggles.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooo that feels funny!  This is the Brooklyn 
bound B-train making local stops at 
wherever the hell I feel like. Watch 
for the closing doors.</speak>

<info>He makes a bing bong noise and sets off down the track.</info>

<info>Newkirk Avenue Station Ruins. Bender stops at the station and 
Fry and Leela get off. A hobo is asleep on Bender's back.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wake up buddy end of the line!</speak>

<info>The hobo mutters and climbs off. Fry looks around.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Gosh my old neighbourhood!  That's the 
bench where I found some shirts!  That 
fire hydrant! In summer we'd light it 
on fire! On that corner, some guy with 
a bushy beard handed out a socialist 
newsletter!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Was it poorly xeroxed?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You'd better believe it!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
The old comedians were right, this place 
is a lot different from LA!</speak>

<info>A mutant pokes his head up through a sewer grate.</info>

<speak who="MUTANT">
Pardon me but did I overhear you saying 
you used to live here?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's right.</speak>

<speak who="MUTANT">
Did you know Andy Goldman?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, he was my neighbour. Why?</speak>

<speak who="MUTANT">
I mutated from him!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Get out of here! What's Andy up to these 
days?</speak>

<info>Andy's head suddenly pokes out from the mutant's chest.</info>

<speak who="ANDY">
The short answer is I'm teaching.</speak>

<info>The mutant disappears back into the sewer.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
He seemed nice.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Sure when he's sober!</speak>

<info>Outside The Ruins Of The Frys' House.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Holy camolies! The house I grew up in! 
It's still there!</speak>

<info>The house is a battered ruin.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Man, father time really took a bat to 
this place.</speak>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Past)</info> Outside The Frys' House. It looks exactly 
the same. Yancy chases Fry into the house.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
That stupid clover is a worthless piece 
of garbage! Give it give it give it!</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Frys' Living Room. Mrs Fry is playing miniature 
golf.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Mom! Help!</speak>

<info>Mrs Fry hits the golf ball and breaks the cup she was aiming 
for.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Yes!</speak>

<info>Enter Fry and Yancy.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Mom, Yancy's trying to steal my clover.</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
<info>(uninterested)</info> Yancy, stealing is wrong.</speak>

<info>Yancy starts chasing Fry again.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
I'm gonna pile drive you!  You're dead 
meat!</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Frys' Basement. Mr Fry reassembles a torch.</info>

<speak who="MR FRY">
What's happenin' up there? Did Kremlin 
Joe let fly with the nukes?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Not yet commander. Yancy's just trying 
to steal my stuff as usual.</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Well he'd better keep his hands off 
these bananas. Gonna need them when 
the radiation turns us all into monkeys.</speak>

<info>He lifts a crate of bananas onto the table and climbs the ladder 
out of the basement. Fry pulls a sheet off something and takes 
his clover out of his pocket.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
The Ronco Record Vault! Yancy'll never 
get his hands on you in here or my money 
back.  Ah The Breakfast Club soundtrack! 
Man I can't wait til I'm old enough 
to feel ways about stuff!  Stay safe 
clover. I may need you again someday.</speak>

<info>He runs up the stairs.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present)</info> The Ruins Of The Frys' Basement. Enter 
Fry, Leela and Bender.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This was the storage room. My dad spent 
years turning it into a bomb shelter.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And yet you guys never had a single 
nuclear war.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What a waste.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
This is it! My Ronco Record Vault!  
I still remember the combination.  Three. 
It's stuck.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
The Achilles heel of the Ronco design 
is it's structural resonance frequency. 
Allow me.  There we go!</speak>

<info>Fry pulls out the record.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Here it is. The Breakfast Club soundtrack.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You mean breakfast club sandwich?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I hid my seven leaf clover in this very 
record jacket so my brother Yancy wouldn't 
get it.  Here goes.  It's gone!  the 
whole place has been cleaned out! Yancy 
stole my clover! That thief!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
How do you know it didn't disintergrate?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Everything else in here held up OK.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Except Sports by Huey Lewis.</speak>

<info>The Ruins Of Prospect Park. Fry, Leela and Bender walk back 
up the street without the clover.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I don't know why my brother hated me 
so much.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aw, brothers always fight. I'm sure 
deep down he loved you. He just never 
got a chance to say it before you got 
frozen.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You think? 'Cause I always kinda wished 
that -</speak>

<info>He gasps. In front of them is a huge statue.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Who is that God-like figure?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It's my brother Yancy! And there in 
his lapel - my seven leaf clover! I 
knew he stole it.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hold the phone. If that's Yancy then 
why does the inscription read Philip 
J. Fry?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a second! That's my name! Good 
Lord. He ditched his goofy name and 
stole mine!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Apparently this brave adonis, this cadillac 
of men, was the first person on Mars.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
First person on Mars?? I should have 
been the first person on Mars! He stole 
my clover, he stole my name and he stole 
my life!  And now he broke my hand.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
His legend lives on.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The statue now stands in the room.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
So you opened the record vault and the 
clover was gone?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yep, nothing in there but all the best 
music of the 1980's in one amazing collection.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Survivor, Pat Benetar, The Scorpions. 
The list goes on.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That clover helped my ratfink brother 
steal my dream of going into space. 
Now I'll never get there.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You went there this morning for doughnuts.</speak>

<info>Hermes reads the statue's inscription.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
First person on Mars? Oh so your brother 
was that Philip J. Fry!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm Philip J. Fry! He stole my name 
after I got frozen.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Shut up friends. My internet browser 
heard us saying the word "Fry" and it 
found a movie about Philip J. Fry for 
us.  It alwso opened my calendar to 
Friday and ordered me some French fries.</speak>

<info>An image of Yancy appears on the screen and changes as the narrator 
narrates.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That should have been me!</speak>

<info>In the movie Yancy board a small plane.</info>

<info>Yancy closes the plane's door and a picture of the clover is 
on it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's my clover! Yancy stole it!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's what I'm known for!</speak>

<speak who="MAN"><info>IN MOVIE</info>
Phil came in right, sturmmed out this 
tune yeah. And I said "That's a number 
one record!"</speak>

<info>The scene changes to an cemetary orbitting the Earth.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So that's where my clover is? Hey, is 
that orbitting cemetary near here?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It will be in a couple hours.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Good. Leela, Bender, we're going graverobbing.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll get my kit.</speak>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Past)</info> The Frys' Living Room. A woman slips a camoflage 
tuxedo onto Yancy.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Thanks for lending me your tux Dad. 
It'll be perfect for my wedding.</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Yancy, that tux got me through Nam in 
style!  I just wish your brother were 
still around to see this.</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
I'll never forget the day Philip disappeared. 
Wisconsin won the rose bowl 17-9. Oh 
I miss him.</speak>

<info>Mr Fry pats her leg.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Oh that reminds me. I was thinking of 
rummaging through Phil's records for 
something to play at the wedding.</speak>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Have a look downstairs. Your brother 
may be missing but his crap sure isn't.</speak>

<info>The Frys' Basement. Yancy sorts through a box marked Phil's 
Stuff. He gets out a Whitefish flag and puts it to one side. 
He pulls out a piece of paper with a crude drawing of a rocket 
and a figure standing on top of it. The figure is labelled "Phil" 
and at the bottom of the paper is "By Philip Fry Aged 20". Yancy 
folds it up and puts it in his pocket. He tries Fry's record 
vault but it won't open. He gets a pot of Doh-Doh out from the 
box, sticks it to the vault, lights it and blows the door open. 
He pulls out a random record.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Hmm Breakfast Club, this'll clear out 
the room at the end of the reception.</speak>

<info>He flips the record over and the clover falls out of the sleeve. 
He picks it up and gasps.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present)</info> The Planet Express flies up from the 
Earth and lands inside Orbitting Meadows National Cemetary.</info>

<info>Cut to: Orbitting Meadows National Cemetary.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
They buried your brother in the world 
heroes section? I'm impressed.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I should be the one in that grave!</speak>

<info>The pass two guards who salute. Fry and Leela salute them and 
Bender whacks his head with the spade.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hmm. We lost Bender.</speak>

<info>Bender is digging up a nearby grave.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
There. Now no one will be able to say 
I don't own John Larroquette's spine!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The crew approach Yancy's grave.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Aha! My brother's grave!</speak>

<info>The monument on top of the grave is in the shape of a rocket 
and Yancy is chiselled onto it. Leela reads the inscription.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(reading)</info> Philip Fry, the original Martian.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It's all lies every word of it! He wasn't 
original, he wasn't a Martian, he wasn't 
Philip Fry and since when is he a the?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You're twice the the he ever was.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It's clovering time!</speak>

<info>They start to dig. Fry hits the monument with his spade and 
knocks some moss off it. He reads the hidden inscription.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Past)</info> Yancy's House. Yancy's wife nurses a baby 
while Yancy stands over them.

<speak who="YANCY">'S WIFE
So, had any ideas for names Yancy?</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Uh, I'm sorta thinking one.  Daddy has 
a present for you today. Do you know 
what it is?  It's a lucky clover that 
can help you be successful at anything 
you do - even breakdancing - and it 
once belonged to someone very special.</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">'S WIFE
I know what name you wanna give him 
Yancy. It's OK.</speak>

<speak who="YANCY">
Really?  Son, I'm naming you Philip 
J. Fry in honour of my little brother, 
who I miss every day. I love you Philip, 
and I always will.</speak>

[He looks across the room. Hanging over the baby's cot is the 
picture Fry drew of him on the rocket. Yancy kisses Philip and 
he giggles.</info>

<info>Fade to: <info>(The Present)</info> Orbitting Meadows National Cemetary. 
Fry reads the inscription out loud.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(reading)</info> Here lies Philip J. Fry, named 
for his uncle, to carry on his spirit.</speak>

<info>Bender forces open the coffin.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Pay dirt! I got the clover! Plus his 
wedding ring.  Sorry ladies, I'm taken! 
Hey Fry you want me to smack the corpse 
up a little?</speak>

<info>Fry, tears in his eyes, takes the clover from Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh, Bender, I think Fry needs a moment 
alone.</speak>

<info>She helps him out of the grave.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright grab a shovel. I'm only one 
skull short of a Mouseketeer reunion.</speak>

<info>He and Leela walk away. Fry puts the clover back in the grave 
and smiles. The episode plays out with Simple Minds' Don't You 
<info>(Forget About Me)</info>.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>