<xml>
<episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 313

<title>BENDIN' IN THE WIND</title>

<author>Eric Horsted</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Federal Law Prohibits Changing The 
Channel.</info>

<info>New New York City Street. Fry and Bender walk down a busy street 
and Bender sings and dances.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Froggy went a-courtin' and 
he did ride, uh-huh, uh-huh

Well, Froggy went a-courtin' and he did ride

Blah blah blah, something, Bender is great!

Froggy went a-courtin' and Bender is great, uh-huh -

</speak><info>A rumbling noise interrupts his singing. He and Fry look through 
a gap in a fence and see Sal in a hover-digger digging a huge 
hole at the NNYC Hole Project. Sall dumps a load down on the 
ground. Amongst some rubble and mud is a bag of fat free potato 
chips. Fry picks it up.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh my God! They dug up a bag of olestra 
chips from my time!  There must be layers 
and layers of old stuff down there.</speak>

<info>Sal dumps another scoop-ful and amongst the dirt is an entire 
VW minivan. Fry gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What's that? One of those Led Zeppelins 
I've heard so much about?</speak>

<info>Fry puts his hands on the VW.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
No, it's an old Volkswagen van.  <info>(shouting)</info> 
Hey, Mister? Mind if I take this old 
van?</speak>

<speak who="SAL">
<info>(shouting)</info> Sure. You wanna dump the 
corpses out of theres, it's yourses.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah yeah, I've gotten used cars before.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Fry grunts and groans as he pushes the 
VW into the hangar. He is wearing the previous owner's bandana. 
Bender sits inside and guzzles down a beer. The rest of the crew 
gather around.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What's that? One of those Jefferson 
Starships I've heard so much about?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It's called a van, and in light of the 
fact that it's not a-rockin', I invite 
you to come a-knockin'!</speak>

<info>He slides open the door and the crew peer inside at all the 
beads and beanbags and throws.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Wow, neat.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
It's a triumph of free-spirited German 
engineering.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey, the speedometer only goes up to 
80. This thing can't go faster than 
80,000 miles an hour?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, it can't, but it's got a driver's-side 
floor and an 8-track player with genuine 
mono sound.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Where's the device that lets you speed 
or slow the passage of time?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Under the seat.</speak>

<info>He pulls out a bong. Leela tries turning the key in the ignition 
and the engine coughs and splutters.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Why won't it start?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
It just needs some gas.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth puts his hand on his shoulder.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wrong again, idiot. There is no gas. 
Petroleum reserves ran dry in 2038.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Gas was an environmental disaster, anyway. 
Now we use alternative fuels.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Like what?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Whale oil.  Bender, lift it up to the 
can opener.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, no, I'm not going near it. Last 
time, that magnetic psycho nearly cut 
my head off.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, right. Plus, the magnet screws up 
your inhibition unit and makes you sing 
folk songs.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What? Who said anything about me secretly 
wanting to be a folk singer? How ridiculous.</speak>

<info>He glances around. Fry puts his hand on his shoulder.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, if you don't open that can right 
now, your fear will own you, and nothing 
that can opener could ever do could 
be worse than that.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
OK, OK, I can do this. It's time to 
take life by the cans.</speak>

<info>He lifts the barrel and looks weakly at the others.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Come on.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
You can do it.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Bender!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Go on, you dummy.</speak>

<info>Bender walks towards the can opener and the magnet grabs him 
and starts cutting into him. Sparks fly from him and he starts 
to sing.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Jimmy cracked corn and I don't 
care</speak>

<info>He screams in pain.</info>

Jimmy cracked corn and I don't care...

<info>He screams again. The rest of the crew cringe and cover their 
eyes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, no!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> 'Cause the master's gone away.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
It's toe-tapping-ly tragic.</speak>

<info>Cedars-Sinewave Robot Hospital. Bender lies on a bed and a doctor 
checks him over. He has huge gashes across his chest.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Doc, I can't move my arms and legs. 
What's wrong with me?</speak>

<info>The doctor sighs.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
This is the worst part of the job.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What is it, good news?</speak>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
Bender, your hydraulics are shot. You'll 
never move again.</speak>

<info>Bender chokes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You mean -?</speak>

<info>The doctor turns to Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="DOCTOR">
I'm sorry, you'll have to get a new 
one.</speak>

<info>He leaves and Bender bursts into tears. The crew murmur to each 
other.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, no, this is terrible.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Poor Bender.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well, let's drag him to the kerb.</speak>

<info>He grabs Bender's arm and Zoidberg takes hold of his legs. Fry 
stops them.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a minute, Bender is my best friend. 
We can't just dump him in the gutter 
like Grandma's ashes.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> Oh, my life is over. I'll never 
know happiness again.</speak>

<info>A horn honks and robot on wheels dressed like a clown rolls 
in.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Ho ho, hello there!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Look, Bender. It's Patch Cord Adams. 
He heals with the power of laughter.</speak>

<info>He holds a robot-shaped balloon above Bender.</info>

<speak who="PATCH CORD ADAMS">
C'mon, take it. What's the matter, can't 
move your arms?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Obviously not, or I'd be strangling 
you right now.</speak>

<speak who="PATCH CORD ADAMS">
Hey, here's a giggle!  Did you hear 
why they're using Windows 3000 as a 
prison guard?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, why?</speak>

<speak who="PATCH CORD ADAMS">
'Cause it always locks up.</speak>

<info>The others laugh weakly.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
For the love of God, somebody kick his 
ass!</speak>

<speak who="PATCH CORD ADAMS">
Well, so long. Get well soon.  Oh, well, 
so long anyway.</speak>

<info>He rolls out and Bender groans.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, I'm doomed. Everybody leave me alone. 
I don't wanna be seen this way.</speak>

<info>Everyone, except Fry, leaves.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Aw, you look so sad. You want me to 
send Patch Cord Adams back in?</speak>

<info>Bender bawls and Fry leaves. The sound of a harmonica stops 
his tears.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, the blues. The tragic sound of 
other people suffering. That's kind 
of a pick-me-up.  Wow, that was great.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Hey, thanks. You a fan?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I dunno. Let me see.  Oh my God, you're 
Beck! I'd get up to shake your hand 
and steal your wallet but my crappy 
body crapped out on me.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Don't take it so hard. I used to miss 
my body too but then I fished this manequin 
out of the 92c Store dumpster.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow. We've sure got a lot in common, 
Beck. I always dreamed of being a musician-poet 
who transcends genres even as he re-invents 
them, just like you.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
So do it, robot. It's easier than it 
looks.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Eh, thanks, but it's hopeless. I'll 
never be a musician now.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Or maybe you'll be the best musician 
ever.</speak>

<info>He motions the doctor to him and whispers something to him. 
He takes the harmonica holder out of Beck's jar and puts it around 
Bender's neck.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What's this for?</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Try and scrape it across your chest 
like a knife on burnt toast.  Come on, 
move those arms. Use the power of mental 
thinking. Make it dynamic.  Yeah-ee! 
Alright, congratulations my friend.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Why? 'Cause I can make annoying noises?</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Exactly. I use those all the time in 
my music. Bender, I want you to become 
my new washboard player.</speak>

<info>Bender gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright!  Go Bender! Go Bender! Go Bender!</speak>

<info>Outside Planet Express. The whole crew are gathered outside 
the building by the side of the road. Fry, still wearing his 
headband, wheels Bender out on a sack truck. He has a small green 
suitcase with him. A large blue bus pulls up and honks its horn.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, that's my good friend, Beck. I'm 
of to rock a series of mid-level venues.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Kudos, Bender. You got mangled and now 
you're a singer. Both our dreams came 
true.</speak>

<info>The bus honks again.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, I have an idea. Who wants to cram 
in my van and follow Bender on tour 
and live there, in the van?</speak>

<info>Behind them, the VW rumbles and backfires.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh, I don't know, Fry. I think I'm too 
poor to follow a band around in a van.</speak>

<info>The bus beeps again and Beck leans out of a window.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(shouting)</info> Come on, move it! We gotta 
get to the concert and make the audience 
wait for it at the start.</speak>

<info>Montage The tour bus passes under the Holland Tunnel with the 
VW right behind it, causing a tailback. They drive from New New 
York, through New New Jersey, Washington A.C., East West Virginia 
to a little town called Squatter's Corner in West Virginia.</info>

<info>Velma Sue's Laundromat. Zoidberg, Amy, Leela and Fry do their 
laundry. Zoidberg dumps the basket of washing on a table in front 
of the others who sit around in their underwear.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Bad news, friends. My shell ran.</speak>

<info>He holds up his clothes. They are a funky tie-dye pink.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Zoidberg, you idiot, my outfit. It's, 
it's -</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Kinda cool.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah, I like it.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Me too, now that I'm used to it.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Then it was all on purpose. You're lucky 
to have Zoidberg as a friend. But cross 
me, and I'll turn on you like that.</speak>

<info>He snaps his fingers and squeals at them.</info>

<info>Squatter's Corners Civic Audeetorium. Beck and the band play 
their gig to some hicks in a barn. They perform Where It's At 
from the album Odelay.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> There's a destination a little 
up the road

From the habitations and the towns we know

A place we saw the lights turn low

The jigsaw jazz and the get-fresh glow

Pullin' out jives and jamboree handouts

Two turntables and a microphone

Bottles and cans just clap your hands just clap your hands.

</speak><speak who="ALL">
<info>(singing)</info> Where it's at!</speak>

<info>Bender scrapes his chest.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(electric voice)</info> Got a washboard stomach 
and a microphone.</speak>

<info>He scrapes his chest.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
That was a washboard break.</speak>

<info>The Planet Express foursome cheer.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh yeah!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah!  One bowl of Jell-O knuckles, 
please.</speak>

<speak who="BARMAN">
That'll be three pick-e-tures of George 
Washington.</speak>

<info>Amy takes some money out of her pocket but it has turned to 
green gloop.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh no, my beautiful money.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It got ruined in the wash.</speak>

<info>She and Fry take money out of their pockets.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Mine too, even my change.</speak>

<speak who="BARMAN">
Get lost you money-less hippies!</speak>

<info>He holds up a picture of nine aliens.</info>

<info>Outside Squater's Corners Civic Audeetorium. After the concert, 
the band's gear is packed away in the bus.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
Bender, that was the best 40-minute 
washboard solo I've ever heard. And 
the parts when I was awake blew my mind.</speak>

<info>Bender hears something and turns around and sees some broken 
robots in some bins, rolling towards a building.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Whoa, check out all those broken robots. 
Howdy, fellas!</speak>

<info>He waves.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
I don't believe my broken eyes, it's 
Bender, the washboard player! Hey man, 
we caught your concert from here.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
You rock!</speak>

<speak who="FEMBOT">
Oh, oh, Bender! Sign my chest!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #3">
Yo, brother, thanks for showing us broken 
robots are still useful.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw, hang in there, folks. I'll bet before 
you know it, you guys'll be -  That 
is so wrong. They can't just melt down 
broken robots. Not right when they're 
kissing my ass.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Whoa, dog. Just cold chill.  You know, 
when I'm upset, I write a song about 
it. Like when I wrote Devil's Haircut, 
I was feeling really...what's that song 
about?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, yeah, I could write a song! With 
real words, not phony ones like "odelay".</speak>

<speak who="BECK">"Odelay" is a word. Just look it up 
in the Becktionary.</speak>

<info>He holds the Webster's Abridged Becktionary (From Bzooty to 
Whiskeyclone).</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooh!</speak>

<info>Beck's Bus. The bus drives down a desert road with the VW behind 
it. Inside, Beck lies on a settee while Bender and writes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm working on my song. Hand me the 
Becktionary.  No, no, the rhyming Becktionary.</speak>

<info>Beck sighs.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
I wish I could help raise awareness 
about broken robots. But what can I 
do? I only weigh eight pounds.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wait a minute, you know lots of rock 
stars, and most of them like to look 
as though they care about things!</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
We can all get together for a big benefit 
concert in San Francisco!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And we could call it "Bend-Aid", after 
me, Bender!</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
And you can sing that song you're writing!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And I'll let you sing backup! But remember 
who the star is. Me: Bender.</speak>

<info>Montage The bus passes through several more states as Bender 
tries to come up with a song. He dabs his eyes with a tissue 
as he reads the song. At another concert, Fry, Zoidberg, Amy 
and Leela rummage through dustbins for food. Fry finds a hotdog 
with mustard and flies and holds it up to the others. Zoidberg 
cuts it up into four pieces and they eat it. They arrive in San 
Francisco at dusk.</info>

<info>Sir Francis Drake Hotel. Bender sits on a bed in his hotel room, 
writing his song.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright. "Hands in the air" rhymes with 
"Just don't care" and...finished!  Eck! 
Smells like something died in the wall!</speak>

<info>Fry, Leela, Zoidberg and Amy walk in.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Surprise!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Mind if we crash here tonight? The colours 
in the van are keeping us awake.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright, but hands off the minibar.</speak>

<info>He closes his chest cabinet which has the minibar in it. Fry 
looks at the TV.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow, I forgot about TV. Living free 
on the road, you realise how much better 
life is without it. Well, let's see 
what's on.</speak>

<info>He turns it. An advertisment comes on and shows a band playing 
on stage.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER #1">
<info>(voice-over; on TV)</info> Tuesday, Golden 
Gate Park, the monsters of vaguely folkish 
alterna-rock will strum your brains 
out at Bend-Aid! Featuring Beck, Wailing 
Fungus and special guest, Bender!</speak>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER #2">
<info>(voice-over; on TV)</info> A portion of the 
proceeds might go to help broken robots.</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hooray, robot!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Bender, you're famous!</speak>

<info>Bender wipes away a tear.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
This coming together of superstars really 
means a lot to you, doesn't it, Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> Uh-huh. Helping my defective 
brothers is the first thing I've ever 
cared about, even the slightest bit. 
You know, when I first got broken, I 
thought my life was over. But look at 
me now. I've got fame, money, groupies, 
and it's all thanks to being completely 
immobolised.  That's why I'll be proud 
to go up on stage, tomorrow, and say, 
"Look at me, world, I am a broken robot!".</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, you can move! You're cured!</speak>

<info>Bender looks at himself in a mirror.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh crap, it's a miracle.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I can move again. <info>(crying)</info> My music 
career is over.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, I don't claim to understand 
"the biz" but wouldn't being able to 
move help your music career?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> No, don't you see? I was a 
hero to broken robots 'cause I was one 
of them. But how can I sing about being 
damaged if I'm not? That's like Christina 
Aguilera singing in Spanish.  Wait, 
that's it. I'll fake it!</speak>

<info>San Francisco Street. Fry drives the van down the winding streets, 
with a cloud of exhaust following it.</info>

<info>Cut to: VW. Zoidberg coughs and hawks into a tissue.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
You'd better not do that at the concert.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I can't stop. When I eat too much dirt, 
I get stuff in my throat.</speak>

<info>He hawks and spits into the tissue.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
You are so disgusting, I -</speak>

<info>She gasps. Zoidberg has spit up blue pearls. Leela takes a handful.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
They're beautiful.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Eww, you're touching them.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I've never seen pearls like this. Dr. 
Zoidberg, you're amazing.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I am? At last! Recognition!</speak>

<info>He spits up some more into Amy and Leela's hands.</info>

<info>Golden Gate Park. Hundreds of hippies and broken robots have 
turned out for Bend-Aid.</info>

<speak who="EMCEE">
Gentle-hippies, put your filthy hands 
together for the folk stylings of Cylon 
and Garfunkel!</speak>

<info>A robot with a guitar and man who looks like Art Garfunkel walk 
onto the stage.</info>

<speak who="GARFUNKEL">
Here's a song that was beautiful when 
it was performed by my ancestor, Art.</speak>

<info>He starts to sing Scarborough Fair.</info>

<info>(singing)</info> Are you going to Scarborough Fair?

<info>Cylon cuts in with a mechanical voice.</info>

<speak who="CYLON AND GARFUNKEL">
<info>(singing)</info> Parsley, sage, rosemary and 
thyme.</speak>

<speak who="GARFUNKEL">
<info>(singing)</info> Remember me to one who loves 
there,</speak>

<speak who="CYLON AND GARFUNKEL">
<info>(singing)</info> She once was a true love of 
mine.</speak>

<info>The VW pulls up behind the crowd and the crew get out. They 
look around and the hippies sitting and lying on the grass.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We're home.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Well, let's earn some bread.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Amy puts a sign on the window that says "Genuine 
Love Beads, $5.00". Fry and Leela are holding some of Zoidberg's 
pearls that have been strung together.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Brothers and sisters, get your love 
beads. Can't journey to the centre of 
your mind without love beads!</speak>

<info>Hippies gather around the van.</info>

<speak who="HIPPIE #1">
Wow, look at these colours. These'll 
go great with my soul.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Glad you like them. I've been making 
fine jewellery for years, apparently.</speak>

<speak who="HIPPIE #2">
I'll take three.</speak>

<speak who="HIPPIE #3">
Give me one, man!</speak>

<speak who="HIPPIE #4">
I'll trade you a bad poem!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="EMCEE">
And now, stand up and turn on your 
hidden tape recorders for...Beck! With 
special guest, Bender the broken robot.</speak>

<info>The stage curtain lifts and Bender and Beck are lowered from 
the ceiling. Broken robots in the audience cheer and the band 
plays Sexx Laws from the album Midnite Vultures.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> Bender rules!</speak>

<speak who="HIPPIE #5">
Groove on, man!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Rock it, Bender!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Play that thing!</speak>

<info>Bender and Beck hit the stage and liquid spills out of Beck's 
jar.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(shouting)</info> Can't you hear those cavalry 
drums

Hijacking your equilibrium...

</speak><speak who="BENDER">
Whoa-oh, yeah!</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(shouting)</info> ...Midnight hags in the mausoleum...</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Day has turned to dusk, the crowd has thinned and 
the band is still playing the same song. Bender scrapes his chest 
and the song ends. The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
Thank you. That song doesn't usually 
last three hours, but we got into a 
serious thing...and then I forgot how 
it ended. Anyway, one last item of business 
before we go.</speak>

<info>Cylon and Garfunkel walk onto the stage with a big cheque.</info>

<speak who="GARFUNKEL">
Bender, to start your foundation for 
broken robots, here's a big cardboard 
cheque for $14,000.</speak>

<speak who="CYLON">
It's been an emotional day for me.</speak>

<info>They prop it up next to Bender, who starts to cry.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> I don't know what to say.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Then maybe you should sing it. Lay it 
down boys.</speak>

<info>The band starts to play Bender's song and the lights dim.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ladies, gentlemen, smoking heaps of 
machinery......this is a song called 
My Broken Friend.</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<info>(singing)</info> People say my broken friend is useless

But I say his mind is free

There's lots of things my mangled robot friend could be

<speak who="BECK">
Kick it!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> He could make a good...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> ...hatrack</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> He only has to stand there</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Or a cheap...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> ...doorstop</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> He doesn't need to move</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Or a great big...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> ...giant Thermos</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> With a twist-off top</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> That would be good for soup</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> He could be a storage closet...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> ...For outdated pants</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
I like 'em tight!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> My broken friend could do 
it all...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Just give him a chance!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> That robot has a tragic secret

That I'd like to share...

</speak><speak who="BECK">
For real?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...My broken friend is closer 
to me

Than an ass to a chair...

</speak><speak who="BECK">
Hm.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...That robot's name I never 
told you...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Who's that?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...You could not foresee...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
C'mon, give it up.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...I'll say it loud and sing 
it proud...</speak>

<speak who="BENDER AND BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> His name is you and me.</speak>

<info>Bender starts dancing.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Don't melt me down into a 
crowbar</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
<info>(singing)</info> It suffers alone</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Just 'cause I can't move my 
arms and legs</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Hey.</speak>

<info>The robots look around and Bender flails his arms and legs around.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Or toss me into a trash can...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Bender, what are you doing?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Just 'cause I can't cook 
you ham and eggs...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
What are you doing?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Don't crush me into an 
anchor...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
What's the dealy-o?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Just 'cause I can't jump 
and dance and sing...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Hold it! What? No!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...I'm telling you, my broken 
friend...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
B-Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Put your hands in the air 
like you just don't care!</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
No!</speak>

<info>Bender bounds off across the stage.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> I'm telling you, my broken 
friend...</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Cut it!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> ...Can do 'most anything!</speak>

<info>He slides across the stage on his knees.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
Cut it!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Cut it!</speak>

<info>The crowds shouts and boos. Bender's harmonica holder falls 
off. He looks at himself.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Curse my natural showmanship!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #1">
<info>(shouting)</info> You big fat fraud! You're 
not really broken!</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT #2">
<info>(shouting)</info> But you will be in a minute! 
Bum-rush the stage!</speak>

<info>The broken robots crawl and hobble towards Bender. Bender backs 
away.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT #3">
Get him!</speak>

<info>Bender folds the cheque away into his chest cabinet, grabs a 
rope and swings over the crowd, screaming like Tarzan. He flies 
towards the VW.</info>

<info>Cut to: VW. He flies through sunroof, slams his head against 
it and lands in the driver's seat. He shifts it into gear and 
speeds off in a cloud of smoke. The others hang on.</info>

<info>Cut to: Golden Gate Park.</info>

<speak who="HIPPIE #6">
Oh harsh, I didn't get my beads.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg coughs and beads rain down on the hippies. Beck watches 
from the stage.</info>

<speak who="BECK">
You, minion, lift up my arm.  After 
him!</speak>

<info>His bus pulls up and he gets on with Cylon and Garfunkel, the 
heads of Neil Young and Joni Mitchell, and Wailing Fungus. The 
bus ploughs through a crowd and a chase sequence lifted from 
Bullit begins.</info>

<info>San Francisco Street. The VW flies down the road, pursued by 
Beck's bus.</info>

<info>Cut to: VW. Bender looks in the rear-view mirror.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well everyone, prepare to get your guts 
kicked out by folk singers.</speak>

<info>Cut to: San Francisco Street. The buses drive past a green VW 
Beetle once, twice, three times, four times...</info>

<info>Cut to: Chinatown. A Chinese street parade is interrupted as 
the buses drive past, blowing the Chinese dragon off a caterpillar-like 
alien.</info>

<speak who="CATERPILLAR ALIEN">
What is this? The Year of the Jerk?</speak>

<info>The VW rounds another corner, carving up another green Beetle.</info>

<info>Cut to: VW.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hurry, the Golden Gate Bridge. Put the 
metal to the pedal to the other metal.</speak>

<info>Bender floors it. Beck's bus gets closer and bumps them. They 
scream. The bus passes a sign that reads "Golden Gate Hoverbridge".</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh no, I forgot this is a hoverbridge.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And I forgot this isn't a hovercar.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Is any of that a problem?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Not if you've lived a life without regret.</speak>

<info>He screams. The VW flies off the edge of the road and plummets 
to the ground below.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll save me!</speak>

<info>He leans out of the window and grabs a cable.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Quick, grab his footcups.</speak>

<info>They all grab Bender's feet.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey? What? No.</speak>

<info>The VW lands softly on a rocky outcrop by the water. Bender 
has pulled the wire and it is very tense.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Phew!</speak>

<info>They all let go of Bender and the tense wire launches him into 
the air. The gang watch him fly off. Leela shrugs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bummer.</speak>

<info>Fisherman's Worf. The fat guy from the Titanic and a thin woman 
buy some food from Tarty McTang's and hear Bender screaming from 
above.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting)</info> Someone fat get in my way! 
<info>(talking)</info> Ah, I'm broken again. I can't 
move any part of me.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Good.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm really sorry I lied, Beck. All I 
ever wanted was to make music with you. 
I never meant to hurt anyone, or help 
anyone.</speak>

<speak who="BECK">
Bender, that's some played-out, new-jack, 
horsecrap. But I know you don't mean 
it so, apology accepted.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
So, I can, uh, keep the cheque?</speak>

<speak who="GARFUNKEL">
Over my dead career!</speak>

<info>He takes the cheque out of Bender's chest cabinet.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, it was worth a shot.</speak>

<info>He gets up and the other three leave.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The bus flies away and Bender sighs. The VW floats 
past. Fry, Leela, Amy and Zoidberg are paddling up the river 
in it. A seal sits on the roof.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> C'mon, Bender. If you're 
done scamming Beck, we're heading home.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright, alright. Let me just do one 
thing to cheer myself up.</speak>

<info>He takes a magnet from Ye Olde Tourist Trappe and puts it on 
his head. His pupils go wild and he starts to sing.</info>

Fry cracked corn

And I don't care

Leela cracked corn

I still don't care

Bender cracked corn

And he is great!

Take that you stupid corn!

<info>He wades out into the water to the VW.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>