<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 314

<title>TIME KEEPS ON SLIPPING</title>

<author>Ken Keeler</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: For Proper Viewing, Take Red Pill 
Now.</info>

<info>Central Park Lake. People enjoy themselves on the lake, sunbathing, 
barbecuing and fishing. The Planet Express crew are there. Hermes 
throws a frisbee.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Go get it, boy!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg runs after it, catches it and eats it. Leela eats a 
sandwich and Fry kneels in front of her.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So, Leela, how about a romantic ride 
in one of those swan boats? They're 
kinda dangerous but I finally mastered 
them.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Those aren't swan boats, they're swans.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh. That explains these boat eggs.</speak>

<info>He holds up some eggs. A shadow creeps over him and he gasps. 
It's a flying saucer. Crowds flee, screaming, as it lands by 
the lake.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wha?</speak>

<info>A screaming man runs past Amy, who is sunbathing topless, is 
briefly distracted by her, then carries on screaming. Amy sees 
the flying saucer and screams. A ramp comes down from the ship 
and a door opens. Nine basketball players walk out, dribbling 
basketballs. The leader, a guy with an afro, steps forward.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Pitiful ballplayers of Earth, I am Ethan 
"Bubblegum" Tate, commander of the Harlem 
Globetrotters.  For generations, your 
puny planet has lived in peace with 
the Globetrotter Homeworld. But now, 
for no reason, we challenge you to defend 
your honour on the basketball court. 
Will no one meet our challenge? Have 
none of you pathetic Earthlings game?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> What happens if we lose?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Nothing. There's nothing at stake and 
no threat - beyond the shame of defeat!</speak>

<info>A player passes him a basketball with Earth on it and he drops 
it into a bin. People gasp and Zoidberg holds Hermes back.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
This will not stand!  I'll take you 
on, you air-balling bozos.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
You, old man? Sweet Clyde, laugh derisively 
at him.</speak>

<info>Another player laughs.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I may be an old man - in fact, I'm fairly 
sure I am - but I'll put you Globetrotters 
in your place with my team of mutant 
atomic supermen!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Hooray, professor!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth has gathered the 
staff in front of a big curtain.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Behold: My mutant atomic supermen.</speak>

<info>He draws back the curtain to reveal five little men in nappies 
in a hamster cage.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
They're only a foot high, professor.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well, they're still young. Mere atomic 
super boys, really. We'll need to speed 
up their growth with time particles 
called Chronitons.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aren't those the particles that destroyed 
an entire civilisation -</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news, everyone. You're off to the 
Tempest Nebula to gather Chronitons.</speak>

<info>Tempest Nebula. Fry, Leela and Bender are tethered to the ship 
and holding jars. Fry and Bender wear space suits. Leela plucks 
a particle from the nebula and hole starts to burn away where 
the particle was. She puts it in the jar. Bender lets them glide 
into his mouth, then he spits them into a jar.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, Leela. Look at me!</speak>

<info>He takes the valve out of his helmet and his head inflates. 
He puts it back in and it shrinks to normal size. He coughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Your face can take a lot of punishment. 
That's good to know.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
There's a lot about my face you don't 
know. Perhaps you and it could get better 
acquainted over dinner.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Alright, cool your jets, hotshot.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
C'mon, Leela, why won't you go out with 
me? We both know there's something there.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No, I mean cool your jets. They're melting 
Bender's face.</speak>

<info>Fry turns around and sees his jets turning Bender red-hot.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting)</info> Ow! Oh my God! Ow!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. The crew return from the nebula. 
Leela holds a huge bottle of the particles.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Here you go. Hot off the nebula.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
None too soon. While you were gone the 
Trotters held a news conference to announce 
that I was a jive sucker.  Behold! My 
invincible nuclear mutants.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hi!</speak>

<speak who="ARACHNEON">
Hello!</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. The bleachers around the basketball court 
are packed. Marv Albert commentates.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Marv Albert here at Madison Cube Garden 
where the Harlem Globerotters take on 
a squad of atomic supermen in what promises 
to be a by-the-numbers athletic contest 
with no surprises whatsoever.  Here's 
the tip-off. Globetrotter ball. Sweet 
Clyde Dixon to Bubblegum Tate. Drives 
down-court - and Curly Joe from the 
rear.</speak>

<info>Curly Joe grabs the five-armed mutant's ass. Zoidberg laughs.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
That one grabbed his behindus!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Shh!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Quiet!</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Who dares laugh at the Jesters of Dunk? 
We came to terrify and humiliate you 
- not tickle your funnybones. Watch 
as I embarrass your civilisation by 
passing the ball to Curly Joe.  Only 
to have it remain in my hands with elastic. 
And perhaps this will wipe the smiles 
from your faces.</speak>

<info>He passes to another player and he throws it to the net.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Goose goes up... Rejected! Growtrium 
from half-court.  Yes!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Supermen lead 45-42. Arachneon with 
the steal, to Thorias. Thorias from 
downtown!  Yes! He's really showing 
us what a man with a cannon in his chest 
can do!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No showboarding, you atomic hotdog!</speak>

<info>He weakly throws a chair and a buzzer buzzes.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
And that's the half, with the Supermen 
up 48-42. Surprisingly dull, so far. 
Bubblegum, the Trotters are down by 
six. Reactions?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
It was always our plan to trail at the 
half. Thus deepening Earth's eventual 
humiliation. Also: What game were the 
refs watching?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The referee throws the ball up. Curly Joe sits on 
the scoreboard with the ball, just out of reach of Growtrium. 
He laughs.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Curly Joe, easily amused by his own 
antics......continues to wreak havoc 
on -</speak>

<info>Everything flashes and the players suddenly change position. 
The ball is now spinning on Tate's finger.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
What the?  Did everything just jump 
around? Or did my brain just stroke 
off there for a second?</speak>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Ladies and gentlemen, something very 
strange has just happened in this basketball 
game between space clowns and atomic 
monsters.</speak>

<info>Tate shrugs and throws the ball. The laser-eyed mutant shoots 
a laser beam at the ball in it bursts into flames. Everything 
jumps around again and the five-armed mutant finds himself flying 
through the air. He hits the back board and lands on the hoop. 
The crowd groans.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Time-out! Time-out!</speak>

<info>The referee blows the whistle.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What's happening?</speak>

<info>Bender shakes.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
We seem to be lurching forward randomly 
in time, like a needle skipping on a 
record player.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
What's causing it? Is it my outfit?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No. It must have something to do with 
those time particles I used to grow 
the Supermen. Time and space are ripping 
apart at the seams.</speak>

<info>The Supermen gasp. Thorias releases the ball from his cannon 
and it hits Arachneon and splats him.</info>

<speak who="THORIAS">
Oops.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, great. Now, on top of everything, 
we need a new fifth man.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ooh, ooh, ooh, put me in, professor. 
I wanna show Leela my skills.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hmm. Will said skills pay the bills?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Who cares? We're 35 points ahead with 
two minutes left. What could possibly 
-</speak>

<info>Time skips. Fry is standing in the middle of the court holding 
the ball. The crowd boos as Tate takes the ball and scores. The 
game ends.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Globetrotters win, 244-86. A dark day 
for humanity, folks. We have been beaten...in 
basketball.</speak>

<info>The Globetrotters cheer and taunt Earth.</info>

<speak who="CURLY JOE">
Yeah, that's ow we do it!</speak>

<speak who="SWEET CLYDE">
How's that?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
You are all fools of the highest calibre.</speak>

<info>Everyone starts to leave.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I don't know what you did, Fry, but 
once again you screwed up. Now all the 
planets are gonna start cracking wise 
about our mamas.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I'm just glad my fat, ugly mama isn't 
alive to see this day.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Enough about your promiscuous mother, 
Hermes. We have bigger problems. This 
time disruption is extremely serious.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Damn right, brother man. This chronological 
wang-dang-doodle could destroy the very 
matrix of reality.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Tate? What do you know about this?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Not much, yet. But I am senior lecturer 
of physics at Globetrotter U. And I 
like to help you investigate.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You're that Bubblegum Tate?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Well I sure ain't his grandma. Now look 
here, prof......I think we got ourselves 
an excess of Chronitons in the subatomic 
interstices.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes, I see. Something involving that 
many big words could easily destabilise 
time itself.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Is that a problem?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Indeed so. At this rate, by Tuesday 
it will be Thursday; By Wednesday, it 
will be August and by Thursday, it will 
be the end of existence as we know it.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
I'll have to ask you to clear out now. 
The circus need to set up for tomorrow's 
big -</speak>

<info>Time skips and the Planet Express staff and the Globetrotters 
find themselves in the middle of a circus. An elephant trumpets 
and they scatter.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The staff watch a news report.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
Time continues to skip forward randomly. 
Details at 11.</speak>

<info>Time skips and it is already 11pm.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
This is the news at 11. The mysterious 
an unexplained -</speak>

<info>Time skips.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
Turning to entertainment news, teen 
singer Wendy might just be the latest 
-</speak>

<info>Time skips.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
...won three Grammys last night -</speak>

<info>Time skips. The picture of Wendy behind her has a "2984 - 3002" 
caption below it.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
...found dead in her bathtub.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth turns the TV off.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Interesting. It's as if we behave normally 
during the time skips, but then we have 
no memory of it.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You mean we just -</speak>

<info>Time skips.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
...my, yes. Ooh, just like that. Any 
luck Bubblegum?</speak>

<info>In the corner of the room, Tate is wearing a lab coat and doing 
some equations on a board.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Not yet. Listen, I hope you don't mind 
if I dribble a little while I work.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Not if you'll grant me the same liberty.</speak>

<info>He wipes his mouth on his sleeve.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooh, ohh, Bubblegum? My name's Bender 
and I'm a huge fan of your work, both 
on and off the court. Can I be a Globetrotter?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Shut up, turkey.</speak>

<info>Bender sighs. Farnsworth swings something around.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Bubblegum, look at this. The background 
time radiation is fluctuating wildly.</speak>

<info>The needle on the time flux meter wobbles back and forth.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Good Lord. That sucker's shaking around 
like some fine, imported booty.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Say, I'm no physicist, but I think I 
know how to stop the skipping. We'll 
just -</speak>

<info>Time skips. Hermes is wearing a funky shirt and playing a steel 
drum while the others have formed a nude conga line.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
I don't know how this was supposed to 
work.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Professor, I hope you find out what's 
wrong before we skip right past my birth 
-</speak>

<info>Time skips. The lounge has streamers and balloons and banners 
around it in celebration of Amy's birthday. There is a cake on 
the coffee table and presents around it.</info>

<speak who="ALL">
Happy birthday, Amy.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hooray, look at all these presents!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I hope we all have as much tomorrow 
at my birth -</speak>

<info>Time skips. Zoidberg sits alone in the empty lounge. There is 
a tiny cupcake on the table with a candle in it. He looks around.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What?</speak>

<info>He sighs.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Corridor. Fry peeps around a door and attracts 
Leela's attention.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Psst, Leela. I've set up a time-proof 
shelter in the closet. There's only 
room for two, and you're the one I wanna 
share it with.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, that's so sweet. Let me see.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Closet. Leela looks inside. There is a mattress in the 
corner, candles, a black light and a bottle of champagne in a 
bucket of ice.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
How exactly will this protect us from 
time jumps?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Because when we're together 
in here, baby, time will stand still.</speak>

<info>Time skips. Fry has a black eye and Leela has gone.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Zoidberg looks over a chess board.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hmm.  Hmm.</speak>

<info>He picks up a piece and eats it. Enter Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dr. Zoidberg, can I talk to you about 
Fry?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Leela, I would be honoured.</speak>

<info>He moves aside on the couch for her.</info>

<info>Time skips. Leela is sat down and Zoidberg is watching TV, ignoring 
her.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
...Does the worst W.C. Fields imitation 
I've ever seen. Zoidberg!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Sorry, you must have been boring me.</speak>

<info>He turns the TV off.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
The thing is, Fry is very sweet. But 
he's so immature. I love his boyish 
charm but I hate his childishness.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
So he's not perfect. You don't wanna 
end up old and lonely like Zoidberg! 
You were saying?</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic. Farnsworth sniffs around with the smellescope. 
Tate and Bender are with him.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah, there is it. The Tempest Nebula. 
Take a whiff through the smellescope.</speak>

<info>Tate puts his spinning ball on Farnsworth's head where it carries 
on spinning. He sniffs and recoils.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
What's that funky jazz?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The odour of pure time leaking. When 
my crew removed the Chronitons, it destabilised 
the nebula, causing time skips throughout 
the universe.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooh, let Bubblegum tell it.</speak>

<info>Tate walks over to a basket of basketballs.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Pretend these basketballs are time particles, 
my silver honky. As the nebula bounce-passes 
them off us......they cause these dents, 
or "time skips".</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You are so smart!</speak>

<info>Tate looks at a map.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Hold up. What if we were to move this 
cluster of starts to these algebraic 
co-ordinates?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Their gravity might just divert the 
Chronitons to the empty side of the 
universe.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Yeah. But is it possible? Moving stars 
would require one bad-ass gravity pump. 
And we'd need all the money on Earth 
to -</speak>

<info>Time skips and Tate and Farnsworth find themselves in the oval 
office. Tate is holding a bad-ass gravity pump proposal.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
What the?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wha?</speak>

<info>They pick up a cheque for all of Earth's money that has been 
signed by Nixon's head.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
Here's the funding for your gravity 
pump. But it damn well better work! 
We can't spend all of Earth's money 
every day. Now, how long will it take 
to build?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
It won't be easy, Nixon. A jim-jam this 
complex might take months or even -</speak>

<info>Time skips and Tate and Farnsworth are in a large building.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah, there we are. One gravity pump. 
Powerful enough to move the stars themselves. 
Now to begin the arduous task of attaching 
it to the ship so th -</speak>

<info>Time skips. Farnsworth is in the Planet Express hangar watching 
the ship take off with the gravity pump attached to its roof.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Off you go - apparently.</speak>

<info>The gravity pump pushes a star forward with some blue stuff.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
<info>(from ship)</info> Easy, Leela. Just finger-roll 
that star to the cosmic basket.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Just a few...more...hundred...thousand...miles. 
There!</speak>

<info>The ship moves the star into place next to over ten others which 
have been placed around the nebula.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
<info>(from ship)</info> Nothing but nebula!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. Leela waves the time flux meter around.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We'll have to run some tests back on 
Earth, but I think we've stopped the 
time skips.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Alright!</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Jamming!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hooray for Leela!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And what better way to celebrate our 
success than by me showing Bubblegum 
the Globetrotter uniform I made myself!</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Let me see.  Hello, lawsuit!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela, I want you to know I think the 
way you moved those stars around was 
really wonderful. I got you something.</speak>

<info>He opens a bottle of champagne and pours it into two glasses. 
Leela gasps.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Moderately-priced, domestic, non-vintage 
champagne? How did you know?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You deserve it. I mean, nobody ever 
stops to tell you what a great captain 
you are.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aww, that is so true and sweet.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You're smart, you're beautiful, and 
best of all, you'll go out with me-ee?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, please try to understand. You're 
a man, I'm a woman. We're just too different.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, Leela. Bubblegum might let me organise 
a bake sale for the Globetrotter wives. 
Can you teach me to make cupcakes?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Alright, but I wanna lick the beaters.</speak>

<info>She and Bender leave. Fry sighs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I got her champagne, I opened it. What 
does a guy have to do?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
86 the chump stuff, F-man. It's time 
to win Leela's heart with a big-showy, 
three-point romantic gesture.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hmm. Maybe this is the moment to show 
her my real surprise.</speak>

<info>He sits in the pilot's chair and moves the ship into gear. Leela 
walks in.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, what are you doing?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Uh-oh. Time to boogie on down to the 
sauna!</speak>

<info>He leaves and Fry presses some buttons.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Look. I've been studying how to pilot 
the ship. Impressed?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah, actually. You're doing OK. The 
core reactor temperature's nominal, 
the blinker's off.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I learned how to work the gravity pump 
too. In case we need to move more stars. 
So are we dating now?</speak>

<info>Leela groans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Is that what this is all about? Please, 
just cut it out now.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Look, Leela. I know there's some perfect, 
amazing thing I can do to make you love 
me, and when I figure out what it is 
-</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, stop. I don't wanna hurt you, but 
there is absolutely, positively no way 
that you and I will ever, ever -</speak>

<info>Time skips. Leela is wearing a wedding dress and Fry is wearing 
a tuxedo. They are in the Temple of Robotology.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
...Man and wife. You may kiss the bride.</speak>

<info>Fry grins and kisses her. The other Planet Express crew and 
Tate throw confetti. Marv Albert is on a seat.</info>

<speak who="ALBERT">
Yes!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The other Globetrotters and the remaining Supermen 
are at the wedding too.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Woo-hoo!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
He looks radiant!</speak>

<info>Time skips. Leela's bouquet is in Fry's mouth.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ye Gods, Bubblegum, we failed. The time 
skips haven't stopped at all.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Even in these formal shorts, I feel 
like a failure.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You tricked me into marrying you, didn't 
you?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Of course not.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
How'd you do it? Drugs in the champagne? 
Hypnosis?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No! Drugs are for losers and hypnosis 
is for losers with big, weird eyebrows. 
I don't know what amazing thing I did 
you make you love me but, whatever it 
was, we're married now. We've got the 
rest of our lives to work -</speak>

<info>Time skips. Leela and Fry are standing before Judge Whitey in 
Famous Original Ray's Superior Court.</info>

<speak who="WHITEY">
Divorce is final.</speak>

<info>He bangs his gavel.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well, let's divide up the china. I guess 
I'll take the NFC helmets and you can 
have the AFC helmets.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Fine. Break my heart again.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Fry sits at the conference table 
and Amy, Hermes, Bender, Zoidberg and Tate are with him. Zoidberg 
puts his claw on Fry.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Don't be so hard on yourself, Fry. You 
lost the woman of your dreams, but you 
still have Zoidberg. You all still have 
Zoidberg.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
How did I do it? How did I get Leela 
to love me? I've got to figure it out.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Maybe you're just a fantastic lover, 
Fry.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Um, no.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I don't know what I'm doing.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Maybe she'd come back to you if your 
best friend Bender were a Globetrotter. 
What do you say, Bubblegum?</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Hell, no.</speak>

<info>Bender groans and Fry sighs.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, it's hopeless. I did something so 
great that it won Leela's heart and 
I'll never, ever know what it was. My 
life is empty.</speak>

<info>He sniffs.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(sexfully)</info> Zoidberg!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic. Farnsworth and Tate look over Tate's 
equations.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No wonder we failed to stop the time 
skips. Diverting Chronitons is mathematically 
impossible. I knew I should have checked 
your showboating Globetrotter algebra.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Man, I thought you knew that algebra 
was all razzmatazz. A Globetrotter always 
saves the good algebra for the final 
minutes.</speak>

<info>Bender laughs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Vintage Bubblegum.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The time skips are worse than ever now. 
Isolated spots are jumping by years 
at a time. Look.</speak>

<info>They look through the window.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Social Security Office. Two kids watch an old 
man walk out.</info>

<speak who="KID">
Stupid senior citizens. Why should we 
have to pay for their social security 
benefits?</speak>

<info>Time skips and the kids turn into old men.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN">
I deserve free money!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Attic.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well, I'm stumped. We'll have to call 
in the finest scientific minds in the 
univ -</speak>

<info>Time skips and the other Globetrotters appear behind them.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Perhaps we could explode the whole damned 
nebula. What do you think, Curly Joe?</speak>

<speak who="CURLY JOE">
No, man. An explosion big enough to 
destroy that mama would take out half 
the universe.</speak>

<speak who="SWEET CLYDE">
You gotta Globetrotter that explosion 
up a little, Farnsy. Make it an implosion.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
By God, Sweet Clyde is right. An implosion 
might just form a black hole that would 
stop more Chronitons from escaping.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Whoa. Slow that brain train down, prof. 
We'd need some kind of doomsday device 
to initiate an implosion like that.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Doomsday device? Ah, now the ball's 
in Farnsworth's court.  I suppose I 
could part with one and still be feared.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Give me some skin, prof. I'm making 
you an honorary Globetrotter. In fact, 
everybody in this room's an honorary 
Globetrotter.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hooray!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Yes!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'm a Globetrotter!</speak>

<info>Bender runs in.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(gasping)</info> Did you just say -</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Too late, hot plate.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, crap.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. Two Globetrotters attach a doomsday 
device to a mechanism and it rises into the ship's cargo bay. 
The other Globetrotters shake hands with the Planet Express staff.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
We must leave now, for we are needed 
elsewhere. But we wish you Godspeed.</speak>

<info>They leave, dribbling their balls. Bender stops Tate.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Please, please let me come with you. 
I can make myself taller.</speak>

<info>He stretches his legs.</info>

<speak who="TATE">
Bender, you can talk trash, you can 
handle the ball. But look in your heart 
and ask yourself: Are you funky enough 
to be a Globetrotter? Are you?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yes.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Are you?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I mean, with time, my funk level could 
-</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Are you?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(sadly)</info> No.</speak>

<speak who="TATE">
Deal with it.</speak>

<info>He leaves and Bender returns to his normal size and begins to 
cry.</info>

<info>The ship flies towards the nebula and Bender emerges from the 
starboard torpedo tube holding the doomsday device. He is tethered 
to the ship and wearing a jet pack. The tether jerks and Bender 
lets go of the doomsday device.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh! No!</speak>

<info>He quickly grabs it again.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Careful with that doomsday device, 
Bender.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What does it matter? I'll never be a 
Globetrotter. My life, and, by extension, 
everyone else's, is meaningless.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Roger.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit. She turns the radio off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela, about the wedding. I don't know 
what I did to make you love me, and 
I don't think I tricked you into it, 
but maybe I did. And if I did, I'm sorry.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's OK, Fry. You know we'll always 
be friends, right?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah. But I don't guess anything I could 
do will ever make you feel the same 
way about me that I do about you.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I guess not.</speak>

<info>She takes his hand, kisses him on the cheek and walks away. 
Bender walks in, dusting his hands.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, the doomsday device is ready. 
Maybe blasting this quadrant of space 
into a hell storm of flaming nothingness 
will cheer me up a little.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK. Let me just take the ship out to 
a safe distance.  Actually, I think 
I'll go down and prep the detonator. 
Fry, why don't you take the helm?</speak>

<info>Fry smiles and sits in the chair. She leaves.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
She's so great. I feel like I can almost 
remember the magical thing I did to 
make her love me. But I guess I never 
will.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sorry, buddy. I too know what it's like 
to have a dream I'll never achieve.</speak>

<info>He walks out, slowly whistling the Globetrotter tune. Fry presses 
some buttons and the ship flies away from the nebula. He glances 
out of the window and sees something.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh!  That's how I must have done it! 
I moved the stars themselves to write 
her a love note in the sky.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Detonation in three, two, one.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(screaming)</info> Nooo!  Did you see it? Did 
you see it?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
The explosion?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No, not the explosion!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Then what?</speak>

<info>Fry thinks for a moment and lowers his head.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(quietly)</info> Nothing.</speak>

<info>Bender starts to whistle Sweet Georgia Brown again as Fry looks 
back through the window at the black hole.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>