<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 402

<title>A TALE OF TWO SANTAS</title>

<author>Bill Odenkirk</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: This Episode Performed Entirely By 
Sock Puppets.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Fry, Leela and Bender sit on the couch 
watching TV.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
In what has become a winter tradition, 
members of the Zarlon 7 Polar Bear Club 
today took the plunge into a river of 
liquid ammonia.</speak>

<info>The TV shows people jumping in.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
There were no survivors.</speak>

<info>Linda chuckles.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
Takes all kinds! And now, with his 
annual Xmas Message, here's the head 
of the Xmas Safety Council, the head 
of Walter Cronkite.</speak>

<speak who="CRONKITE">
Seasons warnings, Linda and Morbo.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
This guy's too trustworthy. What's his 
angle?</speak>

<speak who="CRONKITE">
In all the tinsel and terror of the 
holiday season we too often underestimate 
that murderous brute better known as 
Santa Claus. With images of last year's 
gingerbread massacre freshly baked into 
our memories, I remind you to bolt your 
doors, say goodbye to your pets and 
lock your children in the closet. This 
is Walter Cronkite saying "I told you 
so".</speak>

<info>Some wood appears over the TV. Hermes is boarding it up.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Sacred ball of West and Eastern Samoa. 
We've got to secure for Santa's arrival.</speak>

<info>Fry presses the remote.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Just as well. I'm getting tired of this 
wood show.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. Fry, Bender and Leela are struggling 
to get the armour-plated chimney cover over the chimney. Farnsworth 
walks in and shakes his fists.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Cover that fireplace, confound you! 
I've only a few years to live. I don't 
wanna spend them dead.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
We're pushing as hard as we can.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh! Pushing!</speak>

<info>He pushes it the other way and hurls Fry and Leela over the 
top. Farnsworth sits down.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, we're doomed! Every year we're doomed. 
Thanks be I had these bullet-proof shutters 
installed.</speak>

<info>He flips up the arm of the chair and presses a button.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. Grey armour covers the building 
and knocks Amy off a ladder. She screams. A neon light on the 
hangar roof spells "Trespassers Will Be Shot" and Deck The Halls 
With Boughs Of Holly plays.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Attic Room.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Bring it on, Santa! That bloodthirsty 
cadaver junkie can't touch us as long 
as we're not stupid enough to leave 
this building.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah!</speak>

<info>Bender breathes a sigh of relief.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
In a related matter, you'll be delivering 
this sack of children's letters directly 
to Santa at his death fortress on Neptune.</speak>

<info>Fry, Leela and Bender look shocked.</info>

<info>Outside Planet Express. The ship takes off and gets one of the 
landing legs stuck in the hangar roof. It pulls it free and flies 
away.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Fry, Leela and Bender are rummaging through 
the sack.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
These letters are real butt-nutters! 
Listen to this one: <info>(reading)</info> Dear 
Santa.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Girl's Bedroom.</info>

<speak who="GIRL">
<info>(thinking and writing)</info> Please, please 
don't bring me any gifts. The bicycle 
you fired at me last year from your 
bicycle gun really tore up my insides.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Awful! Let's read some more. <info>(reading)</info> 
Dear Santa.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Boy's Bedroom.</info>

<speak who="BOY">
<info>(thinking and writing)</info> Please bring 
me a coffin for Grandpa. You choked 
him with a chestnut last year and he's 
beginning to smell a lot like Xmas if 
you know what I mean.</speak>

<info>A stiff corpse sits in a rocking chair by a window.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
It's not fair. In my day Xmas was supposed 
to bring people together, not blow them 
apart!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Sure, but who's going to do anything 
about it? Certainly not us. No, sir!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Certainly yes us! Uh-huh, sir! We've 
gotta bring back the kind of Xmas I 
remember.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry's right. It's time to sit on Santa's 
lap -- and hard!</speak>

<info>Neptune Surface. The ship lands outside a little town called 
Jolly Junction at the north pole. There is a the sound of gunfire 
and barking dogs. The cargo bay lift comes down with Fry, Leela, 
Bender and the sack of letters. Leela sees something.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, look! A cute little welcoming party.</speak>

<info>Neptunians walk towards them holding hands.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
Hey! Wanna buy a tiny little kidney?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
I'll let you punch me for a buck.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, look, we've got mail for Santa. 
Are you his elves?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
We're not elves. We're Neptunians.</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
We're just shrimp-y because he doesn't 
feed us.</speak>

<info>Neptunian #2 grabs Fry's hand and slaps himself with it.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
You hit me! You owe me a dollar.</speak>

<info>Jolly Junction. Neptunians are beating each other up and smashing 
bottles over each other's heads. Bender drags the sack down the 
icy street. Two Neptunians shout from in a house.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #3">
Hey, you got any food? Old teabags, 
chewed gum, apple cores? Come on! We're 
starving here!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But you live in a gingerbread house.</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #4">
Hey! It's food or shelter, not both.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You lazy runts! Don't you get paid for 
making the toys?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #4">
Who said "toys"?</speak>

<info>All over the street Neptunians stop and look at Bender.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
Toys? Toys? Who said "toys"?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
False alarm, folks! There's no reason 
to make toys since Santa judges everyone 
to be naughty.</speak>

<info>He points at the toy factory. It has a sign on it reading "Toy 
Works Closed. Coming Soon: Crackhouse".</info>

<speak who="FRY">
That's it! I'm gonna deliver a gift 
of my boot up Santa's chimney. Where 
is he?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
There! In his ice fortress.</speak>

<info>He points up a mountain. The fortress is at the top and lightning 
flashes around it.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We'll need help getting in. Any volunteers?</speak>

<info>None of the Neptunians raise their hand.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
I'll help you!</speak>

<info>Neptunian #2 sees Neptunian #1 has raised both of their hands.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
Ah, phooey!</speak>

<info>Outside Ice Fortress. The Neptunians carry the sack of letters 
up the winding track in a wheelbarrow. They pass a cardboard 
Santa with his arm stretched out like at an amusement park. He 
holds a sign reading "If You Are Taller Than This Prepare To 
Die". A circular saw comes out of the hand and cuts their hats 
off. They pass some dogs who bark Jingle Bells at them. A bird 
lands on the electric fence and gets sizzled. Neptunian #2 picks 
it up.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
An omen?</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
Dinner!</speak>

<info>He takes it and puts it down his trousers.</info>

<info>Ice Fortress. Santa sits in a chair at an enormous screen. He 
laughs maniacally.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Let's see who's been naughty, and who's 
been naughty!  Mobsters beating up a 
shopkeeper for protection money. Very 
naughty!  Shopkeeper's not paying their 
protection money. Exactly as naughty! 
I saw that!  Huh?</speak>

<info>He turns around and sees the Neptunians bring in the wheelbarrow.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
We brought your mail.</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
Don't you ever knock? Who knows what 
naughty things I could be watching? 
I get New Orleans on this thing, you 
know!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
Don't kill us!</speak>

<info>They run off. The sack rustles. Inside are Fry, Leela and Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Santa's a robot, so we should be able 
to destroy him with a logical paradox. 
Bender, you'd better cover your ears.</speak>

<info>She tears open the bag and they leap out. Santa's eyes turn 
evil.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Holy night! Intruders!</speak>

<info>He picks up a missile launcher and aims it at Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hold it Santa!  Consider this: You are 
programmed to destroy the naughty. But 
many of those you destroy are in fact, 
nice. I submit to you, that you are 
naughty, and logically, you must destroy 
yourself.</speak>

<info>Sparks come from Santa's neck. He jitters and his head explodes. 
Fry and Leela cheer but he immediately grows a new head.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Nice try. But my head was built with 
paradox-absorbing crumple-zones.</speak>

<info>He raises the missile launcher again. Leela and Fry duck out 
the way. He aims it at Bender who is still covering his ears. 
He sees Santa and runs off. They run down a corridor and Santa 
shoots missiles at them. They duck into an elevator and a missile 
wedges itself in the door.</info>

<info>Cut to: Elevator. The crew are huddled in a corner. Leela frantically 
presses the down button. The elevator goes down and cuts off 
the top of the missile. It bleeps on the floor. The crew scream.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ice Fortress. Fry and Bender run out followed 
by Leela who is carrying the warhead.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wait! This is what we're running from!</speak>

<info>She tosses the warhead back into the elevator. They get on a 
sled but it doesn't move.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Faster! Faster!</speak>

<info>The bomb explodes and propels the sled down the track. Sentry 
towers shoot at them and the Santa cut-out sticks out its circular 
saw.</info>

<info>Cut to: Jolly Junction. The Neptunians are cooking their bird 
on a spit. The sled slides past and sprays snow over the fire. 
They speed on round a corner and hit the steps of the ship. They 
get off and run inside.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Everyone sits down and Leela presses 
some buttons. The engines start but the ship just shakes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Why aren't we moving?</speak>

<info>Leela presses some more buttons and throws the wheel about.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I don't know. Usually when I do stuff 
like this the ship moves.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. Santa is holding the ship by its engines, 
stopping it from moving.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Ho ho-- Eh?</speak>

<info>He looks down. The radiation from the ships engines begins to 
melt the snow and ice beneath him and he sinks. He lets go of 
the ship and it lands again. The ice solidifies around him and 
the Neptunians and crew gather around.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
He's trapped!</speak>

<info>The Neptunians cheer. One runs forward and kicks him.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
Now we can make toys again!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(chanting)</info> Toys! Toys! Toys!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And I can deliver them. Billions and 
billions in one night.</speak>

<info>He takes Santa's hat and puts it on.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Hah! No human could do all that.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Evil Knievel could!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
Nuh-uh!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Santa's right. We need some sort of 
robot.  Aw, crap! I'm some sort of robot.</speak>

<info>Fry puts his hat on Bender's head. The Neptunians throw their 
hats in the air.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
Hooray!  Hooray!  Hooray!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Bender can't be Santa! He wasn't built 
to Yuletide specifications.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, yeah? Well I wasn't built to steal 
Leela's purse either.  But that didn't 
stop me.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender!</speak>

<info>She takes it from him. Bender turns to the Neptunians.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Bow to your new Santa!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
Our hero!</speak>

<info>Jolly Junction. The Neptunians sing and they skip towards the 
Toyworks.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> We are free and fairly sober,

With so many toys to build.

</speak><info>Cut to: Toyworks.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> The machines are kinda tricky,

Probably someone will be killed,

But we gladly work for nothing--

</speak><speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> Which is good because we don't 
intend to pay.</speak>

<speak who="ALL">
<info>(singing)</info> The elves are back to work 
today!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> Hooray!</speak>

<info>They saw logs and they go down a conveyor belt.</info>

We have just a couple hours,

To make several billion gifts,

<info>A Neptunian boxes some toys. Another adds the polystyrene S's.</info>

And the labour isn't easy--

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> Then you'll all work triple 
shifts,

You can make the job go quicker if you turn up the controls to 
super-speed.

</speak><info>She turns a dial to Lucy.</info>

<speak who="FRY LEELA AND BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> It's back to work on Xmas 
Eve!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(cheering)</info> Hooray!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> And though you're cold and 
sore and ugly,

Fry <info>(singing)</info> Let my happy smile warm your hearts--

</speak><speak who="NEPTUNIAN">
<info>(singing)</info> There's a toy lodged in my 
brain!</speak>

<info>There is a train in his head. Bender sits on the conveyor belt 
being sprayed Santa red by the Neptunians.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> We are getting awfully tired,

And we can't work any faster,

And we're very, very sorry--

</speak><speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Why you selfish little bastards,

Do you want the kids to think that Santa's just a crummy, empty-handed 
jerk?

</speak><info>He kicks a Neptunian.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> Then shut your yaps and back 
to work.</speak>

<info>Outside Toyworks. It is night. Santa's sleigh is being loaded 
with presents.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> Now it's very nearly Xmas,

And we've done the best we could,

</speak><speak who="FRY">
<info>(singing)</info> These toys soldiers are poorly 
painted,</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> And they're made from inferior 
wood.</speak>

<info>She snaps the soldier in half.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(singing)</info> I should give you all a beating,

But I really have to fly,

</speak><info>Santa is still stuck in the ice.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
<info>(singing)</info> If I weren't stuck here frozen,

I'd harpoon you in the eye,

</speak><speak who="NEPTUNIANS">
<info>(singing)</info> Now its back into our tenements,

To drown ourselves in rye,

</speak><speak who="LEELA">
<info>(singing)</info> You did the best you could, 
br>I guess that some of these gorillas 
are OK,</speak>

<info>The Neptunians cheer.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN">
We're adequate!</speak>

<speak who="ALL">
<info>(singing)</info> The elves have rescued Xmas 
Day! Hooray!</speak>

<info>Bender flies overhead and around Santa's fortress. Some presents 
fall out of the sleigh and the fortress defences shoot them.</info>

<info>He flies towards Earth and over the streets of New New York. 
A snowman in the street is wearing a helmet and holding a gun 
with a bayonet.</info>

<info>Jeffery Grant's Rooftop. Bender throws the sack over his shoulder. 
He sees bars on the chimney.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(stupid voice)</info> Duh! Gee, Bender, how 
you gonna get through these bars? (normal 
voice) I dunno, moron, suppose I bend 
them? <info>(stupid voice)</info> Duh, OK!</speak>

<info>He bends them.</info>

<info>Cut to: Jeffery Grant's Lounge. Bender falls into the fireplace. 
The family are hidden behind a couch.</info>

<speak who="GIRL">
Mommy! Mommy! Santa's through the perimeter!</speak>

<speak who="MRS GRANT">
This is it, kids. Take your suicide 
pills so you won't suffer.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No, wait! I'm the good Santa. I've got 
toys ... at very reasonable prices!</speak>

<speak who="JEFFERY">
Don't listen to him. He's the father 
of all lies and the uncle of all tricks!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But I come bearing Tri-ominos!</speak>

<info>Mrs. Grant stands up and raises a crowbar.</info>

<speak who="MRS GRANT">
Go for the shins!</speak>

<info>Bender runs back into the fireplace and scrambles up the chimney. 
The family hit him with metal objects and he cries out in pain.</info>

<info>Cut to: Jeffery Grant's Rooftop. Bender emerges from the chimney 
with his legs completely battered. He crawls into the sleigh.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(groaning)</info> One down...</speak>

<info>Bender lands on another roof and climbs down the chimney.</info>

<info>Cut to: Petunia's Lounge. The room is dark. lights go on and 
Petunia stands in the doorway in her nightie.</info>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Well, hello there, handsome!  Won't 
you have a cookie?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, don't mind if I do.  Ow! What's 
in these things?</speak>

<speak who="PETUNIA">
Why don't you slip into something more 
fiery?</speak>

<info>She blasts him with a flamethrower and he screams.</info>

<info>Cut to: Petunia's Rooftop. Bender flies out of the chimney and 
lands in a charred heap. His sack lands on him.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ow!</speak>

<info>Bender flies the sleigh through the sky. The Kwanzaabot flies 
alongside.</info>

<speak who="KWANZAABOT">
Yo, Kringle! What happened to you, doll?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, it's awful, Kwanzabot. Everyone 
hates me.</speak>

<speak who="KWANZAABOT">
At least they understand you, you know 
what I'm sayin'? Ain't nobody down with 
this Kwanza tip.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey! Maybe you could lend me a hand 
with these deliveries.</speak>

<info>Kwanzaabot makes a noise like a "no" buzzer.</info>

<speak who="KWANZAABOT">
No time! I gotta hand out the traditional 
Kwanzaa book.  I've been givin' these 
out for 647 years!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. Amy flies up to the top of the Xmas 
tree and sprays lights from a can onto it. Leela puts candy canes 
on a bush. Nibbler emerges from it and eats them. Fry and Hermes 
stand by a bathtub of what looks like eggnog.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ah! Bathtub eggnog! Just the way Grandma 
used to drink.  Ew! It went sour!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg sits up in the bath.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Can't I have a scented bath in peace?</speak>

<info>He scrubs his back with a brush.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Remember, Professor: Bender is Santa. 
So we don't need to hurt him, right?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes, yes, yes. You sound like a broken 
mp3!</speak>

<info>Bender lands in thr fireplace.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ho ho--  Ow!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(shouting)</info> Professor! Don't you remember 
what I told you?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(shouting)</info> No!</speak>

<info>He shoots Bender again.</info>

<info>Planet Express Roof. Bender sits on the roof of the dome and 
unrolls his list of presents. He crosses off Farnsworth's name.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> Oh, there's gotta be a better 
way.</speak>

<info>Cut to: New New York City Street. Bender walks past a Toys For 
Tots bin and empties the sack of presents into the sewer.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Bender you're a genius!</speak>

<info>Vyolet stands under the sewer grate waving a Barbie.</info>

<speak who="VYOLET">
This creates and unrealistic standard 
of beauty!</speak>

<info>She snorts.</info>

<info>Cut to: Alleyway. Bender is sat leaning against a dumpster holding 
a bottle of beer.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now it's time for Santa to screw open 
his present!</speak>

<info>He opens the bottle and drinks the beer. From the end of the 
alleyway Smitty and URL watch.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
It's Santa! And we got him cornered!</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Aw, I smell a juicy promotion for me.</speak>

<speak who="SMITTY">
And a juicy re-hiring-back-onto-the-force 
for me!</speak>

<info>They shine a light at Bender.</info>

<info>Newspaper Headline: "Suspect Nabbed In Santa Case. Chanukah 
Zombie Still At Large".</info>

<info>Famous Original Ray's Superior Court. The courtroom is packed 
with people for Bender's trial.</info>

<speak who="BAILIFF">
This Xmas Day session of court will 
come to order. The Honourable Judge 
Whitey presiding.</speak>

<info>Whitey takes his seat and bangs his gavel.</info>

<speak who="WHITEY">
Santa Claus, you stand accused of crimes 
against humanity. How do you plead?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Not Santa!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth stands up and points at Bender.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
There he is again!</speak>

<info>He shoots Bender in the back.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The Hyper-Chicken Lawyer questions the witness, 
a little girl.</info>

<speak who="HYPERCHICKEN">
Now, Pramala, I know it's scary in that 
there witness box but t'ain't no need 
to fear me.  I'm sorry, I thought you 
was corn. Now, would you please point 
at that robot over there.  No further 
questions.  Daddy done good, huh?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Bender cross-examines the girl.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Isn't it true that you have been paid 
for your testimony?</speak>

<speak who="PRAMALA">
Yes. You gave me a dollar and some candy.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And yet you haven't said what I told 
you to say. How can any of us trust 
you?</speak>

<info>Pramala bursts into tears.</info>

<speak who="WHITEY">
Quit badgering the witness!</speak>

<info>The Hyper-Chicken jumps up.</info>

<speak who="HYPERCHICKEN">
Badger? Where?</speak>

<info>He clucks around in a mad panic. Whitey bangs his gavel.</info>

<speak who="WHITEY">
Whereas I have a ham dinner with mayonnaise 
waiting for me at my mansion, I find 
the defendant guilty.  Santa Claus, 
I hereby sentence you to be executed 
at sundown.</speak>

<info>He bangs his gavel. Bender is shocked. Smitty and URL lead him 
away.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's not fair. I just hope that dumb 
chicken is ashamed of himself.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Famous Original Ray's Superior Court. The Hyper-Chicken 
is on the roof, crowing.</info>

<info>Stattica Robot Penitentiary. Smitty and URL lead Bender into 
the cells. They are followed by Mayor Poopenmeyer and the Preacherbot.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Deactivated robot walking. We got a 
deactivated robot walking here.</speak>

<info>A robot leans through his cell bars and stops them.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
Hey, Santa, when you see the Robot Devil, 
tell him I'm-a comin'!</speak>

<info>They past the next cell. The Robot Devil is inside.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, that guy said to tell you that--</speak>

<speak who="ROBOT DEVIL">
I heard him!</speak>

<info>Neptune Surface. The ship lands outside Jolly Junction. The 
steps squash a Jack-in-the-Box and it plays Pop Goes The Weasel. 
Fry and Leela are greeted by the Neptunians, now wearing summer 
gear.</info>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
Greetings, masters. My companion and 
I made lots of toys.</speak>

<info>Leela pushes him aside.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Outta my way, shrimp-oh. We're here 
to bring Santa back so we can prove 
Bender's innocent.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Leela cuts through the ice around Santa with a chainsaw.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Do what you will. But we'll see who 
has the last ho.</speak>

<info>Fry, Leela and the Neptunians use planks and candy canes to 
lift Santa out of the ground in one solid block of ice.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
There.</speak>

<info>The ice starts to melt.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, no! The ice is melting!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
The pollution from the factory. It caused 
a greenhouse effect.</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #1">
That would explain this heat.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
And your breezy short-shorts!</speak>

<speak who="NEPTUNIAN #2">
Uh, yeah! That would explain it.</speak>

<info>Santa breaks through the melting ice. Everyone screams and runs. 
Fry and Leela run into the Toyworks.</info>

<info>Cut to: Toyworks. Neptunians are making toys. Santa runs in, 
shooting a laser and the elves run. Fry and Leela scream and 
jump onto the conveyor belt and over toy soldiers like hurdles. 
Santa follows, still shooting. Fry and Leela jump off the end 
of the conveyor belt. Leela turns one of the soldiers bayonets 
upwards and it impales Santa. He groans.</info>

<info>Cut to: Neptune Surface. Fry and Leela run up the steps.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ships Cockpit. Leela powers up the ship and it takes 
off and tears away from Neptune.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hurry! We've gotta think of another 
way to save Bender or Xmas will be ruined!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Especially for Bender.</speak>

<info>Santa is crouching on the roof of the ship.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Look out, Earth. I'm dreaming of a red 
Xmas.</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<info>Stattica Robot Penitentiary. Bender is being strapped to a table 
for his execution by Magnexecutioner. He is moved forward between 
two giant magnets.</info>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
Ah, good old Maggie!  Eh? When I pull 
this switch, these powerful electromagnets 
will tear you limb-from-limb, killing 
you in the most humane possible manner.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But, Mr. Mayor, that doesn't sound humane.</speak>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
It is for the witnesses because it's 
not boring!  The instant this random 
number generator reaches zero, you'll 
be executed.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Aw!</speak>

<info>Poopenmeyer presses a button. The generator starts displaying 
numbers.</info>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
Ten. Three. Twelve. Three again.</speak>

<info>Enter Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Stop the execution!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Leela!</speak>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
Fifteen. Negative eight.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You got the wrong Santa. And I'll prove 
it.</speak>

<info>Fry walks in dressed in a Santa outfit.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm Santa Claus!</speak>

<info>The witnesses gasp.</info>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
What? Twenty-seven.</speak>

<info>Enter Hermes in a Santa outfit.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
No. I'm Santa Claus.</speak>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
Six.</speak>

<info>Enter Amy and Farnsworth in Santa outfits.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(disguised, deeper voice)</info> We're also 
Santa Claus.</speak>

<info>Enter Zoidberg dressed as Jesus, surrounded by a white light.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
And I'm his friend Jesus!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Your Mayorness, if you execute him, 
you have to execute all of us.</speak>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
You people aren't Santa. You're not 
even robots! Ninety-one. How dare you 
lie in front of Jesus!  Hey! Zero!</speak>

<info>He throws the switch and sends the electricity through the electromagnets. 
Bender's arms and legs are pulled to them.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
No! Not the magnets!  <info>(singing)</info> Swing 
low, sweet chariot, coming for to carry 
me home.  Swing low sweet--</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
This is horrible.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
But it's not boring!</speak>

<info>Santa's sleigh crashes through the wall, knocking off one of 
the electromagnets.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Ho ho ho!</speak>

<info>He shoots the other electromagnet off the wall. Everyone scatters 
except for Fry, Leela, Bender and Poopenmeyer. Fry and Leela 
dive behind some rubble.</info>

<speak who="POOPENMEYER">
My God! The real Santa! Get him, Jesus!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I help those who help themselves.</speak>

<info>Santa shoots at him and he runs out. The sleigh lands.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Santa! You saved my life. Please don't 
kill me!</speak>

<info>Santa laughs.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
I'm not here to kill you, Bender! I 
need you to help me save Xmas.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Gee whiz, Santa! You want me to help 
you?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Don't do it! He's evil!</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
I know he is but I have no choice. I'm 
running late and if I don't complete 
my brutal rampage, well, it just wouldn't 
be Xmas. I guess what I'm asking is: 
Bender, won't you join my slaying tonight?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well ... 'tis the season!</speak>

<info>Santa pulls him out of his constraints and puts him in the sleigh. 
He climbs in and the sleigh flies off.</info>

<info>New New York City Streets. Santa flies the sleigh down a street 
and Bender smashes lights with a blernsball bat. Then Santa shoots 
a missile at a Stinky Stork's Diaper Service truck and it explodes, 
showering people with diapers. Scruffy puts up an umbrella.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
My hair!</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
My wedding cake!</speak>

<info>Santa and Bender laugh.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
Let it snow!</speak>

<info>They fly around a corner and Bender holds handfuls of toys.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Merry Xmas, kids!</speak>

<info>He throws the toys through windows and walls. Santa shoots a 
bike at a little girl. Bender laughs.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Attic Room. The staff and LaBarbara are sat 
in darkness. Outside, buildings burn and police car sirens wail.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
This wangs chun! After all the good 
we tried to do, Xmas turned out as rotten 
as ever.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No heat.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No power.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Huddled together in fear like lice in 
a burning wig.</speak>

<info>He hugs LaBarbara. Zoidberg and Fry are also huddled together.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a second! Maybe your futuristic 
Xmas isn't so rotten after all.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What are you talking about, you crouton? 
You said it yourself: Xmas should be 
about bringing people together, not 
blowing them apart.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But don't you see? Fear has brought 
us together. That's the magic of Xmas!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
That's a big crock of--  Hold me!</speak>

<info>Everyone huddles together.</info>

<info>In the sky, Bender whips the reindeer.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
On, Trasher! On, Smasher!  Hey, Kwanzaabot, 
where you off to?</speak>

<speak who="KWANZAABOT">
Ah, you didn't hear about it? Chanukah 
Zombie's having a luau at the B'nai 
Brith! You comin'?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Word!</speak>

<info>The Kwanzaabot flies off. Santa pulls out a present.</info>

<speak who="SANTA">
By the way, Bender, here's a small token 
of my appreciation for being Santa while 
I was trapped in the ice.</speak>

<info>Bender takes the gift and cheers. He opens it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, chief, you screwed up. There's 
nothing in here.</speak>

<speak who="SANTA">
Oh, it might appear empty but the message 
is clear: Play Santa again and I'll 
kill you next year!  Ho ho ho!</speak>

<info>THE END</info></xml>