<xml>
<episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 403

<title>ANTHOLOGY OF INTEREST II</title>

<author>Lewis Morton, David X. Cohen, Jason Gorbett &amp; Scott Kirby</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Hey TiVo! Suggest This!</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. The Professor hits his What 
If? machine with a hammer.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
There. I've finished fine tuning my 
What If? machine. It can answer any 
What If? question, accurate to within 
1/10th of a plausibility unit.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That's so plausible I can't believe 
it!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Who wants the machine to show them an 
alternate reality?</speak>

<info>Bender steps forward.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I wanna know what would happen if I 
were human. I mean, being a robot's 
great but we don't have emotions and 
sometimes that makes me very sad.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh lordy loo! There he goes again. Well, 
let's give baby what he wants.  What 
if Bender were human?</speak>

<info>He pulls a string.</info>

<info>What If? Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Bender is strapped 
to a table with the crew gathered around him.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Good news everyone. I've discovered 
a way to make Bender human using a process 
I call "reverse fossilisation."</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
How does it work?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well, in regular fossilisation, flesh 
and bone turn to minerals. Realising 
that, it was a simple matter to reverse 
the process. I've already tested it 
by turning the toaster into a racoon.</speak>

<info>He puts the racoon on a table. It runs around a bit before two 
slices of toast pop out of it. Fry takes a bite.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Kinda gamey.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Are you ready Bender?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I dunno. I'm beginning to have second 
thoughts -</speak>

<info>Farnsworth throws a switch and Bender is zapped with electricity 
in a fashion resembling the countless Frankenstein films. He 
slowly starts to take human form. He grows hair, a nose and...</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Cover your shame mon!</speak>

<info>He puts some underpants on Bender. The table tips up and human 
Bender walks off. Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It worked! Eat it everyone who never 
won a Nobel Prize! And that includes 
you Amy!</speak>

<info>Amy cries. Bender looks at his new self.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
So this is the human body huh? Neat! 
Hey, my antenna's gone.  Nah it just 
moved. I'm not getting good reception 
on it though. Maybe if I wiggle it around 
a little.</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
Bender no! You'll make God cry.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well lets see what kind of things thing 
body can do.  Hey that's pretty fun. 
Being human is great!</speak>

<info>He vomits again. Zoidberg cheers.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hooray, its just like Mardis Gras!</speak>

<info>What If? Planet Express: Meeting Room. Bender walks out of the 
men's room.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Guy guys, you've gotta see this. You're 
not gonna believe it!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender it's OK to be pround but don;t 
be a show off.</speak>

<info>Bender looks Amy up and down.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Whoa, you look a lot better than you 
used to for some reason.</speak>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(SEXFULLY)</info>
You're not so bad yourself big boy.</speak>

<info>She kisses him.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey that felt great!  Nah its not working 
anymore.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Speak for yourself!</speak>

<info>What If? O'Zorgnax's Pub. Bender downs a glass of beer and lights 
up a cigar.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Whoa, this is awesome!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender you drank and smoked when you 
were a robot.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But now its bad for me! Woo!</speak>

<info>He picks up another glass. Fry slides a box of nachos onto the 
bar.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Speaking of which, try these nachos.</speak>

<info>Bender tastes one and his eyes widen with delight. He starts 
scoffing the rest of them.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Mmm, why didn't anyone tell me tasting 
things tasted so good?  What's going 
on? That rhythm. Its doing something 
to my human butt.</speak>

<info>He stands up and starts to dance still holding his beer, cigar 
and some nachos.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Bender, part of being human is having 
self control.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh my God I bet I can eat nachos and 
go to the bathroom at the same time!</speak>

<info>He picks up the box of nachos but everyone else restrains him.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
No Bender.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
No!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Stop him.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Let me go.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Come Bender, its time to go home and 
rest. I need you in top shape next week 
when I present you to the Nobel Prize 
committee. Bender?</speak>

<info>Bender climbs out of a window.</info>

<info>Cut to: Street. Bender runs down the street cheering.</info>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
Goodbye moderation!</speak>

<info>What If? Bar. Bender dances with two girls to Conga still with 
a glass of beer and a hot dog.</info>

<info>Cut to: Street. He walks out of D.U.I. Friday's and into Dinkin' 
Donuts.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. He leaves a little while later with his arms around 
two girls.</info>

<info>What If? Academy Of Science. A week later Farnsworth and the 
rest of the crew are at the Nobel Prize committee for the judging. 
Farnsworth is on the stage at a podium trying to buy some time 
while Amy and Zoidberg sit at a table together.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Is Bender still missing for a week? 
Where is he already?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Uh as I've said before, I used reverse 
fossilisation, which is the reverse 
of regular, uh...</speak>

<info>He wipes his brow. Fry pokes his head out from behind a curtain.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
Psst, we found him!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah, them without further stalling for 
time, I present to the Nobel judges, 
the first robot ever turned into a human.</speak>

<info>The curtain slides back. Bender is a huge fat blob. He groans. 
The scientists gasp.</info>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
My God, he needs medical attention!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg scans Bender.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Pulse...300, liver...failing, cholesterol...40?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well that's not so bad.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
No I mean 40 pounds!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth continues but a little shaken.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
This, uh, scientific breakthrough, uh, 
heralds a new dawn in human-robot relations 
yes.</speak>

<info>Bender groans and looks at a woman.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
C'mere and give old Bender a kiss.  
Hey, you like grilled cheese?</speak>

<info>He takes some grilled cheese out from under a roll of flab.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
And, uh thats why I believe I deserve 
the Nobel Prize.</speak>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
Not only do you not deserve a Nobel 
Prize for loosing this bloated man-ball 
on the world but you are hereby kicked 
out of the Academy Of Science.</speak>

<info>The scientists cheer and applaud.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wait. As men of science are not your 
minds open to new ideas? I say, do not 
judge me until you have tried my way 
of life for yourselves.</speak>

<info>The scientists look at each other.</info>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
Young man, you have opened our minds 
and swayed our hearts. Let us therefore 
-</speak>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
Party!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg puts Conga on a jukebox and warbles. Enter Fry with 
a keg and Amy and Hermes with food.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Weee!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The druken scientists are asleep and sitting around 
in their underwear.</info>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
Bender, you were right! Truly you have 
lived more in your one week of being 
human than the rest of us have in our 
entire lives.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Woo!</speak>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
And so to recognise your achievements 
I hereby award you the Nobel Prize......in 
uh......chemistry!</speak>

<info>Everyone applauds.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Care to say a few words Bender?</speak>

<info>Bender doesn't. Fry moves his hand across Bender's eyes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
He's dead.</speak>

<info>Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
When did he die?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth checks Bender's pulse.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
About 12 hours ago when the party started.</speak>

<speak who="WERNSTRUM">
But he just said "Woo."</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No. That was air escaping from the folds 
of his fat.  Goodnight sweet prince. 
You were the greatest man any of us 
will ever know. Well lets get him out 
of here. He's starting to smell up the 
joint.</speak>

<info>The rest of the crew roll Bender out and woos along the way.</info>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
You watched it, you can't unwatch it. 
Stay tuned for more Tales Of Interest!</speak>

<info>The What If? Scenario ends.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Who else has a question for the What 
If? machine? Scruffy? Katrina? Xanfor?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Ooo I have one. I'm good at video games 
and bad at everything else. That's why 
I wish life were more like a video game.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Can you put that in the form of a question?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, What if that thing I said?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth lights a stick of incense.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh great machine we beseech thee. What 
if life were more like a video game?</speak>

<info>What If? A video game ship flies around shoots some asteroids 
like in the game Asteroids and lands in the Planet Express hangar.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Lounge. Enter the crew, back from a 
mission. Farnsworth and Hermes are sat on the couch watching 
Nixon in the TV.</info>

<speak who="NIXON"><info>ON TV</info>
Good evening ignorant pigs. Put down 
your crack pipes and you beer bongs 
and pay attention as I sign a historic 
peace accord with Ambassador Kong of 
planet Nintendu 64.</speak>

<info>Donkey Kong stands next to Nixon holding a barrel over his head.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a second, I know that monkey. His 
name is Donkey.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Monkies aren't donkies! Quit messing 
with my head!</speak>

<info>Cut to: UN Building.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
I'll just put the old John Q. Nixon 
on it.  There. No major crap ups. You're 
on Mr Ambassador!  What the?</speak>

<info>Donkey Kong throws the barrel at Nixon and his jar goes flying. 
Everyone gasps. Donkey Kong climbs a ladder.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside UN Building. Donkey Kong bounces along the roof 
and the floors collapse like in Donkey Kong.</info>

<info>Cut to: UN Building. Mario, the Italian representative, stands 
up.</info>

<speak who="MARIO">
Mama Mia! The cruel meatball of war 
has rolled onto our laps and ruined 
our white pants of peace!</speak>

<info>He runs off.</info>

<info>What If? MilAtari HQ. The crew and a miliatari guy walk down 
a corridor.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Mr Fry rumour has it you know the secrets 
of the video game Chance. Please step 
into the war room.</speak>

<info>A message on the war room door tels them they need the blue 
key to enter. The man holds up the blue key and the door opens.</info>

<info>Cut to: War Room.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
You'll be meeting with General Colin 
Pac-man.</speak>

<speak who="PACMAN">
Wakka wakka wakka wakka. Lets get down 
to business. What can you tell us about 
the Nintendians?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well sir, I spent all of ninth grade 
studying them. Except for that day when 
my eyeballs started to bleed. And in 
my opinion.</speak>

<info>A building outside explodes. Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="PACMAN">
Quickly, to the escape tunnels!</speak>

<info>Everyone runs off wakka-wakka-ing.</info>

<info>Cut to: Pac-man Screen.</info>

<speak who="PACMAN">
This way damn it!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg eats the pellet thingies.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Mmm, delicious! Just like stale marshmellows! 
Ooo and a cherry!</speak>

<info>He eats it and carries on running. He starts chasing Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey watch out!</speak>

<info>He eats him.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Uh oh!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh my god, he ate Fry! Fry is dead!</speak>

<info>Fry slides up behind them,</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Its OK, I had another guy!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<info>What If? Outside Planet Express. Everyone comes out of the end 
of the escape tunnel and are very tired.</info>

<speak who="PACMAN">
Wakka...wakka wa...</speak>

<info>Zoidberg coughs up five pellets, a pixelated cherry, a pixelated 
pretzel and a key. A shadow creeps over them. Spaceships start 
destroying buildings.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Invaders! Possibly from space!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Lrrr's Ship. He opens a window and pokes his 
head out.</info>

<speak who="LRRR">
People of Earth, I am Lrrr of the planet 
Nintendu 64. Tremble in fear at our 
three different kinds of ships!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Alright, its Saturday night. I have 
no date, a two litre bottle of Shasta, 
and my all Rush mix tape! Let's rock!</speak>

<info>What If? Player's Ship. Fry stands at an arcade console listening 
to Rush's Tom Sawyer. He uses the console to control his ship 
and attack the Space Invaders. He shoots and destroys a few ships.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lrrr's Ship.</info>

<speak who="ND-ND">
We're losing ships sir. What are your 
orders?</speak>

<speak who="LRRR">
Increase speed, drop down and reverse 
direction!</speak>

<info>And they do.</info>

<info>Cut to: Player's Ship. Fry gulps down some Shasta.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I've still got a trick or two up my 
sleeve. Watch as I fire up through our 
own shields.</speak>

<info>Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
He's a madman! A madman!!</speak>

<info>Fry fires up through the shield and destroys several more ships.</info>

<speak who="PACMAN">
It's working. Victory is ensured! My 
retirement tomorrow will be all the 
sweeter!  I'm hit! So cold!</speak>

<info>He folds over and dies. Enter Ms Pac-man crying.</info>

MS <speak who="PAC">-MAN <info>(CRYING)</info>
No - wakka wakka!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Amy, tend to the widow pac-man.</speak>

<info>Ms Pac-man cries and wakkas.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Lrrr's Ship. He opens the window.</info>

<speak who="LRRR">
Drop down and increase speed.</speak>

<info>Fry destroys another ship. Only Lrrr's ship remains.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Player's Ship. Zoidberg looks up through the 
window.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
One ship is left only.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Player's Ship. Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Come on Fry get it!</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>SWEATING</info>
It's moving too fast. Oh I could never 
get the last one. My brother always 
got it for me!</speak>

<info>Everyone screams.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Lrrr's Ship. His ship cuts through Fry's shields. 
Lrrr opens the window.</info>

<speak who="LRRR">
Drop down, reverse direction, prepare 
for landing.</speak>

<info>His ship lands. A caption appears. War Over. Congratulations 
Enter Initials. Fry enters "ASS" and chuckles.</info>

<info>What If? Outside Planet Express. The crew are assembled outside 
Lrrr's ship. Some steps come down and several arcade characters 
get out along with Lrrr.</info>

<speak who="LRRR">
You are defeated. Instead of shooting 
where I was you should have shot where 
I was going to be.</speak>

<speak who="BESERK">
All your base are belong to us.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What do you monsters want?</speak>

<speak who="DONKEY KONG">
One thing and one thing only. Quarters! 
A million allowances worth of quarters! 
No slugs or tokens!</speak>

<speak who="BESERK">
Fork 'em over! <info>(different tone)</info> Fork 
'em over!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Forget it you pixelated pirates. We 
need those quarters to do our laundry.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Right on!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Sure thing Professor!</speak>

<speak who="LRRR">
But, but space invaders need to do laundry 
too! I mean look at Donkey Kong here. 
Have you smelled his loincloth lately?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Yes.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Go away. We're not giving you our quarters 
no matter what.</speak>

<speak who="LRRR">
Well...then what if we throw our laundry 
in with yours? Would that be acceptable?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I guess so.</speak>

<info>Lrrr takes off his cape.</info>

<speak who="LRRR">
OK then, that settles that. But if this 
cape shrinks, consider your species 
extinct!</speak>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
Bravo! That'll be hard to top! I pity 
the next Tale Of Interest!</speak>

<info>The What If? Scenario ends.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well, there's time for one last question. 
Let's turn to the Who Ask machine to 
see who's next.</speak>

<info>He turns the machine on.</info>

<speak who="WHO ASK MACHINE">
Um uh um...Amy.  I mean Leela.</speak>

<info>Amy groans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, ahem. As an alien who was abandoned 
on Earth, I've never really belonged 
anywhere.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Boo hoo.</speak>

<info>She hits him on the back of the head and his eyes fly out and 
hit Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow!</speak>

<info>Bender looks around for his eyes.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh...where?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
So my question is this: What if I found 
my true home?  Ow!</speak>

<info>She falls over unconcious.</info>

<info>Cut to: Leela's Dream. Everything is brown and white like in 
Wizard Of Oz. Nibbler wakes up Leela who is dressed like Dorothy. 
Leela looks around. She is in the Planet Express ship.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Where are we?</speak>

<info>A tornado blows around the ship outside. Scruffy, the man witch, 
flies past on a broom. He laughs evily but then can't be bothered 
and flies away. The ship crash lands.</info>

<info>Outside Ship. Leela climbs down the steps. The ship is on its 
side.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nibbler, I don't think we're in New 
New York anymore.  Jeez, apparently 
the phrase tone it down doesn't exist 
on this planet.  Oh no! We hit someone! 
Quick, back into the ships.  Ooo, nice 
boots!</speak>

<info>Nibbler sniffs them but recoils in horror. Enter Cubert, Dwight, 
Tinny Tim, a gay Neptunian elf, a grunka-lunka and Glurmo all 
dressed in weird stuff.</info>

<speak who="CUBERT">
Look everyone! She killed the man-witch 
of the west!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
A witch? That explains how these boots 
magically appeared on my feet.</speak>

<speak who="GLURMO">
No, you stole them, we saw you.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well...its hard to find shoes that fit 
me. So anyway, who are you people? Haven't 
I seen you in some copyrighted movie?</speak>

<speak who="GLURMO"><info>(SINGING)</info>
We resemble but are legally distinct 
from the lollipop guild, the lollipop 
-</speak>

<info>Nibbler eats him. Enter Amy in a bubble.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Greetings Leela, I'm The Cute With Of 
The North!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yeah, can anyone fix my ship so I can 
get home?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Abracaduh! Just ask the Professor! He 
lives in the Emerald Laboratory down 
Martin Luther King Boulevard.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You mean that yellow brick road?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
The city council renamed it in 1975. 
<info>(sarcastic)</info> Ooo those are great shoes!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh thank you.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Do they come in women's sizes?</speak>

<info>Leela presses a button on her wristamajig and the steps come 
out of the ship and crush Amy.</info>

<info>Martin Luther King Boulevard. Leela walks down the road and 
passes a scarecrow in a field that looks like Fry. A crow lands 
on some corn.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
OK crow, prepare to be scared.  And 
then - honk honk - the car honked it's 
own horn!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wow, a talking scarecrow. Wanna come 
with us to see the Professor? He might 
be able to give you a brain.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, that's not a nice thing to say.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Beer. Beer.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Whiskey OK?</speak>

<info>She pours some into his mouth, he belches fire and sets fire 
to Fry's arm. Fry pats out the flames.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now did you say you were off to see 
the Professor? 'Cause I could use a 
heart. A human heart. I need to pump 
a lot of blood out of my basement.</speak>

<info>Enter Zoidberg in a yellow cab.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
And I'm the other guy. Courage. Not 
enough of it. Need some from whatshisname.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. They all skip down the yellow brick boulevard.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mom's Castle. The evil witch Mom watches it on her TV. 
The TV picture goes funny and she hits the TV repeatedly.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Damn this DSL!  Fly my stupids! Fly 
out and get them!</speak>

<speak who="IGNER">
But Mom, you promised you'd make monkey 
cake today.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
By "monkey cake" I meant your ass.</speak>

<info>She slaps them and they fly away.</info>

<info>Cut to: Martin Luther King Boulevard. The foursome are still 
skipping along.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, we've been skipping for hours. 
I need to pull over and take the wiz.</speak>

<info>Walt, Larry and Igner swoop down and take Fry, Leela and Bender.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What do I smell or something?  Oh!</speak>

<info>Mom's Castle.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Why did you bring us here?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
And why did I have to take a cab?</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
I'll tell you why I brought you here 
you twice baked barf bag. Because I've 
always wanted a daughter to love. You 
want to get adopted you little skank?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And live here? And be a witch like you? 
Yeah, alright. As long as I get to hurt 
people and not just dance around at 
the equinox.</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Absolutely.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh mommy, I found my true home!</speak>

<info>They hug. Zoidberg, Fry and Bender cheer.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hooray!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
All right!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's great Leela.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I've heard worse excuses to drink.  
Oops.</speak>

<info>Purple smoke starts to come from Mom.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
I'm melting! Who would have thought 
a small amount of liquid would ever 
fall on me?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well, no point in letting her go to 
waste.</speak>

<info>He pulls a straw out of his chest cavity and starts drinking 
the puddle of Mom.</info>

<info>Outside The Professor's Laboratory. A cab pulls up outside the 
green building which looks like the Planet Express building and 
everyone gets out. Leela knocks on the door. Hermes opens a peephole.</info>

<speak who="HERMES"><info>FROM INSIDE</info>
Yes?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
We're here to see the Professor.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES"><info>FROM INSIDE</info>
No one sees the mighty Professor.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh for the love of Benji.</speak>

<info>She pokes him in the eyes and opens the door. The four walk 
in.</info>

<info>Cut to: The Professor's Laboratory. Farnsworth, with a big head, 
stands behind a curtain.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I am the Professor. Great and...uh...forgetful! 
Now what do you nice kids want?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Nothing, I'm leaving. But if you have 
extra courage I'd haul it away for you 
maybe?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh blithery poop my cowardly lobster! 
You don't need courage. Afterall, who 
needs courage when you have a gun?</speak>

<info>He hands Zoidberg a gun and he pretends to shoot it.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Now world, you put your hands up!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
And you lad, all you need is brain.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Why does everyone keep saying that?</speak>

<info>Bender takes Zoidberg's gun.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
This is a stick up. Give me the bag 
old man!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth chuckles.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Here you go my friend. 5000 Professor 
Land fun bucks!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh crap.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth turns to Leela.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
As for you young lady, you want to go 
home right?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No not anymore. I wanna stay here and 
become the new Wicked Witch.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Nonsense. Now click your big honking 
boots together three times and wish 
to go home to Kansas, to live in poerty 
with your dirt farming, teetotalling 
aunt and uncle.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh, alright. Here I go.  There's no 
place like - I wanna be a witch!  Oh 
no, help, what's happening?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Uh sorry, I think there's a problem 
with your upstairs toilet.</speak>

<info>Leela melts some more.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Bender throws a bucket 
of water on her and she wakes up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wake up!</speak>

<info>Leela coughs and splutters.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela, are you alright? You got wanged 
on the head.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I was having the most wonderful dream. 
Except you were there and you were 
there and you were there.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Never mind Professor, she came to.</speak>

<info>Enter Farnsworth with a box marked Leela's Organs.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, so close.</speak>

<info>Hermes puts his hand on Farnsworth's shoulder.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
There's always next year Professor, 
there's always next year.</speak>

<info>THE END</info></xml>