<xml>
(                                    <section><show>FUTURAMA</show><header>


                                       Episode 405

                                   "LEELA'S HOMEWORLD"

                                           By

                                      Kristen Gore

                         Transcribed by Dave, The Neutral Planet



               
               </header><note>Opening Credits. Caption: It's Like "Hee-Haw" With Lasers.</note>
 
               
               
               <note>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Bender, Amy, Hermes, Fry and 
               Zoidberg are gathered around the table. Enter Farnsworth and 
               Leela.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Good news, everyone! You all know the 
                         orphanarium where Leela grew up?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Sure. We talk about it all the time.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Really?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         No. Burn!

               
               </speak><note>Fry and Bender high-five.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Well done, fellows! Anyway, said orphanarium 
                         has named Leela orphan of the year.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Everyone cheers.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>

                         Yee-ha!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         All right!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character>

                         Your parents must be so proud. Oops! 
                         Sorry.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         And the good news keeps on coming. Behold 
                         my latest invention.
 
               
               </speak><note>He presses a button on a remote and the wall opens up. A big 
               machine with gauges and flashing lights slides forward.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Neat.

               
               </speak><note>Farnsworth pulls a switch on the machine and parts of it start 
               to move around and make noises like the gum machine in Willy 
               Wonka And The Chocolate Factory. A small green thing lands in 
               a tray on the side of the machine.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Ta-da! It's a glow-in-the-dark nose 
                         you can wear over your regular non-glowing 
                         nose. Observe.
 
               
               </speak><note>He puts the nose on then presses a button on the remote and 
               the lights go off. His new nose glows.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>

                         Whoa, clool!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         Now I can punch you in the nose in the 
                         dark.
 
               
               </speak><note>Farnsworth sneezes and the nose flies off and lands on Bender's 
               face. The lights come back on and everyone stares at Bender. 
               He looks around.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         (snuffed) Where'd it go?

               
               </speak><note>Amy goes behind the machine. It is spewing out green waste into 
               barrels.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>

                         Hey, Professor what's all this scloop, 
                         glorking out of the machine?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         That? It's uh...nothing. Yes, nothing. 
                         If you think it's anything you're a 
                         suspicous moron.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         It looks like toxic waste.  And it smells 
                         like toxic waste.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         What does it taste like?

               
               </speak><note>Hermes tastes it.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character><speak>

                         Delicious fig pudding! Ooh, that's good! 
                         But a distinct aftertaste of toxic waste.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Alright, alright so the machine produces 
                         a few toxic by-products! You don't have 
                         to make a federal case out of it.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         I'm afraid I do.  I order you dispose 
                         of that toxic waste properly, or bribe 
                         me. Either way it'll cost $500.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         500 real dollars? That's an outrage! 
                         Professor, I'll take care of that waste 
                         for $499 and 100 cents.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         Hmm, I know that's a rip but I'll pay 
                         for the convenience. Do you take credit 
                         cards?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         Let's find out.

               
               </speak><note>He swipes the card across his mouth.</note>

               
               <note>Planet Express: Attic Balcony. Bender is holding a waste hose.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Alright, environment, you've met your 
                         match!
 
               
               </speak><note>He chuckles. He starts pushing the hose over the railings towards 
               the street. On its way down the hose shoots some waste across 
               the road where it hits and partially dissolves a tree. The tree 
               falls onto a car which melts the road and disappears through 
               a hole. The hose stops by a manhole and pumps waste into the 
               sewers. Bender whistles and fans his money.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. Vyolet the mutant crawls out 
               of the sewer in a wedding dress. She splutters.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> SMITTY </character><speak>

                         Hey, get back in the sewer, weirdy. 
                         No mutants on the surface.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VYOLET </character><speak>
                         But he ruined my wedding dress.

               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Planet Express: Attic Balcony.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Honey, that thing was ruined the minute 
                         it went on you. That's what I'm talkin' 
                         'bout.
 
               
               </speak><note>He struts off with his cigar and money.</note>

               
               <note>Cookieville Minimum-Security Orphanarium Auditorium. Party streams 
               have been put up and there is a banner which reads "Wall Of Fame 
               Induction. No Really Loud Snoring". Warden Vogel stands behind 
               a lectern, addressing the rows of children and the Planet Express 
               staff. Leela sits to his right in front of the wall of fame.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>

                         Y'know, it's not easy being an orphan, 
                         not if I have anything to do with it. 
                          But today's honouree, Turanga Leela, 
                         has really made something of herself 
                         . I'll never forget the night that cute 
                         little alien baby was abandoned on our 
                         doorstep. Because I have a photographic 
                         memory and I remember every night!
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Flashback - Cookieville Minimum-Security Orphanarium: Vogel's 
               Office, 2974. Vogel is in his office and the doorbell goes. He 
               opens the door, looks around, then looks down. baby Leela is 
               in a basket. He picks her up and tickles her. Then he sees a 
               note, written in the alien language.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>

                         What the...? An alien language? I guess 
                         you're an alien. What a beautiful gigantic 
                         eye you ha --  Well, come on in.
 
               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Cookieville Minimum-Security Orphanarium: Hallway. Vogel 
               tosses the basket into an already high pile.</note>
 
               
               <note>Flashback ends.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>

                         From those humble beginnings Leela went 
                         on to become a county-certified starship 
                         captain. And so it is my pleasure today, 
                         to nail her picture alongside those 
                         of our most distinguished alumini.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>The crowd cheers. Vogel starts to hammer a nail into the wall. 
               Leela stands up.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Thank you very much. Like many of you 
                         I never knew my parents...
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>
                          Give me a -- argh!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         ...I don't know if they were mighty 
                         alien overlords or simply underpaid 
                         alien janitors who fought crime on the 
                         side --
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character>

                         Picture's up.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         (shouting) It's crooked!

               
               </speak><note>Vogel curses.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         ...In the end though, it doesn't matter 
                         who my parents were. All that matters 
                         is what I learned here, within these 
                         unscalable walls, that I have strength 
                         to make it on my own, just like all 
                         of you kids here today.
 
               
               </speak><note>The kids in the audience cheer.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> KIDS </character><speak>

                         (chanting) Leela! Leela! Leela!

               
               </speak><note>Nina puts on an eye patch.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> NINA </character><speak>

                         Look at me! I'm Leela!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ALBERT </character><speak>
                         Nuh uh, 'cause I'm double Leela!

               
               </speak><note>He covers both his eyes and runs into the wall. Leela's picture 
               falls off.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>

                         That's it, Albert, no more espresso 
                         for you.
 
               
               </speak><note>Time Lapse. Leela is talking to Fry.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> PHOTOGRAPHER </character><speak>

                         Mind if I get a picture of you with 
                         your picture for the news, ma'am?
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Yes! I mean no! Just make sure you get 
                         my nonchalant side!
 
               
               </speak><note>One of the guys from the wall runs in behind Leela to get in 
               on her photo.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> GUY </character><speak>

                         Wooo!

               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Corridor. Fry is walking when he hears Leela 
               crying.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Planet Express: Locker Room. Leela is sat crying. She 
               takes her wrist thing off, there is a bracelet under it.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         If those aren't tears of happiness, 
                         please stop crying.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         (crying) It's OK, Fry, I'm fine. I won 
                         an award today.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Is it this room that's making you sad? 
                         It's probably the room. Come on, lets 
                         go for a walk.
 
               
               </speak><note>Outside Planet Express. Fry and Leela walk out of the building 
               and walk down the street by the river. Leela has calmed down 
               now.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         I'm sorry you saw that, Fry. I usually 
                         try to keep my sadness pent up inside 
                         where it can fester quietly as a mental 
                         illness.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Yeah, I do that with my stupidness.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         I told a whole crowd today that being 
                         an orphan made me strong. But all </section>
 <section><character> I  </character>

                         really wanted was a mom and dad, to 
                         hold me and stroke my hair and tell 
                         me they loved me.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Then today's your lucky day because 
                         I happen to be a holding, stroking, 
                         lovin' machine! Also spankin'!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         That's not even close to what I had 
                         in mind.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Well, anyway, just remember that people 
                         care about you.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         I know.  Sometimes when I'm lonely, 
                         I look up at the sky and I get this 
                         feeling that somewhere, on some unknown 
                         planet, circling a distant star, my 
                         parents are up there, looking down on 
                         me.
 
               
               </speak><note>From the sewers a pair of cyclopses look up at Leela.</note>

               
               <note>Outside Planet Express. The next morning Bender backs up a truck 
               to the manhole outside the Planet Express building. He hums to 
               himself. Fry and Leela walk out of the building.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Yo yo, Bezender! What up?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         My dumping business is booming. I just 
                         got hired to clean up the set of Free 
                         Willy 3.
 
               
               </speak><note>He presses a button and the truck tips out a whale. Bender forces 
               it down the manhole by stamping on it.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Bender! Cut it out! First of all the 
                         sewer mutants will be mad. Second, everything 
                         else that's horribly wrong with what 
                         you're doing!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         Ah, those stupid mutants can't do anything. 
                         You seem to be forgetting one simple 
                         fact, namely, I'm up here and they are 
                         safely down --
 
               
               </speak><note>Green sewage erupts from a fire hydrant and the manhole. Bender 
               screams. The manhole grows bigger and bigger. Three mutants grab 
               Fry, Leela and Bender and pull them undergroup. They scream. 
               The hole carries on growing and takes Bender's dump truck with 
               it.</note>
 
               
               <note>New New York Sewer. Fry, Leela and Bender are tied up and suspended 
               over a pool of green sewage.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         (shouting) What did I do to deserve 
                         this?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DWAYNE </character><speak>
                         Behold, our once beautiful mutigenic 
                         sewage lake.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VYOLET </character>

                         The radioactive waste you dumped in 
                         it has made it brighten up to see how 
                         ugly we really are.
 
               
               </speak><note>She and Dwayne look at each other and cringe.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DWAYNE </character><speak>

                         Oh, man!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>
                         As if our lives weren't miserable enough 
                         already!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEG MUTANT </character>

                         Tell me about it!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character>

                         Let the punishment commence!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Punishment?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         No fair!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         Bender's innocent!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character>

                         The instant you touch these mutatious 
                         waters your DNA will be forever altered, 
                         turning you into horrible mutants like 
                         us. Especially him!  Allow me to demonstrate!
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>He pulls a lever and a rat is lowered into the sewage. It comes 
               back up as a green pig with fins and bat wings. Leela and Bender 
               groan and Fry wretches.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         It's like that time I peeked in the 
                         kitchen at Imperial Hunan.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>
                         Submerge the prisoners.

               
               </speak><note>The crew are lowered towards the sewage. Bender starts to panic 
               but suddenly comes to a realisation.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Wait. I don't even have DNA. Why am 
                         I screaming?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DWAYNE </character><speak>
                         We're gonna beat you afterwards.

               
               </speak><note>Bender continues panicking.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUTANTS </character><speak>

                         (chanting) Mutate! Mutate! Mutate! ...
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Two hooded figures emerge from the crowd.</note>

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         (shouting) Turanga Leela!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Who said that? How do you know my real 
                         name?
 
               
               </speak><note>The hooded figures climb onto the crane holding the crew over 
               the sewage and turn it so they are no longer suspended over the 
               lake.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Whee!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>
                         What are you doing? Stop it.

               
               </speak><note>Fry, Leela and Bender fall to the ground.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         What happened?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         I don't know. I think I saved us somehow.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character>

                         (shouting) Go after them! The waters 
                         can't mutate us mutants!
 
               
               </speak><note>The mutants dive into the sewage and swim across. Fry, Leela 
               and Bender run away.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Mutant Town. Fry, Leela and Bender run down past the 
               cafe's and Starbucks's.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>

                         They went this way!

               
               </speak><note>The crew stop outside an empty-looking building.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Quick! In there!

               
               </speak><note>He picks up Fry by his ankle and swings him at the window, breaking 
               it. He and Leela jump in. Fry crawls in after them. The mutants 
               run past unaware they are chasing no one.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DWAYNE </character><speak>

                         Kill! Kill! Kill!

               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Building. The trio dust themselves off and look around. 
               Leela sees a wall full of newspaper clippings and things to do 
               with her.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Great chichi's ghost!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         What's this junk?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         It looks like...a timeline of my whole 
                         life.
 
               
               </speak><note>Fry sees a familiar newsclipping.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         That's when we saved Earth from a giant 
                         asteroid of garbage.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         And here's when I dropped out and bummed 
                         around India for a while.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         And this is just last year at Space 
                         Mardi Gras.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Its like some kind of weird Leela museum...and 
                         I'm the Leela!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         (whispering) Dude! Over here!

               
               </speak><note>Leela and Bender walk over to where Fry is, next to a shelf 
               with lots of Leela stuff on it.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         It's all the best stuff I ever flushed 
                         down the toilet! Those are some of my 
                         diary pages. And my screenplay!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         And also - for some reason - the letter 
                         I wrote you full of my personal feelings.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                          Oh, I'm scared!  My whole life has 
                         just been a show for some perverted 
                         mutant!
 
               
               </speak><note>The mutants approach the building.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VYOLET </character><speak>

                          They must be in here.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>
                          Yeah, after them.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         And then Bender ran!

               
               </speak><note>He and Fry run for the door. Leela is still standing by the 
               shelf.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Leela, freak out later. We're not done 
                         escaping yet!
 
               
               </speak><note>She doesn't move. Fry and Bender try to pull her away but she 
               stays rooted to the ground. The mutants run in and grab them.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DWAYNE </character><speak>

                         Got ya!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEG MUTANT </character><speak>
                         Take this!

               
               </speak><note>He kicks Fry in the shin.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Ow!

               
               </speak><note>Mutant Town.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>

                         This time I'm calling for the death 
                         penalty. And not just because I'm running 
                         for re-election as Supreme Mutant.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUTANTS </character><speak>
                         (chanting) Four more years! Four more 
                         years!
 
               
               </speak><note>The hooded figures emerge from the crowd again. One taps Raoul 
               on the shoulder and whispers to him.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>

                         Oh, very well.  Your attention. Instead 
                         of being tortured to death, the prisoners 
                         shall hereby be expelled from the sewers 
                         and never allowed to return.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         (sarcastic) Oh cruel fate! Can we really 
                         never return to this dank pit of sewage?!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Wait a minute. Why aren't you gonna 
                         kill us anymore?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         Yeah! What are you chicken? Buk buk 
                         buk bukuk!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         (whispering) Shut up, you two! We can 
                         kill ourselves when we get home!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character>

                         They'll need transportation to the surface. 
                         Bring in the airship.
 
               
               </speak><note>Some mutants haul in a pretty large patchwork balloon.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Eww!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> RAOUL </character><speak>
                         We constructed it from the remnants 
                         of old discarded Macy's parade balloons: 
                         Underdog's groin, Bart Simpsons's left 
                         ear and right shin, Garfield's owner 
                         Jon's forehead.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUTANT </character>

                         Fire up the sewer gas!

               
               </speak><note>A Triclops Mutant turn the ballon gas on. Fry, Leela and Bender 
               choke and gag. The balloon sails up and hits the roof of the 
               sewers. The Triclops puts a plank out to a ladder.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> TRICLOPS </character><speak>

                         Move it ya ugly normals!

               
               </speak><note>He forces Bender onto the plank. It wobbles. He looks down and 
               gets dizzy.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Uh, I'm gettin' dizzy! I can't walk 
                         straight!
 
               
               </speak><note>He pulls a unicycle out of his chest cabinet and cycles along 
               the plank. Fry and Leela climb on and quickly move across. Leela 
               stops at the bottom of the ladder. The airship sails back down. 
               Bender opens the manhole and he and Fry climb out. Leela, still 
               on the ladder, looks back down.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                          Come on Leela. You can do it!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                          Hurry! We're missing our bus!

               
               </speak><note>Leela climbs the ladder but looks back down again at the mysterious 
               hooded figures. She closes the manhole.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                          Whoa! What are you doing?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                          I'm gettin' on the bus!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         (shouting) Don't worry! I'll be fine! 
                          (talking) They know something about 
                         me and I've got to find out what.  The 
                         lake didn't mutate me. What is going 
                         on here?!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> OCTOPUS </character>

                         It worked for me. I used to be a little 
                         blonde girl named Virginia.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Eurgh!  Who the hell are you?

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         No one. And watch your language young 
                         lady!
 
               
               </speak><note>They run off. She chases them. The Triclops gets in her way.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> TRICLOPS </character><speak>

                         Stop right there! I don't want to hurt 
                         you.  I didn't want you to hurt me either.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Cookieville Orphanarium: Vogel's Office.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Leela's going nuts and I can't save 
                         her unless I learn more about her mysterious 
                         past. Isn't there anything else you 
                         can tell me?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>
                         Nah. Nothing that wouldn't be a waste 
                         of your time.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         That's impossible because my time is 
                         worthless!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character>

                         Huh. Well then there is one thing.  
                         It's the note I found with Leela the 
                         day she was abandoned. But it's written 
                         in Alienese, so no-one on Earth can 
                         translate it. Not even Brainzilla.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Hand it over.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character>

                         Sure.  I just wish I could be more helpful. 
                         Would you like some dirt on any other 
                         orphans?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Look, I'm trying to save someone here. 
                         I'll have to come back for those later.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Fry shows Farnsworth the paper.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Can you translate it?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Of course. But only into Beta Crypt 
                         3, a language so complex, there's even 
                         less chance of understanding it.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I didn't ask for a completely reasonable 
                         excuse. I asked you to get busy.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         Very well.

               
               </speak><note>He presses a button and the machine that makes glow-in-the-dark 
               noses comes out of the wall again. Farnsworth feeds the paper 
               in.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Isn't that the same machine that makes 
                         noses?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         It can do other things. Why shouldn't 
                         it?  Of course, even if it is possible 
                         to analyse the message there's no way 
                         of knowing how long it would take. It 
                         could take an hour or it could take 
                         a hundred million years.
 
               
               </speak><note>The machines dings.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Is it done?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Certainly not. Two dings means it's 
                         done.  But not like that. Slightly more 
                         rapid.
 
               
               </speak><note>Two slightly more rapid dings. Fry gasps. Farnsworth shakes 
               his head.</note>
 
               
               <note>New New York Sewer. Leela chases the hooded figures through 
               the tunnels but loses them where some pipes cross.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Where did they go?

               
               </speak><note>Some rubbish falls on her from above.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                          Good news, Leela. I landed the contract 
                         to empty all the spitoons in Little 
                         Italy.
 
               
               </speak><note>He empties a spitoon. Leela rolls out of the way of the spit.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Ew!

               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Fry is pacing up and down 
               while Farnsworth is asleep. The machine rapidly dings twice. 
               Farnsworth wakes up.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         That's it, it's done!  I can't believe 
                         it! My mind is boggling. The analysis 
                         of the note is printing out now.
 
               
               </speak><note>A dot matrix printer prints off the analysis. Fry tears it off 
               and they both start to read it. Fry gasps.</note>
 
               
               <note>Flashback: 20-Something Years Ago. 100-Something Feet Underground. 
               A baby is born in the house Fry, Leela and Bender hid in in the 
               sewers.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DOCTOR </character><speak>

                         It's a girl.

               
               </speak><note>Two cyclopses look at their baby cyclops. The mother has tentacles 
               and the ather's mouth is sideways.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MOTHER </character><speak>

                         My God! She's beautiful. No extra anythings.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>The father reaches his hand out. The baby grabs his finger and 
               goos.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FATHER </character><speak>

                         What people skills.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MOTHER </character><speak>
                         She's completely perfect!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> DOCTOR </character>

                         In my professional opinion as an ear, 
                         ear, ear, nose and throat doctor, she 
                         is the least-mutated mutant ever born.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FATHER </character>

                         And yet she's cursed to live the horrible 
                         degrading life of a mutant. Like all 
                         of us. Especially him!
 
               
               </speak><note>He points at the Leg Mutant.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEG MUTANT </character><speak>

                         It's true!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MOTHER </character><speak>
                         Maybe we can do better for her.

               
               </speak><note>Outside Cookieville Minimum-Secuirty Orphanarium. The mutants 
               come out of a manhole near the building with their baby. They 
               put it in a basket outside the front door. The father puts a 
               bracelet on the baby's wrist.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FATHER </character><speak>

                         I made this bracelet so that in some 
                         small way, we'll always be with you, 
                         even when it doesn't seem like it. During 
                         your entire life, for example.
 
               
               </speak><note>He kisses her.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MOTHER </character><speak>

                         You won't pass for human, cutie. But 
                         if my PhD in exo-liguistics is worth 
                         diddly-poop, this note should convince 
                         them you're an alien.  And that'll be 
                         enough to give you a real life.
 
               
               </speak><note>She kisses the baby, puts her hood up and runs down the steps. 
               The father rings the doorbell and follows her. Warden Vogel opens 
               the door and sees the baby. The parent's watch from the manhole.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FATHER </character><speak>

                         She'll never know we're her parents.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MOTHER </character><speak>
                         That's our gift to her. Better we should 
                         die than have her learn the shameful 
                         truth of her origin.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FATHER </character>

                         I'm with you.

               
               </speak><note>They hug. Then turn to watch Vogel.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> VOGEL </character><speak>

                         What a beautiful gigantic eye you ha 
                         -- . Well come on in.
 
               
               </speak><note>The parents watch Leela disappear inside, hold their breath 
               and dive into the sewers.</note>
 
               
               <note>Flashback ends.</note>

               
               <note>New New York Sewers. Leela is still chasing the hooded figures. 
               They run into the building and lock the door. Leela climbs a 
               pole and jumps onto the roof.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Building.</note>

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         Keep quiet so she doesn't hear us.
 
                         
               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #2
                         What's there to talk about?

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         Shhh!

               
               <note>Leela stands behind them.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Hands up!  Tentacles too!

               
               </speak><note>The other one puts her tentacles up.</note>

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         Don't say anything stupid, Morris.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         What is all this?  Am I a game to you? 
                         Or some kind of even more boring Truman 
                         Show? Do you belive I'm you Messiah? 
                         Your Mutant Dali Lama? Stop me if </section>
 <section><character> I  </character><speak>
                         guess it!
 
               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #2
                         Well actually there --

               
               </speak><note>Hooded Figure #1 stops him.</note>

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         Morris! Shh!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         (angry) And what about this?!  How did 
                         you get this bracelet? Did you steal 
                         it from me when I was a baby? Or from 
                         my parents. You robbed my parents, didn't 
                         you? I bet you sick mutants killed them. 
                         My parents were confused aliens lost 
                         on Earth and you killed them! Is that 
                         it? Admit it!
 
               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #2
                         (sombre) Yes. We killed them.

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         You guessed the truth.

               
               </speak><note>Leela screams.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Because of you I'll never know my parents. 
                         I'll kill you!
 
               
               </speak><note>She raises her gun.</note>

               
                                     HOODED FIGURE #1
                         That would be best.

               
               <note>Time Lapse. Leela charges her laser. It bleeps. The hooded figures 
               hold each other.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                          Stop!  Thanks Bender! Don't do it Leela!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         They killed my parents!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Close.

               
               </speak><note>He walks behind the hooded figures and pulls their hoods off. 
               They are the mutants from the flashback. Leela lowers her gun.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         They are my parents.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUNDA </character><speak>
                         Yes.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I had the Professor analyse the alienese 
                         letter that was found with you.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         What does it say?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I 'unno. But the analysis showed it 
                         was printed on recycled toilet paper. 
                         A squeezably soft paper used mainly 
                         in the sewers.
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela's mother takes the paper.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUNDA </character><speak>

                         It says, "Your parents love you very 
                         much".
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MORRIS </character><speak>
                         We still do.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         So, I'm not an alien? I'm a mutant.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MORRIS </character>

                         We never wanted you to know. You deserved 
                         a better life.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> MUNDA </character>

                         You must despise us.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         (crying) You're my parents. All I've 
                         ever wanted is to know you.  This is 
                         the happiest moment of my life.
 
               
               </speak><note>They cry. It starts to rain.</note>

               
               <note>Cut to: New New York Street. It isn't raining - Bender is emptying 
               a spitoon on them.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         Aww!

               
               </speak><note>Flashbacks. Over the flashbacks Pizzicato Five's Baby Love Child 
               plays. Baby Leela crawls down a corridor at the Orphanarium and 
               nearly falls down the stairs. Her father's arm comes out of the 
               wall and turns her around. Young Leela sits at a desk in her 
               room studying. Her mother's tentacle comes through the toilet 
               and puts a box of cookies on her desk. Leela smiles and eats 
               them. Adolescent Leela walks around New New York on her birthday 
               with no friends. Her mother puts a present on the pavement for 
               her. She reads the message with it: Happy Birthday Leela. Mid-twenties 
               Leela tosses and turns in bed. Her father puts his arm through 
               the laundry chute and pulls the sheet over her. She smiles and 
               goes to sleep.</note>
 
               
               THE END
</section></xml>