<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 406

<title>WHERE THE BUGGALO ROAM</title>

<author>J. Stewart Burns</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Krafted With Luv By Monsters.</info>

<info>The Planet Express ship flies towards Mars <info>("Mightiest of Planets")</info> 
and lands just outside Wong Ranch <info>(You've Come To The Wong Place)</info>.</info>

<info>The Wongs' Porch. The entire Planet Express staff are there. 
Leela rings the doorbell and Mr. Wong slides a peephole across 
the door.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
<info>(from inside)</info> Yes?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hi, Dad. It's me and my co-workers.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
<info>(from inside)</info> Open up, Leo. It's Amy 
and her weirdos.</speak>

<info>He opens the door.</info>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Howdy, friends! Welcome to Mars!</speak>

<info>The Wongs' Entrance Room. The staff look around the house.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Thanks so much for inviting us, Mr. 
Wong. I've never been to a Mars Day 
barbecue.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Oh, Mars Day much better than Earth 
Day. Dump trash wherever you want! Big, 
empty planet!</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
OK, then. Make yourselves at home.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg stands on the landing, dressed in a bathrobe. He is 
holding a green bottle.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Don't mind if I already did. By the 
way, do you have anymore of this Dom 
Perignon bubble bath? There was only 
enough to fill the tub halfway.</speak>

<info>Mr. and Mrs. Wong growl.</info>

<info>Wong Ranch. The Wongs and the staff pass a field where a man 
is rolling out fully-grown corn.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
This is quite a large ranch you have.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
17.9 billion acres. We own entire western 
hemisphere. <info>(whispering)</info> That the best 
hemisphere!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It's the same on Earth.</speak>

<info>They all look over a fence at a herd of buggalo.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Here is most number one product of all: 
The mighty buggalo. They used for everything; 
Meat, milk and their shells make good 
row boat.</speak>

<info>He points to Zoidberg, rowing a buggalo shell on a lake.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(shouting)</info> I broke your television.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Mon, it must take forever to brand all 
those cattle.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Not really. We own so much stuff, it 
easier just to brand everything that 
not ours.</speak>

<info>He brands Hermes' briefcase with "Not Property Of Wongs" brand.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Please don't do that.</speak>

<info>Amy leaps over a fence to another buggalo. It is surrounded 
with cushy things and has a ribbon around its neck.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Betsy!  This is my sweet, little Betsy. 
I raised her from a larva that ate one 
of my sweaters.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Yes, everybody love Betsy. We going 
to eat her at Amy's wedding. If she 
ever get married!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Dad! Gleesh! Please don't say things 
like that when you meet my boyfriend 
tonight.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Oh, that right. We finally get to spend 
some time with this Mr. Kif.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
I just hope he's a nice man who can 
make us lot of grandchildren. This not 
some parallel universe where you getting 
any younger.</speak>

<info>Nimbus Bridge. The Nimbus is orbiting Mars. Zapp and Kif talk. 
Near them is a photo of Amy.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Now, remember, Kif: The quickest way 
to a girl's bed is through her parents. 
Have sex with them and you're in.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Actually, sir, I'm, I'm a little nervous 
about meeting her family.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Well that's natural. After all you're 
meek and uninteresting. Until now you've 
gotten by on my left-over charisma, 
scrounging off it like a tiny charisma 
parasite.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
I just hope they like me.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
And why wouldn't they? Yes, yes, I know. 
Tiny, meek, uninteresting. Spare me 
your tedious life story, Kif. And above 
all have fun!</speak>

<info>Outside Wongs' House. Lots of people have gathered at the ranch 
for country music and barbecued buggalo on Mars Day. The DJ scratches 
some country music.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah, yeah, get on down!  Oh, yeah! 
Drop another barnyard bomb on us, Vanilla 
Corn!</speak>

<speak who="DJ">
Yo, fool! It's Mixmaster Festus!</speak>

<info>Mr. Wong puts more buggalo meat on the barbecue. A Pepto-Bismol 
tanker pulls up next to a BBQ Sauce tanker and unloads. Fry sets 
his plate of buggalo down on a barrel and pumps some Pepto-Bismol 
onto it. He picks it up and walks over to the barbecue.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So what's Mars Day about, anyway?</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
It commemorate the day centuries ago 
when our ancestor, Sir Reginald Wong, 
bought Mars from stupid natives.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
How can you call the Native Martians 
"stupid"?</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
They sell whole planet for one bead. 
Sound stupid to me!</speak>

<info>He, Mrs. Wong and Fry laugh.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
That is stupid!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I can't believe you're laughing at the 
tragic exploitation of a proud, bead-loving 
people.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Lighten up, Leela. It's funny!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Of course it is. But you don't have 
to laugh!</speak>

<info>Amy and Kif stand by the buffet. Amy kisses him and he is startled.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Amy, no! Not on your parents' planet!</speak>

<speak who="RJ">
Howdy, Amy. Glad to see you've come 
back to the country. It's where the 
flavour is.</speak>

<info>Amy hugs him.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
RJ, this is my boyfriend, Kif.</speak>

<speak who="RJ">
This wimp? You've gone a long way, baby. 
Cigarette, partner?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh, I don't--</speak>

<info>RJ puts one in Kif's mouth and he coughs.</info>

<speak who="RJ">
I haven't even lit it yet!</speak>

<info>He lights it.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh. Is it lit now?</speak>

<speak who="RJ">
Yep.  You're pathetic!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg walks over to the barbecue.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Host-man! Host-woman! I'm having a wonderful 
time!</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
You here five hours and already you 
tear up couch, draw moustache on priceless 
painting and fill pool with brine shrimp.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Not bad for a city boy, huh?  By the 
way, I took the liberty of fertilising 
your caviar.</speak>

<info>Mr. Wong looks at his food and chews slower. At the bar, Bender 
pours himself another drink, knocks it back, stacks the glass 
on top of 13 others, pours the last of the bottle down his neck 
and stacks the bottle on top of 11 others. He belches fire. Kif 
stammers and Amy wipes sweat from his face.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Just relax. I'm sure my parents will 
love you.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
You don't understand. When I get nervous, 
I can't control my camouflage reflex. 
Oh, dear!  Oh, goodness! Oh, odds and 
bodkins!</speak>

<info>Fry refills at the barbecue.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll have a thorax and some feelers.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
You want some salad with that?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yuck!</speak>

<info>Amy and Kif arrive.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Mom? Dad? You remember Kif?</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
This your boyfriend? I have instant 
dislike of him!</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
He too scrawny to father grandchildren.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
He's not scrawny, he's just small-boned.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Actually, I don't have bones. I'm supported 
by a system of fluid-filled bladders 
that--</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Yes, yes! You a big squishy wuss! Amy 
should be dating real man. Like him!</speak>

<info>He points to RJ over by a campfire.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
I can be manly too. I think I'll, uh, 
light up a smoke.</speak>

<info>He takes out a cigarette and lights it.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(whispering)</info> Wrong way!</speak>

<info>Kif drags.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
<info>(wheezy)</info> Smooth!</speak>

<info>He chokes, turns pale and collapses.</info>

<info>Wong Ranch. Kif and Amy lean over a fence and watch the grazing 
cattle.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Look on the bright side: My parents 
left after you passed out so they didn't 
even see you barf.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh, now they'll never think I'm manly 
enough to date their daughter.</speak>

<info>He sobs.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
It's OK, Kif.  I'll go get you a tissue 
from your tote.</speak>

<info>She walks off. RJ puts his hand on her shoulder and stops her.</info>

<speak who="RJ">
Hey there, Amy. Like you to meet my 
buddy, Joe.</speak>

<info>Enter Joe Camel.</info>

<speak who="JOE">
Sorry I'm late. My pool game ran long 
at the jazz club!</speak>

<info>RJ laughs.</info>

<speak who="RJ">
Kids love him!</speak>

<info>Kif watches Amy laugh and growls.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Wong House. A loud noise that sounds like a 
very long "omm" comes into earshot.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What's that weird sound?</speak>

<info>The noise gets louder. Wind blows down the "Happy Mars Day" 
banner.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Dust storm! Oh, dust storm! Everybody 
into house. Hurry, before we die. And 
wipe your damn feet!</speak>

<info>The Wongs' Lounge. Everyone is inside. Mrs. Wong looks out of 
the window.</info>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Phew! Everyone OK? No-one considering 
lawsuit?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hmm. I might have mental anguish.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
I'll have you know I'm friends with 
every judge on planet.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm OK then.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Storm dying down. Leo, check if buggalo 
herd is OK.</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Wongs' Porch. Mr. Wong opens the door and looks 
across at the cattle. A tornado sweeps across the ranch, taking 
the buggalo with it. Everyone gasps.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Oh!</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Wongs' Lounge.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What happened to the buggalo?</speak>

<info>Mrs. Wong comes running.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
They been rustled under cover of storm. 
We ruined!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg puts his arms around Mr. and Mrs. Wong and they struggle.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(screaming)</info> Nooo!</speak>

<info>They push him away.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Don't worry, Daddy. It'll be OK.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Oh, really? Who gonna save us?  One-eye? 
Lobster mooch?  Drunken garbage can?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
This sounds like a job for--</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Lieutenant Kif Kroker!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Alright then.</speak>

<info>He sits down and munches some crisps.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. The other guests have left.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Aye-ah! Those buggalo are what made 
Wong family so rich and powerful. Oh, 
Inez, with them stolen, we ruined!</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
OK. I want a divorce.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg is dressed golf clothes.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Mom! Dad! Don't ask me to choose!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
They're not your parents, I'm not your 
sister and that's not your golf cart.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Aw!</speak>

<info>He reverses the golf cart away.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Everybody just calm down. Kif promised 
he'd catch the rustlers.</speak>

<info>Enter Kif in cowboy gear.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Mrs. Wong, do you have a neckerchief 
I could borrow?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
My plan is to take all the remaining 
buggalo and lead them on a rough, tough 
cattle drive. Then, when the rustlers 
attack, I'll make a citizen's arrest!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It sounds dangerous. Someone could get 
killed. Fry, Leela, Bender, I want you 
to go with him.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Aw, man!</speak>

<info>Leela sighs. Bender mocks Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Don't worry, Mr. and Mrs. Wong. I'll 
get your cattle back or die trying.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Hey, we can't lose!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No, Kif! It's too risky. You don't have 
to do this to prove your manliness.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Oh, yes he does!</speak>

<info>Wong Ranch. RJ leads some things towards Kif.</info>

<speak who="RJ">
Here are your mounts!</speak>

<info>Leela rubs one of the things and it makes a squelching noise.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
She's got a fine coat.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Now, we need buggalo to lure the rustlers. 
How many are left?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You're lookin' at her. Betsy's the only 
one left. She was curled up in my hamper 
when the storm hit.  Aw, she likes you!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Saddle up, men. We got some no good 
rustlers to ... catch!</speak>

<info>Mars Surface. Kif, Leela and Fry ride ahead while Bender sits 
on a wagon playing a banjo and singing a Bonanza-like tune.</info>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SINGING)</info>
We've got a right to pick a little fight 
with rustlers,

Somebody wants to pick a fight with us,

He'd better bite my ass!

</speak><speak who="FRY">
Yee-haw!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wow, look at that: Olympus Mons. The 
tallest volcano in the solar system.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Where?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Right in front of you.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh. Oh!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
We'll camp near the top. The rustlers 
will be sure to spot us there.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Where?</speak>

<info>Olympus Mons. The party have set up camp for the night. Bender 
tells a ghost story around the campfire.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
And even thought the computer was off 
and unplugged, an image stayed on the 
screen. It was ... the Windows logo!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Pfft, that's not scary!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It is if you're a laser printer.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, my turn to tell a ghost story. Once, 
there was this woman driving--</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hook on the hand!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
OK, I've got one. This family--</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Man in the attic!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fine, Mr. Know-It-All-About-Something-Finally, 
you tell a story!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
With pleasure. <info>(spookily)</info> Once, not 
far from here, four people set out on 
a cattle drive--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(speaking fast)</info> Robot gets bored and 
kills Fry with a hammer! <info>(normal)</info> Sorry, 
go on.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Someone peers through the bushes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
And then, while they sat helplessly 
around the campfire ... a demented knife-wielding 
escaped lunatic libertarian zombie mutant 
snuck up and--</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(from bushes)</info> Surprise!</speak>

<info>Fry, Bender, Kif and Leela scream. Amy comes out of the bushes.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Amy? What are you doing here?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I forgot to give you something before 
you left.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
What?</speak>

<info>Amy kisses him and his camouflage kicks in.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Is that your camouflage reflex or are 
you just happy to see me?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Amy and Kif are lying down at the top of the mountain 
looking at the stars.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
I love it out here, Amy. I feel so manly. 
I have a blister, I-I spit! A-And of 
course, I tell no one my feelings.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
But you still have them, right?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh, yes. But I keep them inside until 
I can write them in my diary.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Ah, it's a wonderful night.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
It sure is. I could just lie here beside 
you staring at the sky all night.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I can't!  What's that?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Maybe we just made love.</speak>

<info>Amy and Kif look over the rim of the volcano and into the crater.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
The buggalo! They're in the crater.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
The rustlers must have seen me coming 
and run off, scared.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, Kif! You're so brave!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
<info>(nervous)</info> Sh! They'll hear us!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The next morning. Kif pulls a wire from a mineshaft 
on the side of the volcano.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
OK, the dynamite's in place.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Are you sure there's no other way to 
get the buggalo out?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Not unless your parents have thousands 
of helicopters at their disposal.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Well actually--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Too late! This is more fun!</speak>

<info>He detonates the dynamite and the buggalo are blown out of the 
crater. They roll down the side of the volcano.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Kif! You did it! But how did you know 
the dynamite would work?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
I once took a seminar in ejecting chickens 
from a sand dune. The principle is essentially 
the same.</speak>

<info>The noise returns.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, it's that "barbecue's over" sound 
again.</speak>

<info>Dust flies up and the tornado blows towards them.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(shouting)</info> Sandstorm!  We're in the 
eye of the storm!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Where?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What's that?</speak>

<info>There is a buzzing noise. Three Martians come through the tornado, 
riding flying buggalo. They have blue-grey skin and the tops 
of their heads look like Native American headgear has been fused 
to their head. Amy screams.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
My God!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Who are they?</speak>

<info>The lead Martian, Singing Wind, raises his hand.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Fehk! We are the Native Martians.</speak>

<info>Everyone except Fry gasps. After a late reaction, he also gasps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Also, I didn't know buggalo could fly.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Only those who revere Mother Mars can 
fly buggalo. And only they shall have 
buggalo. And they're us.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
But your, um, Martian-ness, these buggalo 
aren't yours. They belong to the Wong 
family.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
You mean family that took all Martian 
land and gave us one lousy bead?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Uh-huh! Amy Wong.  And you are?</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Mad at Wong family! We plan to ruin 
them by stealing buggalo. But now we 
take girl instead.</speak>

<info>Two other Martians pick up Amy and they fly away.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Wait! I'm too rich to be kidnapped!</speak>

<info>The Martians fly away.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Amy! Nooo!</speak>

<info>He cries.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Don't worry, Kif. I'm sure some other 
beautiful, rich girl will fall in love 
with you.</speak>

<info>Bender laughs and Kif cries.</info>

<info>Wong Ranch. The buggalo are returned and Kif closes the gate 
behind them.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Hooray! You bring back cattle.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Yes ... but ... I'm afraid I've got 
some bad news as well.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Let Amy tell us. That way it soften 
the blow.  Why Amy being so quiet?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Um ... well, um ... that is, um...</speak>

<info>A smaller tornado whips by and drops a piece of paper in front 
of Mr. Wong. He picks up.</info>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Oh, no! Martians kidnap Amy!  I know 
it them 'cause they no use good grammar.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
I'll get your daughter back, sir. I 
swear.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Forget it, squishy. You the one lose 
her in first place. You done enough.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Yeah. This time we get most decorated 
law man in the whole universe!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
You mean--? Oh, no, please. I beg you! 
Oh, for the love of--</speak>

<info>The Wongs' Lounge. The law man has arrived.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
I am the man with no name. Zapp Brannigan, 
at your service!</speak>

<info>Kif sighs.</info>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Please, Mr. Brannigan, we need you go 
get our daughter back.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Very well. I'll clean up Kif's mess. 
I shall go bargain with the Martian's 
personally.  Your gasps intrigue me. 
Explain.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Martians have no land. They been gently 
encouraged to live on reservation deep 
underground. No-one ever dare go there.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
This mission is incredibly dangerous. 
Someone's sure to be killed. Fry, Leela, 
Bender--</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Damn you, old man!</speak>

<info>Mars Surface. Zapp, Kif, Leela, Fry and Bender trek across the 
desert again. Betsy catches up with them and rubs against Kif.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aw, look. Betsy followed you, Kif!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
I didn't realise you were bringing your 
girlfriend, lieutenant!</speak>

<info>He sniggers and Kif sighs.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
She won't leave me alone.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Did I say "girlfriend"? She sounds more 
like a wife!</speak>

<info>There is silence. A tumbleweed blows by.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. They reach a cliff and look over the edge.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Behold: The Great Stone Face of Mars.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hm.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
The only known entrance to the Martian 
reservation.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What about the Great Stone Ass of Mars?</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Well, yeah, but it's way over the other 
side of the planet.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. They prepare to walk through one of the nostrils.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Nose-ward, ho!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Martian Reservation. The nose begins to get darker. 
They mumble. They are surrounded by torches. They gasp. It gets 
lighter and they see they are surrounded by Martians with bows 
and laser-arrows. Singing Wind walks in.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Fehk! I am Singing Wind, chief of the 
Martian tribe.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Take me to your leader.</speak>

<info>The Martians stare blankly at him.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Moving along. Why you trespass on our 
land?</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
We come to negotiate the release of 
Amy Wong. And just to clarify: Land 
is the stuff that has sky over it.</speak>

<info>He drinks from a Slurm can and throws it down. A Martian cries 
� la the Native American in those American public service advertisements.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
They have such respect for the planet.</speak>

<speak who="MARTIAN">
Cynthia used to drink Slurm.</speak>

<info>Singing Wind claps and Martians come in holding Amy.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
We will give back girl when we get back 
planet surface.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
How do we even know she's alive?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I'm fine.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Sh! You're weakening our bargaining 
position. How about instead you give 
us the girl and we carve a bunch of 
our presidents into your sacred mountain?</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
You waste words. We want return of land 
that was taken from us.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh, actually you traded it for a bead.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Tribe suffer heap big buyer's remorse. 
We want land back!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Chief, my people are a people of law. 
And that law is ...  ... no backsies!</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
The time for stupid statements is over!</speak>

<info>He and the other Martians make the "omm" noise. The dust picks 
up.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Oh, boy!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Mars Surface. The Great Stone Face's mouth opens and 
the tornado blows the sand away, revealing a Great Stone Body.</info>

<info>Cut to: Martian Reservation. Dust blows in Leela's face.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Ow, ow, ow, ow! My eye!</speak>

<info>She puts in some eye drops.</info>

<info>Mars University. The tornado blows down the "Knowledge Brings 
Fear" sign and strips away the Martian statue to a skeleton.</info>

<info>Wong Ranch. Zoidberg looks out the window.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ma! Pa! Our precious ranch!</speak>

<info>Mrs. Wong beats Zoidberg over the head with a trophy head.</info>

<info>Martian Reservation. Singing Wind gives a signal and the tornado 
sucks up Amy.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Amy, no! It's too windy!  Stay calm, 
dearest! I'll save you!</speak>

<info>He flies Betsy into the tornado.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Kif!  You're flying Betsy!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Need a lift?</speak>

<info>Amy grabs hold of his face and stretches it.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Great Mother Mars! He has the gift!</speak>

<info>He gives a signal and the Martians stop making the noise and 
the tornado dies away. Kif lands Betsy. Zapp, Leela, Fry and 
Bender cheer.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yay, Kif!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Kroker, that was one Brannigan-esque 
feat of heroism!</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
We have misjudged you, green one. You 
fly the buggalo like us. You have true 
reverence for Mother Mars. Let there 
be peace between us.</speak>

<speak who="MARTIAN #2">
Yes. Let us smoke on peace pipe.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Smoke-em?</speak>

<info>Martian Tent. Singing Wind smokes the pipe and passes it to 
Kif.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Here, take.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Ooh, no thanks. I'm on the peace patch.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
You must smoke peace pipe. And you must 
do it peacefully. Or we'll kill you.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Well it's just really that I don't feel 
that--</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Don't be such a chicken, Kif. Teenagers 
all smoke and they seem pretty on the 
ball.</speak>

<info>Kif takes a puff and everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Yes, sir!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Way to suck it!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Hey, I'm smoking! I'm the greatest! 
Oh, monkey trumpets!</speak>

<info>Martian Torture Chamber. Kif is held down on a rack with rope.</info>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
You have coughed at our offer of peace. 
So you must die!</speak>

<speak who="MARTIAN #2">
The very bead used to crush our dreams 
shall be used to crush your bones.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Well, actually, I don't have bones. 
I'm supported by a system of fluid-filled 
bladders that--</speak>

<info>The Martians ignore him and turn away. The roof opens and Kif 
screams. The bead is lowered in and he whimpers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait. That's the bead you traded your 
land for?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's a gigantic diamond! That thing 
must be worth a fortune.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Really?</speak>

<info>The diamond stops and Kif sighs. Bender takes a look at the 
diamond through an eye glass and stutters.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, Chief, you've made me the happiest 
girl in the world!</speak>

<info>He hugs Singing Wind and he immediately pushes him away.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Y'know, if you still want your land, 
we could just trade back for it.</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Hmm. We always thought bead was worthless. 
We assumed our ancestors were cheated 
because they not have concept of ownership.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
So we can have the diamond?</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
No. We do have concept of ownership. 
You are free to go. Sorry about all 
the rustling and kidnapping.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
But what about your sacred land?</speak>

<speak who="SINGING WIND">
Land shmand! We don't wanna live on 
this planet. It's a dump. We'll buy 
new planet and act like it's sacred. 
With cash like this, who's going to 
argue? Nobody, that's who!</speak>

<info>The Martian ships fly away from Mars with the diamond in tow.</info>

<info>The Wongs' Lounge. Everyone is back.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Then Kif flew Betsy, rescued me from 
the tornado and made peace with the 
Martians.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Please! He too much of a wimp.</speak>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Yeah. I'm sure it was all Mr. Zapp Brannigan 
here.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Please, you give me too little credit.</speak>

<info>Kif sighs.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Captain Brannigan, you're always welcome 
here at Rancho Zoidberg!</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Wongs' Porch. Zoidberg is thrown out. He hits his 
head on a post and scoffs.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Money doesn't make good people, no siree!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Later that night, Amy comes out onto the porch. 
Kif is sat on the porch swing.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Thanks for saving my life, Kif. You're 
my hero.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh, you're kind. But your parents still 
don't like me.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Well globviously! But if they liked 
you then I wouldn't. Don't you know 
anything about girls?</speak>

<info>They kiss. The buggalo run past and the ground shakes. Amy gets 
up and goes back inside. Kif gets out his diary.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Dear diary, I just made love for the 
second time!</speak>

<info>He closes his diary and hugs it.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>