<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 502

<title>JURASSIC BARK</title>

<author>Eric Kaplan</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Not Affiliated With Futurama Brass 
Knuckle Co.</info>

<info>Robot Arms Apartments: Fry and Bender's Apartment. Bender stands 
in front of a mirror wearing a magician's outfit. Fry wears a 
snazzy leotard. Bender speaks into the mirror.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ahem! For my next trick, notice I have 
nothing up my sleeves......and nothing 
in my head.  So if my lovely assistant 
will kindly supply me with an ordinary, 
non-fake pitcher of milk......behold 
the milk has vanished! Exiled, perhaps, 
to another dimension!</speak>

<info>He bows to his "audience." As he bows milk drips out from his 
chest cabinet. Fry applauds.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Amazing! That's why they call you "Bender 
The Magnificent"!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
No it isn't!</speak>

<info>He throws the newspaper across the room into a bin. Fry sees 
the headline: Archeologists Discover "Slice Of Old New York"</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Whoa! They discovered an intact, 20th 
Century pizzeria! Just like the one 
I used to work at!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Interesting. No wait the other thing 
- tedious!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Lets go check it out. You can see how 
I lived before I met you.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You lived before you met me?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Sure. Lots of people did.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Really?</speak>

<info>Museum. Fry and Bender walk down a corridor to the exhibit. 
Bender hums.</info>

<info>Cut to: Museum: Pizzeria.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Truly, they were as Gods who build this 
place!</speak>

<info>A tour group enters.</info>

<speak who="TOUR GUIDE">
Next, we come to the splendidly preserved 
wooden pizza paddle.  Scientists theorise 
it was used to gently discipline the 
delivery boy.</speak>

<info>Fry crouches next to the robot delivery boy and fiddles around 
with his hair so it looks like his robot counterpart's. He notices 
a menu on the wall. A menu which says "Panucci's Pizza."</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait a second! This is Panucci's! I 
used to work in this exact pizzeria! 
And for your information lady, this 
was not just used to paddle my butt, 
it was also used to move pizzas and 
crush rats.</speak>

<speak who="TOUR GUIDE">
I don't know where you get your facts 
sir but I am a volunteer housewife with 
45 minutes of orientation and a harlequin 
romance about archeologists!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Don't wave your fancy degrees at me. 
I recognise all this stuff.  Petrified 
sausages, Old Mr Patelli, and that's 
-</speak>

<info>He gasps. There is a dog shaped black thing in the display case.</info>

<info>Flashback - August 1997.</info>

<info>Street. The dog sits in an alley scratching itself. It sees 
Fry across the street delivering a pizza. Fry buzzes a buzzer.</info>

<speak who="VOICE"><info>ON BUZZER.</info>
Yes?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Pizza delivery for Mr......Seymour Asses.</speak>

<speak who="VOICE"><info>ON BUZZER.</info>
There's no one by that name here...or 
anywhere. I hope that in time you'll 
realise what an idiot you've been.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I wouldn't count on it.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Alley. Fry sits leaning against a wall. He opens the 
pizza box and takes out a slice and starts to eat it. The dog 
crawls out from behind a dumpster and whines. Fry sees him.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Aww. Poor little guy. You look like 
you haven't eaten in a month. Here......but 
if Mr Panucci asks, your name is Seynour 
Asses!  I like you Seymour, you're not 
constantly judging me like all the other 
dogs - are you? Nah. We understand each 
other.  People think you're a dumb mutt 
who smells bad, can't find a girlfriend 
and has a crummy job. But you're keepin' 
it real and call no man "Mister."  Well 
goodbye.  Live long and prosper.</speak>

<info>He rides away. Seymour watches.</info>

<info>Cut to: Street. Seymour chases Fry, barking.</info>

<info>Flashback ends. Bender reacts to the petrified dog.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yuck! That's the least appetising calzone 
I've ever seen!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No! That's my dog in there! It's an 
outrage I say!</speak>

<info>He grabs Bender's foot, smashes the display case and takes Seymour. 
Bender hops around holding his foot.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ow ow ow!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm taking him home and I'd like to 
see anyone try and stop me.  Uh-oh!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Street. The security guards literally throw Fry out 
of the building. He bounces down the steps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow, oo ow, oo ah!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
...And then he was ejected by the guards. 
Needless to say, I was mortified.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well it's not right to make my dead 
pet an exhibit. That's like digging 
up Lassie and putting her on display 
in the Louvre.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Lassie is on display in the Louvre.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I know, I was deliberately describing 
a similar situation.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Why don't you try protesting? Like those 
native Martians. Always whining that 
people don't treat their ancestor's 
bones with respect.</speak>

<info>He takes a slurp from a mug which look suspiciously like a Martian 
skull.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nah, protesting never works.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You're right.  I'll give it a shot!</speak>

<info>Street. Fry is outside the museum holding a sign and a megaphone.</info>

<speak who="CROWD"><info>(CHANTING)</info>
What do you want?</speak>

<speak who="CROWD">
<info>(chanting)</info> When do you want it?</speak>

<speak who="CROWD">
Yaaay!</speak>

<info>He turns on a tape dances to the Hustle. Leela reads a book.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
It says this part of The Hustle implores 
the Gods to grant a favour. Usually 
a Trans-AM.</speak>

<info>Flashback - July 1998 The Summer Of "I Still Know What You Did 
Last Summer."</info>

<info>Street. Fry cycles down the street towards Panucci's singing.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(SINGING)</info>
I'm walking on sunshine! Ooo-oo-ooh! 
I'm walking on sunshine! Ooo-oo-ooh! 
At a boy Seymour! Right here waiting 
for me as always! Just like that huge 
mushroom in my shower!</speak>

<info>He goes inside. Seymour follows through the dog flap.</info>

<info>Cut to: Panucci's Pizza.</info>

<speak who="PANUCCI">
Hey there's our little mascot!  Aww 
you been swimming in the sewer again? 
You little rascal!  Fry, cleanup!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Seymour, cleanup!  Good dog!</speak>

<speak who="PANUCCI">
That's a good Seymour!</speak>

<info>A boy is playing an arcade game when he notices something is 
wrong with his pizza.</info>

<speak who="BOY">
Yo! There's dog fur on my slice!</speak>

<speak who="PANUCCI">
Nah, that's vermicelli! No fur in here!</speak>

<info>He sneezes into the dough and continues rubbing it. Seymour 
swims around in the tomato.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
He's so cute! He can do two things at 
one time: Eat and swim. Ooo - three 
things.</speak>

<info>Flashback ends. Fry is still dancing. It is raining. The music 
is getting muffled.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Fry, its been three days. You can't 
keep boogie-ing like this. You'll come 
down with a fever of some sort.</speak>

<info>Two men - Ben Beeler and his associate Ray - walk out of the 
museum. Beeler introduces himself.</info>

<speak who="BEELER">
Mr. Fry? I'm Dr Ben Beeler, the paleontologist 
who discovered your dog, or as some 
call it, the Beeler-saurus.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So do I get Seymour back? Are you caving 
to political pressure?</speak>

<speak who="BEELER">
No we're sorry but there's just too 
much that fossil can teach us about 
dogs from your time.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
His name was Seymour. He was once intimate 
with the leg of a wandering saxaphonist. 
He had wet dog smell, even when dry. 
And he was not above chasing the number 
29 bus.</speak>

<speak who="RAY">
The 29? Interesting.</speak>

<speak who="BEELER">
That's all I needed, Ray?</speak>

<speak who="RAY">
I'm good.</speak>

<speak who="BEELER">
OK then, here's your dog back.</speak>

<info>He takes Seymour's black fossil out of his briefcase and hands 
it to Fry. He hugs him and chuckles.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Seymour!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Bender the Magnificent has sawn Dr Zoidberg 
in half. Although his feet look oddly human.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Lady and Gentleman! How 'bout a hand 
for my temporary replacement assistant?</speak>

<info>Scruffy and Leela applaud. Zoidberg jumps out of one half of 
the box. He is wearing Fry's leotard.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I was all in this part! Its magic!</speak>

<info>Bender beats him with his wand as he speaks.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You are not fit to wear Fry's leotard!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Stop!</speak>

<info>Enter Farnsworth, Fry and Seymour.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Good news everyone!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hooray, he's back! He's looking for 
a garbage can to put that dog in! Here 
you go buddy!</speak>

<info>He holds up a waste basket.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No, actually we've discovered Fry's 
dog was fast-fossilised, preserving 
it's cellular structure!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Which means...we can clone it! Seymour 
will live again!</speak>

<info>Leela gasps.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
A little land mammal!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Can you believe it Bender? I'm going 
to have my best friend back!</speak>

<info>Bender turns away and starts to cry. His tears turn into balloons, 
he cries doves and his antenna sprouts flowers.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Attic. Farnsworth has set up his cloning machine. 
The crew look on. Enter annoying moron Cubert.</info>

<speak who="CUBERT">
Why the idiot convention?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ah Cubert, my precious babe. I'm going 
to attempt to clone Fry's dog. Using 
the very same apparatus I used to clone 
you!  Ooo look, there's a smidge of 
toe still in here.  You see, beneath 
the fossil's crunchy, mineral shell, 
there's still a creamy core of dog nougat!</speak>

<info>On the screen an arrow points to a yellow blob inside Seymour.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So will Seymour remember how to sing 
Walking On Sunshine?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Amazingly yes. In cases of rapid fossilisation, 
I can press this brain scan button, 
retrieving Seymour's memories at the 
precise instant of doggy death!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm gonna get my puppy back! In your 
face, Grim Reaper!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Crappy ineffective Reaper!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I just need to reset the Clone-O-Mat 
from Human Mode to Dog Mode.</speak>

<info>He turns a switch around to a picture of a dog. It is like a 
child's toy.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">'S VOICE
The dog says </speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Uh-oh, this may take a while.</speak>

<info>He bashes the switch.</info>

<info>Flashback - December 31 1999. Fry is "teaching" a kid to play 
an arcade game at Panucci's.</info>

<speak who="KID">
You stink loser!</speak>

<info>Panucci leans over the counter with the pizza.</info>

<speak who="PANUCCI">
Hey, Fry. Pizza goin' out. C'mon!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But I'm celebrating New Years Eve.</speak>

<speak who="PANUCCI">
Like you got squat to celebrate! You're 
a delivery boy this millenium and you'll 
be a delivery boy next millenium!  What's 
with Seymour? Its like he don't want 
you to go. Or he thinks your pants is 
too short or somethin'. Which is crazy 
'cause frankly you look fabulous. Now 
get goin'!!</speak>

<info>Street. Fry unlocks his bike. Seymour put his paw on the wheel 
so Fry can't go anywhere.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I won't be gone long Seymour. Just wait 
here 'til I come back.</speak>

<info>He rides off. Seymour sits, waiting.</info>

<info>Applied Cryogenics. Fry knocks on a door marked Applied Cryogenics. 
A sign underneath indicates No Power Failures Since 199[7</info>. No 
one opens the door so Fry goes in.]

<info>Cut to: Cryogenics Lab. The room is empty and there are no lights 
on. Weird pods line one of the walls. There are a few machines 
around the room and a desk and a chair in the middle of the room. 
Fry wipes some condesnsation from a window on one of the pods, 
revealing the face of an inanimate man inside.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hello? Pizza delivery for......Icy Wiener?! 
Aw crud! I always thought at this point 
in my life I'd be the one making the 
crank calls!  Here's to another lousy 
Millenium.  What the?</speak>

<info>He looks around and screams. In a flash he is frozen in time.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<info>Robot Arms Apartments: Fry and Bender's Apartment. In the kitchen 
Fry unloads dog food into the cupboards. Enter Bender who notices 
a dog collar on the side.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
A dog collar for me?  You shouldn't 
have!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's for Seymour.</speak>

<info>Bender takes it off.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh.  Say why'd you get me a subscription 
to the Daily Growl? That's not a reputable 
journal of opinion.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh that's also for Seymour. I'm getting 
everything ready for when he's cloned.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Are you on the jump Fry? Why are you 
wasting time on a creature of inferior 
intelligence?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey he was smart. He could fetch.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I can fetch.</speak>

<info>He runs out then back in again carrying an Easter Island Head.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
He could dig up bones.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hello? Charlamange?  Plus, I'll bet 
he couldn't create a laser show with 
his head.</speak>

<info>The lights go out and Bender creates a laser show with his head. 
Grooby music plays.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Look Bender, this has nothing to do 
with you.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
That's impossible!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Now if you'll excuse me I'm working 
on Seymour's doghouse.</speak>

<info>He points to a kennel and holds a sign saying "Seymour" ready 
to nail it on. Bender walks out.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
No one ever asks if Bender would like 
to live in a tiny little house. Not 
that I would. A tiny little house that 
says "Bender" on it.  Ow!</speak>

<info>Flashback - January 1st 2000. </info>

<info>The Frys' House. Mr Fry is on the phone but can only hear Fry's 
answerphone message.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>ON ANSWERPHONE</info>
This is Fry. If you're calling about 
the used towels for sale, they're still 
available for $45 each.</speak>

<info>The answerphone beeps.</info>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Phil, it's your father. Where are you? 
You're holding up New Years brunch. 
Your brother can't wait any longer.</speak>

<info>Yancy picks up a sandwich.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Hello first baloney of the new millenium! 
Ah here he comes. That's him and Seymour.</speak>

<info>Mr Fry opens the door and Seymour runs in barking.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Well that's odd. Seymour's here but 
-  - Go! Go! Touchdown!! But where's 
Philip?</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
I'm tellin' you the Y2K computer's got 
him. We'll face burnin' roads, rivers 
explodin' and calculators transformed 
into SCUD missiles. There's nothing 
we can do.  What's that Seymour? You 
walking on sunshine?</speak>

<info>He runs over to the door and scratches it.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
He's trying to tell us something. Maybe 
he can lead us to Philip.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside The Frys' House. Seymour runs out the front 
door.</info>

<speak who="YANCY">
Should we follow him?</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
To our deaths? Negatory.</speak>

<info>Cut to: The Frys' House.</info>

<speak who="MR FRY">
It's the Y2K tryin' to lure us into 
an ambush. And I ain't buyin' it. Pass 
the baloney.</speak>

<info>He eats a sandwich.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela and Amy wrestle while Fry stands 
at the side holding Seymour. Leela pins Amy down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Are you two gonna be done soon?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Sorry, but we need to practice hand 
to hand combat in case an enemy knocks 
the laser gun out of our hands and they 
slide waaay across the room.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well could you do it some place else? 
I'm setting up Seymour's doggy bed.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK.</speak>

<info>She drags Amy out of Fry's way. Fry kicks the mat out of the 
way and puts Seymour's bed on the floor next to the couch. Enter 
Bender and a Robo-Puppy.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Heel boy, heel! Oh hello Fry, I guess 
I didn't notice you there. I'm having 
such fun with my new best friend Robo-Puppy.</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(NOT CARING)</info>
That's nice.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I was just out walking him. Yes. You 
can walk him. Of course, after he goes 
you have to refill the canisters. C'mere 
boy! Pet, pet, pet.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOPUPPY">
Robo-Puppy receiving petting.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Bender, are you jealous of Fry's puppy? 
That's so adorable!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Jealous? Hah!  Not while I have the 
love of Robo-Puppy here. Robo-Puppy, 
lick my cheek.</speak>

<speak who="ROBOPUPPY">
Robo-Puppy preparing to lick cheek. 
Robo-Puppy commencing cheek licking. 
Licking in progress. Licking complete.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Robo-Puppy truly is robots best friend! 
Eh?</speak>

<info>Fry finishes the bed.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ah there, perfect!</speak>

<info>A fanfare sound sounds and a huge hologram of Farnsworth's head 
appears in the room.</info>

<speak who="HOLOFARNSWORTH">
Good news everyone! The Clone-O-Mat 
is ready!</speak>

<info>The hologram disappears.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Woohoo!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yay!</speak>

<info>Leela slams Amy down.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Finally!</speak>

<info>Bender growls.</info>

<speak who="ROBOPUPPY">
Robo-Puppy commencing two hour yipping 
session.  Robo-Puppy mistreatment alert! 
Robo-Puppy mistreatment alert!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Attic. The crew are standing in front of the 
Clone-O-Mat. The roof is open.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Behold once more the mighty Clone-O-Mat! 
Requiring such vast amounts of electricity 
that we must harness the elemental power 
of nature itself!  I speak of course...of 
molten lava! Deep within the Earth's 
core. To the sub-basement!</speak>

<info>He pulls a lever and the Clone-O-Mat, crew and all go down.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Sub-Basement. Scruffy is pulling the 
platform down. It topples but he rights it. Farnsworth steps 
off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Come on boy! Come back to life!</speak>

<info>He pulls a chain and Seymour's DNA begins to be extracted. Enter 
Bender The Magnificent.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry c'mon, the talent show!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What? I'm in the middle of something.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But, if we don't perform, in what sense 
do we have an act?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender, enough! Leave me alone!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
So that's how it is huh? I thought you 
were my friend. But if you love your 
dog so much then maybe you'd rather 
play fetch!</speak>

<info>He picks up Seymour and throws him into the molten lava.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
No!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh!</speak>

<info>Seymour sinks. Fry gasps. Bender laughs and hugs Fry.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Now I'm all you got!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Fry starts weakly hitting Bender.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I hate you! I hate you! You evil metal 
man!  Ow!</speak>

<info>He falls to the floor and curls up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
So anyway your dog is melted. Now we're 
friends again.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Not necessarily. For the dog may yet 
survive.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
May yet? Really?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Indeed. You see, that fossil was made 
of dolomite. The tough black mineral 
that won't cop out when there's heat 
all about. By contrast, observe the 
lava's affect on this ice swan.  Of 
course, that would have melted even 
at room temperature. I just wanted to 
get rid of it. But had it been made 
of that righteous mineral dolomite, 
there's a slim chance it might have 
survived.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So Seymour might still exist?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Perhaps. For a few minutes. It's dolomite 
baby!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Then I'm goin' in after him.</speak>

<info>He takes his jacket off and rips off his shirt. He pulls off 
his trousers and runs for the lava.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
No!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Stop!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
He'd come after me.</speak>

<info>Flashback - January 1st 2000.</info>

<info>Cut to: Street. Seymour runs down a street and looks in Panucci's 
window. He sniffs Fry's hand and face prints on the pavement.</info>

<info>Cut to: 99c Store. Seymour runs in and sniffs a photo of Fry 
underneath a notice saying "Do Not Take Checks From This Man"</info>

<info>Cut to: Itelli's Barber Shop. Seymour runs in and sniffs some 
red hair clippings. He eats some.</info>

<info>Cut to: Mr Putzz' Mini-Golf. Seymour looks through the railings.</info>

<info>Cut to: Street. Seymour runs down the street and sniffs around. 
A door opens and someone throws out a pizza box. A Panucci's 
Pizza box. Seymour runs inside.</info>

<info>Flashback ends. Fry takes a dive for the lava. Leela and Amy 
push him to the ground.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Acting like a moron won't bring your 
dog back.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Then all hope is lost.  Goodbye Seymour.</speak>

<info>He cries.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Please stop crying Fry. Here.  I assumed 
you were just pretending to love the 
dog. To toy with my emotions. Oh what 
have I done?</speak>

<info>He starts to cry.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You didn't do anything. Don't beat yourself 
up.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry, I'm sorry. I should have understood 
how someone can love an inferior creature. 
Because I love you. Not in the way of 
the Ancient Greeks, but in the way a 
robot loves a human, a human loves a 
dog and occassionally, a gorilla loves 
a kitty.  I'm goin' in!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm a professor! Why isn't anyone listening 
to me? You can't go in because you'll 
melt. The fossil only has a chance because 
it's made of dolomite!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm 40% dolomite!</speak>

<info>He bags his chest and dives in. His hat and cape float on the 
surface. Everyone gasps.</info>

<info>Cut to: Lava.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh it's hot, it's very hot!</speak>

<info>His casing starts to come apart.</info>

<info>Flashback - January 1st 2000.</info>

<info>Cryogenics Lab. Seymour barks at Fry, frozen in the cryo-tube. 
A man fixes a radiator and a cryogenisist sits at his desk nursing 
a hangover.</info>

<speak who="CRYOGENISIST">
Ugh, I am one hungover cryogenisist! 
Just throw that mutt in the freezer 
until his owners get here!</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
You can't solve all your problems by 
freezing them boss.</speak>

<speak who="CRYOGENISIST">
I think you're forgetting our motto.</speak>

<info>He points at a sign that reads "You Can Solve All Your Problems 
By Freezing Them!" Underneath in a cryo-tube is a woman with 
a rolling pin and an apron. Probably the man's wife. Enter Mr 
and Mrs Fry.</info>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Are you the cryogenisist who called 
about our son's dog?</speak>

<speak who="CRYOGENISIST">
Oh you must be the Fry's. Yeah he's 
right over there.</speak>

<info>He points to Seymour who is still yelping at Fry's freezer.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
Sorry we're late, we all got sick from 
eating bad baloney!</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
Y2K!</speak>

<info>Mr and Mrs Fry stand by Fry's freezer but they can't see him 
inside.</info>

<speak who="MRS FRY">
What's he so worked up about?</speak>

<speak who="MR FRY">
He's just upset because our boy's missing. 
C'mon you overgrown rat. Lead us to 
Philip.</speak>

<info>Seymour struggles to go back to Fry but Mr Fry drags him out.</info>

<info>Flashback ends. Bender still hasn't returned to the surface.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender's been down there too long. I'm 
going in after him.</speak>

<info>She starts to rip off her wrestling suit.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Professor! Lava! Hot!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
This is all my fault. I let my best 
friend risk his life just to get my 
dead dog back.  Bender!!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And that is why they call me Bender 
The Magnificent!  Hey where'd everybody 
go?</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
OK! Let's clone us some dog!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Very well. Let this abomination unto 
the Lord begin!  Interesting. It seems 
Seymour died at the ripe old age of 
15.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
15? You mean he lived for 12 more years 
after I got frozen?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Indeed.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Stop the cloning.</speak>

<info>He picks up a spanner and hits the Clone-O-Mat with it.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh sure! Smash the smart guy's machine!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fry, what's wrong?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Think about it. Seymour lived a full 
life after I was gone. He probably added 
new songs to his repertoire.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
But that's a good thing. Walking On 
Sunshine sucks noodles!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I had Seymour 'til he was three. That's 
when I knew him and that's when I loved 
him.  I'll never forget him. But he 
forgot me a long long time ago.</speak>

<info>He kisses Seymour and walks away.</info>

<info>Flashback - January 2nd 2000. The song I Will Wait For You from 
the film Les Parapluies de Cherbourg plays. Seymour sits outside 
Panucci's Pizza waiting for Fry to come back. It changes to summer, 
then autumn, a snowy and rainy winter and back to spring. Panucci 
gives Seymour a slice of pizza. It goes through autumn and winter 
again. Seymour starts to age a little. The "U" from the "Panucci's 
Pizza" sign falls on a man. An aged Panucci pats Seymour on the 
head. Seymour continues waiting for Fry to return, and closes 
his eyes...</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>