<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 504

<title>A TASTE OF FREEDOM</title>

<author>Eric Horsted</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Or Is It?</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Zoidberg dances and sings on the 
table. Everyone else except Fry sits and claps along. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(singing)</info> Freedom, freedom, freedom, 
oy!

Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!

</speak><speak who="FRY">
There's no denying it: The future's 
crazy! Oh, well. Don't wanna stand out.</speak>

<info>He gets on the table and sings and dances with Zoidberg.</info>

<speak who="FRY AND ZOIDBERG">
<info>(singing)</info> Freedom, freedom, freedom, 
oy!

Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!

</speak><speak who="ZOIDBERG">
There's nothing crazy about it. It's 
just Freedom Day!</speak>

<info>He warbles.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Balcony. The staff celebrate Freedom Day with 
their Freedom Day Party. Farnsworth drinks Slurm and Scruffy 
blows a party blower. Amy sits on the railings eating a melon 
while Fry and Bender stand next to her.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
... an extremely dangerous mission ...</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So, what is Freedom Day? Sounds like 
some kind of feminine hygiene product.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg walks over and puts his claw on Bender's shoulder.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
No, it's a fabulous, crab-ulous day!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
If you wanna do something, you do it! 
And to splick with the consequences!</speak>

<info>She throws the melon rind over her shoulder and it hits something.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
You know? Like how I live every day.</speak>

<info>He sticks his leg out and trips up Hermes. His bones crack as 
he lands. Everyone laughs.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Happy Freedom Day! Ooh! I think my wrist 
is broken.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Of course, it wouldn't be Freedom Day 
without the traditional Freedom Tub!</speak>

<info>He presses a button and a hole in the floor opens revealing 
a hot-tub. Everyone reacts with excitement. Hermes dips his finger 
in.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Mmm! That'll feel nice on my shattered 
bones!</speak>

<info>The staff start to undress around Fry. He gasps.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wow! Nude hot-tubbing? That's all I 
need to hear about Freedom Day!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Then consider the following lecture 
a bonus: On Earth, freedom is a given. 
But on my planet, we have to suffer 
for it.</speak>

<info>Flashback. Child Zoidberg wears a hat and comical specs with 
attached mouth flaps. A Decapodian woman is with him.</info>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN WOMAN">
Sure, you can be a comedian instead 
of a doctor -- If you want your parents 
to roll over in their graves!</speak>

<info>Later, grown-up Zoidberg is at a polling station.</info>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN MAN">
Sure. You can vote for Shkinadel -- 
If you want there should be a recession!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg turns away sadly. Back at his home, Zoidberg is holding 
suitcases.</info>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN WOMAN">
Sure. You can go to medical school -- 
If you've given up on your dream of 
being a comedian!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg turns away sadly.</info>

<info>Flashback ends.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
That's why I love Earth! You can do 
what you want, and no-one makes you 
feel guilty because no-one cares.</speak>

<info>Fry is in the hot-tub with everyone else.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
<info>(shouting)</info> We're not listening!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
That's what I'm talking about!</speak>

<info>The ship flies over Washington D.C. (Rededicated to Washington 
the Sweathog, 2475). It flies over the Reflecting Pool where 
people bathe and lands in front of the Fxjkhr Monument. A banner 
has been hung up on it with "Freedom Day-- Express Yourself" 
printed on it. Underneath, a man has painted "I Hate My Job".</info>

<info>Washington D.C. Street. There is a parade. Vehicles carrying 
DOOP missiles float along the street. One has a "Boy Scout Troop 
#254" banner on it. The one behind has "Top Secret Do Not Look" 
on it. People on stilts walk by chanting the Freedom song.</info>

<speak who="STILT PEOPLE">
<info>(chanting)</info> Freedom, freedom, freedom, 
oy! Freedom, freedom, freedom, oy!</speak>

<info>The Fighting Dukaki drive past. On the pavement, Bender and 
other staff push their way to the front of the crowd. Bender 
is wearing a cowcatcher.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Scuse me, comin' through. Freedom train 
arriving on track one.</speak>

<info>He imitates a train whistle.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Ow! You broke my foot!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Freedom!</speak>

<info>In the commentary box, Morbo and Linda watch the parade go by.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
What's this next float, Linda?</speak>

<speak who="LINDA">
Representing our men, women and children 
in uniform, it's Earth's greatest space 
hero, Zapp Brannigan!</speak>

<info>Zapp and Kif are in a rocket float. Zapp waves to the crowd.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Happy Freedom Day, ladies!  Come on, 
let loose and show me something!  Anything. 
Seriously, I'd take an armpit.  Oh, 
yeah! Thank you, Linda!</speak>

<info>He throws some beads. Linda pulls her top down and catches the 
beads.</info>

<speak who="LINDA">
You're welcome! OK, Morbo, now it's 
your turn.</speak>

<speak who="MORBO">
If that is your Freedom Day wish.</speak>

<info>He lifts his shirt and Linda screams.</info>

<info>Fxjkhr Monument. A band plays Hail to the Chief and a man very 
slowly carries Nixon's head and places it on a podium. Crowds 
are gathered in front of the monument.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
Thank you, Secretary of Transportation. 
My fellow Earthicans, we enjoy so much 
freedom, it's almost sickening. We're 
free to choose which hand our sex-monitoring 
chip is implanted in. And if we don't 
want to pay our taxes, why, we're free 
to spend a weekend with the Pain Monster.</speak>

<speak who="PAIN MONSTER">
See you April 15th, folks!</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Cue the fireworks guy!  Incidentally, 
tonight's Freedom Day celebration is 
brought to you by ...  ... "Shankman's 
Rubbing Compound". When something needs 
rubbing, think "Shankman".</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yay! Shankman!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
It costs a little more but it's worth 
it!</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Our planet has been through so much 
this past year: Wars, droughts, impeachments! 
But we've never lost our sense of what's 
truly important: The great taste of 
"Charleston Chew"!  And now, let us 
salute that beloved symbol of freedom, 
our flag, Ol' Freebie!</speak>

<info>Earth's flag comes down. Zoidberg wipes his mouth.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'm swelling with patriotic mucus!</speak>

<info>Fireworks explode.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
In our darkest hour, we can stand erect, 
with proud upthrust bosoms!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Anyone who laughs is a Communist!</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Knowing that, with a shifty glance skyward, 
we will see by the rocket's red glare, 
that our flag is still there.  It's 
gone!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg tears the flag, eats it and belches. The crowd gasp. 
Zoidberg steps forward.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Yes, fellow patriots, I ate your flag. 
And I did it with pride. For to express 
oneself with doing a thing is the very 
essence of Freedom Day! Bless this planet 
and all its wonderful people!</speak>

<info>Crickets chirp.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
<info>(shouting)</info> Kill him! Kill the traitor!</speak>

<info>The crowd rush onto the platform and Zoidberg squeals.</info>

<info>Washington D.C. Street. Zoidberg scuttles around a corner, wooping 
and being chased by the crowd. He runs past a man spraying "Earth 
Sux" on a mailbox.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Hey, it's the guy who desecrated our 
flag!</speak>

<info>The crowd run past.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
Stop that red menace!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Embassy Row. Zoidberg runs past the grey Neutral Planet 
Embassy, the pretty Klingon Embassy and the Globetrotter Homeworld 
Embassy. He tires and stops running and wooping.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'm all scuttled out!  Huh? My planet's 
embassy? They're paid to not kill me! 
A-yoop!</speak>

<info>He jumps into the moat around the embassy and swims over.</info>

<info>Decapodian Embassy. The angry crowd are outside, shouting. Zoidberg 
is inside, sat across a desk from Ambassador Moivin, a man and 
a woman. The curtains close.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I thought I understood this world. I 
thought I was fitting in. But I guess 
I don't belong on here anymore than 
I belong on our crappy home planet-- 
Ooh, sorry.</speak>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN MAN">
What sorry? Our planet stinks, we all 
know it.</speak>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
Enough with the persecution, I'm saying. 
Zoidberg, as Ambassador, I promise you 
the full support of our government already.</speak>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN WOMAN">
Poor boy. You want maybe a nice mug 
cocoa?</speak>

<info>Zoidberg nods.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ambassador Moivin, you and your staff 
are so kind. I'm truly humbled.  What, 
no marshmallows?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Decapodian Embassy.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
Let's storm the place ... without my 
prior knowledge.</speak>

<info>The Planet Express staff push through again.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Scuse me, comin' through. Freedom train, 
step aside. You too, fatso. Freedom!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Cool your jowls, Nixon. You may not 
like it that Dr. Zoidberg desecrated 
a flag. You might even find the image 
of it festering in his bowels somehow 
offensive. But the right to freedom 
of expression is guaranteed by the Earth 
constitution.</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Aroo! Maybe so. But I know a place where 
the constitution doesn't mean squat.</speak>

<info>Supreme Court.</info>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
The Supreme Court hereby accepts the 
case of Earth vs Zoidberg.</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
Sock it to 'em!</speak>

<info>Newspaper Headline: "Lobster Trial Nears". Underneath is a sub-headline: 
"Mobster Trial Nears".</info>

<info>Outside Decapodian Embassy. There is a protest rally.</info>

<speak who="CROWD">
<info>(chanting)</info> Two, four, six, eight,

Eating the flag is bad.

</speak><speak who="SCOUT LEADER">
Now your noose knot has exactly seven 
twists.</speak>

<info>A man plays a guitar.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
<info>(singing)</info> You can eat my dog,

You can eat my truck,

But you eat my flag,

And you're outta luck!

She's a-wavin' proud around the world,

From Dallas to Fort Worth,

Let me say it again,

</speak><info>A truck toots.</info>

<speak who="CROWD">
<info>(chanting)</info> Don't mess with Earth!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
They sure hate Dr. Zoidberg.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Pft. Posers! I was hating Zoidberg before 
it was cool.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Where are we ever going to find a lawyer 
to take his case?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'll ask the head of the ACLU. Once 
he's done singing.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
<info>(singing)</info> Don't mess with Earth. <info>(talking)</info> 
Kill Zoidberg! Goodnight!</speak>

<info>Old Man Waterfall is behind them.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
Howdy there! I'm a lawyer and I'd like 
to help your friend out of his pickle.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Who are you, old man?</speak>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
Name's Old Man Waterfall. But most folks 
just call me "Old Man".</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll never remember that.</speak>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
I'm a veteran of three dozen wars. Name 
a body part and a planet and I've taken 
a bullet in it, on it. All to keep our 
flag flying free.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
And you wanna defend Zoidberg? Are you 
familiar with the old robot saying "Does 
Not Compute"?</speak>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
Son, to me a robot's just a garbage 
can with sparks comin' out it.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(sad)</info> The sparks keep me warm.</speak>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
I don't condone what Dr. Zoidberg did 
but I'll fight tooth and nail for his 
freedom to do it. Or I would if I hadn't 
lost my teeth and nails on Mars and 
Saturn respectively.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait, you're a lawyer? You're hired!</speak>

<info>Supreme Court. A hologram of Zoidberg appears on a table. The 
Planet Express staff sit in the front row.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You OK there in the embassy, Zoidberg?</speak>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
No. There's no coaco marshmallows and 
every night the rats eat a little more 
of my foot.</speak>

<speak who="BAILIFF">
Oyez, oyez, oyez. All rise for the Honourable 
Chief Justice, Myrtle Fu, and the associate 
justices.</speak>

<info>Sal pulls in several heads in jars and the Chief Justice.</info>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
Counsel, you may address the court on 
behalf of Earth, if you're ready.</speak>

<speak who="HYPERCHICKEN">
I was hatched ready! Honourable judge 
heads, yonder crawdad done ate up our 
flag.</speak>

<info>He points at Zoidberg.</info>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
I was doing freedom of speech. Earth's 
most sacred right.</speak>

<speak who="HYPERCHICKEN">
Your Honour, freedom of speech applies 
to what comes out of a mouth. Not what 
goes in.</speak>

<speak who="O'CONNOR">
Can counsel cite precedent?</speak>

<speak who="HYPERCHICKEN">
Uh, yes darlin', I can. In "State Of 
Alabama vs. Giant Space Iguana", chewin' 
the corners off the constitution was 
deemed "nonprotected speech".</speak>

<speak who="SOUTER">
He shut you up, O'Connor.</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
Mr. Waterfall, you may now present arguments 
on behalf of Dr. Zoidberg.</speak>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
Oh, God, I'm nervous. Two of my three 
hearts are having attacks.</speak>

<info>Bender laughs.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Court's kinda fun when it's not my ass 
on the line! Nachos?</speak>

<info>He offers some around. Old Man Waterfall gets up.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
Oh, land-o-Goshen! Your Honours, I'm 
not some slick, big-city lawyer like 
my opponent here.  But I am a veteran 
who has fought for his planet. You see 
this hand of mine?</speak>

<speak who="SCALIA">
Yes, I do.</speak>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
No, you don't  'Cause I lost my real 
hand plantin' the flag when we took 
back Halley's Comet! Yet it was worth 
it. So much do I love that flag.  I 
love it even more than I love my seven 
wives. That's right, I'm a polygamist. 
Yet I would gladly eat a flag myself, 
had I not used my intestine as a rope 
to hoist a flag made of my own skin, 
if it would protect the freedoms of 
the proud people who salute that flag. 
Freedom such as polygamy.  I rest my 
case.  Whoa, jeez!</speak>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
The justices and I will now confer using 
high-speed telepathy.  By a vote of 
six to three, we find that flag eating 
is not protected by the constitution.</speak>

<info>The court gasps.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Six to three? I beat the spread!</speak>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
The court orders an immediate public 
apology.</speak>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
Apology accepted. Just don't let it 
happen again.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
She means you, you turkey of the sea!</speak>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
Me? Apologise? Never! I came to this 
planet to learn the meaning of freedom. 
But I say it's you who should get a 
nice lesson! So do your worst, because 
no punishment could be worse than denying 
my freedom.</speak>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
You are hereby sentenced to death.</speak>

<speak who="HOLOZOIDBERG">
Wait, let me finish!</speak>

<info>The court gasps.</info>

<speak who="MYRTLE FU">
Also, in a rare double-whammy decision, 
the court finds polygamy constitutional.</speak>

<info>The court boos.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
I can't wait to tell my husband!</speak>

<info>The court boos louder.</info>

<info>Outside Decapodian Embassy. DOOP soldiers, led by Zapp, stand 
by the moat.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Remember, men: Take him alive so there's 
something left to kill.</speak>

<info>The troops use a battering ram on the door. The Ambassador and 
Zoidberg run onto the balcony above.</info>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
Stay back! This embassy is sovereign 
mud of the mud planet Decapod 10. Invading 
these mud premises is an act of war.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Yeah? Well what are you going to do 
about it, Shrimp-y?</speak>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
You wanna see, Mr. Big-Shot?  Attack 
Earth.  Yes I know it's a schlep. Just 
do it!</speak>

<info>The DOOP soldiers look up at the sky but nothing happens. Some 
clear their throats. Eventually, several Decapodian ships come 
screeching down from the sky. The ships have crustacean-like 
pincer claws at the front.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Aha! Now the rubber band's on the other 
claw!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Ready? Retreat!</speak>

<info>The soldiers run for it.</info>

<info>Washington D.C. Street. People run away as she ships swoop over 
the top of them. One cuts the legs off the stilt people and another 
grabs a ship and "eats" it. A third cuts the top off the Clinton 
Monument.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Library of Congress. Fry, Leela and Bender run 
inside, screaming, and shut the doors.</info>

<speak who="PERSON">
<info>(from library)</info> Sh!</speak>

<info>They scream quietly.</info>

<info>Cut to: Decapodian Embassy Balcony.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Deny my freedom, will you? Well we'll 
do to you what we did to the Squash 
Men of the Squash Planet! Squish them!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
Charleston Chew?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You bet!</speak>

<info>Washington D.C. Decapodian ships fly around, blowing things 
up. The Nimbus flies over the White House.</info>

<info>Cut to: Nimbus Bridge. Zapp watches the mayhem on the viewscreen.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Alright, Kif, let's show these freaks 
what a bloated, runaway military budget 
can do. Bring me the activation codes 
for our global defence network.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
<info>(unenthusiastic)</info> Aye, aye, sir.</speak>

<info>He drags a computer over to Zapp and it stretches his arm. Zapp 
pushes a button.</info>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Commence lip identification scan.  No 
tongue.</speak>

<info>The computer beeps and opens up. Zapp takes a disc out of it.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
We can't be too careful with these codes. 
Rumour has it a double agent may be 
aboard this very ship.  I'm watching 
you! You, ensign? What's your name?</speak>

<info>The ensign is a Decapodian wearing a wig, a DOOP uniform and 
oven gloves over his claws. He salutes.</info>

<speak who="ENSIGN">
Hugh Man, sir!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Hugh Man? Now that's a name I can trust. 
Run down to the central battle computer 
and enter these codes. Chop, chop!</speak>

<info>The Decapodian takes the disc from Zapp and scuttles out.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Um, sir? There's something about that 
ensign that's--</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
You're damn right there is! That strapping 
young lad's gunning for your job. And 
he just might get it.</speak>

<info>Kif turns around and sees the Decapodian fly a small ship towards 
a Decapodian ship on the viewscreen. He sighs.</info>

<info>The Decapodian ship flies towards the Nimbus with its claws 
at the ready.</info>

<info>Cut to: Nimbus Bridge.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
The enemy approacheth! Lieutenant, fire 
missile one and recommend me for another 
medal. Make it gaudy, I'm going clubbing 
later.  Tick, tock!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Sir, all planetary defences have been 
disabled. Perhaps the Decapodians acquired 
our secret codes, somehow.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Well, Kif, stand by to take the blame. 
Steady, steady ... now!</speak>

<info>Kif screams.</info>

<info>The Decapodian ship grabs the Nimbus and cuts it in half. The 
front part falls towards the ground. Zapp and Kif scream. It 
hits the ground.</info>

<info>Newspaper Headline: "Handsome Invaders Defeat Earth". A sub-headline 
reads "Post Names New Editor" and a picture of a Decapodian.</info>

<info>Slave Camp. People are chained to each other by their ankles. 
They pass buckets along the line and empty it on a big pile of 
mud.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dr. Zoidberg, how can you claim to love 
freedom and then enslave all of Earth?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Bah! Your planet doesn't deserve freedom 
until it learns what it is to not have 
freedom. It's a lesson, I say.</speak>

<info>A Decapodian soldier pinches Fry's chest with a pincer spear.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What the hell is this dirt pile we're 
building anyhow?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
None of your beeswax, slave! You'll 
find out soon enough. Just focus on 
globing that mud. <info>(shouting)</info> Glob!</speak>

<info>The slaves get back to work. Zoidberg and the soldiers leave.</info>

<info>Outside Capitol Building. Fry, Leela, Bender, Kif and Zapp sit 
on the steps at night as Decapodian ships fly overhead. A banner 
reading "Under New Management" has been hung over the door.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm no good at being a slave. I'm thinking 
about graduate school. Y'know? To become 
a barber?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
This can't go on. Today is the day we 
fight back!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
It's already 10 o'clock!</speak>

<info>Leela checks her watch.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh, you're right. Tomorrow is the day 
we fight back.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Yeah? Well good luck, sister. All our 
modern technology is useless.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I know I am.</speak>

<info>He goes to sleep.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey, wait! I'm having one of those things. 
You know? A headache with pictures?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
An idea?</speak>

<info>Fry nods his head.</info>

<info>Museum Of Ancient Weaponry. A banner outside advertises "Nuns 
And Nunchucks: Mother Teresa's Secret Arsenal". Inside, Fry, 
Bender, Leela, Kif and Zapp pass the world's biggest rolling 
pin, a spear <info>(circa 2256)</info>, Dillinger's semi-automatic salad shooter, 
and a sharkapult.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Back in my day, we didn't have your 
fancy all-digital weapons but we still 
managed to kill each other just fine.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah, the crossbow. A pitiless, elegant 
killing machine. The Bender of the 15th 
century.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Not big enough. We need something that 
can take out an entire army. Something 
you could commit a war crime with--</speak>

<info>He sees something and gasps. Leela, Kif, Zapp and Bender see 
it too.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow!  Ow!</speak>

<info>Park. Moivin gives a speech to the slaves from a stage. Zoidberg 
stands to one side of him.</info>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
Earth slaves, behold the fruit of your 
labours: The Mobile Oppression Palace.</speak>

<info>A huge crab-like contraption with the mud from the day before 
dumped on top of it scuttles behind the stage. The slaves gasp.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Neat!</speak>

<info>He takes a photo.</info>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
I don't need to tell you that occupation 
forces are expensive. But with the Mobile 
Oppression Palace, a few dignitaries 
can oppress your entire planet for pennies 
a day.  Warships, dismissed!</speak>

<info>The Decapodian ships turn skyward and fly away. The Mobile Oppression 
Palace scuttles away from the park.</info>

<info>Cut to: Washington DC Street. It bashes down a sign for Johnson's 
Collapsible Top Hats, squeezes and E-Z Squeeze Accordion sign 
and tries to karate-chop a Hair King Unbreakable Combs sign. 
It doesn't work. The Palace tries again three times but can't 
break it so it just pushes the sign over. Old Man Waterfall runs 
in front of the Palace waving Ol' Freebie.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
Do your worst, you sea devils! I'll 
make my stand with Ol' Freebie. You 
can crush me but you can't crush my 
spirit!  Argh! My spirit!</speak>

<info>The Palace lifts its claw. Frieda Waterfall runs from the crowd 
to Old Man Waterfall.</info>

<speak who="FRIEDA WATERFALL">
Great Grandpa, no!  Another victim of 
the mano-centric male-ocracy.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Park.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ambassador Moivin, you killed my lawyer.</speak>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
You're welcome.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
He defended my freedom when no-one else 
would. He was a good and honourable 
man.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Washington DC Street.</info>

<speak who="OLD MAN WATERFALL">
I request a Satanic funeral.</speak>

<info>The crowd boos.</info>

<info>Cut to: Park.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Is it possible that all this slavery 
and oppression is shmutzing up our freedom 
lesson?</speak>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
Ah, take a pill, Zoidberg. <info>(shouting)</info> 
Begin again with the crushing!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Washington D.C. Street. The Palace picks up a car and 
throws it across at a crowd of people.</info>

<info>Cut to: Park.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You haven't won yet, Moivin! You didn't 
expect us to even go to a museum, much 
less steal this ancient heat-seeking 
missile.</speak>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
I don't even know you.</speak>

<info>Fry presses a button. Behind some trees the heat-seeking missile 
launches. It flies behind Fry, Leela and Bender towards the Mobile 
Oppression Palace.</info>

<info>Cut to: Washington D.C. Street. The Decapodians on the balcony 
scream.</info>

<speak who="DECAPODIAN WOMAN">
Oh, it's gonna make such a mess!</speak>

<info>The Palace ducks and the missile passes over it. It comes back 
and flies around it a few times. The Decapodians sigh with relief.</info>

<info>Cut to: Park.</info>

<speak who="AMBASSADOR MOIVIN">
This is your secret plan? Meh! Heat-seeking 
missiles are useless against the Mobile 
Oppression Palace. All Decapodian technology 
is cold-blooded, like us!</speak>

<info>The Palace closes in on a crowd of people.</info>

<info>Cut to: Washington D.C. Street. Zoidberg picks up the flag Old 
Man Waterfall was holding.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
All eyes on Zoidberg!  Ew!</speak>

<info>He shakes the flag and the hand flies off. He takes Bender's 
cigar.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Hey, I need that to smoke!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg sets fire to the flag. The crowd gasps. Zoidberg waves 
the flag around, fanning the flames.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Zoidberg, how could you? I used to think 
you were cool.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Wait! People of Earth, listen. Yes, 
I'm desecrating a flag. But to preserve 
the freedom it represents!</speak>

<info>He throws the flag like a javelin at the Mobile Oppression Palace. 
The heat-seeking missile detects it and flies towards it. The 
Decapodians scream and leap from the balcony. The Palace explodes 
and splatters the crowd with mud. They cheer.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Zoidberg, you set us free! I feel like 
I could stand to hug you! I can't, but 
you know what I'm trying to say.</speak>

<speak who="CROWD">
<info>(chanting)</info> Zoidberg! Zoidberg! Zoidberg!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ah, if only they appreciated freedom 
this much on my home planet. Wait a 
second! They do! Because this is my 
home planet.</speak>

<info>Outside capitol Building. Nixon gives a speech.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
And now, to raise this beautiful new 
flag, a red lobster that won't ruin 
your dinner: Dr. John Zoidberg!</speak>

<info>Enter Zoidberg. The crowd cheers. The Secretary of Transportation 
hands Zoidberg a new flag. He unfolds it.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
You're a nice man, Nixon.</speak>

<speak who="SCOOP CHANG">
Dr. Zoidberg, how's about you take a 
bite of the flag for tomorrow's papers?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh, I couldn't.</speak>

<speak who="NIXON">
No, no, no, go ahead. You've earned 
it!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Well, maybe just a taste.  Mmm! Now 
that's a grand old flag!  I wonder what 
the Shroud of Turin tastes like.</speak>

<info>THE END</info></xml>