<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 507

<title>TEENAGE MUTANT LEELA'S HURDLES</title>

<author>Jeff Westbrook</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Now Interactive! Joystick Controls 
Fry's Left Ear!</info>

<info>Outside Planet Express. It is a calm and peaceful day. Suddenly 
a huge gargoyle crashes through the Planet Express roof and flies 
away.</info>

<info>Cut to: Planet Express: Attic. Farnsworth shakes his fist.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Pazuzu you ungrateful gargoyle! I put 
you through college and this is how 
you repay me?</speak>

<info>Pizzuzu poos on him.</info>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. The Professor is dressed in a long coat, a scarf 
and driving goggles. He puts on some driving gloves.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Let's get this gargoyle hunt on the 
road. Driving gloves, driving goggles. 
Driving thong. There.</speak>

<info>He sits down in the pilot's seat.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Uh, maybe I should drive.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth chcukles.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You? A woman? I'm trying to catch a 
monster not find the quickest route 
to the mall! Let me just adjust the 
seat.</speak>

<info>He pulls a lever and the seat moves forward until his face is 
pressed up against the windscreen. He starts the engine and the 
ship shakes.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
My God, he's gonna do it! Everybody, 
seatbelts to maximum buckling.</speak>

<info>The seatbelts completely cover them. Bender takes out a nail 
gun and nails himself to the wall. The ship takes off.</info>

<info>Outside Ship. The ship joins a space road flying very slowly 
and causes huge tailbacks.</info>

<info>Randy pulls up alongside him.</info>

<speak who="RANDY"><info>FROM HIS CAR</info>
Hey grandpa, move your wrinkly old kiester!</speak>

<info>He drives away. Farnsworth takes a little time to react.</info>

<info>Cut to: Ship's Cockpit.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
For heaven's gate Professor this ship 
can do 99% light speed. Why are we going 
at 35 miles an hour?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Because we're in a hurry that's why.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Plus you have the highbeams on!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Ship. The highbeams point at a roadsign directing 
drivers to the eastern half of the universe.</info>

<info>Outside Gummer's Cafeteria. Farnsworth lands the ship in the 
car park of the Florida driving cafe and they get out.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yo, Captain Cateracts, what are we doing 
here?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh it's 2:30, we can still catch the 
early bird dinner special.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, aren't we looking for your gargoyle?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
My wha?</speak>

<info>Gummer's Cafeteria. Farnsworth orders.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hello Mavis! Surprised to see me back 
again so soon?</speak>

<speak who="WANDA">
Mavis is dead.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I expect you'll want to see my angry 
crotchety grandpa discount card!</speak>

<info>He hands her a card. She reads it.</info>

<speak who="WANDA">
Sir this card is expired.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
But it's good for a lifetime.</speak>

<speak who="WANDA">
Well yours expired.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Table. Farnsworth sits down. Fry, Leela and Bender are 
already eating. Farnsworth gets out his teeth and puts them on 
the table. Leela covers her eyes in disbelief.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh Lord! Teeth do not belong in your 
pants Professor.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well I can't keep them in my mouth. 
They're nuclear powered!</speak>

<info>He presses a button on a remote control and the teeth start 
chomping his food. They bite Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Ow! It bit me!</speak>

<info>The teeth start chomping very quickly.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
No! No! It's tasted human blood!</speak>

<info>The teeth start flying around the room, biting at people. Farnsworth 
slurps his slop through a straw.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Mmm! Damn good meat!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth sits asleep at 
the desk, snoring. Enter the crew.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Professor we've talked it over and everyone 
thinks you're too old.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Right on.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yup.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Uh huh!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
We've decided to do the merciful thing 
and have you Youthasized.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dear God no!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh relax Professor. Youthasizing is 
a trendy new spa treatment, its this 
seasons shark cartilage enema.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
But I like being old. I don't have to 
talk to my parents, no one asks me to 
help move their stuff, I don't need 
to understand today's "edgy TV sitcoms."</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK OK, we're not gonna force you until 
I've finished this sentence. Get him!</speak>

<info>The crew grab Farnsworth. He screams. They carry him out.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
My thong!</speak>

<info>The Bubbling Geezer Hot Spring Spa Entrance. Enter a Neptunian 
woman named Heather.</info>

<speak who="HEATHER">
Hi, I'm Heather your personal Youthasizer! 
Lets get started with a nice botulism 
treatment shall we?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Go to hell Heather!</speak>

<speak who="HEATHER">
Oh!  In small doses botchelism toxin 
tightens and tones the facial muscles 
instead of killing you in the most horrible 
fashion imaginable.</speak>

<info>She injects it into him and his face tightens.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Give me back my floppy face!</speak>

<info>The Bubbling Geezer Hot Spring Spa Massage Parlour. A pink tentacled 
thing massages Farnsworth.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Careful with the giblets!</speak>

<speak who="HEATHER">
Hmm, you're still retaining a lot of 
grump in these joints.  More pressure.</speak>

<info>It applies more pressure and Farnsworth's skin oozes off the 
table.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ahh!</speak>

<info>The Bubbling Geezer Hot Spring Spa Tar Pits. Heather scans Farnsworth 
with an age scanner.</info>

<speak who="HEATHER">
Since this is such a serious case of 
old, we'll have to try our strongest 
treatment. A soothing full body bath 
in searing hot tar. Sir, its not neccesary 
or wise to be naked.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You sound just like my tennis instructor.</speak>

<info>He climbs into the tar.</info>

<speak who="HEATHER">
The tar blisters the age right out of 
the body in what top scientists suspect 
is a miracle.</speak>

<info>She pumps more tar into the bath. Farnsworth gets up.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh I don't have time for this. I have 
to go and buy a single piece of fruit 
with a coupon and then return it, making 
people wait behind me while I complain.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
He still sounds sorta old. Sorta real 
old.</speak>

<info>Bender pushes Heather away from the pump and rolls up his sleeves.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Step aside lady.  Like everything else 
in life, pumping is just a primative 
degenerate form of bending. <info>(mean voice)</info> 
C'mon Bender pump harder! Harder! (weak 
voice) I'm trying as hard as I can. 
<info>(mean voice)</info> Harder damn you!</speak>

<info>The ground beneath the crew starts to crack and the tar and 
Farnsworth fly into the air. The ground gives way and the crew 
slide into the pit. The tar lands back on top of them and covers 
them. They climb out as blackened figures. Farnsworth takes a 
towel from Heather and wipes the tar away. He now has a full 
head of hair and his wrinkles are gone.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Well that was an utter waste of time.</speak>

<info>The crew gasp.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Professor it worked! You look young 
enough to be my father!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Poodlespit!  53 years old?  Now I'll 
need a fake ID to rent ultra-porn.</speak>

<info>Fry talks but his voice is strangely squeaky.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
This is great Professor! We should go 
out and celebrate!</speak>

<info>He wipes the tar away from his face. He is younger. Heather 
scans him. He is 14. The entire crew is younger. Amy is fat and 
Hermes has an afro.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dear Lord, you've all reverted to your 
childhood forms!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg is very small and crawls along the ground.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Hooray! I'm a teenage hearthrob again!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
While I try to restore our normal ages, 
I expect you all to go about your jobs 
like normal professionals.</speak>

<info>Someone fires a spit ball at him. They laugh.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
It wasn't me Mr F, it was Amy!  Stop 
it Amy!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You stink!</speak>

<info>She feebly hits him.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
You know you did it!</speak>

<info>The kids start arguing.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Quiet! Quiet I say!</speak>

<info>He presses a button and a holographic mushroom cloud appears 
in the middle of the table. Enter LaBarbara and Dwight.</info>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
We're here to take my little stub of 
a husband home. Hermes, say goodbye 
to Mr Farnsworth.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Goodbye Mr Dumbsworth!</speak>

<info>He and Dwight laugh.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey, this my chance to spend time with 
my parents too!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But your parents are gross sewer mutants.</speak>

<info>A huge spit ball hits him and knocks him off his chair. Bender 
laughs.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
When I was an orphan I always wished 
I could grow up with my mom and dad. 
And now, thanks to being hurled backwards 
through time -</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
That's not what happened! Shut up and 
go live with your parents.</speak>

<info>Outside Planet Express. Leela walks out of the building with 
a backpack and opens a manhole cover. She climbs down the ladder.</info>

<info>Cut to: Sewer. She climbs down.</info>

<info>Turanga House: Living Room. Leela is with her parents.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's gonna be totally awesome mom! You 
and me can bake and argue about my hairstyle 
hiding my pretty face. And if some kid 
picks on me, my dad can beat up his 
dad.</speak>

<speak who="MORRIS">
Can't I just beat up the kid?</speak>

<info>He chuckles.</info>

<speak who="MUNDA">
Well OK Leela, if you think you can 
put up with your father, welcome home. 
We'll try to respect your independence 
and your freedom.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No! I want the real teen experience! 
Chores, curfew, the works!</speak>

<speak who="MORRIS">
Fine Leela we'll be the strictest parents 
ever. Now, lets all have some tequila 
to celebrate!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dad I'm underage!</speak>

<speak who="MORRIS">
Oh right. Here's a silly straw.</speak>

<info>He puts the straw in the bottle.</info>

<info>Wong Ranch: Amy's Bedroom. Amy sits in bed. Leo and Inez sit 
on the end.</info>

<speak who="MRS WONG">
Oh my Amy's sweet little girl again. 
This like a mother's dream. Bad dream 
that is! At this rate I'm never going 
to get a grandchild!</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Maybe she not grown up but she sure 
grown out! She fat!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Dad, if you're gonna make fat jokes 
until I get cute again I'm just gonna 
stay in my room.</speak>

<speak who="MR WONG">
Stay in room? You so fat you gonna stay 
all around room!</speak>

<info>He chuckles.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I've got to find a way to escape the 
horrible ravages of youth! Suddenly 
I'm going to the bathroom like clockwork 
every three hours! And those jerks at 
social security stopped sending me cheques! 
Now I have to pay them!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm tired of your yapping.  All you 
ever do is complain, you never try to 
make things better. Well I'm running 
away from this dead end family! I know 
there's a place for people like me with 
new ideas. There has to be!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Fine, get going!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh I'm going! You're gonna be all "Where's 
Bender? I miss Bender!"</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
We won't know that until you leave.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh, I'm leaving!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
There's the door.</speak>

<info>Bender thinks for a moment.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'll be good.</speak>

<info>Turanga House: Living Room. Munda sweeps white flakes off the 
sofa.</info>

<speak who="MUNDA">
Ah, do you have to shed your skin on 
the couch? What do we live in, a zoo?</speak>

<info>The doorbell rings.</info>

<speak who="MORRIS">
I'm getting the doorbell.  For me?</speak>

<info>He chuckles.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh, hello sir. It's a lovely evening 
you have tonight. Um I'm here to pick 
up your daughter.</speak>

<info>Leela comes down the stairs wearing a dress. She has a bow in 
her hair.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hi Fry! I like your blazer.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Thanks. These aren't pockets they're 
just flaps. I put my money in my sock.</speak>

<info>They laugh.</info>

<speak who="MUNDA">
So, where are you taking my daughter 
tonight?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
A movie.  A movie ma'am.</speak>

<info>He winks at Leela and she smiles.</info>

<speak who="MORRIS">
Well whatever you're really doing, don't 
wake us if you get in after 12.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dad, you're being too leaneant again! 
I have to be back by 11.</speak>

<speak who="MUNDA">
OK OK you're the boss!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No I'm not!</speak>

<info>Outside Stenchy's. At the mutant cafe Fry and Leela sit in a 
car looking at the menus.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'd like a sewer burger but without 
the rat feces.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What are you on a diet?</speak>

<info>A car pulls up beside them with a guy with moose antlers in 
his head and a girl with eyes on stalks.</info>

<speak who="MOOSE">
Uh Leela you look hot!</speak>

<speak who="MANDY">
Jeez Moose, just dump me right in front 
of her why don't you!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Moose, Mandy, this is my friend Fry 
- from the surface!</speak>

<speak who="MANDY">
Oh so this is the famous Fry! What is 
he like the biggest loser on the surface 
so he has to hang out in the sewer?</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
They're onto me.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey come on, let's act like grown ups 
here! Wanna race?</speak>

<speak who="MOOSE">
Uh yeah!</speak>

<info>They pulls away from Stenchy's and start racing through the 
sewer tunnels. Fry and Leela are lagging behind. Fry shuffles 
up to Leela and tries to put his arm around her but the car jerks 
and he falls over.</info>

<info>Cut to: Sewage Treatment Plant. Sal puts something in the tanks.</info>

<speak who="SAL">
Theres. The worlds drinkings water is 
safes for another days.  Whoas!  Cripe!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Sewers. The cars scrape the sides of the tunnel and 
make sparks. Leela comes alongside Moose. They come to an open 
area of the sewer and a huge tapeworm comes out of the water.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
A tapeworm!</speak>

<info>She and Fry scream and head off down a different tunnel to Moose 
and Mandy.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
We missed the turn, we'll never catch 
them.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Yes we will. This sewer goes right under 
Planet Express and its's 9pm!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Planet Express. The toilet flushes.</info>

<info>Cut to: Sewer. Sewer water floods in behind Fry and Leela and 
the wave pushes them faster. Fry screams. At the finish line 
Moose and Mandy are just about to cross it when Fry and Leela 
fly through and cut the tape first. The crowd and Fry and Leela 
cheer.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
All right!</speak>

<info>The car keeps going.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Leela you can stop winning now, we won!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm too short to reach the handbrake!</speak>

<info>The car crashes into the school.</info>

<info>Cut to: Classroom. Dwayne sits at a desk in amongst the rubble 
and turns to Leela.</info>

<speak who="DWAYNE">
That's detention!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Room. Fry recounts his story to Bender.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
And then, and then, this giant tapeworm 
tried to play us for chumps but we like 
totally dissed Moose!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth strokes the antlers of a moose on the wall.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes, I'd like to meet this "moose." 
But in the meantime I have good news. 
I may have solved our age problem.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yay!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth presses a button and a holographic strand of DNA 
appears.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It seems the Youthasizer tar was saturated 
with time-altering chronitons. A thin 
layer is still stuck to our DNA as well 
as Bender's Robot DNA or "RNA."</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Question.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You stink!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Yes yes. Anyhow I've designed an oil 
eating bacterium that should take the 
tar right off.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
C'mon! Lets go tell Leela so we can 
grow up together!</speak>

<info>Bender makes kissy smoochy noise. Fry frowns.</info>

<info>Turanga House: Living Room.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Thanks Professor but I don't want the 
treatment.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Don't you understand you little nitwit? 
Unless you're treated soon, the only 
way to restore your true age would be 
to grow into it! Just as God intended.</speak>

<speak who="MUNDA">
He has a point honey. What about your 
job and your friends? Do you really 
want to abandon your old life?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
My old life wasn't as glamourous as 
my webpage made it look. All I ever 
wanted was to grow up here. With you. 
Please?</speak>

<speak who="MUNDA">
Well if it's what you really want.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It is. I know it is.</speak>

<info>Fry looks down sadly.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll miss you Leela. I'll come ack and 
visit when I'm all grown up.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
Bring beer.</speak>

<speak who="MORRIS">
No beer 'til you finish your tequila!</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Hangar. The Professor has set up a huge green 
chamber.</info>

<info>Everyone cheers and runs in.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Let's go!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth closes the door.</info>

<info>Cut to: Bacterial Spew Chamber.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Initiating controlled infection.</speak>

<info>He pulls a switch and the spew chamber coughs. The room fills 
with a cloud.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I'm no doctor but this machine guy could 
use a lozenge.</speak>

<info>The cloud clears. The crew are even younger.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Aw poo! We're even younger!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth scans himself. 37.5. 37.4. 37.3. He is still decreasing 
in age.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Damn! the bacteria pigged out on the 
tar and now they're getting freaky deaky, 
spreading chronitons throughout our 
systems. We're getting younger by the 
minute!</speak>

<info>The crew gasp.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What I'm going to revrt through all 
my larval stages?</speak>

<info>He changes shape.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Word! We'll all keep getting younger 
and younger until we suffer a fate worse 
than death - pre-life! Then death.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg reverts to a shell.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth Lab. Farnsworth scans Amy with the 
scanner. She is about 8.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I've got to stop this reverse aging 
before we all shrivel up and suffer 
the agony of unbirth. Think you disco 
duck think!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
What's that squirming under your shirt?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth opens his shirt. Zoidberg has reverted to a lamprey 
and is attached to his chest.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Get off me you parasitic lamprey!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Oh sure like you need all your blood.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth knocks him off and he woops around the floor. The 
kids scream.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Would you all chill! I can't think with 
you kids cramping my style! Oh I need 
a babysitter!</speak>

<info>Turanga House: Leela's Bedroom. Leela is the kids' new babysitter. 
They jump up and down on the bed.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK, quiet time. I know, everyone pretend 
to THING TO CHECK your tongue and I'll 
read you a story.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg is on the floor and has turned into a spiky thing.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I can't see from down here I can't.</speak>

<info>Leela sticks him to the wall.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
There. Todays story is from New Teen 
magazine. What would you rather hear 
about? Four legged Chachi or tentacled 
Chachi?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I wanna hear a space story!</speak>

<info>He holds up a book called A Child's Garden Of Space Legends.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's kind of a baby book. But OK. Let's 
see. Snow White Dwarf And The Seven 
Red Dwarves, Charlotte's Tholian Web, 
The Fountain Of Aging.</speak>

<info>She closes the book and gasps.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Leela talks to Farnsworth 
on the videophone.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The Fountain Of Aging? Hmm, it is just 
a legend. Still, they called the Tooth 
Fairy a legend and now it's head of 
the FBI.</speak>

<info>Turanga House: Living Room. Farnsworth - now de-aged even more 
- knocks on the door. Morris answers.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Sup? Kids ready?</speak>

<info>The kids run out screaming. Fry hugs Farnsworth's leg.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Professy's back!  Eww, you smell like 
smoking.  And drinking.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I had a few beers but I'm cool to drive.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I wish I could come with you to say 
goodbye, before you all turn back in 
to grown ups but I'm grounded for knocking 
the school over.</speak>

<speak who="MUNDA">
Who cares Leela? It was just a public 
school. Now go with your friends, please.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No! A grounded teenager must be confined 
to her room!</speak>

<info>Outside Turanga House. Leela opens her bedroom window and starts 
climbing out.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
...until she sneaks out!</speak>

<info>She climbs out and starts up the ladder after the others.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
When I grow up I wanna be a steam shovel!</speak>

<info>Ship's Cockpit. The kids - now even younger - have disassembled 
Bender and are playing with his pieces. A geeky looking Professor 
flies the ship. Leela reads the book.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
According to this, the fountain is located 
within the darkest, most ancient region 
of space, just past teddybear junction.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Teddybear junction, the worst scum hole 
in the galaxy.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. The ship flies into a solar system full of old planets.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
This solar system is like way old.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Look how high the asteroid belt is pulled 
up on that planet.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Newsflash! Everything's getting older 
the closer we get to that sun!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Dude, the Fountain Of Aging must be 
on the sun itself!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Shut up! I was gonna say that!</speak>

<info>The ship lands next to a swirling blue whirlpool - The Fountain 
Of Aging.</info>

<info>Outside Ship. Leela wheels the kids off the cargo ramp in a 
trolley. They are really young.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
We've got to hurry. The kids have only 
one change of pants!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth puts Zoidberg at the side of the fountain.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
We gotta be real real careful to stay 
in just long enough to make us our right 
ages again.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg falls in and rapidly ages.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Zoidberg! Get out of there!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
The current, its too much already! Help!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg gets closer to the surface, turns grey, cracks, breaks 
up and dies like that bloke in Indiana Jones And The Last Crusade. 
The babies cry.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Jeepers!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Zoidberg is dead!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
No! Zoidberg's brother is dead!  funny 
story. I just reverted to the age where 
my siblings budded from me and my brother 
Norman split off and jumped in the fountain.</speak>

<speak who="SIBLING">
He always had to be the centre of attention!</speak>

<info>The other siblings agree.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh no!  Quick! Get them into the fountain!</speak>

<info>Farnsworth gathers them up and goes down the steps.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Thanks for the help Weewa. Once we're 
gwown up you can go back to your famiwy. 
We'wl never bother you again.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
You can bother me a little.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth climbs in and they age rapidly.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
It's working! Hooray!  I can't hold 
on!</speak>

<info>He lets go and the whirlpool catches him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm coming in after you!</speak>

<info>She ties a baby blanket around her waist.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
No Leela! You can't give up your childhood! 
You'll never have another chance at 
it!</speak>

<info>Leela thinks about it then jumps in. she reaches out to Fry 
and grabs his hand. the others grab on to him. they climb out 
at the side, their ages fully restored.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
We did it! We're the right ages again!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I think I might be a couple years younger.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh, me too!</speak>

<info>She winks at Leela.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
He's too far out! We can't reach him!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Are you back to your original age Professor?</speak>

<info>Farnsworth scans himself.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Even older! Huzzah!</speak>

<info>He cheers and his bones break.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm sorry you had to give up being a 
kid Leela.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well, I guess ever adult wants to be 
a kid sometimes. But I worked hard to 
be the person I am!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The fabulous person!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
With friends like you guys -</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Fabulous friends!</speak>

<info>He hugs her and Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
And I'm really happy I have that life 
back.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth pats the gargoyle.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
And you my faithful fiend! How can I 
ever repay you?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Paris. the gargoyles sit on the roof of Notre Dame.</info>

<info>THE END</info>
</xml>