<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 508

<title>THE WHY OF FRY</title>

<author>David X. Cohen</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Dancing Space Potatoes? You Bet!</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Zoidberg is sitting in a bathtub 
while Amy is sat at the table reading a book called Martians 
Are From Mars, Venusians Are From Venus. Enter Fry wearing a 
spacesuit.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Delivery boy Philip J. Fry reporting 
for duty.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Dr Zoidberg, soaking in brine.</speak>

<info>He relaxes and blows brine through his blowhole. It splatters 
on Amy who barely reacts.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What is the meaning of this? We've got 
a delivery people, let's move, let's 
move!  Amy? Mission profile?  Interesting, 
interesting. Dr Zoidberg, mission bag?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Packed and ready sir.</speak>

<info>Fry takes the brown bag from him. Fry takes something out.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
What's this? This is the same toy surprise 
I got last time!  I can't work under 
these conditions. And without me there 
is no mission. I am the mission!</speak>

<info>The ship lands behind him and Bender and Leela walk out.</info>

<speak who="LEELA"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
We're back from the mission!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wh-what? You went without me?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
You were looking up curse words in the 
dictionary. It seemed like a better 
use of your time.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But, but I'm the delivery boy.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Don't worry, everything went fine.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Better than usual!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
We got medals! Good work team! We really 
pulled together on this one.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Woo-hoo!</speak>

<info>He and Leela bump each other. Fry looks on sadly.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Locker Area. Leela blow dries her hair and Bender 
brushes his eyes with a toothbrush. Fry sits on the bench sadly.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm real sorry I missed the mission. 
I wasn't there and you might have needed 
me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nope.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But if I'd been there I -</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nope.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
L -</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nope.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Bender's great.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nope! Ohh!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Listen Leela, let me make it up by taking 
you out to dinner tonight.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Nope. I've got a date with Chaz.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Chaz?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I met him at that charity cock fight 
last week. He's the mayor's aide.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ooo, you go mutant girl!</speak>

<info>He whips her with his towel.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I do go! He's a very important man.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So? I'm just as important as him.  It's 
just that, the kind of importance I 
have, it doesn't matter if I...don't 
do it.</speak>

<info>He slopes over sadly. Bender hangs his towel over him.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Bender and Fry sit on the couch. Fry 
sighs and strokes Nibbler.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm nobody. There are guys in the background 
with Mary Worth comics who are more 
important than me.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah, buck up meatloaf. Bender'll take 
you out tonight and cheer you up. What 
do you wanna do? And I mean anything. 
You have the power! Name it an I'm there, 
you the man!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Um, OK. Let's go bowling.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nah.</speak>

<info>He puts his feet up and turns the TV on.</info>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine Entrance. Enter Leela and her date Chaz. 
Enter Elzar.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Table for two? Step right this way.</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
I'm afraid we don't have a reservation 
but uh, as you can see......I'm the 
mayor's aide. Table for two please.</speak>

<info>Elzar stares, confused.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
OK then.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Elzar's Fine Cuisine Restaurant. Elzar seats Chaz and 
Leela. Two chef's run out from the kitchen chasing a cockroach. 
It runs onto a table and Elzar whacks it with a piece of bread.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Bam!</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
It's OK my man. I got you covered on 
your next health inspection.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
I really appreciate that mister mayor's 
aide.  Here you go, compliments of the 
house.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Wow, free bread at a restaurant? Is 
there anything you can't do?</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
I can't fail the mayor, not ever.</speak>

<info>Leela sighs, lovestruck.</info>

<info>O'Zorgnax's Pub. Fry sits at a table, lonely. He sees Leela 
and Chaz walk in.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh jeez, better not let Leela see me.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hey, I hear Fry.  Boy am I glad you're 
here!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You are? So things aren't working out 
with whatshisname?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Actually...they are! Confidentially, 
I might not make it back to my apartment 
tonight! Could you walk Nibbler for 
me?</speak>

<info>She hands him her key.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Um..uh...</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
And bring a baggy in case he drops a 
steamer. <info>(shouting)</info> Have a great night!</speak>

<info>Street. Fry walks down the empty street with Nibbler. Nibbler 
spies a lamppost and starts sniffing around it.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh no, please, no!  Perfect!</speak>

<info>Fry puts the bag over his hand and tries to lift the dark matter. 
He struggles. Smitty and URL approach him.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
Whoa, smells like a 289 in progress!</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Failure to scoop, aw yeah!</speak>

<info>He prints off a ticket.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait, I'm trying. It weighs as much 
as a thousand suns!</speak>

<info>He struggles with it some more. URL hands him the ticket. Chaz's 
car pulls up beside them.</info>

<speak who="CHAZ">
Don't worry Fry, I'll pull some strings. 
See if I can't get you tried as a juvenile!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh Chaz!</speak>

<info>She hugs him and they drive off. Fry sighs.</info>

<info>Alley.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm as worthless as this trashcan.</speak>

<info>He kicks it over and sits down against a wall.</info>

<speak who="TRASHCAN">
You think I'm as worthless as you? Try 
catching garbage in your head and raising 
six kids you dumb townie!</speak>

<info>It rolls away. Garbage falls on Fry from a chute above him.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh Nibbler, at least I'm important to 
you. Even if it's only 'cause I clean 
up you poop.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
The poop eradication is but one aspect 
of your importance.</speak>

<info>Fry nods then realises Nibbler has just spoken. He screams.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
D-d-did you just talk?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Indeed. And I have other amazing powers 
as well.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Like what?</speak>

<info>He punches Fry and knocks him unconcious.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Nibbler pulls his spaceship out from its hideaway 
and drags the still unconcious Fry into it. He comes around.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Are you my mommy?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Negative.</speak>

<info>He closes the roof and takes off.</info>

<info>Planet Eternium. Nibbler lands his ship outside the Hall Of 
Eternity.</info>

<info>Cut to: Hall Of Eternity.</info>

<speak who="FIONA">
Welcome Lord Nibbler.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Welcome acknowledged. I bring with me...the 
Mighty One.</speak>

<info>Fry wipes his nose on his sleeve.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Eh?</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
At last, our centuries upon centuries 
of waiting have achieved fruition.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Aww, aren't you a fuzzy wittle guy?</speak>

<info>He tickles Ken and he purrs.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
Stop that! Uh...please. Your mightiness 
-</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Mightiness? Are you off your nut? I 
just got kidnapped by a bunch of guineapigs.</speak>

<info>The Nibblonians gasp and chatter.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
Does he not know?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
He does not know.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
He knows not?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Knows not does he.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLONIAN">
Not he knows?</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
Enough! Fry, it is my duty to inform 
you that the fate of humanity, the fate 
of our race, indeed the fate of all 
that exists and all that will exist 
rests with you. You are the single most 
important person in the universe.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Oh snap!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
On this auspicious occasion, let the 
Hall Of Eternity cut a thunderous blast.</speak>

<info>A Nibblonian feebly blows a trumpet. The floor opens and animals 
on plates rise up in front of the Nibblonians.</info>

<speak who="FIONA">
The Feast Of A Thousand Beasts is begun.</speak>

<info>They tuck in. Fry leaves his zebra.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLONIAN">
You gonna eat that?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Maybe later.</speak>

<info>The table sinks back into the floor.</info>

<info>Time Lapse.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
The time has come to discuss matters 
of the gravest importance.</speak>

<info>He pushes a button and images of the Brainspawn from The Day 
The Earth Stood Stupid appear on a screen.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Fry, do you remember some months ago 
when the Earth was attacked by flying 
brains?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Hmm, I remember the square dancing stomachs, 
although that might have been a milanta 
commerical. Wait! The brains! I do remember! 
But no one else does. They said I was 
crazy.</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
On the contrary. You remember beause 
you were the only one immune to the 
brain's mental attack.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Because I'm so smart?</speak>

<info>The Nibblonians laugh.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
Oh my. Anyway, your immunity is due 
to the fact that you lack the delta 
brainwave.  It's a genetic abnormality 
which resulted when you went back in 
time and performed certain actions which 
made you your own grandfather.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I did do the nasty in the pasty!</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Verily. And that past nastification 
is what shields you from the brains. 
You are the last hope of the universe.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So I really am important? How I feel 
when I'm drunk is correct?</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
Yes. Except the Dave Matthews Band doesn't 
rock.</speak>

<info>Nibblonian Spacecraft.</info>

<speak who="KEN">
For a thousand years, the evil brains 
have been constructing the giant Infosphere, 
a giant memory bank twice the size of 
three ordinary memory banks.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
What's so evil about that?</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
They plan to collect all the information 
in the universe and store it in the 
sphere.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So they're trying to learn things?</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Right.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Those bastards!</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Being brains, they feel compelled to 
know everything. And soon they will.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm as mad as I've ever been.</speak>

<speak who="KEN">
Once their task is complete, they will 
ensure no new information arises in 
the only way possible: by destroying 
the universe.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Now it's personal.</speak>

<speak who="FIONA">
Your mission is to infiltrate the Infosphere 
and plant this quantum-interphase bomb, 
blasting them into an alternate universe, 
from which there is no return.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Then outrun the blast on this Scooty-Puff 
Jr.</speak>

<info>He winds the key in the back of the Scooty-Puff Jr. Fiona attaches 
the bomb to Fry's spacesuit.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
OK, let's go through this once more 
-</speak>

<info>The Nibblonians open the airlock and Fry is blown out into space. 
Fry screams. He rides the Scooty-Puff Jr towards the Infosphere. 
A swarm of brainsspawn fly past him and one hits him on the head.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Aah! Brains!</speak>

<info>Ken appears on Fry's arm communicator.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Fear not Mighty One, your missing brainwave 
makes you invisible to them. So long 
as you avoid intense thinking.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Sorry, what? I wasn't paying attention.</speak>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
That is most wise.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Who?</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Infosphere.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
In a few seconds the brains will finish 
scanning the last bits of information 
in the universe.</speak>

<info>Brains float past a data port and it scans their information.</info>

<info>The scanning ends and the Infosphere initiates a self-scan.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Now the Infosphere will open it's protective 
crust so as to scan itself, completing 
it's thousand year task.</speak>

<info>The Infosphere opens and a scanner comes out. It slowing begins 
to rotate around the Infosphere, scanning as it goes and making 
a noise like a connecting modem.</info>

<speak who="FIONA"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
This is your one chance to enter the 
sphere! Scoot! Scoot now!</speak>

<info>Fry scoots through the Infosphere's crust.</info>

<info>Cut to: Infosphere. The place is swarming with brains and in 
the centre of the sphere is a huge master brain. Fry scoots towards 
it and crashes into it. He climbs to the top where there is a 
computer console.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'm at the input console. I'm a little 
nervous and I've got brain in my buttcrack.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Roger.</speak>

<info>Fry attaches the bomb to the console.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Once you press the detonator, you will 
have 60 seconds for an exciting escape.</speak>

<info>Fry is about to push the button but hesitates.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey wait, this brain knows everything 
about everything right?</speak>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
It will soon. That's why you're supposed 
to be setting off a bomb.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah yeah, but I can't pass up a chance 
to learn the answers to the greatest 
questions of all time.  Is it true that 
post-it stamp glue is made up of -</speak>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
Correct. Toad mucus.</speak>

<info>On the console screen is a video clip of a postman squeezing 
a toad so it's mucus drips into a bucket.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
There's no time for this. Activate the 
bomb.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Wait wait wait.  What really killed 
the dinosaurs?</speak>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
Me!</speak>

<info>On the screen is a video clips of the brain flying over the 
dinosaurs and killing them. A message appears on the screen and 
a computer voice speaks.</info>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Unauthorised Data Access.</speak>

<info>An alarm goes off and brains surround Fry. Fry screams and starts 
to wind his Scooty-Puff Jr. It falls apart in his hands.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh oh.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Detecting trace amounts of mental activity. 
Possibly a dead weasel or a cartoon 
viewer.</speak>

<info>The brains zap Fry.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Eww gross. Cut it out!</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #1">
Odd. He is immune to our sionic attack.</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #2">
Impossible. We're an ambitious young 
squad with everything to prove.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
It appears we are in the presence of 
the fabled one. But without his Scooty-Puff 
Jr, he cannot escape.  Huh?</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #2">
A quantum-interphase bomb? Are you insane 
in the membrane?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You got it poindexter!</speak>

<info>He activates the bomb.</info>

<speak who="BRAIN #1">
Oh, not good!</speak>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Detonation in T-60 Earth seconds.</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #3">
You fool. You'll be transported to the 
other universe with us. Trapped there 
for all eternity.</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #1">
And we'll form a tightly-knit clique, 
that you won't be part of!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well at least I did one important thing 
with my life. Leading good to victory 
over evil!</speak>

<info>The Nibblonians cheer.</info>

<speak who="KEN"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Exactly!</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
The Nibblonians? Good? During your last 
moments in this universe perhaps you 
should query our database concerning 
the night of December 31st 1999.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
The day I got frozen? What about it?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
No! Don't ask about that! It, it would 
be uh...boring!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Eh forget it then.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Query!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
OK sheesh!  What happened to me, Philip 
J. Fry, on the night of December 31st 
1999?</speak>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
Clarification request. Are you the Philip 
J. Fry from Earth or the Philip J. Fry 
from Hovering Squidworld 97A?</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Earth you fat idiot! Hurry up!</speak>

<info>On the console's screen Fry walks into the cryogenics lab.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Hello? Pizza delivery for uh...I. C. 
Wiener? Aw crud!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Eurgh! I can't believe how fat I look! 
Aw, Nibbler's there. Wait! What?!</speak>

<info>On the screen Nibbler blows Fry's tilting chair. Fry begins 
to lose his balance and the chair tips back. Fry rolls back into 
the cryo-freezer.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
What the?</speak>

<info>He panics. The cryo-freezer freezes him in a flash.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I, I don't understand. You made me go 
in the freezer tube?</speak>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Detonation in T-15 seconds.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
You little runts froze me! You took 
away my life!</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
We can explain!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
No you can't. Shut your adorable trap!</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
We had no choice. You were the only 
one who could help us. What is one life 
weighed against the entire universe?</speak>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(CRYING)</info>
But it was my life.</speak>

<speak who="COMPUTER VOICE">
Detonation in 2, 1. Will the owner of 
a white Pontiac Firebird...oh nevermind. 
Zero!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Infosphere. The bomb explodes and the Infosphere 
is sucked into the alternate universe.</info>

<info>Cut to: Infosphere. It reappears in the alternate universe.</info>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Well, here we are. Trapped for eternity.</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #2">
We could sing American Pie.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Go ahead. I deserve it. I wish those 
stupid racoons had never brought me 
to the future.</speak>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
I have shocking data relevant to this 
conversation.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
We don't care you dope! We're in another 
universe, you're not in charge anymore.</speak>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
It is possible for the Philip Fry to 
resume his life on December 31st 1999.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Really? I can go back in time?</speak>

<info>An image appears on the console.</info>

<speak who="INFOSPHERE BRAIN">
There is a nexus point between universes, 
at the space-time you entered the cryogenic 
tube. You and only you can return there.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Interesting. You could stop the Nibblonian 
from pushing you into the cryogenic 
tube.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That is interesting. Why?</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
It would be as if you never came to 
the future. You will have your life 
back and we will suceed in our plan 
to understand and destroy the universe.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Everybody wins!</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #2">
The human will be returned to the past!</speak>

<info>Outside Rocket Skating Rink.</info>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
Meanwhile...</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I love rocket skating! But the wait 
is always so long. Fry once stood in 
line for six hours just to get me a 
ticket.</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
Six hours? Pfft. Sounds like a real 
nobody! But now it's time for somebody 
and some chick he's with to go skating.</speak>

<info>He shows Leela a sign. Closed For Private Function. She gasps.</info>

<info>Cut to: Rocket Skating Rink.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
You reserved the whole rink?</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
Yup. Buzzed ahead, let 'em know who's 
aide was coming by. The mayor's, that's 
who's.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh Chaz!</speak>

<info>She kisses him.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Leela and Chaz are now skating around the rink. 
The kids from the Cookieville Orphanarium look on sadly.</info>

<speak who="SALLY">
Mr Vogel. I thought we was going skating.</speak>

<speak who="VOGEL">
No. We're not important enough. Everybody 
just hold hands until the bus driver 
gets back from his haircut.</speak>

<info>Leela notices the orphans.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aww, let's let those kids skate with 
us.</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
What? Seriously? I'm trying to impress 
you with my cloud here.!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I know, and it's working. But think 
how much skating would mean to those 
kids.</speak>

<speak who="ORPHAN">
We came here instead of eating today.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
This may be their only chance to skate 
in their whole lives. Who are we to 
say they can't?</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
The mayor's aide, and his badge! <info>(shouting)</info> 
Beat it kids! Come back when you got 
connections.</speak>

<info>The kids look away sadly.</info>

<speak who="VOGEL">
Alright kids. Back to the Orphanarium. 
You can slide around the gym in your 
socks.</speak>

<speak who="SALLY">
What socks?</speak>

<speak who="CHAZ">
So am I gonna get lucky tonight or what?</speak>

<info>Leela snatches his badge away from him and stuffs it down his 
throat.</info>

<info>Infosphere. The Infosphere Brain types something into to the 
console. It holds Fry in place.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I hope your calculations are correct.</speak>

<speak who="GIANT BRAIN">
Our calculations are always correct. 
For we are gigantic brains.</speak>

<speak who="BRAIN #2">
Initiate space-time transfer.</speak>

<info>The Infosphere throws a switch and the console zaps Fry and 
makes him go all spliggly. He disappears.</info>

<info>Old New York: December 31st 1999. In a telephone box Nibbler 
makes a phonecall to Panucci's Pizza.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
I hereby place and order for one cheese 
pizza.</speak>

<speak who="PANUCCI"><info>ON PHONE</info>
One pie, nothing good on it. Name?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
I-period C-period Wiener.</speak>

<speak who="PANUCCI"><info>ON PHONE</info>
Uh, talk a little louder. It's sounds 
like you got some kind of tiny head 
on you or something.</speak>

<info>Cryogenics Lab. Nibbler paces around under the desk. Enter Fry.</info>

<speak who="PAST FRY">
Hellooo? Pizza delivery for uh, Icy 
Wiener? Wiener? Aw crud.</speak>

<info>Behind Nibbler, in the corner of the desk Future Fry appears 
and grabs him.</info>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Gotcha!</speak>

<info>Nibbler squeals.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
I don't understand.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Yes you do! You came back in time to 
knock me into that freezer. Now I came 
back in time to stop you.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
I did not come back in time. My people 
lack that ability.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
But, I know you in the future. I cleaned 
your poop.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Quite possible. We live long and are 
celebrated poopers. You will meet me 
when I'm a thousand years older.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Not if you don't freeze me.</speak>

<info>Past Fry sits down on the chair and puts his feet up on the 
desk.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Please. Our saviours foresee that in 
a thousand years, at one moment, the 
fate of the universe will depend on 
you. Since you will not live that long 
I must freeze you now.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Well, why couldn't you just ask me?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
We were afraid you would refuse.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Of course not, I love the future.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER"><info>(CHOKING)</info>
Then why are you choking me right now?</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Because I don't like being used.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Well now it's your choice. Is there 
nothing in the future worth saving?</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Leela. But she doesn't think much of 
me.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Ah, she must be the other.</speak>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Wha?</speak>

<info>Past Fry's chair starts to tumble back. Future Fry holds the 
leg.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
You must not give up on her. I am stationed 
on a distant world known as Vergon 6. 
But if you return to the future I will 
transfer to Earth to give you what help 
I can.</speak>

<info>Outside, the countdown to the millenium begins.</info>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
You really think I would have had a 
chance with Leela?</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
You must choose. The present or the 
future? To save yourself? Or to save 
Leela?</speak>

<info>The countdown reaches 1. Past Fry leans back on his chair and 
blows his party blower. Future Fry blows the chair and Past Fry 
tumbles back into the cryotube which freezes him.</info>

<speak who="FUTURE FRY">
Yes! Here I come future! Oh no! Wait! 
I'm gonna get trapped in the Infosphere 
again! Just remember that Scooty-Puff 
Jr sucks...</speak>

<info>He fades away into nothingness.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
In a thousand years I'll get right on 
it.</speak>

<info>Outside Infosphere. The bomb explodes and the Infosphere is 
sucked into an alternate universe.</info>

<speak who="NARRATOR">
And so, a thousand years later Fry once 
again infiltrated the Infosphere and 
set off his amazing bomb. Only this 
time...</speak>

<info>Fry speeds away from the Infosphere on his huge Scooty-Puff 
Sr.</info>

<info>Alley. Nibbler's ship lands and Fry and Nibbler climb out.</info>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Thank you for saving the universe Fry. 
Here.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whoa, thanks! If you ever need a saviour 
again, just ask.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Oh we will. We will.</speak>

<info>He shuts his ship away and puts his leash on.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Man, I can't wait to tell everyone what 
happened.</speak>

<speak who="NIBBLER">
Uh yes. Incidentally I need to remain 
undercover so I'm blanking your memory.</speak>

<info>His third eye flashes like the memory stick from Men In Black 
and Fry looks dazed.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Huh. Did everything just taste purple 
for a second? Oh well. Let's go home 
you dumb poop machine.</speak>

<info>Nibbler chatters.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela holds up a photo of her and Chaz.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Bender, would you do the honours?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
With gusto.</speak>

<info>He scorches a hole in the photo. Leela looks at it satisfied. 
Chaz's head has been burnt away. Enter Fry. His head appears 
in the hole.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Hey Leela. I guess I got this for you.</speak>

<info>He hands her the flower.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Oh. Thank you. You know what Fry. I 
don't care if you're not the most important 
person in the universe. It really makes 
me happy to see you right now.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Then I am the most important person 
in the universe.</speak>

<info>She kisses him.</info>

<info>THE END</info>

FRY <info>(OVER CREDITS)</info>
Yes!
</xml>