<xml>
(                                 <section><show>FUTURAMA</show><header>


                                       Episode 509

                                      "THE STING"

                                           By

                                    Patric M. Verrone

                         Transcribed by Dave, The Neutral Planet



               
               </header><note>Opening Credits. Caption: A By-Product Of The TV Industry.</note>
 
               
               
               <note>Planet Express: Hangar. Bender and Fry prepare for a game of 
               Virtual Golf. Bender is all kitted out in golf gear. He takes 
               his club from Fry and puts the ball on the tee.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         A hush comes over the crowd. The only 
                         sound is Bender calling everyone else 
                         a jerk and he swings!  And he slices 
                         it into the water, oh man!
 
               
               </speak><note>He plugs himself into the game and appears on the screen. He 
               jumps into the lake. Enter Hermes and Farnsworth.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Bad news everyone. You're not good enough 
                         to go on your next mission.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Hooray!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         Not good enough!

               
               </speak><note>They high-five. Leela descends from above in a harness.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Why? Says who?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Because. And says me. It's an extremely 
                         dangerous mission that killed my last 
                         crew. And you're not nearly as good 
                         as them.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Woohoo!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         We live to suck another day!

               
               </speak><note>They both do a happy dance. Leela disconnects Bender from the 
               game.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         We're just as good as any of those crews 
                         you sent to their deaths. What's the 
                         mission?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Collecting honey. Ordinary honey.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         That doesn't sound so dangerous.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         This is no ordinary honey. It's produced 
                         by vicious space bees. A single sting 
                         of their hideous neuro-toxin can cause 
                         instant death!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         And that's if you're not allergic! You 
                         don't wanna know what happens then, 
                         oh no no, God no!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         Your insides will boil out of your eye 
                         sockets like a science fair volcano!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         I didn't want to know1

               
               </speak><note>He bursts into tears.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         These bees are larger than most Buicks 
                         and twice as ugly!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Larger than an American sedan?  How 
                         big is the honey comb?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         Honey comb's big. Yeah yeah yeah.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         It's not small?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         No no no.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         It'll take more than deadly deadly bees 
                         to keep us from doing our job. Come 
                         on boys!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         But Leela we're no good!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Listen, I'm scared too. But I'm more 
                         scared of disappointing myself.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I'm not scared of that at all!

               
               </speak><note>She pushes him towards the ship.</note>

               
               <note>Ship's Cockpit. The ship flies towards the space beehive and 
               lands just inside. Swarms of bees fly past with their space pollen. 
               Leela paints yellow and black stripes on Bender.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Now bees communicate by dancing.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Like my parents. Oh wait, that was hitting!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         So this language cartridge will let 
                         you distract them.
 
               
               </speak><note>She installs the cartridge into the slot in the back of Bender's 
               head.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Ah good! I always have thoughts and 
                         feelings that can only be expressed 
                         through dance! (in bee) You stink! Bender's 
                         great! Deal with it!
 
               
               </speak><note>He laughs.</note>

               
               <note>Beehive. Leela and Fry are wearing the red spacesuits and they 
               make their way into the hive carrying a long hose. A bee flies 
               in front of them and they gasp.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Bender quick! Waggle something!

               
               </speak><note>As Bender talks Fry and Leela make their escape.</note>

               
                                     BENDER (IN BEE)
                         Hello fellow bees. How's the abdomen? 
                         Swollen with nectar I trust?
 
               
                                     BEE (IN BEE)
                         Duh!

               
               <note>Time Lapse. The crew get closer to the centre of the hive.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Leela let's turn back. There's absolutely 
                         no shame in wussing out.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Relax, everything'll be fine!

               
               </speak><note>They look up and see a ship caked in honey. It has a familiar 
               logo on the tail.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Oh my God! The old Planet Express ship!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         There's the black box!

               
               </speak><note>She picks it up and plays it.</note>

               
                                     MAN <note>ON TAPE</note>
                         Captain, the bees have us surrounded! 
                         Oh the Professor was right, we're not 
                         as good as his old crew!
 
               
                                     CAPTAIN <note>ON TAPE</note>
                         Well I aim to prove him wrong! It'll 
                         take more than a few deadly deadly bees 
                         to -  Oh Lord!
 
               
               <note>He screams some more and Leela switches the tape off.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Uh, couldn't make that out. Too much 
                         static!
 
               
               </speak><note>Fry and Bender aren't so sure.</note>

               
               <note>Time Lapse. The crew crawl into part of the honey comb. It drips 
               with honey.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Ew!

               
               </speak><note>They arrive at the end of the tunnel and gasp.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         We found it! The honey comb hideout!
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Time Lapse. Leela puts the hose into a river of honey and the 
               hose sucks it up. Fry looks at something else.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Hey what's this goop?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Royal jelly. They feed it to the queen.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Bees make honey and jelly? Huh. How 
                         come nothing humans make taste good? 
                          Help! I can't swim in jelly as far 
                         as I know!
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela pulls him out.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Look!  It's a baby queen! Aww she's 
                         so cute! You adorable wittle itty bitty 
                         fuzzy wuzzy -
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Leela! Stop bonding and lets go! I got 
                         jelly in my underpants!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         I'm taking this bee with us. With queen 
                         we can build a hive and make more honey 
                         ourselves. Let me just pack her a lunch 
                         and we'll go.
 
               
               </speak><note>She dips a jar into the jelly.</note>

               
                                     BENDER (IN BEE)
                         Pick up the pace lady! I'm sick of shaking 
                         my booty for these fat jerks!  I didn't 
                         mean you're all fat. Just fatso there.
 
                         
               
               <note>He points at a fat bee.</note>

               
                                     BEES (IN BEE)
                         He insulted our fat queen!

               
                                     QUEEN (IN BEE)
                         You try keeping your figure after 10,000 
                         kids!
 
               
               <note>The bees dive at the crew. They duck. Bender runs away. The 
               queen tries to sting him. Bender grabs a hold of her sting. She 
               shakes him around.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         This is where we distinguish ourselves 
                         from the last crew. Activate emergency 
                         high speed self contained escape pack 
                         crisis response unit! Quick!
 
               
               </speak><note>She flies off with a jet pack. Fry turns his on but he is wearing 
               it the wrong way and flies off upside down. The bees chase him 
               and Leela. Fry hits the sides of the honey comb on the way through 
               the tunnels and Bender hangs onto the queen's sting screaming. 
               Leela dodges a bee and it hits the comb and explodes.
 
               
               [Cut to: Outside Ship. Leela and Fry fly towards it.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Good luck Bender!

               
               </speak><note>They fly through the cargo bay hatch.</note>

               
               <note>Cut to: Ship's Cargo Bay. Leela closes the hatch.</note>

               
               <note>Cut to: Outside Ship. The ship tries to take off but the honey 
               holds it down. The queen prepares her sting.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Ship's Cargo Bay. Her sting comes through with Bender 
               on the end.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         I'm back baby!

               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Outside Ship. The cargo bay hatch closes, the queen 
               falls from the ship and they take off. The bees sting the ship 
               and dent it. The ship speeds away from the hive, blowing the 
               bees back.</note>
 
               
               <note>Ship's Cockpit. Fry cheers and Leela puts the baby queen in 
               a little pet basket.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         We made it! We're alive!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Burn on that old crew! The only things 
                         they did better than us were suck and 
                         die!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Leela we got lucky this time but you 
                         should be more careful. I don't want 
                         anything to happen to you.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Thanks, but I can look out for myself. 
                         Frankly I can smell danger a mile away.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>The bee unfolds it's sting.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Look out!  You want her you'll have 
                         to go through me.
 
               
               </speak><note>The bee goes through Fry and he and Leela fall to the floor. 
               The bee writhes around on the floor, dying. Bender quickly throws 
               it into the airlock and jettisons it. It floats away into space 
               and a space truck hits it. Leela looks where the sting hit her.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         You call that a wound? That's a boo 
                         boo top! But thanks for trying to save 
                         me Fry! Fry?  He's...he's dead.
 
               
               </speak><note>She and Bender kneel beside him.</note>

               
                                     BENDER (CRYING)
                         Who will make Bender waffles just the 
                         way he likes them now?
 
               
               <note>Orbitting Meadows National Cemetery. Fry's funeral has begun. 
               He is in an open casket. Mourners that include Leo and Inez Wong 
               and two Trisolians pay their respects to him. Leela cries.</note>
 
               
               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         It was all my fault! He died because 
                         of me!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         No no no no no no no.  I'm lying to 
                         make her feel better.
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela cries more.</note>

               
               <note>Time Lapse. Hermes and LaBarbara pay their respects to Fry. 
               Hermes puts piece of burning paper on the coffin.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LABARBARA </character><speak>

                         Husband, can't you go anywhere without 
                         lighting something up?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character><speak>
                         It's an old Jamaican accounting tradition. 
                         We burn his timecard. That way his zombie 
                         doesn't come back looking for his final 
                         paycheque.
 
               
               </speak><note>They leave and Amy and Zoidberg stand beside Fry.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>

                         He looks so natural. It's funny to think 
                         he's clammed full of sawdust and preservatives.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ZOIDBERG </character><speak>
                         I only wish I could have removed the 
                         stinger.
 
               
               </speak><note>They look at Fry's body, the huge sting sticks out of him.</note>
 
               
               
               <note>Time Lapse. Father Changstein el Gamahl of the First Amalgamated 
               Church begins the eulogy.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> PRIEST </character><speak>

                         I barely knew Philip, but as a clergyman 
                         I have no problem telling his most intimate 
                         friends all about him.
 
               
               </speak><note>The congregation cries.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character><speak>

                         Soothe us with sweet lies.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> PRIEST </character><speak>
                         It may comfort you to know that Fry's 
                         death took only 15 seconds. Yet the 
                         pain was so intense that it felt to 
                         him like 15 years. And it goes without 
                         saying that it caused him to empty his 
                         bowels.  We now commend Fry's body to 
                         the ages.
 
               
               </speak><note>The coffin turns around and is ejected into space. Scruffy plays 
               Walking On Sunshine on the bagpipes.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>

                         He's walking on sunshine now.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         This makes me the oldest member of my 
                         family.
 
               
               </speak><note>He cries and hugs Bender.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMAZONIAN </character><speak>

                         Him do good snu-snu.

               
               </speak><note>Behind her the radiator from the Miss Universe pageant, Petunia, 
               the girl from The Hip Joint, Morgan Proctor and Michelle aren't 
               so sure.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         All those times I said "Kill all humans" 
                         I'd always whisper "except one." And 
                         Fry was that one. And I never told him 
                         so.
 
               
               </speak><note>He cries and hugs Farnsworth. Terry does his swooshy coat thing.</note>
 
               
               
                                     TERRY (DRAMATICALLY)
                         Farewell from the world of tomorrow!
 
                         
               
               <note>Leela's Bedroom. She tickles Nibbler and wipes her eye with 
               half a hanky. She puts the other half on her bedside table and 
               sees the jar of honey.</note>
 
               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         They say a spoonful of space honey helps 
                         ease the pain.  It's good.  I feel funny. 
                         Haha funny!
 
               
               <note>She laughs and then faints.</note>

               
               <note>Leela's Dream. Leela floats towards Fry's coffin and it opens.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Leela?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Fry? I thought you were dead.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Nope, I'm better than ever. Before the 
                         accident I couldn't do this!
 
               
               </speak><note>He sticks his hand through the sting wound.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Impressive! But it does sorta support 
                         my You-Are-Dead theory.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Then I'll prove I'm alive! By telling 
                         you something only I could know. There's 
                         a surprise for you in my locker. I got 
                         it at a Swedish novelty shop before 
                         we left.
 
               
               </speak><note>Behind him his locker appears. He opens the door and pulls out 
               a gift-wrapped box and hands it to Leela. She gasps.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         It's too beautiful to open! Can I open 
                         it?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Sure. There's just one thing I want 
                         you to.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         What?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I want you to wake up.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Wake up? But I'm not -

               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Leela's Bedroom. She wakes up. It's the middle of the 
               night. Nibbler rolls of the bed.</note>
 
               
               <note>Planet Express: Locker Area. The crew sans Bender are gathered 
               around Fry's locker.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         In my dream Fry said he hid a gift for 
                         me in my locker. If it's true then he 
                         must still exist in some form.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Oh course he still exists. As a frozen 
                         corpse in outer space!  Oh, I made myself 
                         sad.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Well, here goes.

               
               </speak><note>She opens the locker. It is empty. The crew sigh.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ZOIDBERG </character><speak>

                         Bupkiss!

               
               </speak><note>Enter Bender counting some cash and whistling.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Well, I feel better now. Pawning all 
                         the stuff in Fry's locker helped give 
                         me closure.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Was there anything in there that might 
                         have been a gift for me?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         No. Nothing. Not at all. No way Jos�! 
                          Here it is.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         You took this from Fry's locker?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         Hey the guy's dead! There's no law against 
                         grave robbing!
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela opens the gift. It's a squeezy toy.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         That proves it. Fry is alive somewhere 
                         and he's reaching me in my dreams.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Bullpies!

               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. He helps Leela onto a table.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Lay down here and we'll do some tests. 
                         If Fry is out there then Leela's brain 
                         could be acting as a five pound ouija 
                         board.
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela lies back on the table.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Is this some sort of brain scanner?
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Some sort yes. In France it's called 
                         a "guillotine."
 
               
               </speak><note>He pulls a lever. Leela gasps and jumps out of the way, narrowly 
               missing the blade.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Professor! Can't you examine my brain 
                         without removing it?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Yes. Easily.

               
               </speak><note>He scans her brain with a small scanner thing.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         Hey, what if Fry wasn't actually dead 
                         when we buried him? Y'know like Julia 
                         Roberts?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>
                         Well I suppose there's a slim -  I don't 
                         believe it!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         What is it? Is Fry alive in some other 
                         dimension or something?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         No. According to this gizmometer, Fry 
                         is dead and nothing can bring him back! 
                         Remarkable.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         But, my dream. Your science can't unprove 
                         that! How could I have know the gift 
                         was in Fry's locker?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         Easy! He told you about it before he 
                         died! And your grief roasted mind blocked 
                         it out.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Are you saying I'm going crazy?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         No no, no one's saying that! But I'm 
                         certainly thinking it loudly.
 
               
               </speak><note>Leela's Bedroom. She tosses and turns in her sleep.</note>

               
               <note>Cut to: Leela's Dream. Back in space Fry appears to her like 
               the Cheshire Cat, just his hair and mouth.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Hi Leela! I'm just gonna keep talking, 
                         even if you can't hear me. Blah blah 
                         blah, blah blah blah blah blah.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Shut up, I can hear you. The Professor 
                         says you're just a dream.
 
               
               </speak><note>Fry appears fully.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Oh yeah?  Could a dream take you dancing 
                         in an illusion garden?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         Well yes, technically. It's still very 
                         sweet of you.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Then what if we shared a sleigh ride 
                         across the ice fields of Hiperia?
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>The dream changes to an icy landscape. Fry and Leela are pulled 
               along in a sleigh by a woolly mammoth. Fry hands Leela a mug 
               and tears open a packet of cocoa.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Oh Fry you must be alive! I've never 
                         been treated so romantically by my own 
                         imagination before!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Here, take my jacket. You look a little 
                         cold.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Thank you. It's all so beautiful I forgot 
                         how many hundreds of degrees zero it 
                         must be. I just wish I could convince 
                         the others you're alive.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         You can. All you have to do is wake 
                         up.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         No no! Don't say that! This is real!
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Leela's Bedroom. She wakes up and sends Nibbler flying 
               off the bed.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Not another dream!  Fry's jacket! The 
                         one he was buried in! My dream was real! 
                         He's alive!
 
               
               </speak><note>Her neighbour thumps the wall.</note>

               
               
               <note>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Bender is on fire. Hermes, Amy, 
               Zoidberg and Farnsworth blast him with fire extinguishers.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         That's better!

               
               </speak><note>He lights a cigar. Enter Leela with Fry's jacket in a jacket 
               jacket.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Fry's alive! I have proof!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         You do not!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         I'm from Jamaica, the show-me island. 
                         So show me you're blowing it out your 
                         fanny.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         But he gave me his jacket. Look.

               
               </speak><note>She opens the jacket jacket and pulls out...her own green jacket.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         That's not Fry's jacket. Fry's jacket 
                         is red! That's your jacket. An off the 
                         rack lime green affair.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>
                         But Fry...his jacket...and when I woke 
                         up it was on me.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character>

                         You're under a lot of guilt stress Leela. 
                         Here, work it off.
 
               
               </speak><note>He hands the squeezy stress toy and she squeezes it.</note>

               
                                     LEELA <note>SQUEEZING</note>
                         I am not under stress dammit!

               
               <note>The toy explodes.</note>

               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         What?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character><speak>
                         I said everything's going to be alright.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Oh. Maybe I am freaking out a little.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         A little? You're screwier than my Aunt 
                         Rita! And she's a screw!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         I need to calm down. I'd better take 
                         some more of that space honey.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         You've been taking space honey? Be careful 
                         you purple haired imbecile!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ZOIDBERG </character>

                         One spoonful calms you down, two spoonfuls 
                         help you sleep, but three spoonfuls, 
                         you'll go into a sleep and never wake 
                         up! Never!
 
               
               
                                     BENDER (AMY'S VOICE)
                         Never!

               
               </speak><note>Leela gasps.</note>

               
               <note>Planet Express: Lounge. Leela takes a spoonful of honey.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         One spoonful to calm me down.  OK, I've 
                         got a pretty good calm going! Two spoonfuls 
                         to help me sleep.  Uh oh, still awake. 
                         I guess one more spoonful couldn't hurt. 
                          Oh my gosh! I'd better get a sponge! 
                          Fry?  Is that you? I don't need a sponge!
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Why and I sticky and naked? Did I miss 
                         something fun?
 
               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. Farnsworth scans Fry with 
               the gizmometer.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character><speak>

                         Incredible! According to the gizmometer, 
                         Fry touched the royal jelly in the space 
                         hive, leaving an imprint of his </section>
 <section><character> DNA  </character><speak>
                         and brainwaves. Then, when it spilled 
                         on the couch, it recombined with trace 
                         amounts of Fry's hair and skin -
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         And blood! Don't forget about Fry's 
                         blood!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FARNSWORTH </character>

                         Yes Bender, thank you. In short, the 
                         various fluids Fry left in the couch 
                         caused the royal jelly to regenerate 
                         his entire being!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Neat!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         This is great! My buddy's alive and 
                         his credit cards are valid again!  Lets 
                         go get hammered!
 
               
               </speak><note>The crew cheer.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ZOIDBERG </character><speak>

                         I should warn you: I'm a mean drunk.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>They leave, leaving Fry and Leela alone.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Fry, I'm so glad I didn't kill you.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Me too.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Feeling responsible for your death was 
                         driving me mad. But now everything is 
                         alright.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         Uh, not everything.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         What? What do you mean?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         You have to wake up.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Wake up? Oh no! No! It can't be!

               
               </speak><note>Cut to: Planet Express: Lounge. Leela wakes up on the couch. 
               The royal jelly wasn't spilt and Fry didn't come back to life. 
               The two spoonfuls did help her sleep. She gasps and looks around.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Poo.

               
               </speak><note>Planet Express: Meeting Room.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         I'm cracking up. In my dreams I'm happy 
                         because Fry is alive, but when I'm awake 
                         my mind plays tricks on me.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character><speak>
                         Oh take it easy Leela.

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character>

                         In every life we have some trouble.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         But when you worry you make it double.
 
                         
               
               
                                     FARNSWORTH (SINGING)
                         The landlord says your rent is late...
 
                         
               
                                     HERMES (SINGING)
                         He might have to litigate.

               
                                     BENDER (SINGING)
                         But don't worry!

               
               </speak><note>He opens his chest cabinet and a bee flies out and stings Farnsworth's 
               head.</note>
 
               
                                     BEE (SINGING)
                         Bee...

               
                                     FARNSWORTH (SINGING)
                         ...happy!

               
               <note>His head explodes and the meeting room goes dark.</note>

               
                                     ZOIDBERG (SINGING)
                         Ain't got no cash,

               Ain't got no style,

               Ladies vomit when I smile,

               But does Zoidberg worry?

               
               <note>The bee stings him.</note>

               
                                     BEE (SINGING)
                         Bee...

               
                                     ZOIDBERG (SINGING)
                         ...happy!

               
               <note>He explodes. Hermes holds Amy and skates around as the bee flies 
               alongside.</note>
 
               
                                     HERMES (SINGING)
                         Don't worry now Amy!

               
               <note>The bee stings him and he explodes.</note>

               
                                     AMY (SINGING)
                         OK! I'm happy!

               
               <note>The bee stings her and she explodes.</note>

               
               <note>Streamers and glitter falls around the table and Bender dances 
               on it.</note>
 
               
                                     BENDER (SINGING)
                         Take us home Bender! Don't worry!

               
                                     BEE (SINGING)
                         Bee...

               
               <note>It stings him.</note>

               
                                     BENDER (SINGING)
                         ...happy!

               
               <note>He explodes in a rather nice display of fireworks. The smoke 
               clears and everyone is back at the table again.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Uh, were you just singing?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>
                         No I was telling you not to worry. I'm 
                         not allowed to sing - court order.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Ship's Cockpit. Leela takes off in the ship. She is nervous 
               and jittery.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         I'll find Fry's coffin, take his corpse 
                         and keep it under my mattress to remind 
                         me he's really dead. That'll prove I'm 
                         not insane.
 
               
               </speak><note>Outside Ship. Leela stands at the airlock in her spacesuit and 
               looks out at Fry's coffin, floating like the monolith from 2001: 
               A Space Odyssey. She jumps out and floats to it. She puts her 
               hands on it.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         OK, it's just an ordinary coffin. Containing 
                         my ordinary dead friend, who I killed.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>She opens the coffin. Inside are lots of colours going by very 
               fast like in 2001: A Space Odyssey. Leela stares.</note>
 
               
               <note>Cut to: Leela's Bedroom. She wakes up from what was another 
               dream.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         What happened? Why am I in my apartment?
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>Farnsworth's, Zoidberg's, Hermes' and Amy's faces appear on 
               her walls.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Stop it! Stop it!

               
               </speak><note>She tears their faces down like wallpaper. Bender appears on 
               the floor.</note>
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character><speak>

                         You killed Fry!

               
               </speak><note>She grabs the hoover and sucks him up.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         OK, I'm insane! But I'm still sane enough 
                         to know it.  The only time I feel alright 
                         is in my dreams. With you.  Three spoonfuls. 
                         Then I can dream forever.  One.  Two 
                          Here goes. Goodbye waking world.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>The spoon moves towards her mouth. Fry's photo suddenly starts 
               talking.</note>
 
               
                                     FRY'</section>
 <section><character> S PHOTO </character><speak>

                         Leela! No!  Listen to me, you don't 
                         want to lie in bed like a vegetable 
                         and do nothing the rest of your life. 
                         I've tried it. Bedsores hurt!
 
               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         Then what am I s'posed to do?

               
                                     FRY'</section>
 <section><character> S PHOTO </character><speak>
                         Fight it!

               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         I can't!

               
                                     FRY'</section>
 <section><character> S PHOTO </character>

                         You can! The Leela I know doesn't give 
                         up this easily.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         OK. I'll try.  Go away!

               
               </speak><note>She throws the jar at it. The jar and the bee break and the 
               one bee becomes a swarm. Leela picks up Fry's photo and holds 
               it tightly.</note>
 
               
                                     FRY'</section>
 <section><character> S PHOTO </character><speak>

                         I don't know if you can hear me Leela 
                         but there's something I wanna tell you. 
                         I love you.
 
               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         I'm so scared Fry I don't know what 
                         to do.
 
               
                                     FRY'</section>
 <section><character> S PHOTO </character><speak>
                         Just wake up Leela. Please. Just wake 
                         up.
 
               
                                     LEELA (CRYING)
                         I don't understand what you mean!

               
               </speak><note>She hugs the photo.</note>

               
               <note>Cut to: Hospital Room. Leela is in a bed and Fry is sat at her 
               side. His jacket is draped around her and she is in a coma.</note>
 
               
               
                                     FRY (CRYING)
                         Just wake up. Please. Just wake up Leela.
 
                         
               
               <note>Her eyelid flutters and opens. She looks around.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character><speak>

                         Fry. You're alive!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>
                         Leela! You're awake!

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Of course I'm awake. You wouldn't stop 
                         waking me.  Where am I?
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         In the hospital. The ambulance brought 
                         you here right after the bee stung you.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         But the bee stung you. It barely touched 
                         me.
 
               
               </speak><note>Fry lifts up his shirt. There is a patch where his wound was.</note>
 
               
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character><speak>

                         Stinger went right through me and you 
                         got all the poison. My new spleen came 
                         from a guy who liked to motorcycle.
 
                         
               
               </speak><note>He makes revving noises. Enter the rest of the crew.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> HERMES </character><speak>

                         Sweet three toed sloth of ice planet 
                         Hoth! She's awake!
 
               
               </speak><note>They all cheer.</note>

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> BENDER </character>

                         You were in the best coma I've ever 
                         seen!
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character>

                         The doctor said you'd never wake up.
 
                         
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>

                         Really? How long was I out?

               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> AMY </character>

                         Two weeks. Fry never left your side 
                         for a minute.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> ZOIDBERG </character>

                         And he talked non-stop, like a parrot 
                         of the sea he was.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> FRY </character>

                         I though that if you heard a familiar 
                         voice, it might help keep your mind 
                         together. But, who knows if it really 
                         got through.
 
               
                                     </section>
 <section><character> LEELA </character>
                         It got through Fry.  It got through.
 
                         
               
               THE END
</section></xml>