<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 511

<title>THREE HUNDRED BIG BOYS</title>

<author>Eric Kaplan</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Voted "Best."</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. The crew watch a television news 
program.</info>

<speak who="ANNOUNCER"><info>ON TV</info>
This week in the universe... Dateline 
Turantulon 6: The brave warriors of 
Earth under the command of General Major 
Weeblo Zapp Brannigan have achieved 
victory over the spider homeworld.  
And to the victor belong the spoils 
- one trillion dollars in silken treasure.</speak>

<info>Zapp strokes a silk suit.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP"><info>ON TV</info>
Mmm!</speak>

<info>The scene changes to Nixon outside a building making an announcement.</info>

<speak who="NIXON"><info>ON TV</info>
My fellow Earthicans. After meeting 
with top voodoo economists, I have decided 
to refund our silk surplus to you, the 
taxpayers. That's right! I've sent you 
each 300 buckeroos in the form of a 
tricky dick fun bill. Knock yourselves 
out!</speak>

<info>The programs ends and the crew cheer.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
I'm slightly richer!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
What to do what to do? One $300 hookerbot 
or 300 $1 hookerbots?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm going to swim with the whale! They're 
the gentle giants of the deep.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm well aware of that.</speak>

<speak who="SCRUFFY">
Scruffy's gonna get himself one of them 
$300 haircuts. This ones lost it's pizazz!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
A fortune it is! At last, Zoidberg will 
live like a rich man!</speak>

<info>He kisses the $300. Nixon squirms on it.</info>

<speak who="NIXON"><info>ON BILL</info>
Hey, cut it out! Go away! Get away from 
me!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Shmeesh! It's just 300 bucks, what is 
that, like a hundred cups of coffee?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's it! I'm getting a hundred cups 
of coffee! Starting now.  Coffee machine, 
one cup of coffee please.</speak>

<info>He puts the $300 into the machine and it takes $3 off, leaving 
him with $297.</info>

<speak who="NIXON"><info>ON BILL</info>
Smells good!</speak>

<info>Fry takes a sip of the coffee. His first. Zapp appears on the 
screen.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Leela? Are you there?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Oh yes you are! I'm hereby inviting 
you and your oddball co-workers to a 
special reception to display the national 
silk surplus. I believe you know the 
heroic space stallion who captured it. 
Show them my medal Kif.</speak>

<info>Kif points at a medal on Zapp's chest.</info>

<speak who="KIF"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
He rented it with his tax refund.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
So Leela, will you have the pleasure.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What little there is to be had.</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP"><info>ON SCREEN</info>
Tomorrow night at eight them. Smoochies!</speak>

<info>He kisses the screen.</info>

<info>Street. People wander around enjoying their $300. The 99c Store 
changes it's name to 299.99c Store and a crack addict wanders 
out of an alley kissing his money.</info>

<speak who="CRACK ADDICT">
No cheap crack houses for me no more!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Outside Crack Mansion. The crack addict hands a man 
his $300.</info>

<speak who="MAN">
Very good sir. Shall I pre-warm sir's 
crack pipe?</speak>

<info>Above the crack mansion a peddle-plane flies over.</info>

<info>Cut to: Peddle Plane. Amy and Kif are riding it. Kif is struggling.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh Kif, it was so romantic of you to 
rent this peddle plane with your tax 
rebate. We're like two dandelion seeds 
wafting on the breeze.</speak>

<speak who="KIF"><info>(GASPING)</info>
Yes...seeds...wafting.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I almost feel kinda shallow for blowing 
my rebate on this cool talking tattoo!</speak>

<speak who="TATTOO">
Hey Gordon Gecko! I cost as much as 
this whole crummy date!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Shut up!  Ow!</speak>

<info>Geneworks. Farnsworth talks to a woman at a desk.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
As a man it has become too much of a 
chore for me to clean out my wrinkles 
each day. Is it true that stem cells 
may fight the aging process?</speak>

<speak who="GENEWORKS WOMAN">
Well yes, in the same way an infant 
may fight Muhammed Ali! But -</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
One pound of stem cells please.</speak>

<info>He slaps his $300 on the desk and the woman gives him a tub 
of stem cells.</info>

<speak who="GENEWORKS WOMAN">
Of course any age reversing effects 
will be purely temporary.</speak>

<info>She gags and turns away as Farnsworth slaps the stem cell cream 
on his face.</info>

<info>Hacking Jack's Fine Smokables. Bender peruses the fine merchandise 
within. He looks at some Dutch Butts for $1.99 but is more excited 
by the Royal Kooparillo for $300. He looks across at a cigar 
in a glass case, Le Grand Cigar, $10,000.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Say buddy, why's this grand cigar so 
pricy?</speak>

<speak who="CLERK">
Well, as you can see, it's wrapper is 
a piece of the original US constitution. 
It was hand rolled by Queen Elizabeth 
during her wild years and was buried 
with George Burns until graverobbing 
space mushrooms - uh, well you know 
the rest.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Give me 300 bucks worth!</speak>

<speak who="CLERK">
No can do.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Oh alright, I'll just take these $300 
burglars tools then.</speak>

<speak who="CLERK">
Very good sir.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
So uh, what time d'you close tonight?</speak>

<info>Outside The Conrads' House. Dwight sits on the steps and smiles 
as Hermes arrives with a box behind his back.</info>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
Hey pops! Did that tax rebate come?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Came and went! You're now the proud 
owner of Bamboo Boogie Boots!  With 
a warning label this big you know they 
gotta be fun!</speak>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
But pops, I don't wanna have fun, I 
wanna be like you. Boring but prudently 
invested.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Babylon's bells! I tallyed almost 300 
bananas on this entertainment product. 
Now you put 'em on and have fun!</speak>

<speak who="DWIGHT"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
I don't wanna.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Well then I'm gonna put 'em on and make 
you watch me have fun!  See? Fun! Fun! 
Dwight! Help me!</speak>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
I'll save you pops!</speak>

<info>He climbs the bamboo and hangs on to Hermes' feet. Hermes starts 
to lose his balance and he stumbles down the road still wearing 
the boots. Cars swerves to avoid him and honk their horns.</info>

<info>Outside Geneworks. Farnsworth comes out of the building looking 
younger. He sees a group of younger people standing around a 
car listening to loud music.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Hey! Turn that damn music......up!</speak>

<info>Hermes and Dwight stumble past on the bamboo boots.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Isn't this fun?</speak>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
No! I wish I had two mommies!</speak>

<info>They walks past a jewellery shop called Diamonds Are Forever.</info>

<info>Diamonds Are Forever. Randy hands a cushion with jewellery on 
it to Zoidberg.</info>

<speak who="RANDY">
Try these, um, sir.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg puts the rings on his mouth flaps and looks at himself 
in the mirror.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I ask for rich guy stuff and you give 
me shiny pebbles? Bah! I bid you adieu!</speak>

<info>He shakes the rings off and they hit Randy on the head.</info>

<speak who="RANDY">
Ow!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg looks scared, woops and scuttles out.</info>

<info>Brooklyn Aquarium: Whale Tank. Leela is at a stand next to a 
whale tank.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'd like a pass to swim with Mushu please.</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
Well you asked the right guy! I'm the 
whale biologist! Though personally I 
hate whales. <info>(whispering)</info> Espeically 
Mushu.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Then why'd you become a whale biologist?</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
I don't know you well enough to get 
into that. $300 please.  Noon tomorrow. 
If you're late you only get to tread 
water in the scallop tank.</speak>

<info>Leela takes her pass and leaves.</info>

<info>Cut to: Brooklyn Aquarium: Starfishbucks Coffee. Fry waits in 
line for a cup of coffee.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Uh, I'll have a coffee.</speak>

<speak who="MAN">
Guppy, trout, mermaid or -</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Whale please.</speak>

<info>The man pours the coffee and Fry drinks it.</info>

<info>Peddle Plane. Amy and Kif fly over the Aquarium.</info>

<speak who="KIF"><info>(GASPING)</info>
Amy, I-I also spent some of my tax rebate 
on a gift for you.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh Kiffie!</speak>

<info>She opens the box. It is a watch with two faces.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
It shows the time wherever we both are. 
And it's powered by love! Also you have 
to wind it.</speak>

<speak who="TATTOO">
Ohh! Somebody won big at Skeeball!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
You shut up! I love it Kif. I'll use 
it whenever I wanna know what time it 
is.  Ooo! It's Fry and Leela! <info>(shouting)</info> 
Hi Fry and Leela!</speak>

<info>The paddle plane lurches forward and starts falling. Kif screams.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Oh! Keep peddling! Oh for the love of 
God keep peddling!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Fry and Leela. Leela screams and Fry gurgles his coffee.</info>

<info>Cut to: Peddle Plane. They get closer and closer to the ground. 
The plane turns the right way right at the last minute and swoops 
over people's heads. They scream. The peddle plane flies over 
Mushu's tank. Kif wipes his brow and breathes a sigh of relief. 
Amy leans over backwards again and waves.</info>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
Bye Fry and Leela!</speak>

<info>The peddle plane tilts sideways and the watch starts to slide 
of the front of it. Kif panics. The watch slips off and he sighs. 
Mushu leaps up out of the water and eats the watch. The crowd 
applauds.</info>

<speak who="TATTOO">
Oh I can't wait until the tattoos on 
Amy's butt hear about this!</speak>

<speak who="BUTT TATTOOS">
Hear about what? Tell us!</speak>

<info>A horse tattoo neighs.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Meeting Room. Kif cries.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
Don't feel sad my little tadpole.</speak>

<speak who="KIF"><info>(CRYING)</info>
I'm trying not to. But my gift to you 
is in the belly of a whale.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Say, this reminds me of that time I 
ate that other watch Kif gave you!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Hey, it is kinda like that!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
To induce vomitting, that was the solution! 
Everywhere it went!  What a Valentine's 
Day that was!</speak>

<info>Leela looks at her Mushu pass.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Hmm, this may seem like a huge coincidence 
but I happen to have it in with that 
whale!</speak>

<speak who="SCRUFFY">
Scruffy's formulated a plan. But you'll 
need a ready source of nausiatin' rotten 
fish.</speak>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. In the restaurant Fry, Leela, Kif and 
Amy sit around a table with a huge fish in the middle. Enter 
Elzar.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Freshen your coffee sir?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yeah yeah yeah keep it comin' put the 
pot down get away!</speak>

<info>He drinks the coffee. His 31st cup. Leela gets up and goes somewhere. 
Elsewhere in the restaurant Farnsworth is having dinner with 
the woman from earlier.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
You're so young in spirit! Its hard 
to believe you're as old as 25.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
The key is to grab life by the hojos! 
Live every day like it might be your 
last!</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
What'll it be kids?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
One bowl of mild verena.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Elzar's Kitchen. Enter Leela. She opens the fresh fish 
freezer door and looks inside.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Pay dirt!  Heyya!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Restaurant. Leela casually strolls out of the kitchen 
whistling. And sits down. Elzar serves food to Zoidberg.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Here you go big spender: Foie gras and 
caviar!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg sniffs the food.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Goose liver? Fish eggs?  Pah! Where's 
the goose? Where's the fish?</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey, that's what rich people eat. The 
garbage parts of the food.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I ate garbage yesterday and it didn't 
cost me $300! I'm not paying.  Farewell 
good sir!</speak>

<info>He leaves with a very upper-class scuttle and woop.</info>

<info>Outside Hacking Jack's Fine Smokables. On the roof Bender shines 
a torch onto a grate. He cuts it open and starts to lower himself 
through it.</info>

<info>Cut to: Hacking Jack's Fine Smokables. Bender lowers himself 
from the roof a la Tom Cruise in Mission: Impossible and stops 
just above the case containing the $10,000 cigar. He gets a diamond 
out of his chest cavity and cuts through the glass with it then 
throws the diamond in the bin. He reaches in and takes out the 
cigar.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Le Grand Cigar! She's mine! And with 
absolutely no consequences!</speak>

<info>He evily cackles and raises himself out of the room. In the 
corner a security camera watches him. The signal goes along a 
wire, down a dark tunnel, through the sewers where El Chupanibre 
terrorises the leg mutant, up a pole and through a dark hole.</info>

<info>Cut to: Police Station. Smitty watches what's going on on URL's 
chest.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
You see that?</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Grand theft tobacco. Sounds like we 
should get off our fat cop asses and 
ride!</speak>

<info>The siren comes out of his head.</info>

<info>Outside Elzar's Fine Cuisine. The next morning Hermes and Dwight 
are still walking around on the bamboo boots but now they are 
asleep. Elzar comes out the back door of the restaurant with 
a crate of fish.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Pee-yew! This fish is slightly too rotten 
to even make jambolaya!</speak>

<info>He pours the fish into a dumpster and leaves. The dumpster lid 
swings open and Leela and Amy climb out with the fish in a net.</info>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(WHISPERING)</info>
So far so good. Where's Kif?</speak>

<info>Behind them Kif groans as he is dragged along inside the net.</info>

<info>Guadalajara Brown Drip Gourment Coffee. Fry is jittery as he 
has an early morning cup of coffee. He drinks his 51st cup.</info>

<speak who="FRY"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
This isn't Yemeni! It's Sulowesi!  And 
the cup's shaking I don't want my coffee 
shaking!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
You seem a tad wound up buddy. And your 
face is greasy! Real greasy. You been 
up all night?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Of course I've been up all night! Not 
because of caffine it was insomnia I 
couldn't stop thinking about coffee 
I need a nap.  Coffee time!</speak>

<info>He gulps down his 52nd cup. Bender gets out his cigar and sniffs 
it.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ah! Mighty fine smokable!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Fancy cigar why don't you smoke it already? 
Puff puff go go go go go!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Nah, you can't blow smoke from such 
a majestic stogy in just anyone's face. 
I'm saving it for the fancy pants at 
Zapp Brannigan's black tie reception. 
You comin'?</speak>

<info>Fry nods jitterily.</info>

<info>Brooklyn Aquarium: Whale Tank. Leela is kitted out in a swimming 
costume and flippers. The rotten fish is packed into her costume.</info>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
And the fifth reason whales kill is 
for the sheer fun of it.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Anything else?</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
Yeah. You're lumpy and you smell awful. 
Hey, I calls 'em like I sees 'em! I'm 
a whale biologist.</speak>

<info>Leela turns to the tank.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK Mushu, its feeding time!  Oh crud, 
he ate my suit!</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
The suit was ugly - whale biologist!</speak>

<info>Golf Club. Zoidberg swings at the ball but repeatedly misses.</info>

<speak who="CADDY">
Perhaps if you tightened your grip sir?</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Ah. Thank you golf slave!  Bah! Rich 
pople wouldn't waste their time on this 
nonsense! Plus, these eggs are gritty 
and tasteless!</speak>

<info>He spits out three golf balls and whacks them with the half 
club.</info>

<info>Cut to: Picnic Site. Farnsworth and the woman are kissing. One 
of Zoidberg's balls hits Farnsworth on the head.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Ow! Not so rough!</speak>

<info>Brooklyn Aquarium: Whale Tank. The show has started and the 
stands are full of people. Kif, Amy and Bender are already there. 
Leela arrives wrapped in the Please Do Not Feed The Whale sign 
and gives the thumbs up. The orphans sit in front of them.</info>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
Ladies and gentlemen, presenting Mushu! 
The educated whale who thinks he's better 
than you!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
C'mon Mushu! Barf! Barf like a freshman!</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
And now ignorant whale lovers, we'll 
see who's boss as I make Mushu jump 
through this hoop. Jump Mushu!  Who 
wants a fish?</speak>

<info>Mushu throws up and the crowd gasps.</info>

<speak who="LITTLE ORPHAN">
Mushu is sick!</speak>

<info>Smity and URL stand aghast as Bender sneaks out behind them.</info>

<speak who="URL">
It just keep comin' and comin'!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Wait, that chunk, its the watch!  I 
got it Amy! I got it! The plan went 
off without a -</speak>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
He's got Aquarium property! Stop him!</speak>

<speak who="URL">
Better do what he says. He's a whale 
biologist!</speak>

<info>He lifts Kif out of the water.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
You're under arrest you squishy punk!</speak>

<info>Smitty puts the cuffs on Kif and he drops the watch. He sighs. 
Mushu sicks up Leela's swimming costume.</info>

<info>Outside Silk Surplus Reception. Two people walk inside. Two 
hobos try to follow them but a forcefield stops them and the 
fall over.</info>

<info>Cut to: Silk Surplus Reception. Zapp tells his story to Mom 
and her sons and Mayor Poopenmeyer.</info>

<speak who="ZAPP">
The Spiderians, though weak and woman-like 
on the battlefield, are masters of the 
textile arts. Taste like king crab by 
the way. Crazy bugs actually wove this 
tapestry of my heroic conquest while 
I was still killing them!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg scratches the tapestry and sniffs it.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
What? It's not even scratch and sniff? 
But if rich people think it's good, 
I'll buy it!  One art please!</speak>

<info>Mom laughs.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
What a clever impersonation of a stupid 
poor person! How much is that placemat 
actually worth Brannigan?</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Exactly $1 billion!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Now that's walkin' around money!</speak>

<info>She blows her nose on her $300.</info>

<speak who="NIXON"><info>ON BILL</info>
What? Hey! Wait! Arooo!</speak>

<info>Zoidberg looks on sadly. Over on the other side of the room 
an even jitterier Fry just about manages to pour himself another 
cup of coffee. He drinks his 99th cup. Bender "enjoys" a conversation 
with Judge Whitey.</info>

<speak who="WHITEY">
So I said to Kitty "The only way to 
keep the butler from running away is 
to cut off his foot!"  Yes, it reminds 
me of a joke I heard about upper-middle 
class people.</speak>

<info>Bender blows smoke in his face and he coughs. Elsewhere Amy 
and Scruffy talk.</info>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(CRYING)</info>
I've never been sad at a party before. 
I wonder if my mind is thinking about 
Kif being in jail.</speak>

<speak who="SCRUFFY">
Jail's not so bad. You can make sangria 
in the terlet! Course its shank or beshanked.</speak>

<speak who="AMY"><info>(CRYING)</info>
Of course.</speak>

<info>Commander Riker Prison. Kif paces around in his cell still covered 
in the whale sick.</info>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
Look, just give back the property and 
we'll drop the charges.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Fine, have the watch. It's broken anyway.</speak>

<info>He throws the watch but a forcefield stops it from going through 
the bars and it bounces back and hits him on the head.</info>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
I don't want your watch. You're covered 
in precious ambergris.</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Precious ambergris?</speak>

<info>The whale biologist sighs and presses a button on his belt. 
A holographic image of Roseanne appears.</info>

<speak who="HOLOROSEANNE">
Ambergris. Noun. A grease-like product 
of the sperm whale's digestive tract 
that is used as a base in the finest 
perfumes. This has been Roseanne, your 
guide to the world of facts.</speak>

<info>The holo-encyclopedia shuts off.</info>

<speak who="WHALE BIOLOGIST">
You heard Roseanne. Scrape off the priceless 
ambergris and I'll let you go!</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Or better yet I'll simply shed my skin!</speak>

<info>He struggles as he takes it off.</info>

<info>Silk Surplus Reception. Morbo's wife fiddles with his bow tie.</info>

<speak who="MORBO">
Stop it! Stop it! It's fine! I will 
destroy you!</speak>

<info>Bender walks past and blows smoke in their faces. They cough. 
Underneath a giant spider dress Farnsworth and his girlfriend 
make out. A bell tolls.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Wha?  Uh, gotta go, uh fight club!</speak>

<info>He runs out from underneath the dress and covers his face. His 
girlfriend follows.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
What's happening Hubie?</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm afraid the face you fell in love 
with was actually just a blob of living 
gunk I bought with my tax refund.</speak>

<info>The stem cells slide away.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
Well as long as we're being honest, 
I also spent my tax refund on a crazy 
treatment.</speak>

<info>She pulls a plug out of her belly button and she swells up. 
She is really a huge fat woman.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
That certainly is honest.</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
It better for us both to just be ourselves. 
You, wrinkled as a prune.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You, fat as the Queen of Seacows.</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
I love you!</speak>

<info>They kiss and she falls on him.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh my!</speak>

<info>On the other side of the room Leela is now talking to Whitey 
and Kif is reunited with Amy.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
So you see the putrid waxy substance 
I was coated with was -</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Not precious ambergris?</speak>

<speak who="KIF">
Yes! And I managed to sneak some out 
in a usual place! Ta-da!  Using that, 
I'll make you a perfume of lilac and 
jasmine and frankenberry!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Oh Kif, it's so romantic I can't even 
wait! I'm gonna wear it right now!</speak>

<info>She puts some on. Her tattoo splutters. Everyone else chokes 
at he stench.</info>

<speak who="MOM">
Who smells like freaking porpus hork?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
I do! Kiss me Kif!</speak>

<info>They kiss. Zoidberg slinks out sadly.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Silk Surplus Reception. Zoidberg walks out through 
the fire exit and sits on a dustbin.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG"><info>(CRYING)</info>
Oh what a foolish squid I've been. I'm 
not rich! I can't even buy one measley 
masterpiece!</speak>

<info>He cries. The hobos approach him.</info>

<speak who="HOBO #1">
Pardon us gent. Might a couple of hungry 
hungry hobos take a feed from that aluminium 
snack box?</speak>

<info>Zoidberg gets off the bin and the hobos rummage through it.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
So now I'm in the gutter? Surrounded 
by bums who eat garbage. Money brought 
me no happiness. Bupkiss!</speak>

<speak who="HOBO #2">
Ooo this boot's got a little pudding 
at the bottom!</speak>

<info>He licks it off.</info>

<info>Silk Surplus Reception. Bender and Leela talk to Ben Beeler.</info>

<speak who="BEELER">
Interestingly, the Spiderians are more 
closely related to our elephants than 
our spiders.</speak>

<info>Bender blows smoke inhis face and he coughs. Bender chuckles 
then gasps as Hermes and Dwight enter via the window, still walking 
around on the bamboo boots.</info>

<speak who="HERMES"><info>(SHOUTING)</info>
Don't mind us!</speak>

<info>The start to go off balance and one of the bamboo legs knocks 
Bender's cigar out of his hand. It spins through the air and 
sets fire to the tapestry. Other things catch on fire too.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
The loot! The loot! The loot is on fire!</speak>

<speak who="ZAPP">
Leela! My precious rock tub! I'll save 
you!</speak>

<info>He runs towards her but gets caught in a Spiderian web.</info>

<speak who="KIF">
Everyone! To the fire door!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It's on fire!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
We're trapped my sweet hippopotamus!</speak>

<info>Amid the chaos Fry still finds time for a drink.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee 
coffee coffee coffee coffee!</speak>

<info>He drinks the rest of the jug and his heartbeat rapidly increases. 
It's his hundredth cup. He enters a slowed down bullet-time world 
� la The Matrix. He gazes around the room. A champagne cork slowly 
shoots out the top of a bottle. Outside, a hummingbird's wings 
beat slowly � la the hummingbird in Star Trek: Insurrection. 
Fry blows out the fire that has engulfed Leela's shoe, picks 
her up and carries her away. Hermes and Dwight are in mid-fall. 
Fry picks them up, throws them over his shoulder and carries 
them out. He carries a few more people out. Kif is slowly blowing 
out the fire on Bender's burning arm. Fry squeezes his cheeks 
and the flames go away. He puts Bender, Kif and Amy onto the 
sofa with everyone else and wheels it out into the alley through 
the fire door. He picks up a fire extinguisher and quickly puts 
out the flames.</info>

<info>Cut to: Outside Silk Surplus Reception. Everyone looks around, 
wondering where they are.</info>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
Where are we pops?</speak>

<speak who="WOMAN">
What happened to the food?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I think we were saved by a mysterious 
orange blur.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Welcome one and all. I finally figured 
out how money could make me happy! By 
using it to buy my hungry friends a 
feast!</speak>

<info>Behind him the hobos cheer.</info>

<speak who="HOBO #2">
Everyone join us. Oysters rockafeller 
here has provided genuine turkey dogs!</speak>

<speak who="WHITEY">
Heck, you're never too rich to enjoy 
a free turkey dog!</speak>

<info>The rich people cheer.</info>

<speak who="WOMAN">
I'll take four!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Me too!</speak>

<speak who="MOM">
Oh what the hell!</speak>

<info>Everyone sits down and eats. Zoidberg puts a pack of Gobble 
Wieners on a barbecue.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Here Dwight, $299 and 99 cents. You 
invest this penny like you want it.</speak>

<speak who="DWIGHT">
Thanks Dad. I'm gonna take this and 
buy five shares of amazon.com!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
A risk taker? That's my boy!</speak>

<info>Poopenmeyer walks out of the building carrying Nixon's head.</info>

<speak who="NIXON">
The entire surplus has gone! What a 
muguvern I've been! Why did I have to 
issue that crooked tax rebate?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
At least we got a few mildly interesting 
stories out of it.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh my yes!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Speaking of which, my story kinda peetered 
out without me learning a lesson!</speak>

<info>He laughs. Enter Smitty and URL.</info>

<speak who="SMITTY">
There he is!</speak>

<info>Bender panics. They grab him and bash him with their lightsabers.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
All right! Closure!</speak>

<info>THE END</info>
</xml>