<xml><episodeInfo>FUTURAMA

Episode 513

<title>BEND HER</title>

<author>Mike Rowe</author>
<transcriber>Dave, The Neutral Planet</transcriber>
</episodeInfo>
<info>Opening Credits. Caption: Too Hot For Radio.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden. It's Earth's 3004 Olympic Games (Plus Opening 
Act). Crowds cheer as an athlete carrying the Olympic torch runs 
up the steps to light the Olympic flame. He opens a hatch in 
the side, ignites the pilot light and turns the flame up like 
a hotplate. The crowds cheer.</info>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Stands. Farnsworth, Fry, Leela, 
Amy, Bender and Zoidberg watch the games.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
So who should I root for? America or 
one of those countries I learned about 
at the Food Court?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
How 'bout those guys?</speak>

<info>On the track some people dressed in stripy jerseys and French 
berrets and carrying loaves of long bread wave to the crowd.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
No, they're from the Republic Of French 
Stereotypes. Everybody hates them.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh, let's go check on Hermes. All this 
inspiring multi-culturalism is angrying 
up my blood.  Sweden? I don't think 
so!</speak>

<info>He snatches the banner from them and rips it to shreads.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Training Room. Hermes limbos under a limbo 
stick.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Go on stick, touch me! Can't do it!</speak>

<info>The limbo stick is about 5 and a half feet off the ground. The 
four crew members and LaBarbara are gathered around.</info>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
Husband, you haven't been an Olympic 
class limboer for 20 years! Quit lying 
to your podgy self.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
It does seem like Jamaica will be able 
to field a strong limbo team without 
you.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yeah, isn't that basically all Jamaicans 
do?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Jamaicans have other interests. Which 
is why the limbo team got detained at 
the airport.</speak>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
That's when they begged my husband to 
step in and make an ass out of himself.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
And I said I'd try my very best.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But have they seen your...y'know...physique, 
since the old days?</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
I described it to them on the phone, 
using a series of artful euphanisms.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth holds a red and blue jumpsuit.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Don't worry, the fat pig will do fine 
thanks to this flabbo-dynamic spandex 
bodysuit I've designed.  It redistributes 
his weight, shifting his centre of gravity 
closer to his knees.</speak>

<info>The bodysuit contracts around Hermes' waist and his flab equals 
out underneath it.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Ooo, that's snug!  Oh, those haven't 
descended in years.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Now that's a limboer's body!</speak>

<info>Everyone cheers.</info>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
You're that fine Jamaican bacon!</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Stands. Bender and Zoidberg watch some competitors 
warm up on the field. All is quiet between the two.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Shut up Zoidberg, the robot bending 
events are starting!  Something tells 
me I could easily beat those trained 
professionals.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Field. A crane drops an unbendable 
girder into the hands of a robot. And another. The robot bends 
it around.</info>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Stands. Bender gasps as he watches.</info>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Field. The robot holds up the bent 
girders.</info>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Stands.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Wow, that guy must have to be like the 
world's greatest bender. My dreams of 
glory died before they began.</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Welcome to my life!</speak>

<info>He bursts into tears.</info>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Track.</info>

<info>On the track the limboers warm up. A tall athlete takes his 
lane next to Hermes'.</info>

<speak who="BARBADOS SLIM">
Hermes Conrad. Is that you inside that 
dumpy little fat man?</speak>

<info>Hermes gasps.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Barbados Slim! What are you doing here? 
Last time I heard you were in Barbados.</speak>

<speak who="BARBADOS SLIM">
Yes and I'll be going back there with 
a gold medal draped around my elegant 
Carribean shoulders.</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
Your body may be as perfectly scultpted 
as it was 20 years ago when you whupped 
my fat ass every time we met......but 
today, I feel lucky.</speak>

<info>The hood squashes his hair flat and then into a rounded point.</info>

<speak who="BARBADOS SLIM">
I see you're still able to limbo under 
the bar of fashion sense!</speak>

<info>He laughs.</info>

<speak who="HERMES">
That's it Barbados Slim, you've gone 
one talk over the line!</speak>

<speak who="STARTER">
Limboers, on your marks, get rubbery......limbo!</speak>

<info>He shoots the starter gun and the limboers run off down the 
track and under the limbo sticks.</info>

<speak who="COMMENTATOR">
<info>(voice-over)</info> There they go, and Barbados 
Slim takes an early lead. God I hope 
he wins.  What's this? Hermes Conrad 
is closing the gap. He's limboed out 
of retirement and straight into my heart. 
I say go to hell Barbados Slim!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Stands. The crew and LaBarbara watch 
and cheer and hold up a banner reading "You The Mon."</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(shouting)</info> Go bodysuit, go!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
<info>(shouting)</info> Go!</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(shouting)</info> C'mon!</speak>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
<info>(shouting)</info> C'mon Hermes, beat that mahogany 
god!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Track. Hermes closes in on Barbados 
Slim as they approach the last limbo stick.</info>

<speak who="COMMENTATOR">
<info>(voice-over)</info> It's Barbados, then Conrad. 
Conrad pulls ahead!  And Conrad is disqualified! 
Barbados Slim, my hero, takes the gold!</speak>

<info>LaBarbara runs to Hermes' side.</info>

<speak who="LABARBARA">
Aww, there there Hermes.  You did your 
best! If I'd wanted a human Adonis for 
a husband, I'd have stayed married to 
Barbados Slim.</speak>

<info>Cut to: Madison Cube Garden Stands. Disappointed, the crew sit 
down.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Well enough about Hermes, I couldn't 
win a medal either. Even at bending 
- the thing I was built to do. I'm so 
embarassed. I wish everybody else was 
dead.</speak>

<speak who="FEMALE ANNOUNCER">
Up next, the Fembot bending competition.</speak>

<info>On the field Fembots bend coathangers.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Fembots?  Methinks a clever Manbot suitably 
disguised might win those events! But 
the charade would require subtlety, 
nuance, grace.</speak>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Olympic Officials Stand. The officials look 
for Bender's entry form. He is dressed in a dress and a headscarf, 
trying to look like a Fembot.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
What do you mean I'm not registered? 
My name is Coilette and I'm from, uh...Robonia! 
Coilette's a chick's name!</speak>

<speak who="OFFICIAL">
Yes but "Robonia" sounds like something 
somebody made up on the spot.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Ever been beaten up by a guy dressed 
like a chick?</speak>

<info>The official squirms and hands Bender a card.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Field. "Coilette" the Fembot from the Grand 
Duchy Of Robonia prepares for the competition. A whistle blows. 
Bender bends a bent girder. A man puts a protractor to it and 
gives a thumbs up.</info>

<speak who="MALE ANNOUNCER">
And it's straight! Coilette wins!</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Bender has now entered the javelin event. He runs 
with the javelin, stops, bends it, throws it and watches it fly 
across the field. It is the farthest thrown.</info>

<speak who="MALE ANNOUNCER">
Another gold medal for the spunky maid 
from Robonia.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. In what looks to be a diving competition Bender 
stands at the end of a girder shaped diving board. The beeper 
beeps and he dives off the end, grabs the girder and bends it 
as he falls.</info>

<speak who="MALE ANNOUNCER">
A perfect bend and a flawless entry. 
No splash at all!  Perfect scores, a 
record five gold medals for Coilette!</speak>

<info>Bender flips onto his feet and cheers.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I'm great! Everybody else sucks, except 
that guy Bender, he's really somethin'!</speak>

<info>He cheers.</info>

<info>Bender screams.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Tunnel. Farnsworth, Fry, Leela and Amy stand 
around the still disguised Bender.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
You actually thought they'd let you 
walk away without an engine oil sex 
check?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(crying)</info> Oh God, I'm not gonna get my 
medals! They're all I have to remember 
my Olympic career.  Wait, I've got it! 
Professor, make a woman out of me!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh I think we should just stay friends.</speak>

<info>He pats Bender's hand.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
I don't need friends, I need a sex change 
operation and give it to me now!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Bender a robot sex change is a complex 
and dangerous procedure. Replacing your 
testosteroil with Fembot lubricants 
can cause wild mood swings. And the 
effects may be irreversible. Well let's 
get started!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No, you can't!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
If you have even the slightest respect 
for the dignity of women -</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Pfft.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
I'm sorry ladies but I must do this. 
Not for you, not for Bender, but for 
the proud people of Robonia!</speak>

<info>Outside Robot Medical Tent. Three robots line up outside for 
treatment. One has been impaled on a fencing sword, another has 
been impaled with five javelins and another has been impaled 
on a tennis racket. Bender holds up the side of the tent and 
ushers Farnsworth, Fry and Leela inside. He gets impatient.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
<info>(whispering)</info> C'mon!</speak>

<info>Cut to: Robot Medical Tent. Bender lies down on an operating 
table.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I can't watch this 'cause it's creepy 
and wrong and sick. However I will watch 
out of curiosity.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(shouting)</info> Quiet! <info>(talking)</info> I'm about 
to begin the process of reshaping Bender's 
body into a tender delicate form.</speak>

<info>He starts hitting Bender's casing with a sledgehammer. His shadow 
is cast on the wall and Bender cries out in pain.</info>

<info>Time Lapse. Farnsworth jacks Bender's head up. He puts a spanner 
between Bender's legs.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
<info>(dramatically)</info> Draining male oil.  Infusing 
female oil.  Removing item.</speak>

<info>He holds the shears around Bender's antenna. Fry ringes as Bender's 
antenna is snipped off.</info>

<info>Robot Gender Testing. A robot and a Fembot wait for Coilette.</info>

<speak who="ROBOT">
We can't wait for Coilette any longer 
dammit. I have to get home to watch 
The Zombie Osbournes.</speak>

<info>A curtain draws back and Coilette walks out of the Robot Medical 
Tent.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
I'm ready for my test now boys.</speak>

<info>The robots' jaws drop - off.</info>

<info>Madison Cube Garden Field. The winner's podiums have been set 
up and Coilette stands wearing five gold medals. She looks like 
your run of the mill ordinary trannybot. Brown hair, slim figure, 
alarming amount of lipstick. She sings the Robonian national 
anthem.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(singing)</info> Hail, hail Robonia, a land 
I didn't make up!</speak>

<info>The crowd cheers and bouquets of flowers are thrown.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The crew watch Coilette cheering on 
the podium. She does a victory dance and takes her top off.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE"><info>ON TV</info>
Ooo yeah c'mon baby boom!</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Oh yeah baby c'mon! Work your can! That's 
it shake it out!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I don't know which I'm more, enraged 
or disgusted!</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
I'm just out there making us ladies 
look good.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Snuh-uh! You're making us look like 
jerks in front of the other genders.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
But you're not really a lady anyway. 
Right?</speak>

<info>He puts a glass of water on the table.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Of course not.</speak>

<info>She puts Fry's glass on a coaster.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Dear Lord, a coaster! The Femzoil must 
be sacheting girlishly into your processor.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Then change me back. My breasts are 
keeping me awake at night anyway.  Hello...? 
What...? A guest spot on Late Night 
With Humorbot 5.0...? I'd love to!  
My own limo...? No I don't have my own 
limo. You'd better send one.  I need 
a raincheck on that nad-swap Professor. 
I'm going on TV. C'mon Fry help me pick 
out a pantsuit!</speak>

<info>Late Night With Humorbot 5.0 Studio. The studio looks like the 
studio for The Tonight Show With Jay Leno. The audience are all 
robots. Humorbot 5.0 speaks with his usual mechanical voice and 
interviews a popular soap star.</info>

<speak who="HUMORBOT 5">.0
So Calculon, do you want to set up this 
clip from All My Circuits?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
No I think it's self-explanatory.</speak>

<info>A screen comes up behind them and they turn to face it. On the 
screen a pirate barbecues some stuff and Calculon gives a dramatic 
performance.</info>

<info>In the studio the audience applaud and stop instantly.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Funny story, the script called for me 
to say "yes" but I gave it a little 
twist.</speak>

<speak who="HUMOUBOT 5">.0
Anecdote accepted. Snappy comeback not 
found. Please put your hands together 
for my next guest. Winner of five Olympic 
medals - Coilette from Robonia.  So 
Coilette, many young Fembot's wish to 
emulate you. Any advice for them?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Yes Humorbot. If you ask me, women today 
are too stuck up to go out and jiggle 
their jello like everybody wants them 
to. In fact, should I do it now?  Alright 
then!  Woo! Look out baby! Work it out! 
Oo shake that thing! You gotta use it 
lady! Shake it up a little! Look at 
that! C'mon! Work it out!</speak>

<info>The audience cheers and Calculon is impressed.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Madam, I am one impressed celebrity.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Oh I bet you say that to all the five 
Olympic gold medal winning Fembots!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
<info>(sexfully)</info> From this day forward I shall 
do so whenever possible.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Golly...what?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Coilette this may be presumtuous....</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
That's my favourite kind of this!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
...but I would be honoured if you would 
join me for dinner sometime.</speak>

<info>The audience hoot.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Calculon. You'd be fulfilling this naive 
Robonian farmgirl's fantasy!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Of course I would.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Locker Area. Coilette stands in front of a locker 
admiring herself in a mirror. She is dressed in pink Fembot clothes. 
The crew are gathered around.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
This top makes me look fat. Is it trampy 
to go on a first date nude?</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Yes.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Perfect.</speak>

<info>She takes the top off.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
You gotta tell me. You're not actually 
attracted to Calculon right? And if 
you are don't tell me. Are you?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Certainly not. But just once I'd like 
to eat dinner with a celebrity who isn't 
bound and gagged. Is that so much to 
ask?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well I think you dating a Manbot is 
a disgrace. And I refuse to be involved. 
And you have way too much lipstick on.</speak>

<info>Amy nods.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Are you kidding? I need more lipstick! 
Much more!  Ooo yeah that's the stuff! 
Men love it when you really glob it 
on!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
No they don't.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No way!</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Oh please. Every man wants a tramp! 
No wonder you girls aren't married! 
I tell you, men are so much better 
at being women.</speak>

<info>She puts some earrings on using a nailgun.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
But what if he wants to, I mean if he 
tries to...uh...Barry White?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
I'll just tell him I needed commitment 
first. That'll stick a potato in his 
tailpipe!</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Good Lord man what kind of temporary 
woman are you?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Look, why don't all of you just back 
off? Can't a girl enjoy herself without 
being judged?</speak>

<info>She takes her handbag, slams the locker door and storms off.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Oh dear. Her mood swings are getting 
wilder. She's becoming a slave to her 
emotions. Just like all women, particularly 
you Leela.</speak>

<info>She slaps him.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
I'm worried about him too Professor.</speak>

<info>Elzar's Fine Cuisine. Tonight's special is leg of salmon. Coilette 
chomps her way through a leg.</info>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Hey ma'am, you sure can put it away! 
You saved me a trip to the dump! Bam!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
I'd appreciate it if you didn't bam 
the young lady.</speak>

<speak who="ELZAR">
Well, I'd appreciate it if I did, so 
I guess we're even.</speak>

<info>He leaves.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
You know Coilette, I've never before 
met a woman as fascinating as I am. 
You're such a sweet, soft Fembot. And 
you have this free spirit about you. 
And there it is. It's as if you understand 
the male mind better than I!  I've never 
met anyone like you.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Oh yes you have.</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Coilette. I'd like to spend some <info>(whispering)</info> 
quality time with you.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
What? Ahh! Whoa, no way! Not gonna happen. 
What kind of girl do you think I am?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Have I mentioned that I own the world's 
biggest and most elegant yacht?</speak>

<info>Coilette's eyes light up.</info>

<info>Montage Coilette and Calculon date to Tom Jones' She's A Lady. 
They enjoy a trip on his yacht Calculon's Pride which sails on 
a pool on an even larger yacht called Calculon's Talent. They 
dance under a mirrorball. Calculon swings Coilette around and 
her arms extend and she knocks all the other robots over. They 
sit in an oil hot tub and their photo appears on the cover Famous 
Actor And Athlete Couples Illustrated magazine.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. The crew feed scraps to a begging Zoidberg. 
Enter Coilette.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Woo! I'm a trophy girlfriend!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
No kidding. These gifts have been coming 
non-stop!  I think Calculon's falling 
for you.</speak>

<info>The puppies bark and Coilette throws her hat down and puts her 
coat over the top of them.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Bah. Any day now he'll dump me for a 
new wad of arm candy. And then I can 
turn back into a guy and hock all this 
stuff! It's just a game.</speak>

<info>Amy and Leela glare at him. Enter Calculon via the wall.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Coilette, I can't stop thinking about 
you. I can't sleep at night - although 
as a robot I don't do that anyway. But 
if I did I couldn't because I love you 
so.  Oh my darling......Will you marry 
me?</speak>

<info>Coilette looks up at the gobsmacked crew.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Oh Calculon, yes I will!</speak>

<info>Calculon puts the ring on her finger. Amy nudges Leela.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
<info>(whispering)</info> Maybe she's right about 
the lipstick.</speak>

<info>Time Lapse. Calculon is gone and Coilette is preparing to leave.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
I'll miss you buddy. You've been like 
a brother and then a sister to me. And 
now you're getting married. I love you.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
The marriage is a scam.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Cool. What's for dinner?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
What do you mean a scam?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
I marry Calculon, divorce him, take 
half his money and turn back into a 
guy. It's sort of a two-person pyramid 
scheme.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
That's marriage alright!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
That is so unbelievably manipulative.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Come on, you never went on a date with 
a guy just 'cause you were hungry?</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Well I...uh...I thought I might like 
him on a full stomach.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Nice try sister. Now if you'll excuse 
me, I need to meet with my wedding planner. 
<info>(shouting)</info> Zoidberg.  <info>(talking)</info> Zoidypoo, 
please tell me frilly is in this year.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg flips through a catalogue.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I saw a frilly cake in here you would 
remember all your life. I know I will. 
Late at night it haunts me with it's 
frosted beauty. <info>(shouting)</info> Order the 
cake dammit!</speak>

<info>Hot Air Balloon. Calculon and Coilette enjoy a day together.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
I have something for you.</speak>

<info>He hands her a remote control.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
A remote control? You got me a TV?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
No my dearest, it's the remote control 
to my heart! It symbolises the power 
you have to sway my emotions.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Will it work on my TV?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
We don't need TVs, we have each other! 
Coilette if I weren't able to spend 
my life with you I would leap from this 
very balloon.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Come on now - really?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Yes! We were meant <info>(dramatically)</info> to 
be!</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
So...you really and truly love me?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
So much so that I'm prepared to give 
up showbusiness itself to be with you!</speak>

<info>Coilette gasps.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
But, you always said you'd rather burn 
down a convent than give up showbusiness.</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
I always said many things. But now all 
I want is a peaceful life and a quiet 
villa overlooking a vineyard....with 
you.</speak>

<info>Coilette starts to cry.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(crying)</info> Would we have donkeys?</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
All you can eat!</speak>

<info>She hugs him.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(crying)</info> Oh take me in your arms and 
compress me. Compress me tight!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Stop! Let us climb to the heavens that 
the gods themselves might embrace!</speak>

<info>He picks up Boxy and throws him out of the balloon. The balloon 
climbs into the sky.</info>

<info>Planet Express: Lounge. Coilette sits at the table crying. The 
crew are sat around.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(crying)</info> I just don't think I can go 
through with this scam.</speak>

<info>The crew gasp.</info>

<speak who="AMY">
What?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
So now you do wanna marry him?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(crying)</info> No, I just don't wanna hurt 
him, or humiliate him. Oh, curse this 
woman's heart!</speak>

<info>She cries more.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Eck!</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
You're falling into the final debilitating 
stages of womanhood. You've waited too 
long to switch back you dingbat!</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
OK look. If I help you with this do 
you promise to get out of my gender 
and stay out?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
<info>(crying)</info> Uh-huh.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Alright. Now there's no way to stop 
this marriage without hurting Calculon. 
But he's an actor. If there's one kind 
of pain he can handle, it's soap opera 
pain.</speak>

<info>Outside Church. Above the church doors is a banner reading "Celebrity 
Wedding. Ordinary People Not Invited." Farnsworth walks Coilette 
up the aisle and a little robot carries her train. At the back 
of the crowd are Fry, Hermes, Amy, Zoidberg and Leela. Fry is 
dressed in a hat and sleeveless jacket, Zoidberg is kitted out 
in medical scrubs and Leela wears a blonde wig and a dress. She 
puts a sunglass over her eye.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
<info>(whispering)</info> OK, is everyone ready?</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Yep.</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Uh-huh.</speak>

<speak who="HERMES">
Check!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Impassively.</speak>

<info>They split and Zoidberg scuttles off and woops. At the front 
the ceremony begins.</info>

<speak who="PREACHERBOT">
Dearly beloved actors and casting people 
who may be looking for somebody to play 
a preacher, I welcome you! The bride 
has written some vows that we will now 
all pretend to be interested in.</speak>

<info>Coilette and Calculon turn to each other.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Dearest Calculon. Forever is not enough 
time to tell you of the many ways I 
love you.</speak>

<info>She faints theatrically. The crowd gasps.</info>

<speak who="HEDONISMBOT">
Oh my!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Is there a doctor in the -</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
I came as soon as I could.  It appears 
to be a case of African Hydraulic Fever!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Dear God! The very illness my TV character 
caught in season two, when I was holding 
out for more money! It's often fatal.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Whatever happens, remember, the flame 
of my eternal love will burn forever.</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Of course. But smoochiepups, I thought 
one could only catch hydraulic fever 
deep in the diamond mines of the Congo.</speak>

<info>Leela calls out from the crowd.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
Coilette! You she-devil!  You really 
thought you could steal those diamonds 
from me and Congo Jack?</speak>

<info>Coilette stands up.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Those gems belong to the natives!</speak>

<info>Leela kicks Coilette in the face and Amy restrains her.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Oh how cruel and melodramatic fate is. 
<info>(dramatically shouting)</info> Whhhy?</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Calculon, my darling, your loud "why" 
brought me partway back to life.  Congo 
Jack!</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
Another shocking twist!</speak>

<info>Hermes plays some shocking twist music.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yes. And I have a message for you from 
Colonel Mitumba! He says this......is 
from Congo Jack.</speak>

<info>He throws the spear. It hits a flower pot.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Uh, um...</speak>

<info>She takes it out of the flower pot and tucks it under her arm, 
screams, and falls over.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON">
No! Nooo! <info>(dramamtically shouting)</info> N-O-O-O!</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
I won't leave you. Not until I'm sure 
you understand the thing I said before. 
About my eternal love for you burning......et 
cetera.</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
<info>(crying)</info> I do. I do.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
OK then.</speak>

<info>She dies in a very dramatic and soapy way. At the back Zoidberg 
eats what is left of the buffet.</info>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG"><info>EATING</info>
I'm a doctor, she's dead.</speak>

<speak who="CALCULON">
She lives no more. But let us all find 
comfort knowing that she truly loved 
me. To honour my pain, I shall star 
in a film dedicated to her memory. And 
this time the Academy will not deny 
me. Not when they see Coilette: A Calculon 
Story.</speak>

<info>Planet Express: Farnsworth's Lab. The crew watch Calculon's 
film on TV. The Coilette character is lying dead with Calculon 
at her side. In the background Preacherbot waves.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON"><info>ON TV</info>
Coilette. Your death fills me wih sorrow, 
<info>(angry)</info> anger, <info>(fearful)</info> fear, <info>(normal)</info> 
every emotion an actor can display.</speak>

<info>Farnsworth files away the last bit of hair from Coilette's head.</info>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Turn off that crap-o-rama! One mistake 
now and Bender will be trapped forever 
between the already ill-defined robot 
sexes.</speak>

<info>He chisels something between Coilette's legs.</info>

<speak who="COILETTE">
Ow, oo, ow.</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Well Bender, I hope this has taught 
you a lesson about changing your sex 
to win five gold medals.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
It truly has. My romance with Calculon 
has shown me a lot about myself.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Almost done.</speak>

<speak who="COILETTE">
If only somehow, someway he and I could...</speak>

<info>Bender's antenna springs up.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
...drive to Vegas, pick up some Flooziebots 
and void their warranties all night 
long!</speak>

<info>He sits up and cheers.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
Yay my buddy's home! And his respect 
for women is back to normal.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
I kind of hope this whole experience 
would have left you a little more open 
to your sensitive side.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah you'd think but what you gonna 
do?</speak>

<info>He takes a puff from a cigar. On the TV it is raining and Calculon 
holds Coilette in his arms..</info>

<speak who="CALCULON"><info>ON TV</info>
Coilette, the skies themselves weep 
upon the sweetest flower of all the 
field.</speak>

<speak who="LEELA">
Aww!</speak>

<speak who="AMY">
Aww!</speak>

<speak who="FRY">
Eww!</speak>

<speak who="ZOIDBERG">
Gross.</speak>

<speak who="FARNSWORTH">
Sentimental drivel-poop.</speak>

<info>Zoidberg, Farnsworth and Hermes leave.</info>

<speak who="FRY">
C'mon Bender let's go. This chick flick 
is getting me all barfy.</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
Yeah. Emotions are dumb and should be 
hated.</speak>

<info>Fry leaves and he starts out after him. He stops and looks at 
the TV.</info>

<speak who="CALCULON"><info>ON TV</info>
Goodnight Coilette, my turtledove.</speak>

<info>Bender's eyes well up with tears.</info>

<speak who="BENDER">
Goodnight Calculon.</speak>

<info>Amy and Leela turn around.</info>

<speak who="LEELA">
What did you say?</speak>

<speak who="BENDER">
I said you two don't dress trampy enough. 
I still got it!</speak>

<info>He twangs his antenna.</info>

<info>THE END</info></xml>