<xml><metadata><artist>Bessie Smith</artist><title> Backwater Blues Version 1</title>
<songInfo>by 
Bessie
Smith

recording of February(?) 17 1927, New York City

from 
The
Complete Recordings, Vol. 3 (Columbia/Legacy
C2K-47474)
,


</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



When it rains five days and the skies turn dark as night

When it rains five days and the skies turn dark as night

Then trouble's takin' place in the lowlands at night



I woke up this mornin', can't even get out of my door

I woke up this mornin', can't even get out of my door

There's been enough trouble to make a poor girl wonder where she want
to go



Then they rowed a little boat about five miles 'cross the pond

Then they rowed a little boat about five miles 'cross the pond

I packed all my clothes, throwed them in and they rowed me along



When it thunders and lightnin' and when the wind begins to blow

When it thunders and lightnin' and the wind begins to blow

There's thousands of people ain't got no place to go



Then I went and stood upon some high old lonesome hill

Then I went and stood upon some high old lonesome hill

Then looked down on the house were I used to live



Backwater
1
 blues done call me to pack my things and go

Backwater blues done call me to pack my things and go

'Cause my house fell down and I can't live there no more



Mmm, I can't move no more

Mmm, I can't move no more

There ain't no place for a poor old girl to go



__________

Note: This was one of her most successful records; it was recorded
just before the catastrophic 
great
Mississippi flood of 1927
;

Note 1: backwater, mostly old river beds which are left to take the
excess flood water to relieve pressure on the 
levees

(embankments). As the height of the water is excessive, however,
breaches in the levee walls are deliberately made at certain points
to allow particular areas to flood and thus lessen the pressure of
water. These are the "backwaters," which occur in the St. Francis
Basin to the west of the river between 
Memphis

and Helena, in the great 
Yazoo-Mississippi
Delta
 north of 
Vicksburg
,
in the Tensas Basin west of 
Natchez
,
and at other selected points.





































</lyrics></xml>
