<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>B.B. King</artist><title> Better Not Look Down</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Will
Jennings
 </name><name> 
Joe
Sample

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1978</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
King
Of The Blues 4 CD Box Set (MCA
MCAD4-10677)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>I've been around and I've seen some things

</l>
<l>People moving faster than the speed of sound

</l>
<l>Faster than the speeding bullet

</l>
<l>People living like Superman

</l>
<l>All day and all night

</l>
<l>And I won't say if it's wrong or if it's right

</l>
<l>I'm pretty fast myself

</l>
<l>But I do have some advice to pass along

</l>
<l>Along in the chorus of this song



</l>
<l>Better not look down, if you want to keep on flying

</l>
<l>Put the hammer down, keep it full speed ahead

</l>
<l>Better not look back, or you might just wind up crying

</l>
<l>You can keep it moving, if you don't look down



</l>
<l>An old girl friend of mine showed up the other day

</l>
<l>That girl have lived in love and for love,

</l>
<l>and over love, and under love all her life

</l>
<l>If the arrows from cupid's bow that had

</l>
<l>passed through her heart had been sticking

</l>
<l>Out of her body she would have looked like a porcupine,

</l>
<l>And she asked me "B.B. do you think I've lived my life all
wrong?"

</l>
<l>And I said: "The only advice I have to pass

</l>
<l>along in the chorus of this song", girl



</l>
<l>Better not look down, if you want to keep on flying

</l>
<l>Put the hammer down, keep it full speed ahead

</l>
<l>Better not look back, or you might just wind up crying

</l>
<l>You can keep it moving, if you don't look down



</l>
<l>I was walking down the street at sunrise one morning, in London,
England

</l>
<l>And there was a very large Rolls Royce limousine,

</l>
<l>pulling slowly along the street

</l>
<l>And in that Rolls Royce was the queen of England, looking tired

</l>
<l>Just go back from a party, and the queen leaned out and,

</l>
<l>she said: "Aren't you B.B. King?"

</l>
<l>She said: "Oh B.B., sometimes it's so hard to pull things
together.

</l>
<l>Could you tell me what you think I ought to do?"

</l>
<l>And I said:



</l>
<l>Better not look down, if you want to keep on flying

</l>
<l>Put the hammer down, keep it full speed ahead

</l>
<l>Better not look back, or you might just wind up crying

</l>
<l>You can keep it moving, if you don't look down



</l>
<l>Better not look down, if you want to keep on flying

</l>
<l>Put the hammer down, keep it full speed ahead

</l>
<l>Better not look back, or you might just wind up crying

</l>
<l>You can keep it moving, if you don't look down</l></lyrics></xml>