<xml><metadata><artist>Albert King</artist><title> Blues Power</title>
<songInfo>by 
Albert
King

recording of 19

from 
The
Best Of Albert King (Stax 60-005 or Fantasy
60005)
, 
</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



(Spoken:

This is blues power!



Well



Play it now)



Ev'rybody understands the blues

Are you listening?

YEAH! #91;audience replies#93;



I say ev'rybody understands the blues

Ev'rybody from one day to another has the blues



You take the little baby that's layin' in the cradle

He can't get that milk bottle fast enough

He go to kickin' an'cryin'

An' goin' on, tearin' up the little baby bed

He got the blues

Can ya dig it?

YEAH! #91;audience replies#93;

Ha, ha, ha



You take this girl that's got this main squeeze

That's her boyfriend, that is, you know



An' he just bought a brand new GTO

You know she wanna be wit' him ev'rytime he cranks it up

An' go around the corner to the soda fountain

This is where she wanna go an'show it off

Where all the girls and guys be

You know what I mean?



An' she get ready to go out this particular night

An' her mother say, "Daughter you was just out last night

You can't go out tonight, that's too many nights in a row"



She go in the room an'fasten the door

An' won't answer the phone, won't eat

Won't talk to nobody

She got the blues

That's what's wrong wit' her



Some people call them the reds, the pinks

When ya get through

It's the old-fashioned country blues

That's right



I haven't seen my main squeeze

In ten long weeks, today

You know I got the blues

Can you dig it? ha, ha, ha

YEAH! #91;Audience replies#93;



Woo! Alright!



Ah but wait, I don't think you're with me

Let's ev'rybody get a thing goin' right here

Yes, yes, yes



Can you feel it?

YEAH!

I can't hear you, can you feel it?

YEAH!

Yes, yes

Sounds awful good, keep it, keep it, right there chilin'

Keep it right there, ha ha ha ha



The blues!

An' when you're doin' the blues

They so strong, that's the reason there named

They call 'em blues power, yeah



An' would you believe I invented blues power?

YEAH!

Ha, ha

Can you dig the blues power?

YEAH!

Let ev'rybody say "yeah"

YEAH!

Say it again, say "yeah"

YEAH!



Alright! Alright! Hey! Hey! Hey! Oh! Alright

Ha, ha, ha! Well! Woo! Ha, ha, ha! Oh man! Hey!

Ooh-oh!

Woo!



Thank you!

Thank you very much!

Thank you very kindly!

Woo!







































</lyrics></xml>
