<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Broke</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Albert
Collins

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1983</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Don't
Lose Your Cool (Alligator ALCD-4730)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>I used to be a big shot long ago

</l>
<l>I had a Cadillac an' a whole lotta dough

</l>
<l>Real fine women used to chase me down

</l>
<l>Now, not one-a those gals can be found

</l>
<l>They're never home whenever I call

</l>
<l>Don't seem to want me around at all



</l>
<l>I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke

</l>
<l>Stone-cold broke, I ain't got a lousy dime



</l>
<l>Went to a nightclub an' had my fun

</l>
<l>Shuckin' an' 
jivin'
wit' </l>
<l>ev'ryone

</l>
<l>Drinkin' that beer an' gin an' wine

</l>
<l>Boy, I'm tellin' ya I had a good time

</l>
<l>When I got home I didn't have no loot

</l>
<l>Had to go down an' pawn my suit



</l>
<l>I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke (ha-ha)

</l>
<l>Stone-cold broke, I ain't got a lousy dime



</l>
<l>Now, I'm a low-down dirty bum

</l>
<l>Right back where I started from

</l>
<l>I got no car, I got no gal

</l>
<l>I ain't even got a pal

</l>
<l>Huffin' an' puffin' can't raise a cent

</l>
<l>Put me out, I can't pay my rent



</l>
<l>I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke, I'm broke

</l>
<l>Stone-cold broke, I ain't got a lousy dime



</l>
<l>(Spoken:

</l>
<l>"Damn, I'm broke man, I got no damn money"



</l>
<l>"What n' the hell am I gonna do now?"



</l>
<l>"Oh hey, Jim, what's happenin' man?"



</l>
<l>"Oh man, I'm sure glad to see you!"



</l>
<l>"Yeah, I know I owe you twenty dollars man,

</l>
<l>but you know hey, look it"



</l>
<l>"Well you know they picked up my car up this mornin'?"



</l>
<l>"What?" (hm, a-ha)



</l>
<l>"You know they say a man ain't suppose to cry?"



</l>
<l>"Man, I'm gonna tell ya, you know that they didn't lie"



</l>
<l>"Ay, I, I, I'm broke man, I swear I'm broke"



</l>
<l>"Ha, I ain't had, man I ain't got it, I got about two dollars, man

that's it"




</l>
<l>"Ha, swear I'm broke man"



</l>
<l>"Hm yeah, yeah I'm broke, yeah"



</l>
<l>Fading:

</l><l>"Trust me I'm broke, man, yeah I am")</l></lyrics></xml>