<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Big Maceo Merriweather</artist><title> Can't You Read</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Big
Maceo Merriweather

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of<dateRange> <date>1941</date>-<date>1942</date></dateRange>

</recordDate><album>from 
Bluebird
Recordings 1941-1942 (RCA 66715)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Way back in the nineteen hundred and ten

</l>
<l>The monkey and the baboon, they came walkin' in

</l>
<l>The monkey told the baboon, "Let's shoot a game a pool"

</l>
<l>The monkey could shoot, but the baboon wasn't no fool



</l>
<l>Next thing came along was a little mule

</l>
<l>He said, "You know I'm so mad, I even can't wear no shoe"

</l>
<l>Next thing came along, there was Mr. Cat

</l>
<l>"We ain't gonna have no such a-stuff goin' on here like that"

</l>
<l>Next thing came, was a little mouse,

</l>
<l>"Let's all get drunk an' break up this doggone house"



</l>
<l>Can't you read, now can't you read

</l>
<l>If you keep on readin' I'm bound to put you out



</l>
<l>Well, the monkey an' the elephant, they went out for a little
drive

</l>
<l>The elephant hit the monkey right square in his eye

</l>
<l>The monkey looked up with a tear an' a sigh

</l>
<l>Said, "Look at here big boy, you oughta get someone your size,

</l>
<l>One of these days I'm gonna climb your tree,

</l>
<l>Remember big boy you gotta march right under me"

</l>
<l>"When you march under me, you better march careful 'n fast,

</l>
<l>I'll get me a limb an' break it 'cross your...

1




</l>
<l>Now can't you read, now can't you read

</l>
<l>If you keep on readin', I'm bound to put you out



</l>
<l>If anybody just happen to ask you

</l>
<l>Where the weddin' gonna be?

</l>
<l>Come right down there on Hazen street

</l>
<l>Cold down there just about the end of the week

</l>
<l>You can get most anything that you care to eat

</l>
<l>If you don't like shrimp, just name your dish

</l>
<l>They'll even serve you some a that ol' fillet fish



</l>
<l>Now can't you read, now can't you read

</l>
<l>If you keep on reading, mama, I'm bound to put you out



</l>
<l>Yeah, play it Mr. Maceo! (piano)



</l>
<l>Well, fifteen cents you know that's the regular price

</l>
<l>If you got two fifteen, we'll even serve you twice

</l>
<l>Can't you read, now can't you read

</l>
<l>If you keep on reading, I'm bound to put you out



</l>

<note>Note: vocals by Big Maceo and Tampa Red;

Note 1: "The last line in the 3rd verse is missing a word at the end
on purpose. The word is "ass" but he doesn't sing it (rhymes with
fast) and I guess the listener is suppose to fill in the blank. Can
you imagine they didn't sing "bad words" back then?", Anita Cantor
a.k.a. Ooohwebaby.</note></lyrics></xml>