<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Cash Talkin' (The Workingman's Blues)</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Doug
MacLeod

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1986</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Cold
Snap (Alligator ALCD-4752)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>

<l>Well I walked down to my bank, just to see what I could see

</l>
<l>I asked the man behind the desk, I say "Ah, is there any money for
me?"

</l>
<l>Now he didn't know just what to say

</l>
<l>I say, "I need that money in a terrible way!"

</l>
<l>Now he didn't say "yeah" but he didn't say "no"

</l>
<l>He just shook my hand and showed me the door



</l>
<l>Oh Lord, the blues is killin' me

</l>
<l>Oh Lord, Lord, Lord, these blues is killin' me

</l>
<l>Yes sir



</l>
<l>Now my wife loves money and it bothers my mind

</l>
<l>She runs to the store and she buys, on time

</l>
<l>T.V's, radios, stereos and I got all kind a princess phones

</l>
<l>A one of these days, ya'all-a, I think they all gonna be gone



</l>
<l>My baby need clothes, my wife needs a car

</l>
<l>It's a wonder ya'all ha, I got this far! Hey!

</l>
<l>Landlord knockin', and he wants some rent

</l>
<l>Now I'm lookin' for the money that my wife just spent



</l>
<l>Oh Lord, um-hm, the blues is killin' me

</l>
<l>Oh Lord, Lord, Lord, these blues is killin' me

</l>
<l>Tellin' ya



</l>
<l>Tax time, ain't nothin' but a mess

</l>
<l>Payin' Uncle Sam more an' I'm gettin' less

</l>
<l>The po' stay po' and the rich stay rich

</l>
<l>An' I'm right here in the middle

</l>
<l>Now ain't that a.....!



</l>
<l>Barely gettin' by, makes me mean

</l>
<l>'Cause the politicians I'm payin', are livin' real clean

</l>
<l>Step down Mister Politician, and live like I do

</l>
<l>I want you to know, the workin' man blues



</l>
<l>Oh Lord, oh Lord, these blues is killin' me

</l>
<l>Oh Lord, Lord, Lord, these blues is killin' me



</l>
<l>Payin' these taxes worry me to death...



</l>
<l>Buyin' new T.V's an' radios an' stereos...



</l>
<l>Baby needs clothes...



</l>
<l>Wife need a old car to get around in...



</l>
<l>Oh it's a bitch bein' po'...



</l>
<l>I say it's a ___!
1
, bein' po...



</l>
<l>Fading:

</l>
<l>Now ain't that a bitch?

</l>
<l>(Boy it's rough, I'll tell ya)



</l>
<note>Note 1: ___ this is not a missing word, Albert just leaves out the
word, 'bitch' and bends a note to fill in instead of saying the
word</note></lyrics></xml>