<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>B.B. King</artist><title> Confessin' The Blues</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Walter
Brown
 </name><name> 
Jay
McShann

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1969</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
King
Of The Blues 4 CD Box Set (MCA
MCAD4-10677)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Yeah, here I stand before you with my heart in my hand

</l>
<l>I want you to great it baby, hopin' that you'll understand

</l>
<l>I said baby, honey please don't dog me around

</l>
<l>Because I'd rather love you woman, honey than anyone else I know in

town




</l>
<l>Because you're so nice and lovely and you have such pleasant ways

</l>
<l>If you take to your heart I'll be there the rest of my days

</l>
<l>I said baby, that's the truth

</l>
<l>Honey, I declare I wouldn't lie

</l>
<l>Because I gotta love you baby

</l>
<l>If I don't, I swear I hope I die



</l>
<l>Oh baby, don't you want a man like me?

</l>
<l>Can you hear me woman, don't you want a man like me?

</l>
<l>You gotta think, you gotta think about our future, baby

</l>
<l>And you forget about your used to be



</l>
<l>Well, my days are long and dreary

</l>
<l>and the sun refuse to shine

</l>
<l>I will never be blue and lonely

</l>
<l>only if I knew where you are

</l>
<l>I got the blues baby

</l>
<l>You can make everything alright

</l>
<l>Can I see you today baby

</l>
<l>Or will it have to be tomorrow night



</l>
<l>Yes, this is still my confession baby

</l>
<l>And I'm thrilled by all your charms

</l>
<l>It seems that I'm in heaven when I hold you in my arms

</l>
<l>Baby, woman you can have me for yourself

</l>
<l>You know I was meant for you baby

</l>
<l>And I don't want nobody else, no I don't



</l>
<l>Hey, you told me that you love me, woman, you meant it from the
start

</l>
<l>You said that we would be together until death do us part

</l>
<l>But you lied to me baby, yes and you called it on the phone

</l>
<l>Now how can I be happy woman, with all the wrong you done



</l>
<l>When you know just where I stand

</l>
<l>I don't wanna lose you woman, wanna keep you if I can

</l>
<l>But baby, baby you know I never had a friend

</l>
<l>You're my one and only woman, you're all I have that stays

</l><l>Now let me come in here</l></lyrics></xml>