<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Robert Johnson</artist><title> Cross Road Blues, take 1</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Robert
Johnson

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of 3rd of 5 sessions, November 27 1936, San Antonio,
Texas

</recordDate><album>from 
The
Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 amp; Columbia/Legacy C2K-46222
amp; Columbia 4622 amp; Sony 64916)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>I went to the crossroad, fell down on my knees

</l>
<l>I went to the crossroad, fell down on my knees

</l>
<l>Asked the Lord above "Have mercy, now save poor Bob, if you

please"




</l>
<l>Yeoo, standin' at the crossroad, tried 
to
flag a ride

</l>
<l>Ooo eeee, I tried to flag a ride

</l>
<l>Didn't nobody seem to know me, babe, everybody pass me by



</l>
<l>Standin' at the crossroad, baby, risin' sun goin' down

</l>
<l>Standin' at the crossroad, baby, eee, eee, risin' sun goin' down

</l>
<l>I believe to my soul, now, poor Bob is sinkin' down



</l>
<l>You can run, you can run, tell my friend Willie Brown
1

</l>
<l>You can run, you can run, tell my friend Willie Brown
1

</l>
<l>That I got the crossroad blues this mornin', Lord, babe, I'm sinkin'

down




</l>
<l>And I went to the crossroad, mama, I looked east and west

</l>
<l>I went to the crossroad, baby, I looked east and west

</l>
<l>Lord, I didn't have no sweet woman, ooh well, babe, in my

distress




</l>

<note>Note 1: this could either be the close friend of Son House named
Willie Brown with whom he played together when Robert Johnson first
began to play, or the younger Willie Brown who did some recordings
for the Library of Congress or yet another completely unknown Willie
Brown, who knows(?);

Note: did Robert Johnson sell his soul to the devil at the
crossroads?



In the Delta of the Mississippi River, where Robert Johnson was born, they said that
if an aspiring bluesman waited by the side of a deserted country
crossroads in the dark of a moonless night, then Satan himself might
come and tune his guitar, sealing a pact for the bluesman's soul and
guaranteeing a lifetime of easy money, women, and fame. They said
that Robert Johnson must have waited by the crossroads and gotten his
guitar fine-tuned.</note></lyrics></xml>