<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Don't Go Reaching Across My Plate</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Albert
Collins

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1980</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Frostbite
(Alligator ALCD-4719)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>If one thing in this world

</l>
<l>I just can't stand

</l>
<l>Is bein' at the table wit' an ill-mannered man



</l>
<l>Now, if he's sittin' on your left

</l>
<l>Before you could eat a bite

</l>
<l>He'll reach across your plate

</l>
<l>An' you know that ain't right



</l>
<l>Now I like to eat, as well as any man

</l>
<l>But there's some rules, a fool should understand

</l>
<l>When ya have one little helpin'

</l>
<l>An' one extra piece of cake

</l>
<l>I tell ev'rybody, don't go reachin' across my plate



</l>
<l>I was at a party last night, at over Big Murray

</l>
<l>Cat reached 'cross my plate

</l>
<l>Got a coat sleeve in my gravy

</l>
<l>I didn't say a word, just looked him dead in the eye

</l>
<l>He reached across my plate, an' cut him a piece a pie



</l>
<l>Now I don't care if he did it for a prank

</l>
<l>I don't care, if you had a drink

</l>
<l>Especially when I'm out, a-with my date

</l>
<l>Now don't you go reachin' across MY plate



</l>
<l>At a party last week, there was some high-class folks

</l>
<l>Ev'rything on the table, an' that ain't no joke

</l>
<l>They had barbecue possum
1
, rattlesnake gravy

</l>
<l>Chicken fried skunk

2
, an' it smelt real crazy




</l>
<l>Ev'rything went fine, but one thing made me blue

</l>
<l>A cat reached across my plate, for some armadillo
3

</l>
<l>stew

</l>
<l>Now when you at the table, you act real nice

</l>
<l>You say, "pass me that" or "pass me the platter"

</l>
<l>But just because you hungry, an' happen to come in late

</l>
<l>Don't you go reachin', across MY plate



</l>
<l>(Spoken:

</l>
<l>"Pass some a-that turkey over there, baby!"



</l>
<l>"No, don't give me none of that skunk, I don't want none a-that"



</l>
<l>"I, I beg your pardon"



</l>
<l>"If this cat stop reachin' 'cross my plate, I can maybe ask for

somethin'"




</l>
<l>"A pass me a little a-that turkey there, baby"



</l>
<l>Fading:

</l>
<l>Na na na na-na-na-na



</l>
<l>Yeah-heya



</l>
<l>"Party' nice, party's nice"



</l>
<l>"Yeah, ah give gimme some a that chicken over there, baby"



</l>
<l>"Chicken fried skunk? "ah no"



</l>

<note>Note: possum, opossum, any of a family (Didelphidae) of American
marsupials that usually have a pointed snout and prehensile tail;
especially : a common omnivorous largely nocturnal and arboreal
mammal (Didelphis virginiana) of North America having grayish to
blackish fur with white on the cheeks;

Note 2: skunk, any of various common omnivorous black-and-white New
World mammals (especially genus Mephitis) of the weasel family that
have a pair of perineal glands from which a secretion of pungent and
offensive odor is ejected;

Note 3: armadillo, any of a family (Dasypodidae) of burrowing
edentate mammals found from the southern U.S. to Argentina and having
the body and head encased in an armor of small bony plates.
See

illustration
.</note></lyrics></xml>