<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Janis Joplin</artist><title> Ego Rock</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Nick
Gravenites
 </name><name> 
Janis
Joplin

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of April 4 1970, San Fransisco

</recordDate><album>from 
Joplin
in Concert (Columbia CGK-31160)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>(Spoken: Let's go, let's go let's go let's go

</l>
<l>Peter you start it

</l>
<l>Richard, you start it

</l>
<l>Somebody start it)



</l>
<l>I just had to get out on the Texas plane, Lord, well it was bringing
me down

</l>
<l>Yeah, I had to get out of Texas, baby, Lord, it was bringing me
down

</l>
<l>I been all around the world, but Port Arthur is the worst place that

I've ever found




</l>
<l>I guess they couldn't understand it there, honey, they'd laugh me off
the street!

</l>
<l>Lord, I guess they couldn't understand me, baby, honey, they'd laugh,
I said they'd laugh me right off the street, yeah

</l>
<l>I said I want to keep on moving, baby, be the last person I ever

wanna meet




</l>
<l>Yeah, yeah, yeah, honey ain't it hard when you're all alone

</l>
<l>Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, honey ain't it hard, Lord, when you're
all alone

</l>
<l>I might die real old lady, but I'd never call Texas my home, no, no,

no, oh!




</l>
<l>You say you come from Texas, baby, she says she left Texas with just
her name

</l>
<l>(Spoken: That's what she told me)

</l>
<l>Yes she's from Texas I tell you, she says she left Texas with just
her name

</l>
<l>Yes, well I swear when that girl came to the big city, Lord, she
learned a brand new game

</l>
<l>Well, yeah!



</l>
<l>Honey, I hear you talkin' about sorrow, baby but you don't know my
pain, that's right!

</l>
<l>Mercy! Mercy!

</l>
<l>I hear you talking about my sorrow, you don't know my pain

</l>
<l>You know there's an inside kind of sorrow, Lord, the women are always
singin' the blues

</l>
<l>All right, all right mother fucker, you sing!



</l>
<l>You know I, I dealt the Ace to the Queen, you know I played scrabble
with L.B.J.

</l>
<l>Yes, I dealt an Ace to the Queen, didn't I'll tell ya I's playin'
scrabble with L.B.J.

</l>
<l>Well, I don't care what the name of the game is, baby, I tell you I

always seem to get my way




</l>
<l>I used to be a doggone fool, fall for a woman's story every time

</l>
<l>But no more, I swear

</l>
<l>Well, I used to be a, be a doggone fool, fall for that old woman's
story every time

</l>
<l>Yes I, I'm a big boy now, yeah, they gotta come up with some kind of
heavy line

</l>
<l>Well, well, yeah!



</l>
<l>Sounds like I found the man, who could take care of my time

</l>
<l>It ain't me babe, it ain't me babe!

</l>
<l>It appears to me that I found a man, that could take care of my
time

</l>
<l>Well, I got my own trouble, I got my own car, I got my own little
lady, I got my hotel

</l>
<l>Oh what are you talking about!

</l>
<l>Don't try to take it!

</l>
<l>Somebody talks as fine as he does, oughta be able to take care of

</l>
<l>One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine



</l>
<l>Woman, woman, it just makes me mad

</l>
<l>Ahh, ahh! Woman, yeah

</l>
<l>Woman, yeah

</l>
<l>Woman, yeah

</l>
<l>Woman, yeah

</l>
<l>Woman, yeah, yeah, it just makes me mad

</l>
<l>Oh man, shit, man...

</l>
<l>Yes, she played me for the fool I tell ya

</l>
<l>Yes and I've got to love every man she's ever had, yeah



</l>
<l>If I found a man who could put me down the way you do

</l>
<l>I mean so handy-like, you know what I mean?

</l>
<l>Yeah, I found a man, whoa, who could put me down the way you do

</l>
<l>I mean so easy like it was second nature, y'know what I mean,
man?

</l>
<l>Ah maybe that man could help me, at least, honey I thought I would
give you a chance

</l>
<l>I said I, what I said I could try after the, after the show tonight

maybe uh ...




</l>
<l>I'm just a working man, you know

</l>
<l>Ha ha ha ha, you don't work too hard, baby!

</l>
<l>You know I ain't no Hollywood star

</l>
<l>I'm not Joe Namath, you know, I read about that in the papers
today

</l>
<l>You know I'm just a working man, you don't work too hard, baby!

</l>
<l>I never ran in a football game 200 yards

</l>
<l>Ha ha ha ha ha, that's the kinda man I like, that's the kinda man I
like

</l>
<l>But you know I can take care of those country girls

</l>
<l>Well I can mess around in that farmyard

</l>
<l>Lord, Lord, whoaah!



</l>
<l>Ha ha ha! ha. Whew! Whew! Wow! That's getting a little too close, too
heavy here

</l>
<l>That's Nick Gravenites, that was a tune called Ego Rock. No! ...



</l>
<l>All right, rock, rock &amp; roll song</l></lyrics></xml>