<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Bessie Smith</artist><title> Empty Bed Blues</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
J.
C. Johnson

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of March 28 1928, New York City

</recordDate><album>from 
The
Complete Recordings, Vol. 4 (Columbia/Legacy
52838)
,


</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>I woke up this morning with a awful aching head

</l>
<l>I woke up this morning with a awful aching head

</l>
<l>My new man had left me, just a room and a empty bed



</l>
<l>Bought me a coffee grinder
</l>
<l>that's the best one I could find</l>
<l>
Bought me a coffee grinder that's the best one I could find

</l>
<l>Oh, he could grind my coffee, 'cause he had a brand new grind



</l>
<l>He's a deep sea diver with a stroke that can't go wrong

</l>
<l>He's a deep sea diver with a stroke that can't go wrong

</l>
<l>He can stay at the bottom and his wind holds out so long



</l>
<l>He knows how to thrill me and he thrills me night and day

</l>
<l>Oh, he knows how to thrill me, he thrills me night and day

</l>
<l>He's got a new way of loving, almost takes my breath away



</l>
<l>Lord, he's got that sweet somethin' and I told my girlfriend Lou

</l>
<l>He's got that sweet somethin' and I told my girlfriend Lou

</l>
<l>From the way she's raving, she must have gone and tried it too



</l>
<l>(Part 2)



</l>
<l>When my bed get empty make me feel awful mean and blue

</l>
<l>When my bed get empty make me feel awful mean and blue

</l>
<l>My springs are getting rusty, sleeping single like I do



</l>
<l>Bought him a blanket, pillow for his head at night

</l>
<l>Bought him a blanket, pillow for his head at night

</l>
<l>Then I bought him a mattress so he could lay just right



</l>
<l>He came home one evening with his spirit way up high

</l>
<l>He came home one evening with his spirit way up high

</l>
<l>What he had to give me, make me wring my hands and cry



</l>
<l>He give me a lesson that I never had before

</l>
<l>He give me a lesson that I never had before

</l>
<l>When he got to teachin' me, from my elbow down was sore



</l>
<l>He boiled my first cabbage and he made it awful hot

</l>
<l>He boiled my first cabbage and he made it awful hot

</l>
<l>When he put in the bacon, it overflowed the pot



</l>
<l>When you git good lovin', never go and spread the news

</l>
<l>Yes, he'll double-cross you, and leave you with them empty bed
blues</l></lyrics></xml>