<xml><metadata><artist>John Lee Hooker</artist><title> I'mIn The Mood (Version 2)</title>
<songInfo>by 
John
Lee Hooker
 / 
Bernard
Bessman

recording of 1989

from 
The
Healer (Silvertone ZD74307)
,

</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood for love, yes I am

I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood for love

I'm in the mood, in the mood, I'm in the mood for love, Lord,
Lord



Hooked on you, I say, hey!, night time is the right time, be with the
one you love

But night 'n, night come baby you're so far away, away, 'way

I'm in the mood for love, Lord, Lord I'm in the mood, in the mood,
mood,

I'm in the mood for love

I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood, oh Lord, I'm in the mood for
love



Bonnie Raitt!

Yeah, yes, my daddy told me,

(I know he did)

leave that man alone

Yes he did

But my daddy didn't tell me, Lord, what that man was puttin' down

(Hmmm, puttin' down, down, down down,down)

In the mood, baby,

(No he didn't)

I'm in the mood for some of your love

(Baby)

I'm in the mood, I'm in the mood for love

(Oh, love, ah!)

All right John Lee, play it, play it, play it baby!

(Yeah)

Lord love you, Bonnie Raitt



I don't want be with no, no, no, one else

I can't get my thrill, babe, hon', unless I be with you, you, you

'Cause night, night time is right time

Oh Lord, oh Lord, to be with the one you love

I'm in the mood, in the mood baby

Oh Lord, I'm in a mood for love

Lord have mercy on me

Have mercy on me, on me, on me

Ha!, have mercy on me, on me, on me,. on me

Lord, Lord, I'm in the mood for you babe, the mood for you babe

An' now, now, Bonnie, now Bonnie, now Bonnie

What can I do, what can I do baby?

(Hmm, hmm)

I, I love you, I love you, I love you, you

(Hmm, hmm, I hear you knock)

I love you, I love you, Bonnie

What can I do, what can I do?

(Hmm, hmm, hmm, I hear you call)

I'm in the mood

Some of your love, some of your love, ha!

(I'm in the mood)

Some of your love, some 'o your love

(I'm comin' on)

I'm in the mood, hmmm

I'm in the mood, baby, yeah

(ha, ha, ha!)

I'm in a mood for some love

(No, no)



































</lyrics></xml>
