<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Muddy Waters</artist><title> Interview With Alan Lomax</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
McKinley
Morganfield a.k.a. Muddy Waters

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of August 24-31, 1941, Stovall Plantation, Stovall,
Mississippi

</recordDate><album>from 
The
Complete Plantation Recordings (Chess/MCA
CHD-9344)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Interview no.1, after recording the song, "

Country
Blues
"




</l>
<l>Question: I wonder if you'd tell me, if
you can remember, ah when it was that you made that blues, Muddy
Water?

</l>
<l>Answer: I made that Blue up in '38.



</l>
<l>Question: Remember the time, the year,
the..?

</l>
<l>Answer: I made it up 'bout the 8th of

October in '38.




</l>
<l>Question: Do you remember where you were
when you were doin' your singin'? No, I mean, how it happened? No, I
mean, where you were sittin', what you were thinkin' about?

</l>
<l>Answer: Thinkin' a punchin' on my car.

And I'd been mistreated by a girl and it just looked like it run in
my mind to sing that song.




</l>
<l>Question: Tell me the, tell me a little

of the story of it, if you don't mind? I mean if it's not too
personal, I mean I wanna know the facts on how you felt and why you
felt the way you did, that's a very beautiful song.


</l>
<l>Answer: Well, I just felt blue, an the

song came into my mind an come to me just like that song and I start
to singin' an went on.




</l>
<l>Question: Well, when you ah, do you, do
you, know is that tune, the tune from any other blues that you
know?

</l>
<l>Answer: Well, yes, it's been some blues

played like that.




</l>
<l>Question: What, what tune, other blues
do you remember, are like that same tune?

</l>
<l>Answer: Well, this song come from the

cottonfield and the boy went, put the record out, Robert Young, he
put it out, Walking Blues.




</l>
<l>Question: What was the title he put it
out under?

</l>
<l>Answer: He put it out, on as "Man

Walking Blues"




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, did you know the tune
before you heard it on the record?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes, sir, I knew the tune before

I heard it on the record.




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, who'd you learn it
from?

</l>
<l>Answer: I learn it from Son House.



</l>
<l>Question: Son House, who's that?

</l>
<l>Answer: That's a boy, pick a guitar and

I don't ...(inaudible)




</l>
<l>Question: Oh, and how old, how old is
Son House?

</l>
<l>Answer: Ah, I'm not even sure his age,

he's about forty-two




</l>
<l>Question: Did you know Johnson,
yourself?

</l>
<l>Answer: Robert Johnson? No, I didn't

know him, personally




</l>
<l>Question: Is a, is a, House a better
player than Johnson is, you think?

</l>
<l>Answer: I think they both 'bout

equal.




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, well ah, how did it
come to first that you wanted to play the guitar? Why did you decide
that you gonna?

</l>
<l>Answer: I just loved the music and saw

Son singin' an playin' and I just wanted to do it an I took after
it.




</l>
<l>Question: Well, about how much have you
practiced? How many hours when you were first pickin' it up, how long
did you have to play everyday to learn how to play?

</l>
<l>Answer: An hour and a half to two

hours.




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, everyday?

</l>
<l>Answer: Everyday.



</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, you remember what the
first piece you ever tried to learn was?

</l>
<l>Answer: First piece I ever tried to

learn was, How Long (Blues) whatever you wanna call it.




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, did you learn that
from a record or from seein' it?

</l>
<l>Answer: I learned that from the

record.




</l>
<l>Question: How would you do? How would
you learn that song?

</l>
<l>Answer: We just heard the song, ya know,

put out, ah, Leroy Carr (?) put it out.




</l>
<l>Question: Would you sit down with the
record and play a little of it and then try and play it?

</l>
<l>Answer: I just got the song in my ear

and then went on and just tried to play it.




</l>
<l>Question: Well, how did you learn how to
play with this bottle?

</l>
<l>Answer: Picked that up from Son

House.




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, what do you call
that?

</l>
<l>Answer: Just a bottle-neck. I call it a

slide.




</l>
<l>Question: You call it a slide?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes.



</l>
<l>Question: Wear on your little
finger?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes.



</l>
<l>Question: And how do you have that
guitar tuned? What's the name of that tuning?

</l>
<l>Answer: Spanish (strums guitar)



</l>
<l>Question: Spanish?

</l>
<l>Question: Do you know any other ways to
tune the guitar than that?

</l>
<l>Answer: Well, I know the natural. Show

you the natural.




</l>
<l>Question: Do you have another tuning, ah
besides that?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes sir, I have another

tuning.




</l>
<l>Question: What's the name of that other
tuning?

</l>
<l>Answer: That's just straight E, yes

sir.




</l>
<l>Question: Straight E? Do you have
another name for a straight E?

</l>
<l>Answer: Another song for a straight

E?




</l>
<l>Question: No, I mean no is there any
other name for that tuning than straight E?

</l>
<l>Answer: Well, we call it, we call it, a

"cross noting"




</l>
<l>Question: Uh-huh, well can you play that
other Country Blues that you played there then while ago that fast
one?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes.



</l>
<l>Question: In this same tune here?

</l>
<l>Answer: Yes.



</l><l>Question: Well, just a minute, I'll tell</l>
<l>you when I'm ready</l></lyrics></xml>