<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Master Charge (version 1)</title>
<songInfo>by 
Gwendolyn
Collins

recording of 1978 resp. 1993

from 
Ice
Pickin (Alligator ALCD-4713)
 &amp;

Collins
Mix (Virgin 39097 or Pointblank V2-39097)
,

</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



(Sax intro by Jon Smith)



I got my wife a charge card

Just the other day

I owe five hundred dollars

Just for yesterday



I said, "Honey, here's a present

Go out and shop around,

buy you a couple a-dresses,

browse around downtown"



She did just what I told her

Bought one, two, three

Came home lookin' silly

Makin' goo-goo eyes at me



Mastercharge, I'll break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, I'll break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, I'll break an' bury her card



Oh yeah, charge it!



Said, "Did you get your dress?"

"Yes, one or two"

I needed me some shoes,

I needed some jewelry, too"



Two hundred dollar dresses

I could-a made, I can't sew

It made me so mad

I could call her a so and so



Mastercharge, I'll break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, break an' bury her card



Oh yeah, charge it for me, charge it, baby!



Hey! Ow!



For one-a that gal's dresses, yeah

I paid one and a half

I'm so mad, I just had to laugh



I could see in my mind

On a horse like Paul Revere

Hate to check my mail boxes

'Cause these bills keep comin' here



Mastercharge, break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, break an' bury her card

Mastercharge, break an' bury her card



Oh, let's charge it!



(Speaks with instrumental back up)



"Oh, don't get too much on the bill, dear"

("Oh, I put five hundred dollars already, baby")

"Yeah, but I know, but I'm-a, you know that, that, that, 18% is
killin' me!"

"Yeah, I understand darlin', but I know you wanna charge it an'
everything but, yeah, darlin' "

("They have 'American Express")

"But, wait a minute, man, I, I told ya to take that Master Card with
ya

And take one wit' ya and leave one at home

"But you look good in them blue jeans, though"

("Yeah, I understand about dresses")

Yeah, they got 'em on sale up there, upside the wall, there"

"Fifteen dollars, man, on sale darlin', here, let me look for ya"

"I'm gonna bet you, be struttin' down the street in them blue jeans,
haha"



"Yeah, but you can even wear them dresses on the weekend"

"Yeah, I hear ya baby, well charge it then baby, that's alright,
yeah"



("I have a Visa"!)



"What"? (heh, heh)

"Give me the scissors, I'm gonna cut 'em up"



Well, you ought to be ashamed of yourself, you!"



"Yeah I know, darlin', I am"



("Charge it")



"Here, go on charge, darlin' "



"I'm guilty callin' em, I know you're gonna charge it anyway"



"Ooh, I know you gonna look good in them blue jeans

You look like you been poured in 'em"!



(Fading)

Oh, charge it baby!

Yeah, I see you later on, an' hour

I'm gone to work here, n' when I come back

I wanna see you with them jeans on, baby



Yeah, love her, yeah, you look good baby

Yeah, I know, I know... (fades out to end)

































</lyrics></xml>
