<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>George Thorogood</artist><title> One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Beer</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
John
Lee Hooker

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1977</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
George
Thorogood &amp; The Destroyers (Rounder
CD-3013)
 &amp; 
Live
(EMI E 2-46329)
 &amp; 
The
Baddest Of George Thorogood And The Destroyers (EMI E2-97718 or
Capitol 97718)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Wanna tell you a story,

</l>
<l>about the house-man blues

</l>
<l>I come home one Friday,

</l>
<l>had to tell the landlady I'd-a lost my job

</l>
<l>She said that don't confront me,

</l>
<l>long as I get my money next Friday

</l>
<l>Now next Friday come I didn't get the rent,

</l>
<l>and out the door I went



</l>
<l>So I goes to the landlady,

</l>
<l>I said, "You let me slide?"

</l>
<l>I'll have the rent for you in a month.

</l>
<l>next I don't know

</l>
<l>So said let me slide it on you know people,

</l>
<l>I notice when I come home in the evening

</l>
<l>She ain't got nothing nice to say to me,

</l>
<l>but for five year she was so nice

</l>
<l>Loh' she was lovy-dovy,

</l>
<l>I come home one particular evening

</l>
<l>The landlady said, "You got the rent money yet?",

</l>
<l>I said, "No, can't find no job"

</l>
<l>Therefore I ain't got no money to pay the rent

</l>
<l>She said "I don't believe you're tryin' to find no job"

</l>
<l>Said "I seen you today you was standin' on a corner,

</l>
<l>leaning up against a post"

</l>
<l>I said "But I'm tired, I've been walkin' all day"

</l>
<l>She said "That don't confront me,

</l>
<l>long as I get my money next Friday"

</l>
<l>Now next Friday come I didn't have the rent,

</l>
<l>and out the door I went



</l>
<l>So I go down the streets,

</l>
<l>down to my good friend's house

</l>
<l>I said "Look man I'm outdoors you know,

</l>
<l>can I stay with you maybe a couple days?"

</l>
<l>He said "Let me go and ask my wife"

</l>
<l>He come out of the house,

</l>
<l>I could see it in his face

</l>
<l>I know that was no

</l>
<l>He said "I don't know man, ah she kinda funny, you know"

</l>
<l>I said "I know, everybody funny, now you funny too"

</l>
<l>So I go back home

</l>
<l>I tell the landlady I got a job, I'm gonna pay the rent

</l>
<l>She said "Yeah?" I said "Oh yeah"

</l>
<l>And then she was so nice,

</l>
<l>loh' she was lovy-dovy

</l>
<l>So I go in my room, pack up my things and I go,

</l>
<l>I slip on out the back door and down the streets I go

</l>
<l>She a-howlin' about the front rent, she'll be lucky to get any back
rent,

</l>
<l>she ain't gonna get none of it

</l>
<l>So I stop in the local bar you know people,

</l>
<l>I go to the bar, I ring my coat, I call the bartender

</l>
<l>Said "Look man, come down here", he got down there

</l>
<l>So what you want?



</l>
<l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer

</l>
<l>Well I ain't seen my baby since I don't know when,

</l>
<l>I've been drinking bourbon, whiskey, scotch and gin

</l>
<l>Gonna get high man I'm gonna get loose,

</l>
<l>need me a triple shot of that juice

</l>
<l>Gonna get drunk don't you have no fear

</l>
<l>I want one bourbon, one scotch and one beer

</l>
<l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer



</l>
<l>But I'm sitting now at the bar,

</l>
<l>I'm getting drunk, I'm feelin' mellow

</l>
<l>I'm drinkin' bourbon, I'm drinkin' scotch, I'm drinkin' beer

</l>
<l>Looked down the bar, here come the bartender

</l>
<l>I said "Look man, come down here"

</l>
<l>So what you want?



</l>
<l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer

</l>
<l>No I ain't seen my baby since the night before last,

</l>
<l>gotta get a drink man I'm gonna get gassed

</l>
<l>Gonna get high man I ain't had enough,

</l>
<l>need me a triple shot of that stuff

</l>
<l>Gonna get drunk won't you listen right here,

</l>
<l>I want one bourbon, one shot and one beer

</l>
<l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer



</l>
<l>Now by this time I'm plenty high,

</l>
<l>you know when your mouth a-getting dry you're plenty high

</l>
<l>Looked down the bar I say to my bartender

</l>
<l>I said "Look man, come down here", he got down there

</l>
<l>So what you want this time?

</l>
<l>I said "Look man, a-what time is it?"

</l>
<l>He said "The clock on the wall say three o'clock

</l>
<l>Last call for alcohol, so what you need?"



</l>
<l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer

</l>
<l>No I ain't seen my baby since a nigh' and a week,

</l>
<l>gotta get drunk man till I can't even speak

</l>
<l>Gonna get high man listen to me,

</l>
<l>one drink ain't enough Jack you better make it three

</l>
<l>I wanna get drunk I'm gonna make it real clear,

</l>
<l>I want one bourbon, one scotch and one beer

</l><l>One bourbon, one scotch, one beer</l></lyrics></xml>