<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Same Old Thing</title>
<songInfo>by 
Albert
Collins

recording of 1993

from 
Collins
Mix (Virgin 39097 or Pointblank V2-39097)
,

</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



(Spoken:

Take a lot a entertainers, sing songs

'Bout the things they experienced in life

Some entertainers sing songs that they-a,

seen other people experience in life

Well, I'm gonna tell you some of the things

I experienced in life)



The old lady got mad with me the other night

Packed that overnight grip

Got the house by myself, just me and the dog. Ha, ha

Sometime ya know that your animal layin' in the floor, lookin'

at you like, say, "Uh, you done messed up buddy"

It's that same old thang



(Sings)

Same old thang, baby where ya been?

Said, same old thing, woman where ya been?



Been gone two days, today

I'm sittin' here all alone

I been waitin' babe

Waitin' by my telephone



Said, same old thing

Woman where ya been?

It's that same old thing

Baby, where ya been?



I been up all night, waitin' in vain

Without you baby, it just ain't the same

Everytime I go through this baby

We play that same old game



Now if I ever catch ya messin' around

Then there's no need to plead

Just send your soul on to heaven

'Cause the rest is home to me



Same old thing, baby where ya been?

It's the same old thing, woman where ya been?

It's the same old thing



Hey!



My patience done run out

My love gone bad

I really started to leave ya woman, but

But you're the best thing I ever had



Same old thing, woman where ya been?

Same old thing, baby where ya been?



I been up all night, waitin' in vain

Without you baby, it just ain't the same

Every time I go through this thing with you

You play that same old game



Now if I ever catch you messin' around

There's no need to plead

Just send your soul on to heaven, haha

'Cause the rest belong to me



Said same old thing, baby where ya been?

Said same old thing, baby

Woman, where ya been?



Spoken:

("I was at Carol's house last night")

No you wouldn't

Carol was over here, her and the baby last night

Where ya gonna be?

Ya gotta find somethin' else baby 'cause you know

I started to leave you, but you the best thing I've ever had

("Then I went by Mollie's house")

No, hell no, Mollie called here lookin' for ya

You've got to come right with me, baby

No wigglin' of the hip

See the same old thing baby



I done told you, no, don't do that to me, no mo'

'Cause I, I love you baby

I'm really in love wit' cha baby































</lyrics></xml>
