<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>B.B. King</artist><title> Saturday Night Fish Fry</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> E. Walsh </name><name> 
Louis
Jordan

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1999</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Let
the Good Times Roll: The Music of Louis Jordan (MCA
12042)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Now if you've ever been down to New Orleans

</l>
<l>Then you can understand just what I mean

</l>
<l>All thru the week it's quiet as a mouse

</l>
<l>But on Saturday night they go from house to house

</l>
<l>You don't have to pay the usual admission

</l>
<l>If you're a cook, a waiter or a good musician

</l>
<l>So if you happen to be just passin' by

</l>
<l>Stop in at the Saturday Night Fish Fry



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn



</l>
<l>Now my buddy and me was on the main stem

</l>
<l>Foolin' around just me and him

</l>
<l>We decided we could use a little something to eat

</l>
<l>So we went to a house on Rampart Street

</l>
<l>We knocked on the door and it opened up with ease

</l>
<l>And a lush little Miss said, "Come in, please"

</l>
<l>And before we could even bat an eye

</l>
<l>We were right in the middle of a big fish fry



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn



</l>
<l>Now the folks was havin' the time of their life

</l>
<l>And Sam was jivin' Jimmie's wife

</l>
<l>Over in the corner was a beat up grand

</l>
<l>Being played by a big fat piano man

</l>
<l>Some of the chicks wore expensive frocks

</l>
<l>Some of them had on bobbie socks

</l>
<l>But everybody was nice and high

</l>
<l>At this particular Saturday Night Fish Fry



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn



</l>
<l>Now the women were screamin' and jumpin' and yellin'

</l>
<l>The bottles was flyin', and the fish was smellin'

</l>
<l>And way above all the noise we made

</l>
<l>Somebody hollered, "You better get outta here, this is a raid!"

</l>
<l>I didn't know we was breaking the law but

</l>
<l>Somebody reached over and hit me on the jaw

</l>
<l>Now they had us blocked off from front to back

</l>
<l>And they was puttin' 'em in the wagon like potatoes in a sack



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn



</l>
<l>I knew I could get away if I had a chance

</l>
<l>But I was shakin' like I had the St. Vitus dance

</l>
<l>So I tried to crawl in under a bath tab

</l>
<l>When a policeman said, "Where are you goin' there, bub?"

</l>
<l>Now they got us out of there like a house on fire

</l>
<l>And put us all in the black Maria

</l>
<l>Now they might have missed a pitiful few

</l>
<l>But they got both me and my buddy too



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn



</l>
<l>Well we headed for jail in a dazed condition

</l>
<l>They booked each one of us on suspicion

</l>
<l>Now my chick came down and paid my bail

</l>
<l>And finally got me outta that rotten jail

</l>
<l>Now if you ever want to get a fist in your eye

</l>
<l>Just mention a Saturday Night Fish Fry

</l>
<l>I don't care how many fish in the sea

</l>
<l>But don't ever mention a fish to me



</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn

</l>
<l>It was rockin', it was rockin'

</l>
<l>You never seen such scufflin'

</l>
<l>And shufflin' 'till the break of dawn</l></lyrics></xml>