<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Bo Diddley</artist><title> Say Man</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Ellas
McDaniel a.k.a. Bo Diddley

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1959</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Bo
Diddley's 16 All-Time Greatest Hits (Checker LP
2989)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>(Alternate lines spoken by Bo Diddley and 

Jerome
Green
):




</l>
<l>Say man

</l>
<l>What's that boy?

</l>
<l>I want to tell you 'bout your girlfriend

</l>
<l>What about my girl?

</l>
<l>Well, you don't look strong enough to take the message

</l>
<l>I'm strong enough

</l>
<l>I might hurt your feelings

</l>
<l>My feelings are already hurt by being here with you

</l>
<l>Well, I was walking down the street with your girl the other day

</l>
<l>Ah-ha

</l>
<l>And the wind was blowin' real hard

</l>
<l>Is that right?

</l>
<l>And the wind blew her hair into my face

</l>
<l>Ah-ha

</l>
<l>You know what else happened?

</l>
<l>What happened?

</l>
<l>The wind blew her hair into her face

</l>
<l>Yeh?

</l>
<l>And we went a little further; you wanna hear the rest of it?

</l>
<l>I might as well,

</l>
<l>The wind blew her hair into the street!

</l>
<l>Ok; since you told me about my girl, I'm gonna tell you about yours.
I was walking down the street with your girl

</l>
<l>Yes?

</l>
<l>I took her home, for a drink, you know

</l>
<l>Took her home?

</l>
<l>Yeh, jus' for a drink

</l>
<l>Oh

</l>
<l>But that chick looked so ugly, she had to sneak up on the glass to
get a drink of water!

</l>
<l>You've got the nerve to call somebody ugly; why you so ugly the stork
that brought you in the world oughta be arrested!

</l>
<l>That's alright; my momma didn't have to put a sheet on my head so
sleep could slip up on me!

</l>
<l>Look-a here!

</l>
<l>What's that?

</l>
<l>Where are you from?

</l>
<l>South America

</l>
<l>What's that?

</l>
<l>South America

</l>
<l>You don't look like no South American to me

</l>
<l>I'm still from South America

</l>
<l>What part?

</l>
<l>South Texas!

</l>
<l>Where are your workin' boots at?

</l>
<l>I've got 'em on

</l>
<l>Those aren't no boots you got on; those broguettes!

</l>
<l>Hey, look-a here!

</l>
<l>What's that?

</l>
<l>I've bin tryin' to figure out what you is

</l>
<l>I already figured out what YOU is!

</l>
<l>What's that?

</l>
<l>You that thing I throw peanuts at!

</l>
<l>Look-a here!

</l>
<l>What's that?

</l>
<l>You should be ashamed of yourself

</l>
<l>Why?

</l>
<l>Calling people ugly

</l>
<l>I didn't call you ugly

</l>
<l>What you say?

</l>
<l>I said you was ruined, that's all!

</l>
<l>You know somethin'?

</l>
<l>What?

</l>
<l>You look like you've bin whooped with a ugly-stick!

</l><l>Hey! I ain't got nothin' to do with it, but I beat the fellah</l>
<l>right...!</l></lyrics></xml>