<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Snowed In</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Albert
Collins

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1980</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Frostbite
(Alligator ALCD-4719)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Last winter I was in Chicago and the weather was awfully bad

</l>
<l>Last winter I was in Chicago, and the weather was awfully bad

</l>
<l>They say I was stuck in China Town, for the worst winter they ever

had




</l>
<l>"I'm gonna go on right here

</l>
<l>And see if I can get this truck started right quick"



</l>
<l>"These old shoes ain't ready for the winter"



</l>
<l>"Oh, I'm 'bout to fall an' break my neck here in a minute, buddy



</l>
<l>"See if I can get this key in this door here"

</l>
<l>"I know it don't lock it, lock, it done froze up on me an'"

</l>
<l>"Lock it won't act right, it already half-tore up anyhow"



</l>
<l>"Yeah, I got it now, I'm gon get here an' try to crank this old
thing"

</l>
<l>"An' pat the accelerator a little bit"



</l>
<l>"Yeah, I almost got it"

</l>
<l>"Pat the accelerator a little bit more"

</l>
<l>"It's cold, that wind just whistlin' out there"



</l>
<l>"Oh it sure cold weather out here"

</l>
<l>"You get frostbite out here"



</l>
<l>"Try it one more time"



</l>
<l>"Ya'all, it ain't gonna start"



</l>
<l>Yeah, I don't mind a little snow, an' I can handle rain

</l>
<l>I say, I don't mind a little snow, an' I can handle a little rain

</l>
<l>Now I don't mind bein' cold but this winter, man it's sure insane



</l>
<l>"If I go now hit this old gas station,

</l>
<l>I think I can get me somebody to"

</l>
<l>"Walk on down the street here, 'bout a block"

</l>
<l>"See if I can, get somebody to give me a boost off here an' get my

battery charged"




</l>
<l>"Oh man, this stuff is in a mess here!"



</l>
<l>"I'm gonna fall, break my neck"



</l>
<l>"Oh get on by man, I'm gonna get out your way, I'm in the street"

</l>
<l>"I'm tryin' to walk here, ya'all runnin' these damn trucks an' cars

an' goin' on"




</l>
<l>"Come on by man"



</l>
<l>"Oh man, the station is done closed!"



</l>
<l>Now the gas station was closed, and the snow was eight feet tall

</l>
<l>Now the gas station had closed, hm, and the snow was eight feet
tall

</l>
<l>The telephone cable was down, an' you couldn't even make a call



</l>
<l>You couldn't go out for groceries, hm, nobody would deliver to
you

</l>
<l>I said, you couldn't go out for groceries, nobody would deliver to
you

</l>
<l>In a bad situation like that, what in the hell, ya'all, what-a I'm

suppose to do?




</l>
<l>"Yeah, it's a tough winter, I tell ya"



</l>
<l>"I go back out here one more time an' see if I get this, thing

started right here"




</l>
<l>"Old battery might be done be at the level, I might get it started

now"




</l>
<l>"Besides, I'm about to fall"



</l>
<l>"Man, I'm gonna tell ya, I'm a, whew!"



</l>
<l>"Rough, rough here in Chicago!"



</l>
<l>"Wanna get on back across that desert in Los Angeles, somewhere"

</l>
<l>"Florida somewhere"

</l>
<l>"If I can get outta here, I know I'm snowed in"



</l>
<l>"Try to crank this damn thing one more time"

</l>
<l>"I think I can get it to crank, I hope so"



</l>
<l>"Let me see if I can get it cranked"



</l>
<l>"Pat the accelerator a little bit"



</l>
<l>"Might get it started, now"



</l>
<l>"Oh yes, I got that thing together now, boy"

</l>
<l>"She's kickin' now!"



</l>
<l>"Yeah"

</l>
<l>"Yeah, will let her get warmed up"



</l>
<l>"Hey!"



</l>
<l>"Hey!"



</l><l>"Hey!"</l></lyrics></xml>