<xml><metadata><artist>Bessie Smith</artist><title> St. Louis Blues</title>
<songInfo>by 
W.C.
Handy

recording of 1924-1925

from 
The
Complete Recordings, Vol. 2 (1924-1925) (Columbia/Legacy
C2K-47471)
, 
</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>



I hate to see the ev'nin' sun go down

Hate to see the ev'nin' sun go down,

'cause my baby, he done left this town



Feelin' tomorrow like I feel today

Feel tomorrow like I feel today,

I'll pack my trunk, make my getaway



St. Louis woman with her diamond rings

Pulls that man 'round by her apron strings,

't'want for powder and for store-bought hair



The man I love, would not gone nowhere,

got the St. Louis blues just as blue as I can be

That man got a heart like a rock cast in the sea,

or else he wouldn't have gone so far from me



Been to the gypsy to get my fortune told

To the gypsy, to get my fortune told,

'cause I'm most wild about my 
jelly
roll



Gypsy done told me, "Don't you wear no black"

Yes, she done told me, "Don't you wear no black,

go to St. Louis, you can win him back"



Help me to Cairo, make St. Louis by myself

Gone to Cairo, find my old friend Jeff

Goin' to pin myself close to his side,

if I 
flag his train
, I
sure can ride



I love that man like a schoolboy loves his pie

Like a Kentucky Colonel loves his mint and rye
1

I'll love my baby till the day I die



You ought to see that stovepipe brown of mine,

like he owns the diamond Joseph line

He'd make across-eyed old man go stone blind



Blacker than midnight, teeth like flags of truce

Blackest man in the whole St. Louis

Blacker the berry, sweeter is the juice



About a crap game, he knows a powerful lot,

but when work time comes, he's on the dot

Goin' to ask him for a cold ten spot,

what it takes to get it, he's certainly got



A black-headed gal make a freight train jump the track

Said a black-headed gal make a freight train jump the track

But a redheaded woman makes a preacher

ball
the jack



___________

Note 1: rye, a hardy annual grass that is widely grown for grain and
as a cover crop. Also used to make whiskey.





































</lyrics></xml>
