<xml><metadata><artist>Robert Johnson</artist><title> Terraplane Blues</title>
<songInfo>by
Robert Johnson
recording of 1st of 5 sessions, November 23 1936, San Antonio, Texas
from
The Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 &amp; Columbia/Legacy C2K-46222 &amp; Columbia 4622 &amp; Sony 64916)
,
</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>





And I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan
When I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan
Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
, for you since I been gone.

I'd said I flash your lights, mama, you horn won't even blow
(spoken: Somebody's been runnin' my batteries down on this machine)
I even flash my lights, mama, this horn won't even blow
Got a short in this connection, hoo well, babe, it's way down below








I'm gion' heist your hood, mama, I'm bound to check your oil
I'm goin' heist your hood, mama, mmm, I'm bound to check your oil
I got a woman that I'm lovin', way down in Arkansas

Now, you know the coils ain't even buzzin', little generator won't get the spark
Motor's in a bad condition, you gotta have these batteries charged
But I'm cryin', pleease, pleease don't do me wrong.
Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
now for, you since I been gone.

Mr. highway man, please don't block the road
Puh hee hee, please don't block the road
'Cause she's reachin' a cold one hundred and I'm booked and I got to go

Mmm mmm mmm mmm mmm
Yoo ooo ooo ooo, you hear me weep and moan
Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
now for, you since I been gone

I'm gon' get down in this connection, keep on tanglin' with your wires
I'm gon' get down in this connection, oh well, keep on tanglin' with these wires
And when I mash down on your little starter, then your spark plug will give me fire

__________
Note 1: the Terraplane was a 1930's car model of the Hudson Motor Company,
see a picture
and read more about it.



         

         by 
Robert
         Johnson

         recording of 1st of 5 sessions, November 23 1936, San
         Antonio, Texas

         from 
The
         Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 &amp; Columbia/Legacy
         C2K-46222 &amp; Columbia 4622 &amp; Sony
         64916)
, 
copyright
         notice

         
      

   

   

      

         

         And I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan

         When I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan

         Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
, for you since I
         been gone.

         

         I'd said I flash your lights, mama, you horn won't even
         blow

         (spoken: Somebody's been runnin' my batteries down on this
         machine)

         I even flash my lights, mama, this horn won't even blow

         Got a short in this connection, hoo well, babe, it's way
         down below

      

      

         

      

   

   

      

         

         I'm gion' heist your hood, mama, I'm bound to check your
         oil

         I'm goin' heist your hood, mama, mmm, I'm bound to check
         your oil

         I got a woman that I'm lovin', way down in Arkansas

         

         Now, you know the coils ain't even buzzin', little generator
         won't get the spark

         Motor's in a bad condition, you gotta have these batteries
         charged

         But I'm cryin', pleease, pleease don't do me wrong.

         Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
 now for, you
         since I been gone.

         

         Mr. highway man, please don't block the road

         Puh hee hee, please don't block the road

         'Cause she's reachin' a cold one hundred and I'm booked and
         I got to go

         

         Mmm mmm mmm mmm mmm

         Yoo ooo ooo ooo, you hear me weep and moan

         Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
 now for, you
         since I been gone

         

         I'm gon' get down in this connection, keep on tanglin' with
         your wires

         I'm gon' get down in this connection, oh well, keep on
         tanglin' with these wires

         And when I mash down on your little starter, then your spark
         plug will give me fire

         

         __________

         Note 1: the Terraplane was a 1930's car model of the Hudson
         Motor Company, 
see
         a picture
 and read more about it.

      

   














 
 













































(Trying out this banner exchange service)













</lyrics></xml>
