<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Robert Johnson</artist><title> Terraplane Blues</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name>
Robert Johnson

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of 1st of 5 sessions, November 23 1936, San Antonio, Texas

</recordDate><album>from
The Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 &amp; Columbia/Legacy C2K-46222 &amp; Columbia 4622 &amp; Sony 64916)
,
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>

<l>
And I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan

</l>
<l>When I feel so lonesome, you hear me when I moan

</l>
<l>Who been drivin' my Terraplane

1
, for you since I
been gone.




</l>
<l>I'd said I flash your lights, mama, you horn won't even
blow

</l>
<l>(spoken: Somebody's been runnin' my batteries down on this
machine)

</l>
<l>I even flash my lights, mama, this horn won't even blow

</l>
<l>Got a short in this connection, hoo well, babe, it's way

down below


















</l>
<l>I'm gion' heist your hood, mama, I'm bound to check your
oil

</l>
<l>I'm goin' heist your hood, mama, mmm, I'm bound to check
your oil

</l>
<l>I got a woman that I'm lovin', way down in Arkansas



</l>
<l>Now, you know the coils ain't even buzzin', little generator
won't get the spark

</l>
<l>Motor's in a bad condition, you gotta have these batteries
charged

</l>
<l>But I'm cryin', pleease, pleease don't do me wrong.

</l>
<l>Who been drivin' my Terraplane

1
now for, you
since I been gone.




</l>
<l>Mr. highway man, please don't block the road

</l>
<l>Puh hee hee, please don't block the road

</l>
<l>'Cause she's reachin' a cold one hundred and I'm booked and

I got to go




</l>
<l>Mmm mmm mmm mmm mmm

</l>
<l>Yoo ooo ooo ooo, you hear me weep and moan

</l>
<l>Who been drivin' my Terraplane
1
now for, you

</l>
<l>since I been gone



</l>
<l>I'm gon' get down in this connection, keep on tanglin' with
your wires

</l>
<l>I'm gon' get down in this connection, oh well, keep on
tanglin' with these wires

</l>
<l>And when I mash down on your little starter, then your spark

plug will give me fire





</l>

<note>Note 1: the Terraplane was a 1930's car model of the Hudson Motor Company.
</note></lyrics></xml>