<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert King</artist><title> That's What The Blues Is All About</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> Strickland </name><name> Patterson

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1973</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
The
Best Of Albert King (Stax 60-005 or Fantasy
60005)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Oh you come home one eve'nin'

</l>
<l>To nothin' but the four walls

</l>
<l>And then ya find your phone been disconnected

</l>
<l>You can't even make no call

</l>
<l>Ya hung out for your baby, oh, an'she's not there

</l>
<l>You look in the closet, buddy, an'you find it's all bare



</l>
<l>Oh, that's what the blues is people

</l>
<l>That's what the blues is all about

</l>
<l>Well that's a hard pill to have to swallow, um!

</l>
<l>When you find what the blues is all about



</l>
<l>Now listen to this:



</l>
<l>I went out to my backyard

</l>
<l>Ya know I whistled for my dog [3 whistle sounds]

</l>
<l>He ran up under the house, people

</l>
<l>Like he didn't even know me at all

</l>
<l>Now I hadn't fed him in two or three days

</l>
<l>An' he was lookin' kinda thin

</l>
<l>Oh, when your dog turn his back on ya, buddy

</l>
<l>You know ya haven't even got a friend



</l>
<l>That's the blues, people

</l>
<l>That's what the blues is all about

</l>
<l>Oh it's a hard pill to swallow, um!

</l>
<l>When ya find out what the blues is all about



</l>
<l>Oh, look out!

</l>
<l>Uh!

</l>
<l>Oh no!

</l>
<l>I think I got 'em!



</l>
<l>I went out to my mail box

</l>
<l>I got a bunch-a bills that I can't pay

</l>
<l>I guess my wife been out shoppin' again

</l>
<l>While I been at work all day



</l>
<l>I see the man comin' with his tools

</l>
<l>Now is he gonna cut off my water?

</l>
<l>You know they got my gas yesterday

</l>
<l>An' they comin' right back for the lines tomorrow



</l>
<l>Ah, that's what the blues is people

</l>
<l>That's what the blues is all about

</l>
<l>Well that's a hard pill to swallow, buddy

</l><l>Oh, when you find out what the blues is all about</l></lyrics></xml>