<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>B.B. King</artist><title> There's Something On Your Mind</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> 
Cecil
James McNeely

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1993</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Blues
Summit (MCA 10710)
, 
</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>There's something on your mind

</l>
<l>By the way you look at me

</l>
<l>There's something on your mind, baby

</l>
<l>By the way you look at me

</l>
<l>And what you're thinking brings happiness

</l>
<l>Oh and it brings misery



</l>
<l>Please, please, don't try to tell me

</l>
<l>I think, I, I understand

</l>
<l>No, no, don't try to tell me, baby

</l>
<l>'Cause I think, I, I understand

</l>
<l>You want me to try and forget you

</l>
<l>Well, I'll do

</l>
<l>Baby, I'll do the best I can



</l>
<l>You know it hurts you when you're in love with someone and you know

that someone don't love you. It carries a heavy burden on your heart
to know that the someone that you're in love with is in love with
your best friend. And I'll tell you, when someone else is rocking
you, rocking your cradle, you know, better than you can rock your
cradle yourself, then there's only one thing for you to do. You just
pack your clothes, turn around, and slowly walk out of the door. Look
over your left shoulder as you go out, then you hang your head and
you say:




</l>
<l>Oh please don't try to tell me

</l>
<l>Uh huh, I think, I understand

</l>
<l>No, no, no, no

</l>
<l>Please don't try to tell me

</l>
<l>Because you think, you think I understand

</l>
<l>Oh you want me to try

</l>
<l>To try to forget you, baby

</l>
<l>And I'll tell you, I'll do the best I can



</l>
<l>You know after you have done all you could do and you can't take no

more, then you go downtown, you get your big baseball bat and you
come back on the scene where they both are still together, and then
you just go and kick down the door. Now as you kick down the door you
just start beating the hell of everybody that you can see, everybody
that comes through the door, and just as you make up your mind that
you're gonna try to forgive her, then out comes another one of your
friends, and that really blows your mind. So you go and think about,
you say to yourself, baby, I realize I've done wrong but please
forgive me. And with a smirky smile on her face then she look up at
you and she say.




</l>
<l>If you ever think about me

</l>
<l>(Oh I think about you, baby)

</l>
<l>If you ever charge your mind

</l>
<l>(Oh you're staying on my mind, baby)

</l>
<l>If you ever think about me

</l>
<l>(Oh I think, I think about you all the time)

</l>
<l>And if I ever cross your mind

</l>
<l>(You stay on my mind)

</l>
<l>Well, you know, you know

</l>
<l>You know I'm yours

</l>
<l>And I know, I know you got to be mine

</l>
<l>(Yeah)



</l>
<l>There's something on your mind, B.

</l>
<l>I can tell by the way you look at me

</l>
<l>(Oh there's something, on my mind, Miss James)

</l>
<l>There's something on your mind

</l>
<l>(Oh can you tell, there's something on my mind)

</l>
<l>By the way you look at me

</l>
<l>(Oh the way I look at you, you look good to me)

</l>
<l>And what you're thinking brings happiness

</l>
<l>(Yes, baby)

</l>
<l>Oh and it can bring misery

</l>
<l>(Yes, all right)</l></lyrics></xml>