<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><metadata><artist>Albert Collins</artist><title> Too Many Dirty Dishes</title>
<songInfo><songwriter><name> Newton

</name></songwriter><recordDate>recording of <date>1986</date>

</recordDate><album>from 
Cold
Snap (Alligator ALCD-4752)
,

</album></songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>


<l>Too many dirty dishes in the sink for just us two

</l>
<l>I said, too many dirty dishes in the sink for just us two

</l>
<l>You got me wonderin' baby

</l>
<l>Who's makin' dirty dishes with you?



</l>
<l>I get up an' go to work in the mo'nin'

</l>
<l>I come right home at night

</l>
<l>When I leave the sink is empty

</l>
<l>When I come back home

</l>
<l>She got 'em stacked up out of sight



</l>
<l>Too many dirty dishes in the sink just for us two

</l>
<l>Well you got me wonderin' baby,

</l>
<l>Who's makin' dirty dishes with you?



</l>
<l>(Spoken:

</l>
<l>Look at this kitchen!

</l>
<l>Pots an' pans, ev'rywhere, it's pitiful!

</l>
<l>Look at all these glasses layin' all up on the sink!

</l>
<l>Looks like she even had a party up in here, too

</l>
<l>You wait 'til I see this woman, when she get home



</l>
<l>That glass over there, got a cigar in it or sump'in

</l>
<l>I don't smoke no cigar

</l>
<l>Um, servin' caviar

</l>
<l>I don't eat no caviar

</l>
<l>What's wrong with this woman?

</l>
<l>All these pots in here, gonna run me some water right here



</l>
<l>Yeah now, you wait 'til I see this woman when she get home

</l>
<l>Pots 'n pans all stacked up here

</l>
<l>There's a pot, let me scrap this pot out



</l>
<l>Oh it's pitiful an' I don't know why this woman come an' have a
party

</l>
<l>When I'm at work



</l>
<l>Gettin' all this stuff under my fingernails,

</l>
<l>Run some more water in here

</l>
<l>Yeah, now I can wash these glasses out, wash them up first



</l>
<l>Yeah, that's pretty clean now, though

</l>
<l>Now I got all this, now I gotta work on these pots a little bit
more

</l>
<l>Makes me so mad, I don't know what to do



</l>
<l>Thought I was her husband, 'stead a maid!



</l>
<l>Like ol red chili or somethin' all done got dried up on all these

pots




</l>
<l>She never fix me none of this good food!



</l>
<l>You wait 'til that woman get home, I'm scrappin' all these pots for

her)




</l>
<l>Sings:

</l>
<l>I've done your dirty dishes

</l>
<l>How much am I suppose to take?

</l>
<l>When I left I had corn flakes for breakfast

</l>
<l>Now there's a bone from a T-bone steak



</l>
<l>Too many dirty dishes in the sink for just us two

</l>
<l>You've got me wonderin' baby

</l>
<l>Who in the hell is makin' dirty dishes with you?</l></lyrics></xml>