<xml><metadata><artist>Robert Johnson</artist><title> Walkin' Blues</title>
<songInfo>by
Robert Johnson
recording of 3rd of 5 sessions, November 27 1936, San Antonio, Texas
from
The Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 &amp; Columbia/Legacy C2K-46222 &amp; Columbia 4622 &amp; Sony 64916)
,
</songInfo></metadata>
<lyrics>

I woke up this mornin', feelin' round for my shoes
Know 'bout 'at I got these, old walkin' blues
Woke up this mornin', feelin' round for my shoes
But you know 'bout 'at I, got these old walkin' blues

Lord, I feel like blowin' my woh old lonesome horn
Got up this mornin', my little Bernice was gone
Lord, I feel like blow ooohn' my lonesome horn
Well I got up this mornin' woh all I had was gone

Well ah leave this morn' of I have to, woh,
ride the blind
, ah
I've feel mistreated and I don't mind dyin'
Leavin' this morn' ah, I have to ride a blind
Babe, I been mistreated, baby, and I don't mind dyin'

Well, some people tell me that the worried, blues ain't bad
Worst old feelin' I most ever had, some
People tell me that these old worried old blues ain't bad
It's the worst old feelin', I most ever had

She got an Elgin
1
movement from her head down to her toes
Break in on a dollar most anywhere she goes, oooh ooooh
(spoken: To her head down to her toes, oh, honey)
Lord, she break in on a dollar, most anywhere she goes

___________
Note: this song has so many things reminiscent of Son House's style that it's probably a song Robert learned from him. The rhythm, with the short rest before each vocal phrase, has the same work-gang phrasing that Son used in a number of his songs. These songs were so closely linked to their work-gang roots that they were still phrased with that short pause left for what was probably an (pick)axe blow. Chopping songs recorded in southern prisons have this same characteristic form of a short vocal line, the (pick)axes lifting while the songster sings the phrase, then the sharp noise of the (pick)axes hitting the (ground) tree, all of it in a steady, slow rhythm that a strong chain-gang could keep up for hours;
Note 1: only meaning for Elgin I found in was a place in Illinois. However Scott Niedentohl suggests: "I think he's talking about an Elgin watch or clock. It 's a brand name. She's got a real fine, real smooth "movement" - like a fine watch." Thanks to Scott for this contribution. Any idea's on Scott's suggestion?. If so or if anyone knows another more likely meaning, please mail me,
bluesmanharry@bigfoot.com

Top



         

         by 
Robert
         Johnson

         recording of 3rd of 5 sessions, November 27 1936, San
         Antonio, Texas

         from 
The
         Complete Recordings (CBS 467246 2 &amp; Columbia/Legacy
         C2K-46222 &amp; Columbia 4622 &amp; Sony
         64916)
, 
copyright
         notice

         

         I woke up this mornin', feelin' round for my shoes

         Know 'bout 'at I got these, old walkin' blues

         Woke up this mornin', feelin' round for my shoes

         But you know 'bout 'at I, got these old walkin' blues

         

         Lord, I feel like blowin' my woh old lonesome horn

         Got up this mornin', my little Bernice was gone

         Lord, I feel like blow ooohn' my lonesome horn

         Well I got up this mornin' woh all I had was gone

         

         Well ah leave this morn' of I have to, woh, 
ride
         the blind
, ah

         I've feel mistreated and I don't mind dyin'

         Leavin' this morn' ah, I have to ride a blind

         Babe, I been mistreated, baby, and I don't mind dyin'

         

         Well, some people tell me that the worried, blues ain't
         bad

         Worst old feelin' I most ever had, some

         People tell me that these old worried old blues ain't
         bad

         It's the worst old feelin', I most ever had

         

         She got an Elgin
1
 movement from her head down to
         her toes

         Break in on a dollar most anywhere she goes, oooh ooooh

         (spoken: To her head down to her toes, oh, honey)

         Lord, she break in on a dollar, most anywhere she goes

         

         ___________

         Note: this song has so many things reminiscent of Son
         House's style that it's probably a song Robert learned from
         him. The rhythm, with the short rest before each vocal
         phrase, has the same work-gang phrasing that Son used in a
         number of his songs. These songs were so closely linked to
         their work-gang roots that they were still phrased with that
         short pause left for what was probably an (pick)axe blow.
         Chopping songs recorded in southern prisons have this same
         characteristic form of a short vocal line, the (pick)axes
         lifting while the songster sings the phrase, then the sharp
         noise of the (pick)axes hitting the (ground) tree, all of it
         in a steady, slow rhythm that a strong chain-gang could keep
         up for hours;

         Note 1: only meaning for Elgin I found in was a place in
         Illinois. However Scott Niedentohl suggests: "I think he's
         talking about an Elgin watch or clock. It 's a brand name.
         She's got a real fine, real smooth "movement" - like a fine
         watch." Thanks to Scott for this contribution. Any idea's on
         Scott's suggestion?. If so or if anyone knows another more
         likely meaning, please mail me, 
bluesmanharry@bigfoot.com

         
         
Top

      

   














 
 













































(Trying out this banner exchange service)













</lyrics></xml>
