<lyrics>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>Car rides to Malibu</l>
<l>Strawberry ice cream, one spoon for two</l>
<l>And tradin' jackets</l>
<l>Laughin’ 'bout how small it looks on you</l>
<l>(Ha-ha-ha-ha, ha-ha-ha-ha-ha, ha-ha-ha-ha)</l>
<l>Watching reruns of Glee</l>
<l>Bein' annoying, singin’ in harmony</l>
<l>I bet she's braggin' to all her friends, sayin' you're so unique, hmm</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>So when you gonna tell her that we did that, too?</l>
<l>She thinks it's special, but it's all reused</l>
<l>That was our place, I found it first</l>
<l>I made the jokes you tell to her when she's with you</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu when she’s with you?</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu? (Ah) Hmm</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu, huh?</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>Do you call her, almost say my name?</l>
<l>’Cause let's be honest, we kinda do sound the same</l>
<l>Another actress</l>
<l>I hate to think that I was just your type</l>
<l>And I bet that she knows Billy Joel</l>
<l>’Cause you played her "Uptown Girl"</l>
<l>You're singin' it together</l>
<l>Now I bet you even tell her how you love her</l>
<l>In between the chorus and the verse (Ooh; I love you)</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>So when you gonna tell her that we did that, too?</l>
<l>She thinks it's special, but it’s all reused</l>
<l>That was the show we talked about</l>
<l>Played you the songs she's singing now when she's with you</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu when she's with you?</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu? (Oh-oh)</l>
<l>Do you get déjà vu?</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>Strawberry ice cream in Malibu</l>
<l>Don't act like we didn't do that shit, too</l>
<l>You're tradin' jackets like we used to do</l>
<l>(Yeah, everything is all reused)</l>
<l>Play her piano, but she doesn't know (Oh, oh)</l>
<l>That I was the one who taught you Billy Joel (Oh)</l>
<l>A different girl now, but there's nothing new</l>
</section>
<section type="outro">
<l>I know you get déjà vu</l>
<l>I know you get déjà vu</l>
<l>I know you get déjà vu</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
