<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--AHHHHHHHHH-->
<root>
    <title>Country Loaf (Pain de Campagne)</title>

    <authorInfo>
        <author>
            <name part="first">Deb</name>
            <name part="last">Lindsey</name>
        </author>
        <publisher>for The Washington Post</publisher>
    </authorInfo>

    <date>SEP 10, 2014</date>
    <intro>
        <para>Washington author Sam Fromartz has been making sourdough variations of this yeast
            bread for years. Here, he adds fermented cider for flavor. A mild beer may be
            substituted; an IPA would be too bitter. The loaf is sized to last a few days.</para>

        <prep>
            <para>The optional tablespoon of water is to compensate for the variable absorption of
                the rye and whole-wheat flours. You'll need a colander, a pastry cloth or clean dish
                towel and a covered cast-iron or enameled cast-iron pot.</para>

            <para>Make Ahead: The dough needs four
                    <time><quant>20</quant>-<unit>minute</unit></time> rests, plus an
                        <time><quant>8-to-24</quant>-<unit>hour</unit></time> stay in the
                refrigerator and a final <time><quant num="1.5">1
                    1/2</quant>-<unit>hour</unit></time> rise. </para>
            <para>Storage Notes: Store the cooled loaf in a paper bag for a day, and store in a
                plastic bag for a few days after that. Do not refrigerate.</para>
        </prep>
    </intro>

    <servingsInfo><heading>SERVINGS:</heading>
        <size type="tested">Tested size:<quantity> 10-12</quantity><unit> servings</unit>;</size>
        makes one 11-ounce loaf 10 to 12 slices</servingsInfo>

    <IngredientList>
        <heading>INGREDIENTS</heading>
        <li>
            <measure>
                <quant num="1.25">1 1/4</quant>
                <unit>cups</unit>
                <alt>(<quant>160</quant>
                    <unit>grams</unit>)</alt>
            </measure>
            <material> white bread flour, plus more for dusting</material>
        </li>
        <li>
            <measure><quant num="0.25">1/4</quant>
                <unit>cup</unit> (<quant>38</quant>
                <unit>grams</unit>)</measure>
            <material>stone-ground whole-wheat flour</material>
        </li>
        <li>
            <measure><quant num="0.25">1/4</quant>
                <unit>cup</unit> (<quant>32</quant>
                <unit>grams</unit>)</measure>
            <material> stone-ground whole rye flour</material>
        </li>
        <li>
            <measure>
                <quant num="0.5">1/2</quant>
                <unit>teaspoon</unit>
            </measure>
            <material> instant yeast or bread machine yeast</material>
        </li>
        <li>
            <measure>
                <quant num="1">1</quant>
                <unit>teaspoon</unit>
            </measure>
            <material>table salt</material>
        </li>
        <li>
            <measure><quant num="0.25">1/4</quant>
                <unit>cup</unit> (<quant>55</quant>
                <unit>grams</unit>)</measure>
            <material>dry fermented cider (may substitute Pilsener beer; see headnote)</material>
        </li>
        <li><measure><quant num="0.5">1/2</quant>
                <unit>cup</unit> (<quant>120</quant><unit> grams</unit>) <material>lukewarm
                    water</material> (<quant>80</quant>
                <unit>degrees</unit>),</measure> plus an optional <quant>1</quant><unit>
                tablespoon</unit></li>
    </IngredientList>
    <heading>DIRECTIONS</heading>
    <instructions>
        <step num="1">Whisk together the <material>flours, yeast and salt</material> in a mixing bowl.
            Combine the <material>cider and water</material> in a liquid measuring cup.</step>

        <step num="2">Add the liquid to the <material>flour mixture</material>; use a spatula or
            bench scraper or your hand moistened with water to blend them for about <time>a
                    <unit>minute</unit></time>. The dough should be shaggy yet cohesive. Cover the
            bowl with a towel; let the dough rest for <time><quant>20</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit></time>.</step>

        <step nume="3">Moisten your kneading hand. If the dough seems stiff, add the optional
            tablespoon of water. Stretch one edge of the dough (still in the bowl), then press it
            into the center of the bowl. Repeat this about a dozen times, moving clockwise to catch
            all sides of the dough. (This should take <time><quant>1 or 2</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit>.</time>)</step>

        <step num="4">Turn the dough over so the seams are on the bottom. Cover and let rest for
                    <time><quant>20</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit></time>. Repeat the clockwise stretching and folding two more
            times, with <time>20-<unit>minute</unit></time> rests after each. Cover and refrigerate
            at least <time><quant>8</quant>
                <unit>hours</unit></time> and up to <time><quant>24</quant>
                <unit>hours</unit></time>. The dough should have doubled. If it hasn't, leave it on
            the counter until it does.</step>

        <step num="5">Lightly flour a work surface. Use a pastry cloth or clean dish towel to line a
            round colander. Dust the cloth with flour.</step>

        <step num="6">Transfer the dough to the floured work surface. Fold the edges toward the center
            to create a round shape, turning it over so the seams are on the bottom. Let it rest for
                <time>5 <unit>minutes</unit></time>, then transfer to the colander, seam side up.
            Cover with a towel and let the dough rise for <time><quant num="1.5">1 1/2</quant>
                <unit>hours</unit></time>.</step>

        <step num="7"><time><quant>Thirty</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit></time> before baking, place a cast-iron Dutch oven (lid on) or
            enameled cast-iron pot with a lid (on) in the oven; preheat to
                    <temperature><quant>475</quant>
                <unit>degrees</unit></temperature>.</step>

        <step num="8">Carefully remove the hot pot from the oven.</step>

        <step num="9">Turn the dough out onto the counter so the seams are on the bottom. Use kitchen
            scissors to make 8 snips on the top of the dough in an evenly spaced spoke pattern, each
            about <quant num="0.25">1/4</quant>-<unit>inch</unit> deep. Lift the dough and carefully
            drop it into the hot pot. Immediately cover with the hot lid. Bake for
                    <time><quant>30</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit></time>, then reduce the heat to <temperature><quant>450</quant>
                <unit>degrees</unit></temperature>. Uncover and bake for <time><quant>8 to
                    10</quant>
                <unit>minutes</unit></time> or until the crust is dark brown. Try to minimize the
            amount of time the oven door is open.</step>

        <step num="10">The bread is done when its internal temperature registers
                    <temperature><quant>205</quant>
                <unit>degrees</unit></temperature> on an instant-read thermometer and the loaf
            sounds hollow when knocked on the underside.</step>

        <step num="11">Transfer the loaf to a wire rack to cool for at least <time><quant>1</quant>
                <unit>hour</unit></time> before cutting.</step>
    </instructions>
</root>
