<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle><fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Gets an</epTitle><szn>10</szn>x<epNum>07</epNum></ep>
<date>11/27/98</date> <runtime>04:10</runtime></metadata>

<music>♪<stage> Chorus Singing </stage></music>

<stage> Bell Ringing </stage>

<stage> Whistle Blowing </stage>

<stage> Beeping </stage>

<music>♪ <stage>Jazzy Solo </stage></music>

<stage> Beeping </stage>

<stage> Tires Screeching </stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>! <stage> Screams </stage>

<stage> Air Blowing </stage>

And may we burn in painful and foul-smelling f*re... forever and ever.

A... Men-nonite minister... will be giving a guest sermon next Sunday.<stage>/i</stage>

Go in peace.

A- <stage> Coughing </stage>

Don't make me come up there. men.

Whoo-hoo.!

<stage> <person>Moe</person> </stage> Let me outta here. The guy never stops talking.

<stage> Stomach Grumbling </stage>

Oh! I'm starving.

Mom, can we go Catholic so we can get Communion wafers and booze?

No. No one's going Catholic.

Three children is enough, thank you.

Hang in there, Son. I'm taking us out... for our traditional Sunday brunch.

<stage> Driver</stage> Idiot!

He zinged you, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

<stage> Giggling </stage>

<stage> Gasps </stage>

Brunch is served.

<stage> Gulping, Chomping </stage>

I feel guilty coming here every Sunday... and never actually buying anything.

Why? We're following the rules. <stage> Chomping </stage>

If it has a toothpick in it, it's free.

Hey!

<stage> Gargling </stage>

Ah. This is my kind of aisle.

Soy substitute. "Whizless" cheese.

<stage> Gasps </stage> Oven-roasted cud.

It's packed in its own drool.

Gavin, honey, help Mommy pick a cereal.

Oh. How about Alfalfa-Bits?

Those suck! I hate this store!

But, sweetheart, Mommy-

I hate you too!

I wanna live with one of my dads.

Mmm!

So, you say this product is known as "fudge"?

Yes.Just like it was last week.

If you're gonna get snippy, I'll take my business elsewhere.

"Jerry Garcia"? <stage> Groans </stage>

"Honey Bono"? "Desmond Tutti-frutti"? Eh!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, help Daddy find some normal flavors. <stage> Strains </stage>

"Candy Warhol." "Xavier Nougat."

Naw. Nothin' made of d*ad guys.

What's in the back? <stage> Grunts </stage>

<stage> Yelps, Shivering </stage>

Hurry up. My hands are getting cold.

Ah-choo!

Oh, my goodness!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, get her out of there.

Aw!

<stage> Teeth Chattering </stage>

<stage> Groans </stage> "Sherbert Hoover"?

We've gotta get you home to a warm blanket and a cold compress.

Ooh. <stage>Jabbering </stage>

<stage> Clears Throat </stage> Those are eight dollars a pound, sport.

Eight dollars a pound times, say, oh, five pounds is, um-

Let's see. How many pounds in a gallon?

Oh, I can't afford that.

<stage> Gasps </stage> Unless-

Ah-choo!

<stage> Chuckling </stage> I told you. I'm a financial genius.

I buy an eight-dollar lobster... fatten it into an 80-dollar lobster and eat the profits.

Lobsters need saltwater.

I'm way ahead of you.

<stage> Murmurs </stage>

<stage> <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> </stage> Dad, the fish.!

Son, I'm still fine-tuning.

Uh, uh- Uh-oh.

Uh. Uh. Perfect.

Ah-choo!

Oh, you don't sound so good.

We'd better get you some cold medicine.

No problem.

I picked some up at the store.

<stage> Sighs </stage>

Oh, <fam>Homie</fam>. You made breakfast.

Nothin's too good for my one and only.

Eat! Eat! You're nothing but skin and bones.

Ah-choo! <stage> Groans </stage>

<stage> Blows Nose </stage>

How are you feeling, sweetie?

Much better. Ah-choo!

Oh, my. You're burning up.

I'm going to tell the school you're staying home.

I'm afraid I can't allow that.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>!

Mom! No, wait. We can make a deal.

You don't have anything I want.

Oh.

<stage> Man Narrating </stage> The ocean abounds with fearsome creatures... but none att*cks its prey with more fury... than the seaweed shark.

The struggle is soon over.

Oh, you shouldn't be watching The Learning Channel.

You need to take it easy.

But I'm hardly learning at all.

Why don't you play with one of <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s video games instead?

Hugh Downs says they're the latest craze.

<music>♪ <stage> Game Soundtrack </stage></music>

<stage> Sighs </stage>

<stage> Chortling </stage>

<stage> Aussie Accent </stage> Foolish dingo.

You must find and devour the seven crystal babies... or spend eternity trapped in deep didgeridoo!

I am so scared.

All right. I guess you're supposed to go through this stupid door.

Hmm. I wonder what's in this glowing barrel.

<stage> Shrieking </stage>

What? Nunchakus? Those aren't even Australian.

<music>♪ <stage> Funeral March </stage></music>

Oh, great. So I'm d*ad now.

Fine. I'm sick of this stupid game anyway.

Yes.! I am just four power wands away from an antigravity lozenge.

Hope I don't run into that weird little troll.

Hi, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

No! Pause! Pause!

I brought your homework. We have to read this.

"The Wind in the Willows"?

It's about a toad and a badger and a mole.

I drawed on mine. <stage> Chuckles </stage>

Is this my house?

No. You live in a different house.

Choo, choo, choo, choo! Woo-wooo!

And I shall rule the "down under-verse!" <stage> Chortling </stage>

We'll see about that, mate.

Okay. Together, we weigh 300 pounds.

According to my driver's license, I weigh I 40 pounds.

That means that you weigh, oh- 1 60 pounds!

Oh! You're doin' great.

No, no. Yes, that's it! Bite! Bite! Bite!

<stage> Knocking </stage> <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>?

<stage> Snoring </stage>

Oh, sweetie, you look so much better.

Ready to go back to school?

<stage> Weakly </stage> Oh, I don't know.

<stage> Coughs </stage> I mean, I could risk it, but-

No, no. You just stay put.

Wow. You didn't even feel her forehead.

How do I get that kind of credibility?

With eight years of scrupulous honesty.

Eh. It's not worth it.

Oh, I really need one more day, Mom.

I think the germs are regrouping.

Now, for breakfast, I'll have hash browns, coffee and a short stack.

And would it k*ll you to heat up the syrup?

<stage> Tires Screech </stage>

But I- I might infect the other kids.

That's a risk I'm willing to take.

So long!

Welcome back, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. I trust you got the homework I assigned.

The Wind in the Willows? Oh, yeah. <person>Ralph</person> brought it over.

Perfect. Then I won't need to excuse you from the test.

<stage> Gulp </stage> Test?

<stage> Aussie Accent </stage> Game over, mate.

<stage> Sighs </stage>

Okay, all right.

You can bluff your way through one test.

Mr. Toad has a red blank. Okay. Skip that one.

Mr. blank needs a blank in order to blank his blank.

Oh, I am in deep blank.

And the lowest grade in the class-

She's gonna say my name!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Simpson- zero.

<stage> Gasps </stage>

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, the president of Harvard would like a word with you.

Nasty business that zero.

Naturally, Harvard's doors are now closed to you.

But I'll pass your file along to- <stage> Snickers </stage> Brown.

Mmm. Heck of a school. Weren't you at Brown, Otto?

Yep. Almost got tenure too.

<stage> Gasps </stage> No! Not Brown!

<stage> Echoing </stage> Brown. Brown. Brown.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, you're saying "Brown" an awful lot. Are you okay?

Well, actually, I do feel a little feverish.

Aw, don't worry about the test. Just get yourself a nice drink of water.

Then come back and finish the test.

<stage> Gasps </stage>

I need a miracle. Come on. You owe me.

'Sup, Sis?

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, shouldn't you be in class?

I am. It's a little something I whipped up in shop. Mostly latex.

What are you doin' out here?

We've got a test, and I didn't read the book.

I'll get a zero for sure. <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, what do I do?

Well, if it was me, I'd just take the zero.

<stage> Growls </stage>

Uh, but that's not for everyone.

There's one other possibility.

Hey! I can't go in there.

Relax. There's nothing here you didn't see when Dad boycotted pants.

<stage> <person>Nelson</person> </stage> Hang on. I'll buzz you in.

Buzz.!

Teacher and subject.

Miss Hoover. Wind in the Willows.

<music>♪ <stage> Humming </stage></music>

Oh. Here we go.

<stage> Gasps </stage> Oh, my God! These are the answers to the test.

I don't wanna cheat.

Hey, hey. These are study aids.

They're for novelty purposes only.

If a few bad apples use 'em for cheating, I can't be held responsible.

Forget it. I'd rather get a zero.

Good for you, lass.

I got me a zero once, and my life turned out just fine.

Ach! Whoa-ho!

That's a nasty clog.

Ooh, you've got yourself a partner, have ya?

Yah!

Keep the change.
Come here, you slippery rascals.

Good news, my delicious friend.

You're going to be a free-range lobster.

Come on, boy. Dig in.

They'll give you a big, strong thorax.

Wh-Whoa!

Why, you little-

<stage> Whimpers </stage>

Oh, look at him cower. Just like the boy.

I can't stay mad at such a helpless little mammal.

<stage> Giggles </stage> I'm gonna get you for that, you little scamp.

Here! Yeh! Take that, Pinchy.

<stage> Giggling </stage>

I graded this morning's test over lunch... and most of you did quite well.

I got a "B."

No, <person>Ralph</person>. That's an "F." I must have spilled some Kahlua.

Perfect, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. And you got all the extra-credit questions... even the one that got cut off by the copy machine.

Well, I guess I was just on a roll. <stage> Whimpers </stage>

Don't be so modest, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

You earned that A-plus-plus-plus.

Actually there are four pluses.

No. That's Drambuie. Mmm!

Oh, so plump andjuicy.

Mmm! He's gonna boil up nicely. <stage> Slurps </stage>

Well, I guess this is it, old pal. This is your big day.

Water's boiling. Quick. Chuck him in.

Uh-

Come on. Chuck him in.

Okay.

Let's go. In the pot. In the pot.

<stage> Murmurs </stage>

<stage> Cooing </stage>

But, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, look at this little guy.

<stage> Gasps </stage>

<stage> Growling, Hissing </stage>

Looks like an ordinary- Ow! Son of a-

Feel that, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>? He likes you.

And now for the main course- steamed <location>Maine</location> cabbages!

<stage> Clears Throat </stage> Pardon me for asking... but where the hell's my stupid lobster?

We're not eating Mr. Pinchy. He's part of the family now.

<stage> Grunts </stage>

Pinchy, I made you some risotto.

What? You gotta be kidding me!

Dad!

What's your problem, veggie? You don't even eat lobster.

No, but I enjoy the smell.

Lobster or no lobster, this is still a very special dinner.

Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> broke her own record by two whole pluses.

Mom! Where did you get that?

It just turned up in the course of my daily rummaging.

By the way, I oiled the hinge on your diary.

Aren't you proud of your big sister, Mr. Pinchy? Hmm? Hmm?

Oh! I am sick of everyone being so proud of me!

That's my girl.

<stage> <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> </stage> Cheer up, Lise.

You got a good grade without even reading the book. That's win-win.

Can't you see the difference between earning something honestly... and getting it by fraud?

Hmm. I suppose, maybe, if, uh-

No. No, sorry. I thought I had it there for a sec.

<stage> Bell Rings </stage>

Psst. <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, check it out. Tomorrow's fraction quiz.

I'll give you the numerators free... but the denominators are gonna cost ya.

I don't want your dirty denominators.

Well, la-di-da, Lady "Cheaterly."

Can I at least keep you in my Rolodex?

No.

I never cheated before, and I never will again.

Oh, I almost wish I hadn't gotten away with it.

<stage> <person>Skinner</person> On P.A.</stage> <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Simpson, report to the principal's office... to discuss the results of yesterday's test.

We never met.

I'vejust received some rather unusual news... regarding your unprecedented A-triple-plus.

To be honest, I'm surprised and saddened-

N-No. Not "saddened." What's the word?

Ah, yes. "Delighted."

What?

I'm delighted to report that your grade... brought the entire school's G.P.A. up to our state's minimum standard.

We now qualify for a basic assistance grant.

It's the greatest honor the school has ever received...

and it's all thanks to you.

Your devotion to scholarship is a shining beacon to all who-

Stop it! I cheated!

Cheated! Cheated! Cheated! Cheated! Cheated!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, what are you trying to say?

I cheated!

<stage> Gasps </stage>

<stage> <person>Skinner</person> </stage> You cheated?

Oh, Lordy, Lordy, Lordy. Why didn't Miss Hoover tell me?

She doesn't know. You're the only one I've told.

Well, then, one could make the argument... that there really is no problem.

But what I did was wrong.

Oh, very much so.

But as long as we handle this in a mature and, above all, quiet manner... we'll still get that grant money.

<stage> Chuckling </stage> Oh, you really scared me there.

But we can't accept that money. It's tainted.

Now, now. Leave the money out of this.

It's not the money's fault you cheated.

Besides, I've already started spending it. Check out the new scoreboard.

<music>♪ <stage> Fanfare </stage></music>

<stage> Crowd </stage> Charge!

<stage> Chuckling </stage> I'm still learning all the buttons.

Well, if you're gonna cover this up...

I'll just have to go over your head to Super- <stage> Loud Buzzer </stage> intendant- <stage> Loud Buzzer</stage> Chalmers!

<stage> Incoming Whistle </stage>

<stage> Loud expl*si*n </stage>

<person>Skinner</person>! I am outraged that you've kept this from me.

You were supposed to call as soon as the new scoreboard was in.

Tell me, does it play that song "Charge"?

Oh, does it ever.

You can't keep this scoreboard.

Because there's not gonna be any grant money.

Because I cheated!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, let's take a walk.

A little traveling music, Seymour.

<music>♪ <stage> "Charge" Stomp </stage></music>

Uh! Good Lord, what a dump.

<stage> Dog Barking </stage>

<stage> Cat Screeching </stage>

It's not surprising. This school was once classified... the most dilapidated in all of Missouri.

<stage> Together</stage> Hmm? Huh?

That's why it was shut down and moved here, brick by brick.

Look around, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. That grant money could do a lot of good.

Don't you think those youngsters deserve a regulation tetherball?

Ow!

Ohh!

We can buy real periodic tables... instead of these promotional ones from Oscar Mayer.

Who can tell me the atomic weight of"balonium?"

Ooh. "Dee-licious"?

Correct.

I would also accept "snack-tacular."

And for the first time ever, our computer lab actually has a computer in it.

<stage> Typing Slowly </stage>

Hi, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. Hi, Super Nintendo Chalmers.

<stage> Beeps </stage>

<stage> Meow </stage>

I'm "learnding."

Aw, way to go, <person>Ralph</person>.

Oh, she's a beaut. You can't b*at a Coleco.

How many can I put you down for? A lot?

Please say a lot. I need this.

I don't know. I'm not even sure we can keep this one.

It's up to <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

What do you say, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>?

Will you keep our little secret for the good of your classmates and your school?

And let's not forget old <person>Gil</person>, huh?

The wolf's at old <person>Gil</person>'s door.

Oh, I guess I don't have much choice.

Oh, thank God! Now let's talk rustproofing.

These Colecos will rust up on you like that.

Shut up, <person>Gil</person>. Close the deal. Close the deal.

Relax, boy. We're not gonna cook you.

Enjoy your day at the beach.

Ooh! Look, here's a little playmate for you.

<stage> Yelps, Whimpering </stage>

Hey, you don't have to take that from no punk-ass crab.

What's wrong with you?

Arr! It's not his fault he's a sissy.

Someone's been coddling him.

Don't look at me. I wanted to eat him.

Sorry. It's usually the mother.

You know, I run a small academy for lobsters like this one.

We stress tough love- daily chores and the like.

No. We're not sending the lobster away to some snobby boarding school.

Arr. I understand. It's hard to let go.

Uh, tell me this then. Do you have any spare change?

And now to present the grant money... a legendary figure in educational disbursement-

State Comptroller Atkins.

<stage> Applauding </stage>

Whoo!

<stage> Flashbulbs <location>Popping</location> </stage>

Thank you. I'm here tonight to honor the girl... whose unprecedented test score has set a new standard in excellence.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

<stage> Applause, Cheering </stage>

Thank you. I know this giant check is very important to everyone here... but what's even more important is the truth.

What?

Huh?

<stage> Murmuring </stage>

Because, after all, education is the search for truth.

No. No, it isn't. Don't listen to her. She's out of her mind.

And the truth is we don't deserve this grant... and I don't deserve your applause.

I cheated on that test.

<stage> Gasping, Booing </stage>

Wait! How dare you condemn this girl?

Who among you can honestly say you've never cheated?

On your wives or your husbands.

<stage> All Murmuring </stage>

What she just did took courage.

And where I come from- <location>Canada</location>- we reward courage.

So I hereby decree that you keep the grant... and let's give this brave girl the ovation she deserves.

<stage> Applauding, Cheering </stage>

Oh, honey, I'm so proud of you.

You got the highest grade in the class.

But, Mom-

The highest grade.

Okay. <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>'s gone.

Places, people.

<stage> Straining </stage> Man! Acting is tough.

I'll be in my trailer.

Oh, good old predictable <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

I knew her conscience was a ticking time b*mb.

Heads up! Here comes the real comptroller.

This grant ensures a lightbulb in every classroom... and a high-definition TV for the teachers' lounge.

<stage> Flashbulbs <location>Popping</location> </stage>

<stage> Applause, Cheering </stage><stage>/i</stage>

Now, where's the little girl who made this grant possible?

Where's <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Simpson?

<stage> Microphone Feedback </stage>

<stage> Scattered Applause </stage>

Come on up here, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

Well, how about that? Smart and modest.

Well, I should be going now. These giant checks don't hand themselves out.

Okay, people, let's have a round of applause... for the real comptroller.

<stage> Applause, Cheering </stage><stage>/i</stage>

Hmm?

Idiot.

I know a liquor store where we can cash this right now.

<stage> Cheering </stage>

And so. That's one grade I truly earned.

<stage> Groans </stage> Who left these muddy claw prints on my clean floor?

Sorry, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>. Pinchy got all dirty in the yard chasing birds.

But don't worry. I put him in a nice hot bath.

<stage> Sniffs </stage> Hey, what smells so good?

Yeah- Pinchy?

Pinchy? Oh!

Pinchy! <stage> Whimpering </stage>

<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Sobbing </stage>

<stage> Sobbing Continues </stage>

Oh, man, that's good.

<stage> Sobbing </stage> Oh, pass the butter.

<stage> Sobbing </stage>

<stage> Chomping, Swallows </stage>

Are you gonna eat that all by yourself?

<stage> Whimpering </stage> Uh-huh. Pinchy would've wanted it this way.

My dear, sweet Pinchy.

No more pain where you are now, boy.

<stage> Grunting </stage>

<stage> Cracking </stage>

<stage> Slurps </stage> Oh, God! That's tasty.

I wish Pinchy were here to enjoy this.

<stage> Sobbing </stage>

<stage> Chomping </stage>

<stage> Whimpering </stage> Oh, Pinchy.

<stage> Murmuring </stage>

Shh!
</txt></xml>