<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Make Room For <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam></epTitle><szn>10</szn>x<epNum>16</epNum></ep>
<date>03/05/99</date> <runtime>15:53</runtime></metadata>

<music>♪<stage> Chorus Singing </stage></music>

<stage> Bell Ringing </stage>

<stage> Whistle Blowing </stage>

<stage> Beeping </stage>

<music>♪ <stage>Jazzy Solo </stage></music>

<stage> Beeping </stage>

<stage> Tires Screeching </stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>! <stage> Screams </stage>

<stage> All Grunting </stage>

<stage> Bird Cawing </stage>

<stage> Man On Radio </stage> Okay, F.D.R. is in <location>the White House</location>... an ice-cream cone costs a nickel... and a hot new tune by Benny Goodman is hitting the charts.

The year is I 939.

<stage> Snoring </stage>

<music>♪ <stage> Swing </stage></music>

1 9- I 939?

Oh, my God! I've gone back in time!

I've got to warn everybody about h*tler!

And get to the ice-cream store!

Hey, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, what's all the hubbub?

Let me guess. You travel back in time again?

Shut up! You haven't even been born yet!

Easy, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>. I'll bring you back.

<stage> Stations Changing </stage>

<music>♪ <stage> New Wave Rock </stage></music>

Ohh!

Oh, boy, am I glad to see you guys.

<stage> Man </stage> That was Men Without Hats.

Or as they're known today, Men Without Jobs.

<stage> Men Laughing </stage>

<stage> Man 2 </stage> Don't go there, Marty!

I'm not goin' anywhere.

I'm staying right here at P.J. O'Harrigan's.

<stage> Crowd Whooping </stage>

We're broadcasting live from P.J. O'H.'s... and this place makes Animal House look like Terms of Endearment.

We're kicking off our 3 5th consecutive happy hour with no end in sight.

So come on down.

<stage> Cheering </stage>

Yeah, that sounds like a swingin' shindig.

Yeah, too bad we gotta work, huh, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?

<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> On Radio </stage> Whoo-hoo! Let's <location>party</location>!

Wake up, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

<stage> Groans </stage>

Come on! Move your butt. You're blocking traffic.

<stage> Horn Honking </stage>

That's no way to address Sir Drinks-a-Lot.

<stage> Groans </stage> Come on.

<stage> Horns Honking </stage>

Let's get you inside and scrape the gum out of your hair.

Okay. Hey, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

What's your favorite radio station?

Well, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>?

What?

What's your favorite radio station?

Okay, Dad, we're ready!

Okay, Dad, we're ready!

Hey, that's super. See you later.

Dad, don't you remember? It's our special Saturday.

You agreed to spend one Saturday a month doing something with the kids.

Ohh!

Oh, quit complaining. It's half the work of a divorced dad.

Yeah, but it's twice as much as a deadbeat dad.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

They know I'm kidding.

<stage> Both Groan </stage>

Okay, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, it's your turn to pick.

Where are we headed? Bowling? Demolition derby? P.J. O'Harrigan's?

Isn't that a funny name? Huh? Huh?

Hysterical. But I traded my turn to <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> for her dessert.

Oh! We did a <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> thing last month!

<stage> Groans </stage>

<stage> Chuckles </stage> And I'm glad we did.

But now I think we should do something normal people would like.

Why do you assume that I won't pick something fun?

Let's see.

Oh, this looks very educational.

Oh!

Well, this could be quite enlightening.

Ohh!

Fine, how about-

Ohh!

She didn't say it yet!

Go ahead, sweetie.

The book fair.

Oh, no! I'm not falling for that again!

If it doesn't have Siamese twins in a jar, it's not a fair.

Oh! This is perfect!

We're gonna go see Marmaduke?

No. The Smithsonian traveling exhibit.

It encapsulates <location>America</location> and makes history come alive!

What? And Marmaduke doesn't?

Sorry, Dad. My mind is made up.

This is all your fault for trading away your turn! Just for that, no dessert tonight!

Trade you my next turn for your dessert.

Deal.

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

Hey, how come the Smithsonian... needs to be sponsored by a cell phone company?

I can answer that. Uncle Sam needs to spend our tax dollars on the essentials: antitobacco programs, pro-tobacco programs... k*ll wild donkeys and lsrael.

Good old government.

Yeah, but corporate sponsorship cheapens our nation's treasures.

Actually, they're Omnitouch's treasures now.

We bought 'em during the last budget crisis.

<stage> Gasps </stage> Look, they have Lincoln's hat.

Thank God for grave robbers.

Oh, <location>America</location>'s greatest citizen... summed up in one piece of clothing.

<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Gasps </stage> Fonzie's jacket.!

Who's Fonzie?

Who's Fonzie?

Don't they teach you anything in school? He freed the squares.

How can they put a prop from a TV show next to the Bill of Rights?

So what's so great about the Bill of Rights?

It guarantees all of the basic freedoms- speech, religion, the right to a speedy trial.

<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> </stage> Where? I don't see that.

<stage> Alarm Buzzing </stage>

<stage> Gasps </stage> Dad, don't do that!

<stage> Rips </stage>

Hmm, hmm.

Get out of Archie Bunker's chair now!

<stage> Gasping </stage> Relax.

I'm just boning up on the old Constitution.

<stage> Rips </stage>

Oh, you're gonna regret that, pinko!

<stage> Yelps </stage>

Oh, I am so sick of people hiding behind the Bill of Rights!

Look! He got chocolate on it!

I didn't mean to.

Look!

Mm-hmm. You just licked off the part that forbids cruel and unusual punishment.

<stage> Chuckles </stage> Beautiful.

Really? That much?

It's gonna cost $1 0,000 to repair that document.

Wha-

Of course, Omnitouch understands that real money doesn't grow on trees- not these days.

Finally a company that understands my needs.

We sure do. It's called caring.

So we're even then?

Not by a long sh*t.

But I have a solution that'll work out for both of us, especially you.

<stage> Man Shouts, Indistinct </stage>

I don't want a cellular transmitter sticking out of my roof.

We prefer to think of them as "keep in touch" towers.

It's called caring, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.

Plus you've increased <location>Springfield</location>'s roaming capabilities 64%.

You gotta admit, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, that's a lot more roaming.

<stage> Groans </stage> I guess.

<stage> Grunting </stage>

Hey, this is pretty comfortable.

That Andy Capp was onto something.

Uh! That antenna is an eyesore.

Just pretend it's a tree, honey. Or as we say at Omnitouch, a progress tree.

Yeah? Well, I hope it doesn't hum too loud. I have a ton of homework to do.

And if I don't finish it by- <stage> Screams </stage>

My room.!

<stage> Electronic Beeping </stage>

What? I heard a yell! Did you touch a wire?

What happened to my room?

Nothing. They just needed a place to put all the electronic gizmos... and I know how much you like that science-y stuff.

So I de-

You gave away my room?

Come on, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. Try and see this from the Omnitouch Corporation's point of view.

Your father's right, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. Cellular service is about communication and unity- community.

Hmm?

<stage> Groans </stage>

I can't believe you did this, Dad.

Why didn't you put that thing in your room?

Hmm. That thought never occurred to me.

Funny how your mind works in a crisis.

It's just until we pay off Daddy's desecration of a priceless artifact.

I thought I'd never have to say that again.

But where am I supposed to live?

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, what's your favorite movie?

Until you taped over it, The Little Mermaid.

That's right, The Odd Couple.!

So meet your comically mismatched roommate, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> Simpson!

<music>♪ <stage> Scatting TVTheme </stage></music>

I'm gonna make your life a living hell.

<stage> Groans </stage>

<music>♪ <stage> Continues </stage></music>

But, Dad!

Whoa!

<music>♪<stage> Fades, Ends </stage></music>

Okay, if you're gonna live in my room, you're gonna obey my rules.

One: I am <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, thy god.

If I am out, the <person>Krusty</person> doll is thy god.

If the doll's with me, you will worship the night-light.

Should the night-light be unable to fulfill its duties-

Shut up.

You shut up!

<stage> Sighs </stage> This is not gonna work.

No, you shut up!

Ohh!

<stage> Sucking </stage>

<stage> <person>Skinner</person></stage> Hello, Mother?

<stage> Gasps </stage> <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>?

Seymour, you were supposed to call me three minutes ago.

Ooh!

Sorry, Mother. I was driving through a tunnel, and my cell phone wouldn't work.

I don't want you driving through tunnels! You know what that symbolizes!

But, Mother, it cuts 90 minutes off my drive.

No tunnels!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, we're picking up cell-phone calls over the baby monitor.

Ooh! Anything spicy?

Oh, that's not the point.

We should report this to an Omnitouch care rep. People's privacy is at stake.

Great. I'm gonna eat mayonnaise.

<stage> Groans </stage>

<stage> Squeaking </stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, stop it!

Stop what?

Squeaking that chair.

Hey, that's what I do in my room, Lise. I squeak my chair.

<stage> Grunts </stage> Oh, quit it, quit it, quit it, quit it!

Well, well, if it isn't Frick and Frack, Jack and Jill, Fred and Ethel, the Three-

Dad, will you please tell <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> to stop squeaking his chair?

I'm trying to do my homework!

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, stop squeaking your chair.

If you've got to do something, click this pen.

<stage> Clicking </stage>

No-o-o!

Hey, that looks like fun.

Race ya.

You're on! <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, you play winner!

<stage> Laughing </stage> Come on, come on!

I'm gaining on ya! <stage> Laughing </stage>

Oh, honey, you missed a great race.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> was winning. Then he said, "This is stupid." And he stopped, and I won!

Dad, I am trying to do my homework.

Hmm. Hey, you're mad at me. That wasn't your mayonnaise, was it?

Dad, why did you have to take away my room?

Maybe you'd feel better if we watched some TV together.

<stage> Groans </stage> I just want to study!

That's no fun.

It is to me.

No, it's not.

Dad!
Ooh, here's something you'll like: When Animals att*ck Magicians.

<stage> Man </stage> Pick a card. Any- <stage> Screaming </stage>

<stage> Chimpanzee Screeching </stage>

No, no.! Pick another card.!

<stage> Laughing </stage>

That's awful.

Awful entertaining.

<stage> Stomach Rumbles </stage>

Oh, my stomach hurts.

<stage> On Monitor</stage> Hey, it's <person>Krusty</person>. I need you to get me out of another jam.

I picked up this chick last night. At least I thought she was a chick.

Showbiz is so fascinating.

<stage> Groans </stage> Mom, I don't feel so good.

<stage> Stomach Rumbling </stage>

<stage> Groaning </stage>

What is it, honey?

My tummy really hurts.

Somebody wants Mommy to change baby's diaper!

Is that somebody you, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?

Yes, it is!

<stage> Sucking </stage>

Okay, then you can take <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> to <person>Dr. Hibbert</person>'s.

Great.

Maybe on the way back, we can swing by the demolition derby and have a nice talk.

<stage> Chuckles </stage> Sounds great.

<stage> Rumbling </stage>

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, I'm afraid your tummy ache may be caused by stress.

Well, that's a relief.

<stage> Chuckles </stage> Yes.

Anyway, when it comes to stress, I believe laughter is the best medicine.

You know, before I learned to chuckle mindlessly, I was headed for an early grave myself.

<stage> Chuckling </stage>

Give it a try, honey.

<stage> Chuckles Weakly </stage>

Oh, now, you call that chuckling? Come on, child! Force it!

I'm really not the chuckling type.

It's true.

I'm always making clever noises, and she never chuckles at 'em.

Well, I could prescribe some harsh antacids... but I think <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> would benefit more from some herbal teas or aromatherapy.

Yeah. You know, some of that all-natural stuff is really very well-

Oh, no, you don't! Screw that touchy, q*eer-y crap!

We'll take the harsh antacids.

Nothing's too good for my little girl.

I sure settled his hash.

Imagine that quack thinking he'd try one of those crazy new age cures.

They're not all crazy, Dad.

Sure they are, honey.

You know, just because you say something is crazy, doesn't make it so.

And just because you think museums are boring and demolition derbies are fun... doesn't make that true either!

I'm sorry, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

Oh, it's not your fault.

I know we love each other, Dad, but we're two very different people.

And much as I hate to say it, as time goes on... we'll probably just drift further and further apart.

Oh, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, honey, I won't ever let that happen.

Oh.

Dad, you don't have to go to a new age store just for me.

I know you think this stuff is stupid.

Nah, you must be thinking of your mother.

I'm always exploring alternatives... and expanding my horizons into realms of-

Can't we just go in?

<stage> Bell Jingles </stage>

Oh, good! I've been meaning to buy a-

"Dream catcher"? Give me a break!

I just wish you could keep an open mind about other cultures.

Other cultures are fine.

I'm just saying I can get along in life without a "toothbrush."

Namaste.

And a-ooga-booga to you too.

May I tell you about our white-light specials?

Absolutely not. My little girl's tummy hurts.

Do you have anything to stop her complaining?

Dad!

Here. Try this wheat grass juice.

<stage> Gags </stage>

Well, your tongue works.

Mm-hmm. Hmm. Let's try some Oil of Lorenzo.

And what's keeping Joan Rivers alive?

Fetal grindings. But I have a better idea.

Oh, no. No freezing.

No, Mr. Simpson.

This is a sensory-deprivation t*nk.

It blocks out all the external distractions that b*mb our souls.

Can you pee in it?

I'll take two hours.

Me too.

You're about to take a journey into the mind.

You may see and experience things that are strange and frightening.

But remember, they can't physically harm you... though they may destroy you mentally.

So what?

<stage> Thinking </stage> Ah, this is kind of relaxing.

But it's so hard to turn off my brain.

I have to stop thinking, starting now.

Hey, it worked! Oh, no. That's thinking.

<stage> Thinking </stage> Boring.

<stage> <person>Lenny</person> </stage> Well, dish!

<person>Groundskeeper Willie</person>- You know, the guy in the skirt?

He bought himself a mail-order bride. But he's too cheap to pay the C.O.D., right?

So she's still in a crate down at the post office.

You wanna go have a look-see?

Ooh, this sounds juicy.

Hmm.

Hey, <person>Milhouse</person>, want to have some fun?

Uh, okay!

How am I supposed to hallucinate with all these swirling colors distracting me?

Hey.

Ah, it's a ball of yarn.

That's funny. I feel like batting it around.

Whoa! I have a paw!

<stage> Scampering </stage>

Oh, my gosh. I've entered the body of our cat.

<stage> Sucking </stage>

Aah.! <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>.! Hey, hey.! Get your sticky hands off me.!

Ow.! <stage> Hisses </stage>

Oh, bad cat! Leave her alone! <stage> Groans </stage>

<stage> Thuds </stage>

<stage> Screams </stage>

Wow. My mind just created that out of nothing.

This t*nk is releasing the full potential of my brain.

<music>♪ <stage> Singing Novelty Song </stage></music>

Come on, come on! I need some gossip here!

<stage> Static </stage>

Where is everybody? Does this town shut down at 5:00?

<stage> <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, Disguised Voice </stage> Frankie, it's me, k*ll.

Huh?

I just busted out of prison and the cops are after me.

<stage> Siren Wailing </stage>

Oh, talk to me, baby.

Okay, I think I lost 'em.

<stage> Siren Stops </stage>

<stage> Mooing </stage>

Uh-oh. A cow.

<stage> Caps <location>Popping</location> </stage>

Eat <location>lead</location>, Bossy.

Listen, Tony. I need someplace to hide. Oh, this place looks good.

7 42 <location>Evergreen Terrace</location>.

<stage> Gasps </stage>

Now, to open the door and k*ll whoever's inside.

I'll start by turning the knob.

<stage> Gasping </stage>

<stage> Chuckles </stage> Gotcha, Mrs.- Ow!

<stage> Groans </stage>

Oh, my God.

<stage> Laughing </stage> Oh, Mom.

You are a prankster's dream.

Wow, you really clobbered him.

That was a horrible trick to play on your mother.

Yeah? Well, it serves you right for eavesdropping.

<stage> Groans </stage> Well, I guess we both learned a lesson.

But if anybody asks, you hit him.

<stage> <person>Milhouse</person> Groaning </stage>

But you can'tjust repossess our merchandise. The I Ching said I had six months till bankruptcy.

Hey, channel somebody who gives a damn.

Can't we discuss this over some sympathy tea?

Sorry. The teas are already on the truck.

There's only enough room on the truck for this one.

We'll get the other one later. <stage> Straining </stage>

<stage> Straining </stage>

Hey! This piece of junk is finally doing something.

<stage> Chuckles </stage>

Oh, man, this is heavy!

You should lift with your legs.

Yeah, aw, screw it. I got health insurance. Oh!

Abracadabra.

The crystal says your baby shall be a girl!

Shut up!

Whoo! Sensory deprivation kicks ass!

<stage> All Gasp </stage>

Oh, Neddie, you almost hit that coffin!

<stage> Gulps </stage> Leapin' Lazarus! Is this what passes for eternal rest these days?

Rod, go get Daddy his buryin' shovel.

Yea!

You sure buried him deep, Daddy.

<stage> Chuckles </stage> Not so deep the Lord can't find him... and judge him.

This is the best birthday I ever had.

Okay, I'm ready to get out now.

Yoo-hoo, hippie lady!

Hippie lady? Hey, hippie lady!

<stage> Screaming </stage> What's going on?

<stage> Screaming Continues </stage>

Oh! Ow! Oh! This inner peace stuff is tough on the old coconut!

<stage> Yelping </stage> Hippie lady, I want to get out.! Hey.!

<music>♪ <stage> Humming </stage> Hmm!</music>

Look, Daddy, a whale egg!

Oh, geez. I am so sick of companies dumping their crud in our ocean without a permit.

It's not like those permits are hard to get.

You're going right back where you came from.

But, Daddy, you're on vacation.

Crime doesn't take a vacation.

Hey, hey, hey, careful! You'll pop it!

<stage> Gasps </stage> It's happening again. I wonder where I'm going this time.

What's that?

Oh, yuck. That sandwich is full of meat.!

There's bacon.

Canadian bacon.

Mexican bacon.! <stage> Guttural Sigh </stage>

And a mouthwatering veal chop.

<stage> Munching </stage> Oh, no. Now I'm Dad!

<music>♪<stage> Orchestral </stage></music>

Oh, and I'm at a stupid, boring ballet.!

<stage> Yawns </stage>

<stage> Snoring </stage>

<music>♪ <stage> Stops </stage></music>

Dad, wake up.! Your snoring is disturbing the dancers.

Hmm!

How can you embarrass me like this? <stage> Groans </stage>

You won't sit through anything that doesn't have car crashes!

<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>'s Voice </stage> I'm sorry, honey.

<stage> Thinking </stage> Geez, why is <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> so mad at me?

I only came to this dump so I could be with her.

<music>♪<stage> Resumes </stage></music>

And what happened to my big sandwich?

<stage> Snoring </stage>

<stage> Snorts, Yawns </stage>

Uh! Boy, I can really be a pain in the butt.

Gee, I should cut Dad some slack.

After all, he did take me to the ballet and the Smithsonian exhibit.

In fact, he takes me lots of places he hates.

<music>♪<stage> <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Singing Novelty Song </stage></music>

<music>♪ <stage> Stops </stage></music>

Hi, sweetie.

Hi, Dad! How was it?

I went on a wild ride without ever leaving the building.

How was yours?

Pretty cool.

But now, what do you say we go do something we'll both enjoy?

Oh, like what?

Whoa! Look at that car burn!

Does it get any better than this?

Not to me, Dad.

<stage> Crashing </stage>

Oy!

<stage> Siren Wailing </stage>

<stage> Man On P.A.</stage> And here comes the ambulance.!

<stage> Man On P.A.</stage> And here comes the ambulance.!

<stage> Murmuring </stage>

Shh!
</txt></xml>