<xml>
 <source>Disney's <title>Mulan</title> Compiled by Barry Adams during theater showings in 1998 Last updated:
   August 18, 1998 Source: The Internet Movie Scripts Database (IMSDb):
  <sourceLink>https://imsdb.com/scripts/Mulan.html</sourceLink> Mulan is the property and copyright of the Walt
  Disney Company, Inc. The script on this page was compiled while watching Mulan in the theater
  during the summer of 1998 when the film originally aired.</source>

 <stage>Chinese guard is seen walking on The Great Wall. Shan-Yu's falcon swoops down and hits the
  guard on the head knocking his helmet off. The falcon lands on top of a flag pole in front of a
  full moon and lets out a large cry. One grappling hook comes over The Great Wall. The guard walks
  over to the edge and sees many grappling hooks coming towards him</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Guard <stage>yelling</stage></speaker> We're under attack! Light the signal!</sp>

 <stage>Guard runs to the tower and up the ladder as Hun Bald Man #1 and Hun Long Hair Man appear
  trying to stop him. Hun Bald Man #1 breaks the ladder with his sword just as Guard reaches the
  top. The guard picks up the torch to light the fire and sees Shan-Yu jump over the edge of the
  tower and looks at him across from the caldron. The guard throws the torch into the caldron
  lighting a large fire. Shan-Yu watches as each tower lights their caldrons one by one</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Guard <stage>sternly</stage></speaker> Now all of China knows you're here.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>taking the flag and holding it over the fire</stage></speaker>
  Perfect.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to the palace. The large doors to the central chamber open as General Li walks in
  flanked on his left and right by soldiers and approaches the Emperor. He bows, then looks
  up</stage>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> Your Majesty, the Huns have crossed our Northern border.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Impossible! No one can get through The Great Wall. <stage>The Emperor
   motions for Chi Fu's silence</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> Shun-Yu is leading them. We'll set up defenses around your palace
  immediately.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor <stage>forcefully</stage></speaker> No! Send your troops to protect my people.
  Chi Fu, </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Yes, your highness.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> Deliver conscription notices throughout all the provinces. Call up
  reserves and as many new recruits as possible.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> Forgive me your Majesty, but I believe my troops can stop
  him.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> I wont take any chances, General. A single grain of rice can tip the
  scale. One man may be the difference between victory and defeat.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan using her chopsticks to single out a grain of rice on top of the mound of
  rice</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Quiet and demure...graceful...polite...<stage>picking up some rice
   with her chopsticks and eating a mouthful</stage> delicate...refined...poised... <stage>She sets
   down her chopsticks and writes down a final word on her right arm</stage> punctual. <stage>A cock
   crows</stage> Aiya. <stage>Calling out</stage> Little brother. Little brother. Lit- ahhh, there
  you are. Who's the smartest doggie in the world? Come on smart boy, can you help me with my chores
  today?</sp>

 <stage>Mulan ties a sack of grain around Little Brother's waist. She ties a stick onto Little
  brother so that end of it is in front of Little Brother's face. She ties the bone on the end of
  the stick just out of reach. Little Brother begins to run after the bone which he cannot reach.
  Mulan opens the door for Little Brother and he runs into the door frame, then out the open door.
  Little brother runs by the chickens and Khan - the family horse</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan's Father, Fa Zhou, kneeling and praying before the Fa family's
  ancestors</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Honorable ancestors, please help Mulan impress the matchmaker today. </sp>

 <sp>Little Brother <stage>running into the temple and around Fa Zhou scattering grain around the
   floor</stage>: Bark, bark, bark, bark, bark.</sp>

 <stage>The chickens follow Little Brother into the temple and begin to feed on the grain</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Please, PLEASE, help her.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan steps up to the temple seeing Little Brother on his hind legs trying to get the bone.
  Mulan bends the stick down so that Little brother can reach the bone. Little brother gnaws on the
  bone happily. Mulan continues toward the temple</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling out</stage></speaker> Father I brought your--whoop! <stage>Fa
   Zhou bumps into Mulan. The cup falls to the ground and Fa Zhou catches the teapot with the handle
   of his cane</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Mulan--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I brought a spare. <stage>Mulan pulls out a cup from underneath the
   back of her dress and begins to pour the tea</stage>
 </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Mulan--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>hurried</stage></speaker> Remember, the doctor said three cups of tea in
  the morning--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Mulan--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> And three at night. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Mulan, you should already be in town. We're counting on you to
  up--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> --uphold the family honor. Don't worry father. I wont let you down.
   <stage>Mulan covers over the writing on her arm with here sleeve</stage> Wish me luck.
   <stage>Mulan hurries down the stairs</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>calling out</stage></speaker> Hurry! <stage>to himself</stage> I'm
  going to...pray some more. <stage>Fa Zhou turns and walks back into the temple</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to the town with Fa Li looking worried</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Bath Lady <stage>poking out of her building</stage></speaker> Fa Li, is your daughter
  here yet? The matchmaker is not a patient woman. <stage>She goes back into the
  building</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> Of all days to be late. I should have prayed to the ancestors for
  luck.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>walking in with a Cri-Kee in a cage</stage></speaker> How lucky can
  they be, they're dead. Besides, I've got all the luck we'll need. <stage>Speaking to
   Cri-Kee</stage> This is your chance to prove yourself. <stage>Cri-Kee chirps approvingly. Grandma
   Fa covers her eyes steps into a busy street</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>excitedly</stage></speaker> Grandma No!</sp>

 <stage>The traffic barely misses Grandma Fa as she crosses the busy street. But two horse and
  carriage collide causing a big accident. She arrives at the other side of the street, uncovers
  here eyes and looks at Cri-Kee</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa</speaker> Yep, this cricket's a lucky one. <stage>Cri-Kee falls over out of
   fright</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>sighing in relief</stage></speaker> Hai.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan arrives on Khan jumping over the recent accident in the street and jumps off with hay
  stuck in her hair</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I'm here. <stage>Seeing a stern look from her mother</stage> What? But
  Mama I had to--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> None of your 'xcuses. Now let's get you cleaned up. <stage>They walk
   together into the preparation area</stage></sp>

 <stage>Song: Honor to us all</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Bath Lady</speaker>
  <stage>all the while Bath Lady undresses Mulan and pushes her into the Bath</stage> This is what
  you give me to work with? Well, honey, I've seen worse. We're gonna turn this sow's ear Into a
  silk purse. <stage>Bath Lady moves the silk partition aside showing Mulan in the bath</stage>
 </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> It's freezing.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> It would have been warm if you were here on
  time. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Bath Lady <stage>washing Mulan's hair</stage></speaker> We'll have you Washed and
  dried Primped and polished till you glow with pride Trust my recipe for instant bride You'll bring
  honor to us all</sp>

 <sp>Fa Li <stage>grabbing a sponge and Mulan's right arm to start cleaning her. She notices the
   writing</stage>
  <stage>spoken</stage>: Mulan, what's this?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>Drawing her arm back and batting her eyelashes</stage>
   <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> Ahh, notes, in case I forget something?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> Here, hold this <stage>hands the cricket to
   Fa Li</stage>. We'll need more luck than I thought. <stage>Mulan looks on with an air of
   disappointment</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to the hair dressers</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Hair Dresser 1 <stage>Brushing and combing Mulan's hair much to Mulan's
    chagrin</stage></speaker> Wait and see When we're through</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hair Dresser 2</speaker> Boys will gladly go to war for you</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hair Dresser 1</speaker> With good fortune </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hair Dresser 2 <stage>Finalizing the hairdo to look exactly like
   hers</stage></speaker> And a great hairdo</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Both</speaker> You'll bring honor to us all</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li and others</speaker>
  <stage>Mulan following her Mother passes a xiangqi game and pauses to make an impressive move.
   Mulan has a smug look on her face when Fa Li comes back and drags Mulan away</stage> A girl can
  bring her family Great honor in one way By striking a good match And this could be the day</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Dresser 1 <stage>Dresser 1, Dresser 2, and Fa Li dress Mulan</stage></speaker> Men
  want girls with good taste</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Dresser 2</speaker> Calm</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> Obedient</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Dresser 1</speaker> Who work fast-paced</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> With good breeding</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Dresser 2 <stage>Pulling the dress tight around her waist</stage></speaker> And a tiny
  waist </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>expressing her waist being squeezed tight</stage>
   <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> huh.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>All Three</speaker> You'll bring honor to us all </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chorus</speaker>
  <stage>Mulan follows Fa Li and sees boy stealing a doll from a girl. Mulan grabs the doll from the
   boy and returns it to its owner</stage> We all must serve our Emperor Who guards us from the Huns
  A man by bearing arms A girl by bearing sons </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Make-up Lady/Fa Li</speaker>
  <stage>Putting on Mulan's face, powder, lipstick and eye liner</stage>
  <stage>in a 3 person round</stage> When we're through you can't fail Like a lotus blossom soft and
  pale How could any fellow say "No sale" You'll bring honor to us all <stage>Make-Up Lady holds a
   mirror so Mulan can see her reflection. Not looking pleased, Mulan takes her single, short bang
   and brings it down in front of her forehead and smiles</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>spoken. Fa Li places a hair comb in Mulan's hair</stage></speaker> There,
  you're ready.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> Not yet! An apple for serenity
   <stage>putting an apple in Mulan's mouth</stage>...A pendant for balance <stage>places a yin-yang
   pendant under her sash</stage>
  <stage>sings</stage></sp>

 <sp>Beads of jade for beauty <stage>putting beads around Mulan's neck</stage> You must proudly show
  it <stage>Grandma Fa raises her chin high with her hand</stage> Now add a cricket just for luck
   <stage>putting the cage with Cri-Kee under Mulan's sash in the back. Cri-Kee doesn't look
   pleased</stage> And even you can't blow it</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker>
  <stage>Walking to catch up with the other maidens</stage> Ancestors Hear my plea Help me not to
  make a fool of me And to not uproot my fam'ly tree Keep my father standing tall</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Maidens and Mulan</speaker>
  <stage>Mulan taking the parasol from Fal Li and running to fall in line with the other 4
   maidens</stage> Scarier than the undertaker We are meeting our matchmaker</sp>

 <sp><speaker>All Townspeople</speaker> Destiny Guard our girls And our future as it fast unfurls
  Please look kindly on these cultured pearls Each a perfect porcelain doll</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Maiden #1</speaker> Please bring honor to us Maiden #2: Please bring honor to us
  Maiden #3: Please bring honor to us Maiden #4: Please bring honor to us Mulan and Maidens: Please
  bring honor to us all! </sp>

 <stage>All Girls and Mulan arrive before the Matchmaker crouched down behind their parasols. End of
  song</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker <stage>looking at her clipboard</stage></speaker> Fa Mulan</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>Jumping up and raising her hand</stage></speaker> Present.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker</speaker> Speaking without permission.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Oops. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>to Fa Li</stage></speaker> Who spit in her bean curd?</sp>

 <stage>Mulan walks into the Matchmaker's building with the Matchmaker following behind and closing
  the door</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker <stage>looking over Mulan</stage></speaker> Huh, Hmm, too skinny.
   <stage>Cri-Kee escapes from his cage. Mulan struggles to catch him</stage> Hmph, not good for
  bearing sons. <stage>Mulan puts Cri-Kee in her mouth when Matchmaker turns around to face
   her</stage> Recite the final admonition.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>nodding and smiling</stage></speaker> Mmm-Hmm. <stage>Takes out fan and
   covers her mouth as she spits out Cri-Kee</stage> Ptu</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker</speaker> Well...</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>with dignity</stage></speaker> Fulfill your duties calmly and
   re...f--<stage>looking at her arm with smeared writing</stage> spectfully. Reflect before you
  snack <stage>surprised, Mulan looks at her arm again</stage> act. <stage>now rapidly</stage> This
  shall bring you honor and glory. <stage>Fanning herself rapidly and sighing in relief</stage>
  Huh.</sp>

 <sp>Matchmaker <stage>snatches the fan and looks at it on both sides looking for notes not finding
   any. Mulan smiles big when Matchmaker looks at her. Matchmaker grabs Mulan's right arm pulling
   her along while smearing the writing and leaving some ink on her hand</stage> Hmmm, this way.
  Now, pour the tea <stage>Pushing a teapot towards Mulan</stage>. To please your future in-laws you
  must demonstrate a sense of dignity <stage>Matchmaker smears ink around her mouth. Mulan staring
   at Matchmaker pours some tea onto the table then notices her mistake and pours the tea into the
   cup</stage> and refinement. You must also be poised. <stage>Mulan notices Cri-kee in the tea-cup
   as Matchmaker takes the cup</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>quiet and timid</stage></speaker> Um, pardon me.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker</speaker> And silent! <stage>Matchmaker sniffs the tea</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>reaching and grabbing the teacup</stage></speaker> Could I just take that
  back...one moment.</sp>

 <stage>They struggle for the teacup and it turns over on Matchmaker and Cri-kee jumps down
  matchmaker's dress</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker</speaker> Why you clumsy--<stage>Matchmaker feels Cri-Kee in her dress and
   dances around</stage> Wooo, woooo, wooooooo, <stage>Matchmaker knocks over her pot of coals, and
   sits down on the coals. Matchmaker jumps around screaming</stage> Ahhhhhhhhhhh <stage>Mulan grabs
   her fan and briskly fans the charred area on Matchmaker's behind causing it to flame up. Mulan
   looks surprised about her mistake</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to outside Matchmakers building showing Grandma Fa with much noise coming from
  Matchmaker's building</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>to Fa Li</stage></speaker> I think it's going well, don't you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Matchmaker <stage>running out of the building screaming</stage></speaker> Put it out!
  Put it out! Put it out! <stage>Mulan takes the teapot, throws the tea on Matchmaker and puts out
   the fire. She bows, hands the teapot back to Matchmaker and covers her face as she walks toward
   Fa Li and Grandma Fa</stage>
  <stage>with anger</stage> You are a disgrace! <stage>Matchmaker throws the teapot down smashing it
   to pieces</stage> You may look like a bride, but you will never bring your family honor!</sp>

 <stage>The townsfolk who have gathered whisper and walk away</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan walking through the gate with her home leading khan. She looks sorrowful. Fa
  Zhou sees his daughter and smiles. Mulan sees her father's smile. She covers her face with Khan's
  head and leads him to the water trough</stage>

 <stage>Song: Reflection</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Look at me <stage>looking at her reflection in the water
   trough</stage> I will never pass for a perfect bride <stage>taking off her earrings and beads of
   jade</stage> Or a perfect daughter <stage>Mulan watches Fa Li relating what happened at the
   Matchmaker's to Fa Zhou</stage> Can it be I'm not meant to play this part? <stage>Mulan releases
   Cri-Kee back to the wild</stage> Now I see That if I were to truly To be myself <stage>Mulan hops
   along the bridge railing</stage> I would break my family's heart</sp>

 <sp>Who is that girl I see <stage>Mulan looks into the pond and sees her own reflection</stage>
  Staring straight Back at me? <stage>Mulan puts her hand on the Great Stone Dragon and looks toward
   the temple</stage> Why is my reflection someone I don't know? <stage>Cri-Kee rowing across the
   pond on a lily pad</stage> Somehow I cannot hide <stage>Mulan walking into the family
   temple</stage> Who I am <stage>Cri-Kee watches Mulan in the temple seeing multiple reflections of
   herself in the ancestors' stones</stage> Though I've tried <stage>Mulan bows to the
   ancestors</stage> When will my reflection show Who I am inside? <stage>Mulan finishes wiping off
   her make-up seeing her reflection in the stones</stage> When will my reflection show Who I am
  inside? <stage>Mulan gets up and heads out the temple</stage></sp>

 <stage>End of song. Mulan sits on a bench under the blossom tree. Fa Zhou approaches her, clearing
  his throat. Mulan sees him approaching and turns her head away. Fa Zhou sits down beside
  Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> My, my, what beautiful blossoms we have this year <stage>looking up
   into the blossom tree</stage>. But look, this one's late. But, I'll bet that when it blooms, it
  will be the most beautiful of all. <stage>Mulan and Fa Zhou share smiles. Drums start pounding
   announcing the arrival of Chi Fu and two guards on horseback</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> What is it?</sp>

 <stage>Fa Zhou gets up and walks to the entrance of their house with Mulan following</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> Mulan, stay inside.</sp>

 <stage>Grandma Fa clears her throat catching Mulan's attention and motions inside. Mulan spies the
  railing near the wall and climbs up to watch over the roof</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Citizens I bring you a proclamation from the Imperial City: the Huns
  have invaded China! </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Townspeople <stage>expressing surprise</stage></speaker> No!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> By order of the Emperor, one man from every family must serve in the
  Imperial Army. The Xiao family <stage>a family member steps up, bows to the guard and takes the
   conscription notice from the guard</stage>. The Yi family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yi's Son <stage>holding his old father back</stage></speaker> I will serve the Emperor
  in my father's place.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> The Fa Family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> No.</sp>

 <stage>Fa Zhou gives his cane to Fa Li and walks toward Chi Fu. Fa Zhou bows before the
  horsemen</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>standing proud</stage></speaker> I am ready to serve the Emperor.
   <stage>Fa Zhou reaches for the conscription notice</stage></sp>

 <sp>Mulan <stage>running outside to keep her father from taking the conscription notice</stage>:
  Father, you can't go.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>turning to see his daughter</stage></speaker> Mulan!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Please sir, my father has already fought bravely--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Silence! You would do well to teach your daughter to hold her tongue
  in a man's presence.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>looking away from Mulan</stage></speaker> Mulan, you dishonor me.</sp>

 <stage>Grandma Fa guides Mulan back away</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>handing Fa Zhou the conscription notice</stage></speaker> Report
  tomorrow at the Wu Shu camp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Yes, sir. <stage>Fa Zhou walks back into the homestead refusing to
   take his cane from Fa Li</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>fading out as we follow Fa Zhou</stage></speaker> The Chu family. The
  Wen family. The Chang family. The...</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Fa Zhou in his armory at night. Fa Zhou takes out his sword and practices his
  stances. Whan he balances on his right leg, his leg injury acts up and he falls. Unbeknownst to
  her father, Mulan watches in horror. She breathes heavily</stage>

 <stage>Cut to dinner. The Fa Zhou, Grandma Fa, Fa Li, and Mulan eat in silence. Thunder can be
  heard and lightning can be seen through the opaque window. Mulan pours the tea for her family. She
  slams her teacup down on the table and stands up</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> You shouldn't have to go.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li</speaker> Mulan!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> There are plenty of young men to fight for China.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> It is an honor to protect my country and my family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>angrily</stage></speaker> So you'll die for honor!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>standing up and angered</stage></speaker> I will DIE doing what's
  right.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>starts to speak but is cut off</stage></speaker> But if you--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> I know my place, it is time you learned yours.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan looking like she's about to cry, turn away from Fa Zhou and runs outside into the rain
  storm and cries</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan sitting at the base of the Great Stone Dragon in the rain. Mulan looks down to
  see her reflection in the puddle caused by the rain. She watches her parents in the bedroom. Fa Li
  turns away from Fa Zhou and walks out of site. Fa Zhou blows out the light. Mulan gets up and
  walks to the Fa Family Temple. Mulan's image reflects off the stone tablets as she lights incense
  and places it in the hanging encense holder. She bows and prays to her ancestors. Getting up,
  Mulan hurries down the steps. Cri-Kee sees her and hops down from above and follows her. Mulan
  goes to her parent's bedroom and takes the conscription notice replacing it with the hair comb her
  mother gave to her. She pauses to give her parents a loving, sorrowful look and hurries out. Cut
  to Mulan in the armory. She opens the cabinet with the armor. Using her father's sword, she cuts
  her hair short and ties it up above her head. She finishes putting on the armor and ties it in the
  front. She takes the sword and places it in the scabbard to her left. Cut to Mulan in the stable
  doorway. Khan rears back in fright at the sight of Mulan. Mulan goes forward and comforts Khan
  letting him know her identity. Mulan walks Khan out of the stable, Cri-Kee watches from the ground
  as she passes by. Mulan takes one sorrowful glance back at her parents bedroom and rides Khan
  through the gate and off to camp.</stage>

 <stage>Cut to the face of a statue in the Fa Family Temple. The eyes glow. Cut to Grandma Fa. She
  wakes up with a start rising in bed. Cut to Grandma Fa walking into Fa Li and Fa Zhou's bedroom,
  both are in bed</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa</speaker> Mulan is gone.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>waking up</stage></speaker> What? It can't be. <stage>Fa Zhou looks at
   his night stand and notices the hair comb in place of his conscription notice. He checks the
   cabinet and sees his armor is gone. He hurries outside</stage>
  <stage>calling out</stage> Mulan! <stage>He stumbles while walking because of his leg
   injury</stage> No.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>kneeling down beside the fallen Fa Zhou</stage></speaker> You must go
  after her. She could be killed!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou <stage>sadly</stage></speaker> If I reveal her, she will be. <stage>Fa Zhou
   embraces Fa Li</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa</speaker> Ancestors, hear our prayer: Watch over Mulan.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to the Fa Family Temple. A wind blows out the incense at the base of the center stone.
  The center stone begins to glow as First Ancestor comes to life</stage>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>motioning to a bronze dragon</stage></speaker> Mushu,
  awaken!</sp>

 <stage>Mushu comes to life and falls to the ground flat on his back all being obscured by
  smoke</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>rising from the smoke arms stretched out</stage></speaker> I live! So
  tell me what mortal needs my protection Great Ancestor. You just say the word and I'm there.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>agitated</stage></speaker> Mushu!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Hey, let me say something. Anybody who is foolish enough to threaten
  our family, vengeance will be MINE. Hrrrrr.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>sternly to silence Mushu</stage></speaker> Mushu! These are the
  family guardians <stage>motioning towards the stone statues on pedestals near the ceiling</stage>.
  They...</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>dejectedly</stage></speaker> Protect the family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>pointing to the empty pedestal</stage></speaker> And you, oh
  demoted one.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> I...ring the gong.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor</speaker> That's right, now, wake up the ancestors.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> One family reunion coming right up. <stage>ringing the gong</stage>
  Okay people, people look alive, lets go! C'mon get up. Let's move it, rise and shine. You're way
  past the beauty sleep thing now trust me!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 1</speaker> I knew it, I knew it. That Mulan was a trouble maker from the
  start.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 3</speaker> Don't look at me, she gets it from your side of the family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 2</speaker> She's just trying to help her father.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 4 <stage>appearing out of thin air</stage></speaker> But, if she is
  discovered, Fa Zhou will be forever shamed. Dishonor will come to the family. Traditional values
  will disintegrate.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 5</speaker> Not to mention they'll lose the farm.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 1</speaker> My children never caused such trouble. They all became
  acupuncturists.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 3</speaker> Well, We can't all be acupuncturists.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 6</speaker> No, your great granddaughter had to be cross-dresser!</sp>

 <stage>All ancestors argue at once, except First Ancestor</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 7</speaker> Let a guardian bring her back. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 8 <stage>grabbing Mushu and bringing him next to a guardian</stage></speaker>
  Yeah, awaken the most cunning.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 4 <stage>taking Mushu and holding him next to the stone rabbit
    guardian</stage></speaker> No, the swiftest.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 9 <stage>grabbing Mushu and holding him next to the stone monkey
    guardian</stage></speaker> No, send the wisest.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor</speaker> Silence! We must send the most powerful of all
   <stage>Motioning to the Great Stone Dragon as it is seen through the window</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>climbs up the empty guardian post laughing</stage></speaker> Ho, ho, heh,
  heh. Okay, okay, I get the drift, I'll go. <stage>All Ancestors give a quick look of surprise and
   laugh uncontrollably</stage> You all don't think I can do it. Watch this here. <stage>Mushu
   produces a small flame from his mouth</stage> Ah, ha, Jump back, I'm pretty hot huh. Don't make
  me have to singe nobody to prove no point.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>grabbing Mushu and pulling away from the post</stage></speaker>
  You had your chance to protect the Fa family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 6</speaker> Your mis-guidance led Fa Deng to disaster.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Deng <stage>with his decapitated head on his lap</stage></speaker> Yeah, thanks a
  lot.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> And your point is?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor</speaker> The point is we will be sending a real dragon to retrieve
  Mulan.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> What? But I'm a real dragon.</sp>

 <sp>First Ancestor <stage>grabbing Mushu and pulling him away from the guardian post as Mushu
   fights to hold on</stage>: You are not worthy of this spot. Now, awaken the Great Stone Dragon.
   <stage>First Ancestor throws Mushu out of the temple</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>looking back into the temple</stage></speaker> So you'll get back to me
  on the job thing.</sp>

 <stage>An ancestor throws Mushu's gong and hits Mushu in the face</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>walking with a slouch and banging the gong on the
   ground</stage></speaker> Just one chance is that too much to ask? I mean, it's not like it'll
  kill ya.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>rings the gong and looks at the Great Stone Dragon</stage></speaker> Yo
  rocky, wake up! You gotta go fetch Mulan. <stage>pauses as nothing happens. Mushu walks over to
   the side of the statue</stage> C'mon boy, go get her, go on, <stage>throws the gong stick off the
   screen and whistles</stage> Come on. <stage>Angrily while climbing up the Great Stone
   Dragon</stage> Grrr, Grrrr. <stage>speaking in his ear and banging the ear with the gong</stage>
  Hello, helloooooo. <stage>curtly</stage> Hello <stage>bangs the gong extra hard against the ear
   causing it to break off</stage>. Uh oh. <stage>The Great Stone Dragon crumbles to the ground,
   head intact minus the ear</stage>. <stage>knocks on the dragon's head</stage> Uh, Stoney,
  Stooooneeey. Oh man, they're gonna kill me!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>calling out through the temple window</stage></speaker> Great
  Stone Dragon, have you awaken? </sp>

 <sp>Mushu <stage>holding the head of the Great Stone Dragon up to that First Ancestor can only see
   it's head and Mushu's body</stage>: Uhhh, Yes, I just woke up. And I am the Great Stone Dragon,
  good morning <stage>Mushu waves</stage>. I will go forth and fetch Mulan. Did, did I mention that
  I was the Great Stone Dragon?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor</speaker> Go, The fate of the Fa Family rests in your claws.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Don't even worry about it, I will not lose face. <stage>Mushu falls
   down the hill under the weight of the Great Stone Dragon's head and lands on the dragon's
   pedestal with the head falling on top of him</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>muffled</stage></speaker> Ow, my elbow. Aw, aw, I know I twisted
  something. <stage>Throwing the head off him</stage> That's just great. Now what? I'm doomed! And
  all 'cause miss man decides to take her little drag show on the road.</sp>

 <stage>Cri-Kee enters stage right</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee</speaker> Chirp, Chirp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Go get her? What's the matter with you? After this great stone Humpty
  Dumpty mess, I'd have to bring her home with a medal to get back in the temple. Wait a minute,
  that's it! I make Mulan a war hero, then they'll be begging me to come back to work. That's the
  master plan. Oh, you've gone and done it now. <stage>Mushu runs off stage right</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee <stage>hopping along side of Mushu</stage></speaker> Chirp. Chirp Chirp
  Chirp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>pushing Cri-Kee away</stage></speaker> Hey, what makes you think you're
  coming?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee</speaker> Chirp, Chirp. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> You're lucky? Ho, ho, heh. Do I look like a sucker to you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee</speaker> Chirp. Chirp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Whach' you mean loser? How 'bout I pop one of your antenna's off and
  throw it across the yard. Then who's a loser, me or you?</sp>

 <stage>Interlude</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Shan-Yu leading his army at a charge on horseback through a forest. He stops and
  motions stage right. Hun Archer, Hun Strong Guy, Hun Long-Hair Guy dismount and walk into the
  forest. They throw down two Imperial scouts before the rest of the army</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Long-Hair Guy</speaker> Imperial scouts. </sp>

 <stage>Shan Yu dismounts and walks towards the scouts</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Scout #1</speaker> Shan-Yu.</sp>

 <stage>He crouches down in front of them</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>adjusting Scout #1's collar</stage></speaker> Nice work, gentlemen. You
  found the Hun army. <stage>motioning to the soldiers on horseback. The Hun army
  laughs</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Scout #2</speaker> The Emperor will stop you.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>grabs Scout #2 by the shirt collar and lifts him up to his
   face</stage></speaker> Stop me? He invited me. By building his wall, he challenged my strength.
  Well I'm here to play his game <stage>Shan-Yu throws Scout #2 to the ground and points his sword
   at Scout #1 as he gets up and runs</stage>
  <stage>calling out to the scouts</stage> Go! Tell your emperor to send his strongest armies.
   <stage>Quietly</stage> I'm ready. </sp>

 <stage>The Imperial Scouts run off towards the palace</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>scratching his chin</stage></speaker> How many men does it take to
  deliver a message.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Archer Guy <stage>drawing back his bow</stage></speaker> One.</sp>

 <stage>End Interlude</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan on a hill outside of the camp. Khan is sitting watching</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Okay, okay, how 'bout this? Ahem, <stage>in her manly voice</stage>
  excuse me, where do I sign in? Hah, I see you have a sword. I have one too. They're very manly and
  tough <stage>Mulan bites her lip as she mishandles pulling the sword out of the scabbard and it
   falls to the ground. Khan rolls on his back in laughter. Mulan throws her shoe and hits Khan in
   the head with it quieting Khan</stage>. I'm working on it. Who am I fooling? It's going to take a
  miracle to get me into the army.</sp>

 <stage>Mushu appears as a giant shadow being cast on a rock with flames on either side. Mushu's
  real appearance remains out of sight</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>in a Southern Baptist Preacher's voice</stage></speaker> Did I hear
  someone ask for a miracle!? Let me hear you say aye!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>Running and hiding behind a rock</stage></speaker> Ahhhhhh.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> That's close enough.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>from behind a rock</stage></speaker> Ghost.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Get ready Mulan your serpentine salvation is at hand. For I have been
  sent by your ancestors-- <stage>notices Cri-Kee making a hand shadow of a dragon on the rock and
   stamps him down with his foot</stage> to guide you through your masquerade. <stage>bending down
   to Cri-Kee</stage> C'mon, you're gonna stay you're gonna work. <stage>returning to Mulan</stage>
  Heed my word, 'cause if the army finds out that you are a girl, the penalty is death. <stage>big
   flames shoot up from the rocks</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Who are you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Who am I? Who am I? I am the guardian of lost souls. <stage>Mulan
   smiles big in anticipation of seeing her guardian</stage> I am the powerful, the pleasurable, the
  indestructible <stage>coming out from the rocks to show his real size</stage> Mushu! Oh hah, hah,
  pretty hot, huh? <stage>Khan stomps on Mushu. Mulan pushes Khan back</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Ah, my ancestors sent a little lizard to help me?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Hey, dragon, dragon, not lizard. I don't do that tongue thing
   <stage>flips out his tongue to show Mulan what he means</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> You're uh...</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Intimidating? Awe inspiring?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>making a hand gesture to denote his smallness of size</stage></speaker>
  Tiny.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>with a look of disappointment</stage></speaker> Of course. I'm travel
  size for your convenience. If I was my real size, your cow here <stage>patting Khan on the
   nose</stage> would die of fright. <stage>Khan tries to bite Mushu</stage>
  <stage>pointing to the ground speaking to Khan</stage> Down Bessy. My powers are beyond your
  mortal imagination. For instance, <stage>leaning in and looking at Mulan's chest</stage> my eyes
  can see straight through your armor. <stage>Mulan cover her bust with her left arm and slaps Mushu
   with the right</stage> Ow. <stage>angrily</stage> All right, that's it! Dishonor! Dishonor on
  your whole family. <stage>aside to Cri-Kee</stage> Make a note of this <stage>Cri-Kee grabs a leaf
   and a pen and starts writing</stage>. <stage>Loudly with gusto</stage> Dishonor on you. Dishonor
  on your cow. Dis-</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>pleadingly while covering Mushu's mouth</stage></speaker> Stop! I'm
  sorry, I'm sorry <stage>kneeling down in front of Mushu</stage>. I'm just nervous. I've never done
  this before.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Then you're gonna have to trust me. And don't you slap me no more, we
  clear on that? <stage>Mulan nods emphatically</stage>. All right. Okey dokey, let's get this show
  on the road. Cri-Kee, get the bags <stage>Mushu starts walking to the camp</stage>. <stage>to
   Khan</stage> Let's move it heifer.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan at the camp's entrance</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>hiding in Mulan's armor poking his head out from her
   back</stage></speaker> Okay this is it, time to show 'em your man walk. Shoulders back, chest
  high, feet apart, head up <stage>Mushu pulls Mulan's head back</stage> ...and strut 2, 3, break it
  down, 2, 3 and work it, <stage>Mulan walks into the camp drawing the attention the men who see
   her. Mulan walks into a tent and sees a man picking his nose and another man picking out dirt
   from between his toes with chopsticks</stage> Beautiful isn't it?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>making a face of disgust and continuing to walk</stage></speaker> They're
  disgusting.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> No, they're men. And you're going to have to act just like them, so
  pay attention.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan stops and watches Yao, Ling, Chien-Po and Tattoo Soldier</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Tattoo Soldier <stage>showing the dragon tattoo on his chest and
   belly</stage></speaker> Look, this tattoo will protect me from harm.</sp>

 <stage>Yao thinks for a moment, then punches Tattoo Soldier in the stomach causing Ling to laugh.
  Mulan watches in utter amazement. Yao kisses his hand</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>laughing</stage></speaker> I hope you can get your money back.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I don't think I can do this.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> It's all attitude. Be tough like this guy here <stage>looking at
   Yao</stage>.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan looks at Yao as he hocks up a loogie and spits</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>noticing Mulan watching him</stage></speaker> What are you looking at?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Punch him, it's how men say 'hello.'</sp>

 <stage>Mulan looks at her fist, then punches Yao from behind on the shoulder. The force causes Yao
  to run into Chien-Po</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po</speaker> Oh Yao, you made a friend.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Good, Now slap him on the behind, they like that.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan slaps Yao on the behind</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Wu hoo hooooo. <stage>grabbing Mulan buy the collar</stage> I'm going to
  hit you so hard it'll make your ancestors dizzy.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>Holding and picking up Yao</stage></speaker> Yao, relax and chant with
  me. Yaaaaaaa Moouuuu Ahhhhhh Doooou Fuuuu Daaaaa.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Ya Mi Ah To Fu Da.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po</speaker> Feel better? </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>relaxed</stage></speaker> Yeah. <stage>Chien-Po places Yao back on the
   ground</stage>
  <stage>to Mulan while walking away</stage> Aaaaa, you ain't worth my time chicken boy.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>loudly</stage></speaker> Chicken boy!? Say that to my face ya limp
  noodle!</sp>

 <stage>Yao grabs Mulan by the collar cocking back his arm to punch. Mulan ducks as Yao hits Ling
  standing behind her</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Oh, sorry Ling. Hey!</sp>

 <stage>Yao grabs Mulan's foot as she starts to crawl away. Ling kicks Yao on the butt causing him
  to land on Chien-Po's stomach. Ling Jump attacks Mulan, but she ducks and he lands on Yao on top
  of Chien-Po</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> You're dead. <stage>They fight on top of Chien-Po. Mulan runs away.
   Ling notices Mulan and then points toward her</stage> Oh, there he goes.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan runs into a tent and stops. Yao, Ling, and Chien-Po (in that order) run through the
  tent. Yao stops short as he is about to run into a soldier in a line for food. He looks behind him
  with concerned eyes as Ling stops in time. Chien-Po bumps into Ling causing the entire line of
  soldiers to fall forward and knock over the pot of congee and the cook behind it. The men look to
  the back of the line and spy Mulan who has emerged from the tent. They angrily start walking
  towards her. Mulan has a look of horror on her face as if trouble is about to brew</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Hey guys. </sp>

 <stage>Chi Fu watches and then walks into the tent. General Li and Li Shang are in the
  tent.</stage>

 <sp><speaker>General Li <stage>motioning with his pointer to a map of the region</stage></speaker>
  The Huns have struck here, here and here. I will take the main troops up to the Tung Shao Pass and
  stop Shan-Yu before he destroys this village.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Excellent strategy, Sir. I do love surprises, Ha ha, ha, ha.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> You will stay here and train the new recruits. When Chi Fu
  believes you're ready, you will join us...Captain. <stage>General Li hands a sword to
   Shang</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Captain?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Oh, this is an enormous responsibility, General. Uh, perhaps a
  soldier with more experience--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> Number one in his class, extensive knowledge of training
  techniques, <stage>leaning back smugly stroking his chin</stage> an impressive military lineage. I
  believe Li Shang will do an excellent job.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>excitedly</stage></speaker> Oh, I will. I wont let you down. This is, I
  mean, I...<stage>somberly</stage> yes sir.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li <stage>gets up and starts walking out of the tent</stage></speaker> Very
  good then. We'll toast China's victory at the Imperial City. <stage>to Chi Fu</stage> I'll expect
  a full report in three weeks.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>to Shang</stage></speaker> And I wont leave anything out. <stage>exits
   through the tent</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>while tying his sword to his uniform</stage></speaker> Captain Li Shang,
  Hmmm, leader of China's finest troops. No, the greatest troops of all time. Heh, heh, heh, heh.
   <stage>Shang walks out of the tent to see the recruits fighting. He stands stage left of Chi Fu
   and General Li. Injured Recruit sees the General and salutes him as he falls to the ground.
   General Li steps over Injured Recruit and mounts his horse</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Most impressive.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>General Li</speaker> Good luck Captain. <stage>The general and his mounted troops
   leave the camp</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>quietly, to himself</stage></speaker> Good luck, Father. <stage>Shang
   looks at his troops and sighs</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>smirking, with board and brush in hand</stage></speaker> Day one.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>shouting</stage></speaker> Soldiers!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>All Recruits <stage>backing away revealing Mulan and pointing at her. Mulan is
    crouching in the fetal position on the ground</stage></speaker> He started it!</sp>

 <stage>Shang approaches Mulan and looks down over her. Mulan looks up, sees Shang over top of her
  and gets up quickly dusting herself off</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>to Mulan</stage></speaker> I don't need anyone causing trouble in my
  camp!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Sorry, <stage>in her man voice</stage> Uhh, I mean, sorry you had to
  see that. <stage>with her fist she taps Shang on the shoulder</stage> You know how it is when you
  get those, uh <stage>pounding her chest</stage> manly urges and you just have to kill something
   <stage>slapping her hand</stage>, fix things, uh, cook outdoors.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> What's your name?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>stumbling</stage></speaker> Ahh, I, uhhh, I, uh--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>stepping into Mulan's face</stage></speaker> Your commanding officer
  just asked you a question.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Uhh, I've got a name. Huh. And it's a boys name too.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>from the back of Mulan</stage></speaker> Ling, How 'bout Ling?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>to Mushu motioning with her head to Ling</stage></speaker> His name's
  Ling.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> I didn't ask for his name. I asked for yours.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Try, uh, ahh, Chu!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Ah Chu.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Ah Chu?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Gesundheit. He He, I kill myself.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>whispering over her shoulder</stage></speaker> Mushu.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Mushu?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> No.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Then what is it!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Ping! Ping was my best friend growing up!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> It's Ping.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Ping.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Of course Ping DID steal my gir-<stage>Mulan reaches back and grabs
   holds Mushu's mouth together</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Yes, my name is Ping.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Let me see your conscription notice. <stage>Takes the notice from
   Mulan</stage> Fa Zhou, *the* Fa Zhou?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> I didn't know Fa Zhou had a son.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Um, he...doesn't talk about me much. <stage>Mulan tries to hawk up a
   loogie and spit but the saliva just runs from her mouth. The recruits laugh</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> I can see why, the boy's an absolute lunatic.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>to the recruits</stage></speaker> Okay gentlemen, thanks to your new
  friend Ping, you'll spend tonight picking up every single grain of rice. And tomorrow, the real
  work begins.</sp>

 <stage>All recruits growl at Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>Popping out the front of Mulan's armor</stage></speaker> You know, we
  have to work on your people skills.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan sleeping in her tent. Mushu winds up Cri-Kee's wings. Cri-Kee rings like an
  alarm clock</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> All right, rise and shine sleeping beauty. <stage>Mulan rises and
   blinks</stage> C'mon <stage>rapping on Mulan's head with each syllable</stage> hup, hup, hup.
   <stage>Mulan groans, lies back down and pulls the covers over her head. Mushu pulls the covers
   off Mulan entirely</stage> Get your clothes on. Get ready. Got breakfast for ya. <stage>Mushu
   jumps onto Mulan's knee with a bowl of porridge</stage> Look, you get porridge, and it's happy to
  see you. <stage>Mushu shows her the bowl with two eggs and bacon looking like a smiley face.
   Cri-Kee pops up out from the bowl of porridge</stage> Hey, get outta there, you gonna make people
  sick! <stage>Mushu uses chopsticks to push Cri-Kee out of the porridge</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Am I late?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>while feeding Mulan</stage></speaker> No time to talk. Now remember, it's
  your first day of training so listen to your teacher and no fighting. Play nice with the other
  kids, unless of course one of the other kids wanna fight, then you have to kick the other kid's
  butt.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>with her mouth full of food</stage></speaker> But I don't wanna kick the
  other kid's butt.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Don't talk with your mouth full. Now let's see your war face
   <stage>Mulan looks at him with wide eyes and chipmunk cheeks full of food</stage>. I think my
  bunny slippers just ran for cover. C'mon scare me, girl! </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>swallows the food</stage></speaker> Rrrrrrr!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>rolling back into the half eaten bowl of porridge</stage></speaker> Oh,
  that's my tough looking warrior. That's what I'm talking about. Now get out there and make me
  proud. <stage>Mushu ties up Mulan's hair</stage></sp>

 <stage>Khan whinnies and pokes his head into the tent</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> What do you mean the troops just left? </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>acting surprised</stage></speaker> They what!? <stage>Mulan hurriedly
   puts on her clothes and jumps out of the tent going off to join the other recruits</stage>
 </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>running out from the tent calling after Mulan</stage></speaker> Wait, you
  forgot your sword. My little baby off to destroy people <stage>sniffle</stage>.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to the troops muddling around near Shang's tent</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>enters stage left</stage></speaker> Order people, order!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Recruit #2</speaker> I'd like a pan fried noodle.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po</speaker> Oh, oh, sweet and pungent shrimp <stage>Ling and others begin to
   laugh</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Recruit #3</speaker> Moo goo gai pan</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> That's not funny.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan comes running up to the group</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>noticing Mulan's arrival</stage></speaker> Looks like our new friend slept
  in this morning. <stage>Mulan stops between Ling and Yao</stage>
  <stage>to Ping</stage> Hellooo Ping, Are you hungry?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Yeah, 'cause I owe you a knuckle sandwich. <stage>grabs Mulan by the
   shirt collar drawing back his other arm. Mulan hides her face with her hands. Ling looks away,
   closes his eyes, and puts his fingers in his ears so that he wont hear anything</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>All Soldiers <stage>in agreement with Yao</stage></speaker> Yeah.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>loudly</stage></speaker> Soldiers! <stage>The soldiers line up quicky.
   Shang takes off his shirt and grabs a bow and quiver of arrows. Mulan is duly impressed by
   Shang's physique</stage> You will assemble swiftly and silently every morning. <stage>Shang walks
   down the line of soldiers</stage> Anyone who acts otherwise will answer to me.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Ooooo, tough guy.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>turning around with knocked arrow pointing towards Yao</stage></speaker>
  Yao. <stage>All recruits take a step back leaving Yao one step forward. Shang Points arrow skyward
   and shoots it into the top of a high pole</stage> Thank you for volunteering. Retrieve the
  arrow.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>bows to Shang</stage></speaker> I'll get that arrow pretty boy. And I'll do
  it with my shirt on. <stage>Yao prepares to leap onto that pole</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> One moment, you seem to be missing something. <stage>Chi Fu brings out
   two large bronze disks. Shang takes out one disk and holds it high speaking to all the
   troops</stage> This represents discipline <stage>Shang hands the weight to Yao and the weight
   falls to the ground taking Yao's arm with it</stage> and this represents strength <stage>Shang
   hands the other weight to Yao making him fall to the ground. The troops laugh while Mulan looks
   concerned</stage>. You need both to reach the arrow.</sp>

 <stage>Yao climbs up the pole then slips down under the weight. Ling, Chien-Po, and Mulan each take
  their turn and fall down. Mulan rubs her behind as she walks away in front of Shang</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> We've got a long way to go.</sp>

 <stage>Song I'll Make a Man Out of You</stage>

 <stage>Shang throws staffs to the soldiers. Yao intercepts Mulan's staff and trips her with
  it</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Let's get down to business-- to defeat the Huns.</sp>

 <stage>Shang throws up two clay pots and breaks them apart with his staff. The troops are highly
  impressed</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Recruits <stage>putting their staffs out at arms length, spoken</stage></speaker>
  Hua</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Did they send me daughters when I asked for sons? <stage>Ling puts a
   cricket down Mulan's back causing her to flail erratically</stage> You're the saddest bunch I
  ever met <stage>Most soldiers fall as Mulan moves uncontrollably</stage> But you can bet before
  we're through <stage>Shang does a somersault in the air landing near Mulan. He takes a pole in the
   stomach. Shang stops Mulan and takes her staff. He grabs her by the collar</stage> Mister, I'll
  make a man out of you </sp>

 <sp><stage>Shang steps on a lever throwing up 3 targets which he hits with 3 arrows from one
   bow</stage> Tranquil as a forest <stage>The recruits try and fail. Mulan gets ready to fire when
   Mushu sticks a target on her arrow before she shoots. Mulan looks at Mushu's in shock and pauses.
   Shang looks disdainfully at Mulan as she cracks a huge smile</stage> But on fire within
   <stage>Shang balances a bucket of water on his head holding a staff. The recruits fire stones at
   him which Shang deflect with the staff</stage> Once you find your center You are sure to win
   <stage>Mulan wobbles with the bucket of water on her head. As the recruits throw stones at her
   the bucket tips over onto her head</stage> You're a spineless, pale, pathetic lot And you haven't
  got a clue <stage>Shang throws his hand down into a river and retrieves a fish. Mulan throws her
   hand down into the river and retrieve's Yao's foot. Mushu comes out of the water with a fish in
   hand to give to Mulan</stage> Somehow I'll make a man out of you!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>running through a field of fire arrows</stage></speaker> I'm never
  gonna catch my breath</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>following Chien-Po, falls and gets hit in the butt with an
   arrow</stage></speaker> Say good-bye to those who knew me</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>Banging his head on a stone slab</stage></speaker> Boy I was a fool in
  school for cutting gym</sp>

 <stage>Shang practices martial arts with Mulan. With a punch to the face he knocks her back into a
  tree</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>from the tree acts as a boxing coach</stage></speaker> This guy's got 'em
  scared to death</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>Mushu pushes Mulan back out into the ring</stage></speaker> Hope he
  doesn't see right through me</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>stops as he's hopping across poles protruding from water causing Shang
    and the recruits to pile into him</stage></speaker> Now I really wish that I knew how to
  swim!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang and Chorus</speaker>
  <stage>Cannon fire misses the target in the middle of an open field. Ling kicks the support
   structure out from Mulan's cannon and it begins to fall. Mulan quickly grabs the cannon and it
   fires high and back towards the camp landing and exploding Chi Fu's tent</stage> (Be a man) We
  must be swift as the coursing river (Be a man) With all the force of a great typhoon (Be a man)
  With all the strength of a raging fire <stage>Picture of Shang looking over the camp from the hill
   not looking pleased</stage> Mysterious as the dark side of the moon </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>his troops laden with poles on their shoulders carrying bags of grain -
    one on each side. They march up a mountain</stage></speaker> Time is racing toward us till the
  Huns arrive <stage>Chi Fu points Shang's eyes back to a struggling Mulan who falls to the ground.
   Cri-Kee and Mushu try to pick her up but hide when Shang comes up to her. Shang picks up her pole
   with grain, puts it on top of his and returns to the troops. Mulan looks rejected</stage> Heed my
  every order and you might survive <stage>Shang hand the reigns of Khan to Mulan</stage> You're
  unsuited for the rage of war So pack up, go home, you're through How could I make a man out of
  you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang and Chorus <stage>Mulan takes the weights and tries to climb the pole
    again</stage></speaker> (Be a man) We must be swift as the coursing river <stage>Mulan ties the
   weights together behind the pole and uses the cloth to help her shimmy up the pole</stage> (Be a
  man) With all the force of a great typhoon <stage>As the sun begins to rise the recruits come out
   of their tents to cheer on Mulan</stage> (Be a man) With all the strength of a raging fire
   <stage>As Shang comes out of his tent, the arrow he shot up onto the pole comes down to his feet.
   He looks up and sees Mulan sitting on top of the pole</stage> Mysterious as the dark side of the
  moon</sp>

 <sp><stage>order of events during the last repeat of the chorus Troops hit all targets with arrows
   correctly. Mulan racing in front of Shang and the recruits with the pole and weights on her
   shoulders. Mulan kicking Shang in the face with a round house. Shang looking pleased. Chien-Po
   doing acrobatics on the poles as the troops follow. Staffs being thrown to troops, Yao hands
   Mulan hers. Yao running through arrows. Yao grabs Mulan's staff and hands it to her. Troop staff
   practice #1. (Hya) Ling breaking the block Troop staff Practice #2. (Hya) Mulan holding up fish.
   Troop staff practice #3. Cannon fire hitting the Hun Target. Troop staff practice #4 - jumping in
   the air (Hya)</stage> (Be a man) We must be swift as the coursing river (Be a man) With all the
  force of a great typhoon (Be a man) With all the strength of a raging fire Mysterious as the dark
  side of the moon</sp>

 <stage>End Song</stage>

 <stage>Interlude</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Shan Yu sitting on top of a tree. He cuts off the very top with his sword. His falcon
  swoops buy and drops a doll. Shan-Yu takes the doll, sniffs it, looks surprised, and drops down to
  the ground</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>tossing the doll to Hun Strong Man</stage></speaker> What do you
  see?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Strong Man <stage>feeling the doll</stage></speaker> Black pine, from the high
  mountains. <stage>Long Hair Hun Man takes the doll from Hun Strong Man. Bald Hun Man #1 takes a
   hair as it passes by him</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Bald Hun Man #1</speaker> White horse hair. Imperial stallions. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Long Hair Hun Man <stage>sniffing the doll</stage></speaker> Sulfur, from
  cannons.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> This doll came from a village in the Tung Shao Pass, where the
  Imperial Army's waiting for us.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Archer</speaker> We can avoid them easily.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>shaking his head</stage></speaker> No, the quickest way to the Emperor
  is through that pass. Besides, the little girl will be missing her doll. We should return it to
  her.</sp>

 <stage>End Interlude</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan by the lake with Mushu, Khan, and Cri-Kee</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Hey, oh, ah, no, this is not a good idea. What if somebody sees
  you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>from behind the reeds</stage></speaker> Just because I look like a man
  doesn't mean I have to smell like one. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>holding a towel covering his eyes with his ears</stage></speaker> So a
  couple of guys don't rinse out their socks, picky, picky, picky. Well myself I kinda like that
  corn chip's smell.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>running by Mushu and jumps into the lake splashing water on
   Mushu</stage></speaker> Ahhhhhhh.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Okay, all right, all right, that's enough. Now, c'mon, get out before
  you get all pruny and stuff <stage>holding out a towel towards Mulan keeping his eyes
   covered</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Mushu, if you're so worried, go stand watch.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Yeah, yeah, <stage>walking in a womanly fashion speaking in woman's
   voice</stage> stand watch Mushu while I blow our secret with my stupid girly habits. <stage>back
   to normal</stage> Humph, hygiene.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee <stage>alarmed, tugging on Mushu's whiskers</stage></speaker> Chirp,
  Chirp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Me first! Me first! Me First! <stage>Yao, Ling and Chien-Po run by Mushu
   smacking him in the face with colored boxers</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>gasps</stage></speaker> Ah. We're doomed! There a couple of things I know
  they're bound to notice!</sp>

 <stage>Yao and Ling jump into the water. Chien-Po dips in his toe to check temperature then jumps
  in causing a large wave. Yao and Ling ride the wave towards Mulan. Mulan sees them and hides her
  face behind a lily pad</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>calling</stage></speaker> Hey, Ping.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan peeks over the lily pad and spreads it on the water covering her chest</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>speaking nervously and unnaturally in a manly voice</stage></speaker> Oh
  hi guys, I didn't know you were *here*. <stage>Yao, Ling and Chien-Po share "this boy is strange"
   looks</stage> I was just washing, so now I'm clean and I'm gonna go. Bye, bye. <stage>Mulan hides
   behind a rock keeping her front facing the rock</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>from behind Mulan</stage></speaker> Come back here. I know we were jerks
  to you before so lets start over. <stage>extending his hand to shake hands with Mulan</stage> Hi,
  I'm Ling!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>covering her chest with her left arm, she turns and shakes his hand with
    an outstretched right arm, smiling</stage></speaker> Heh, heh. <stage>Mulan turns and wades away
   from Ling and runs into Chien-Po</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>taking a lily pad off his head</stage></speaker> And I'm
  Chien-Po.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>waving slightly and smiling</stage></speaker> Hello Chien-Po.</sp>

 <stage>Yao stands on top of a rock looking down at the others. Mulan looks down into the water and
  hides her eyes with her free hand</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> And I am Yao, king of the rock. And there's nothin' you girls can do
  about it.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>taking a fighting stance</stage></speaker> Oh, yeah? Well, I think Ping
   <stage>elbowing Mulan</stage> and I could take you.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>wading away</stage></speaker> I really don't want to take him
  anywhere.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>following Mulan</stage></speaker> Ping, we have to fight!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> No we don't. <stage>unnaturally</stage> We could just close our eyes
  and swim around.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> C'mon don't be such a g--Ouch! Something bit me.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>popping out of the water between Mulan and Ling</stage></speaker> What a
  nasty flavor.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>with fear and gusto</stage></speaker> Snake! </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>while all three of them climb up the rock and on each
   other</stage></speaker> Snake, snake.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan whistles for Khan and wades back to shore. Khan comes close enough to shore and Mulan
  hides behind Khan as she wraps a towel around her body</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Yao, Ling and Chien-Po calmed down sitting on the rock</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> Some king of the rock! <stage>Yao pushes him off the rock</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan with towel wrapped around her</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Boy, that was close.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>brushing his teeth</stage></speaker> No, that was vile! You owe me
  big!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I never want to see a naked man again. <stage>the rest of the troops
   run by naked and jump into the lake</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Hey, don't look at me. I ain't biting any more butts.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan outside Chi Fu's Tent having dressed fully. Chi Fu and Shang are talking from
  inside</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>fading in</stage></speaker> You think your troops are ready to fight?
  Hah! They would not last a minute against the Huns. </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> They completed their training.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Those *boys* are no more fit to be soldiers than you are to be
  Captain. Once the general reads my report, your troops will never see battle.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>from outside the tent</stage></speaker> Oh no you don't. I've worked to
  hard to get Mulan into this war. <stage>to Cri-Kee</stage> This guy's messing with my plan.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>grabbing onto the front of Chi Fu's clip board</stage></speaker> We're
  not finished.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>pulling the board away</stage></speaker> Be careful, Captain. The
  General may be your father, but I am the Emperor's council. And, oh, by the way, huh, I got that
  job on my own. <stage>opens the entrance to the tent for Shang</stage> You're dismissed.</sp>

 <stage>Shang storms out of the tent and starts to walk by Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>in a manly voice</stage></speaker> Hey, I'll hold him and you punch, heh,
  heh... <stage>Shang walks by without reacting</stage> or not. <stage>calling out to Shang</stage>
  For what it's worth, I think you're a great captain. <stage>Shang pauses to glance back, then
   continues forward</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>looking at Mulan's fixed gaze on Shang</stage></speaker> I saw that!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>innocently</stage></speaker> What?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>teasing</stage></speaker> You like him don't you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> No, I--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Yeah right, Yeah sure. Look, <stage>pointing to Mulan's tent</stage>
  go to your tent. <stage>Mulan walks away with a look of delight. Mushu talks to Cri-Kee</stage> I
  think it's time we took this war into our own hands <stage>rubbing hands together</stage>.</sp>

 <stage>Mushu and Cri-Kee wait outside Chi Fu's Tent. Chi Fu emerges with carrying a scrub brush and
  wrapped in a towel and with big showering slippers on his feet. He whistles as he walks off. Mushu
  and Cri-Kee enter his tent. Cri-Kee uses his legs to write up a letter. He finishes and Mushu
  takes the paper</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Okay, okay, let me see what you've got. From General Li, dear son,
  we're waiting for the huns at the pass and it would mean a lot if you'd come and back us up.
   <stage>sarcastically</stage> That's great except you forgot, "and since we're all out of
  potpourri, maybe you wouldn't mind bringing up some." Hellooooo, this is the army! Make it sound
  more urgent, please! You know what I'm talkin' about? <stage>Cri-Kee starts writing the note
   again</stage> That's better, much better. <stage>taking the note</stage> Okay, Let's go.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Khan drinking water from the trough. Mushu is on his back</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Khan-ie baby, hey, we need a ride. <stage>Khan squirts Mushu off his
   back with water from his mouth</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to Chi Fu walking out of the lake wrapped in a towel, sounds of laughter can be heart
  from the troops</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>muttering</stage></speaker> Insubordinate ruffians. <stage>then calling
   to the troops</stage> You men owe me a new pair of slippers. And I do not squeal like a girl.
   <stage>a panda bear chomps down on the slipper Chi Fu is holding</stage> Aaaaaahhhhhh!</sp>

 <sp>Mushu <stage>sitting on top of the panda bear behind a dummy of a soldier using sticks to
   gesticulate with the dummy's arms to push the note towards Chi Fu. Cri-Kee works the
   mouth</stage>: Urgent news from the general! <stage>Chi Fu looks over the panda</stage> What's
  the matter, you've never seen a 'black and white' before?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Who are you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Excuse me! I think the question is: who are you? We're in a war man!
  There's no time for stupid questions. I should have your hat for that, <stage>the panda starts
   walking forward</stage> snatch it right off of your head <stage>swiping with an arm at Chi Fu's
   hat. Mushu turns the upper half of the dummy around after the panda passes Chi Fu. Chi Fu begins
   reading the message</stage>. But I'm feeling gracious today, so carry on before I report you.
   <stage>the panda walks up a tree taking Mushu and Cri-Kee with him out of sight</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>looking around for Mushu but not finding him, then runs into Shang's
    tent</stage></speaker> Captain. Urgent news from the General. We're needed at the front.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>from up in the tree</stage></speaker> Pack your bags Cri-Kee, we're
  movin' out. <stage>Cri-Kee high fives Mushu</stage></sp>

 <stage>Song: A Girl Worth Fighting For</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Army Chorus <stage>troops walking up hill</stage></speaker> For a long time we've been
  marching off to battle</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>close-up of Yao, then a shot of 2 cows</stage></speaker> In a thundering
  herd we feel a lot like cattle</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cow <stage>spoken</stage></speaker> Moo</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Army Chorus <stage>showing troops marching</stage></speaker> Like the pounding beat
  our aching feet aren't easy to ignore</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>catching up to Yao and Chien-Po</stage></speaker> Hey, think of instead, A
  girl worth fighting for <stage>Yao, Ling and Chien-Po look upwards dreamily</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>spoken from behind</stage></speaker> Huh?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>grabbing Mulan and drawing her close while pulling out a
    centerfold</stage></speaker> That's what I said, a girl worth fighting for <stage>Mulan runs
   away seeing the centerfold</stage></sp>

 <sp><stage>artistry section where the images are drawn like painted people. Ling is seen looking at
   a woman and then kissing her</stage> I want her paler than the moon with eyes that shine like
  stars</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>lifting and lowering a woman over his head then opening his chest to show a
    gaping wound that we can see the woman through</stage></speaker> My girl will marvel at my
  strength, adore my battle scars</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>Chien-Po and a woman circle around then land on the edge of a large
    bowl of rice as a cow, pig and chicken fall beside them</stage></speaker> I couldn't care less
  what she'll wear or what she looks like It all depends on what she cooks like: Beef, pork,
  chicken... <stage>end painted people section, the last image fades into statues that the troops
   just passed</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>All Three</speaker> Mmm...</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>looking at Mulan while crossing the river with swords over their heads.
    Mulan looks disgusted and hurries forward</stage></speaker> Bet the local girls thought you were
  quite the charmer</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>with armor full of water to make him look muscular</stage></speaker> And
  I'll bet the ladies love a man in armor <stage>the water leaks out making Ling look like his
   normal self</stage></sp>

 <sp>Army Chorus <stage>Mushu whistles to ladies working in the rice field from out of the carriage
   holding cannons. Cri-Kee looks shocked. The ladies look and giggle at Mulan who hides her
   face</stage>: You can guess what we have missed the most since we went off to war What do we
  want? A girl worth fighting for!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>Mulan walks away from Yao and into Chien-Po</stage></speaker> My girl will
  think I have no faults</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po</speaker> That I'm a major find</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>Caught between Yao, Ling, and Chien-Po who all look up dreamily waiting
    for her ideal woman. She is forced to speak (sing)</stage></speaker>
  <stage>spoken</stage> Uh, <stage>singing</stage> How about a girl who's got a brain, <stage>Yao
   starts to look unimpressed</stage> Who always speaks her mind? <stage>Mulan shrugs her
   shoulders</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling, Yao and Chien-Po <stage>disdainfully, looking disappointed and
   disgusted</stage></speaker> Nah!</sp>

 <sp>Ling <stage>grabbing Mulan's shoulder and leaning on her, she takes his hand off and shakes her
   head disapprovingly. Ling leans against the carriage of cannons</stage>: My manly ways and turns
  of phrase are sure to thrill her</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>hitting Khan so that the carriage runs out from under Ling. Ling looks
    upset then falls in the mud</stage></speaker> He thinks he's such a lady-killer!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> I've a girl back home who's unlike any other.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>aside to Mulan</stage></speaker> Yeah, the only girl who'd love him is his
  mother! <stage>Mulan smiles</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Army Men <stage>lining up locking arms across each others shoulders with Mulan in the
    middle to her discontent</stage></speaker> But when we come home in victory they'll line up at
  the door!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>sitting on top of Chien-Po</stage></speaker> What do we want?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Army Chorus</speaker> A girl worth fighting for!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> Wish that I had</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Army Chorus <stage>Mulan breaks away and walks in the opposite direction of the
    army</stage></speaker> A girl worth fighting for! (whistle) <stage>Mulan sees Ling, Yao, and
   Chien-Po with snowballs about to pelt her so she turns around</stage> A girl worth
  fighting--</sp>

 <stage>All have stunned looks on their faces</stage>

 <stage>End Song</stage>

 <stage>Cut to ruins of a burned out village. The soldiers walk through the singed gate and look
  around at the few planks that remain from the buildings</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>from mounted horse</stage></speaker> Search for survivors.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan walking around the burned-out village. She finds a the doll that Shan-Yu was
  holding and looks up sorrowfully. Shang comes to her side</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> I don't understand. My father should have been here.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>calling out from the top of a hill overlooking a
   valley</stage></speaker> Captain! </sp>

 <stage>Chi Fu points down to the valley where the remains of General Li's army can be seen. Flags
  poking up out of the snow, armor lying face down, broken cannon carts. Ling, Yao, Mulan, and a
  soldier have the look of horror on their faces as they look into the valley. Chien-Po walks up
  from the valley carrying a helmet</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-po <stage>handing the helmet to Shang</stage></speaker> ...the General.</sp>

 <stage>Shang takes the helmet and walks to the edge of the hill. He draws his sword and stabs it
  into the snow upright. He kneels down and places the helmet on top of the sword. Mulan approaches
  him from behind</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>softly</stage></speaker> I'm sorry.</sp>

 <stage>Shang gets up, turns around and puts his hand on Mulan's shoulder and he walks by. Shang
  walks to the center of the troops. He grabs his horse by the saddle, takes one quick look of grief
  then mounts his horse</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> The Huns are moving quickly. We'll make better time to the Imperial
  City through the Tung Shao Pass. We're the only hope for the Emperor now. Move out!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan looks at the sword, takes out the doll she found and places the doll at the base of
  the sword. She turns around and joins the rest of the troops marching on</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan standing next to Khan saddled to the cart with cannons. A cannon blast shoots
  out of the cart and explodes in the air. The troops look surprised. Mulan glances back with a
  scowl into the hole in the canopy of the cart to see Mushu with a sorrowful face. Mushu points at
  Cri-Kee. Shang charges up to Mulan on his horse, Chi Fu right behind</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>angrily</stage></speaker> What happened?!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>stumbling</stage></speaker> Uhhh--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> You just gave away our position. Now we're--<stage>an arrow hits Shang
   in the shoulder as he falls to the ground. Shang pulls out the arrow</stage>
  <stage>calling out</stage> Get out of range!!</sp>

 <stage>The troops hurriedly run away as many arrows start falling all around them. Mulan pulls Khan
  by the reins to hurry him up. Fire arrows start hitting the cart with cannons attached to Khan.
  The cart begins to blaze with fire</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Save the cannons!</sp>

 <sp><stage>The troops form a human chain and start taking the cannons out of the burning cart one
   by one while Mulan steadies Khan to keep him from bolting. Chien-Po grabs many and hauls them on
   his own. The troops grab</stage>as many cannons as they safely can and Mulan cuts Khan free from
  the cart. She mounts Khan and charges away from the fire. The cart explodes sending Mulan flying
  off Khan losing her helmet and sword which land near her. Mushu and Cri-Kee, sent flying by the
  blast, scream and land near Mulan.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Oh sure, save the horse.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan grabs Mushu with her right hand and grabs the sword with her left and runs to the
  troops position. Cri-Kee and Khan follow. Yao, Ling, Chien-Po and other recruits set up cannons
  against rocks. They dodge a set of arrows that fall around them</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Fire!</sp>

 <stage>They launch a volley at the mountain where the archers are stationed. As the cannon fire
  explodes, Shan-Yu's army hides</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Fire!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan, Ling and Chien-Po launch a second volley at the mountain where the archers are
  stationed. No more arrows can be seen coming from the mountain position</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Hold the last cannon. <stage>Yao poised to light his cannon, pauses.
   Shan-Yu and his troops appear at the top of the mountain</stage> Prepare to fight. If we die, we
  die with honor.</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu raises his sword high above his head and charges down the mountain at Shang's
  position. His falcon flies off his shoulder on Shan-Yu's war cry The Hun army follows</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Yao, aim the cannon at Shan-Yu.</sp>

 <stage>The line of Shang's troops with Mulan at the end draw their swords. Mulan looks down at her
  sword and sees the reflection of a large snow embankment hanging to the side of a cliff. She
  rushes forward</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>being pushed aside by Mulan as she grabs the cannon</stage></speaker> Hey.
  Shang: Ping, come back. Ping!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan charges forward towards the oncoming horde of the Hun army being led by Shan-Yu and
  his falcon. Mushu looks over her at the oncoming horde with worry in his eyes</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>starting to run after her waving his arms</stage></speaker> Stop!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan plants the cannon and aims it for the cliff with the snow overhang</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>seeing Shan-Yu riding closer to their position</stage></speaker> All
  right, you might want to light that right about now. Quickly! Quickly!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan takes out the flint and tries to light the fuse. Shan-Yu's falcon swoops buy knocking
  Mulan down scattering the flint rock</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>speaking to Ling and Chien-Po</stage></speaker> C'mon, we've gotta help.
   <stage>they charge towards Mulan's position</stage></sp>

 <stage>Mulan searches for the flint in the snow in vain. She sees Mushu, grabs him and stretches
  him causing him to light the fuse. Mushu lands on the cannon and the cannon fires off just above
  the charging Shan-Yu</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>tailing off as he rides the cannon toward the snow
   embankment</stage></speaker> You missed him! How could you miss? He was three feet in front of
  you!</sp>

 <stage>The cannon lodges in the snow and explodes causing the beginning of a large avalanche. Mulan
  looks up with an evil grin on her face and Shan-Yu watches in horror as many of his troops begin
  to be swallowed up by the snow</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>recollecting himself and focusing in on Mulan</stage></speaker>
  Yrrrrrrraah. </sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu swipes at Mulan with his sword hitting her in the right side. Mulan falls back
  grabbing her right side. Shan-Yu's horse stumbles. Mulan uses this break to bolt away from the
  avalanche. Shan-Yu gains his composure and starts to gallop away from the avalanche on his horse.
  Shang looks with shock as hee sees the avalanche coming toward him. Mulan grabs Shang as she
  passes by him, turning him around and helping him run away from the avalanche</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao, Chien-Po and Ling <stage>running towards the oncoming avalanche</stage></speaker>
  Yeeahhhhhh! <stage>they stop. noticing the oncoming avalanche they turn around and run back to
   where they came from</stage> Waaaaaaaaaa!</sp>

 <stage>Khan jumps away from the troops position and starts to run towards Mulan passing Ling, Yao
  and Chien-Po. The avalanche swallows up Shan-Yu and his horse. Khan arrives at Mulan's position
  just ahead of the avalanche. Mulan jumps onto Khan and reaches for Shang. She grabs his hand, then
  the avalanche rushes forth breaking their grip, turning Khan around facing the oncoming avalanche
  of snow</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Ling, Yao and Chien-Po standing behind a rock. They see the snow approaching close
  and run to larger shelter where the rest of Shang's army is positioned just as the avalance
  reaches their posision</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mushu riding down the snow on a shield</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>calling out</stage></speaker> Mulan! Mulan! <stage>seeing hair sticking
   up from the snow</stage> Mulan? <stage>Mushu picks up the Hun by the hair</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Soldier</speaker> Arrrrr.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>pushing the hun soldier back under the snow</stage></speaker> Nope.
  Mulan! <stage>Mushu picks up Cri-Kee out of the snow</stage> Man, you are one lucky bug.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan riding Khan above the snow into the teeth of the avalanche. Khan and Mulan are
  swept under by the snow and reemerge quickly. She looks back and sees Shang passed out riding the
  wave of snow</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling loudly</stage></speaker> Shang, Shang! <stage>Mulan turns around
   and rides to Shang's position. She picks him up and places him on Khan. She turns Khan around
   again to be riding upstream</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to Chien-Po with Ling standing on him and Yao standing on top of Ling</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po</speaker> Do you see them?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>extatically</stage></speaker> Yes! <stage>Yao shoots an arrow with a rope
   attached</stage> Perfect! Now I'll pull them to safe--<stage>Yao grasps at air as the rope
   completely passed through his hands</stage>--ty.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan and Shang on Khan with Mushu and Cri-Kee riding up to her on his shield</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>riding on the shield up to Mulan, Khan and Shang speaking loudly, above
    the noise of the avalanche</stage></speaker> Hey Mulan, I found a lucky cricket.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>speaking loudly</stage></speaker> We need help! <stage>Yao's arrow lands
   near by Mulan and she picks it up and starts to tie the rope to Khan</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>Getting off the shield and carrying Cri-Kee with him</stage></speaker>
  Ooo, nice, very nice, you can sit by me. <stage>Mushu sees that they're about to fall over the
   cliff. He and Cri-Kee look frightened</stage> Ahhhhh! We're gonna die! We're gonna die! I know
  we're gonna die! No way we can survive this! Death is coming! <stage>Mulan knocks the arrow and
   shoots it toward Yao</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>crying</stage></speaker> I let them slip through my fingers. <stage>Mulan's
   arrow lands in Yao's hands. He grabs on and is pulled toward the cliff, the soldiers grab onto
   Yao and hold him steady near the cliff edge with the rope taught over the cliff</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Pull</sp>

 <stage>Chien-Po prays as he calmly walks up to the group of soldiers. He lifts them all up and
  pulls backward hauling Mulan, Shang, Khan, Mushu and Cri-Kee to safety</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> I knew we could to it. You da man. <stage>Mulan looks pleased</stage>
  Well sorta. <stage>Mulan grimaces</stage></sp>

 <stage>The soldiers help them up to the cliff</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> Step back guys, give 'em some air.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>catching his breath</stage></speaker> Ping, you are the craziest man I've
  ever met. And for that I owe you my life. From now on, you have my trust. <stage>Mulan smiles
   big</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling</speaker> Let's hear it for Ping! The bravest of us all.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>lifting his arm high</stage></speaker> You're king of the mountain!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>jumping up and down</stage></speaker> Yes, yes, yes!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>beginning to stand up</stage></speaker> Ahhh, <stage>she clutches her
   right side</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Ping, what's wrong? <stage>Mulan removes her hand slightly to show the
   blood on her hand and seeping through the armour</stage>
  <stage>loudly</stage> He's wounded, get help! <stage>Ping starts to pass out. The images of Shang,
   Yao, Ling, and Chien-Po begin to fade as she loses consciousness</stage> Ping, hold on. Hold
  on.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to outside of the medic tent. Mulan and Medic are inside. Shang stands by the entrance.
  Yao, Ling and Chien-Po look quite concerned. Ling drums his fingers on his knees. The medic comes
  out from the tent and whispers to Shang. Shang looks astonished and goes into the tent. Mulan is
  lying down. She opens her eyes, sees Shang and smiles at the sight of him. She sits up allowing
  the blanket to fall to her waist revealing her form fitting bandages on her chest. She sees
  Shang's surprised look and realizes her feminine form is noticeable</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>gasping as she covers up</stage></speaker> Huh, I can explain.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>stepping into the tent</stage></speaker> Huh? So it's true.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling after Shang as he steps out of the tent</stage></speaker>
  Shang!</sp>

 <stage>Cut to outside the tent. Chi Fu hauls out Mulan by the arm. Mulan uses her other hand to
  hold the blanket</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> I knew there was something wrong with you. <stage>Chi Fu takes off
   Mulan's hair tie and throws her to the ground</stage> A woman.</sp>

 <stage>Ling, Yao and Chien-Po are shocked</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>to the troops</stage></speaker> Trecherous snake.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>on the ground kneeling and hunched over, speaking to
   Shang</stage></speaker> My name is Mulan. I did it to save my father.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>to the troops</stage></speaker> High treason!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I didn't mean for it to go this far.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>getting in Mulan's face and speaking to her while she
   whinces</stage></speaker> Ultimate dishonor.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> It was the only way. Please believe me.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>to Shang</stage></speaker> Hmph, Captain?</sp>

 <stage>Shang walks over to Khan and takes the sword out of the scabbard attached to Khan. Khan
  rears back</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>to the soldier by Khan</stage></speaker> Restrain him.</sp>

 <stage>Shang walks toward Mulan with sword in hand</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao, Ling and Chien-Po <stage>rushing toward Mulan</stage></speaker> Noooooo!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>putting his hand to stop Ling, Yao, and Chien-Po from proceeding
    further</stage></speaker> You know the law.</sp>

 <stage>Shang stands over Mulan. Mulan looks at Shang then bows her head in anticipation. Shang
  lifts the sword high above his head and throws it down in front of Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> A life for a life. My debt is repaid. <stage>turns and walks towards
   the Imperial City</stage> Move out!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>coming up to Shang's face</stage></speaker> But you can't just...</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>getting in Chi Fu's face</stage></speaker> I said, "Move out!"</sp>

 <stage>The troops walk off toward the Imperial City leaving Mulan behind with Khan, Cri-Kee, and
  Mushu. Mulan is sitting, shivering. Khan takes his blanket and wraps it around Mulan with his
  mouth and sits behind her. Cri-Kee lights a fire with twigs. When he doesn't get warm, he moves
  under the blanket wrapped around Mulan. Mushu walks toward Mulan carrying a stick</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> I was this close, this close to impressing the ancestors, getting the
  top shelf, an entourage. Man, all my fine work, ffft. <stage>Mushu picks up a dumpling with his
   stick, slumps down in front of the fire Cri-Kee made and begins to cook the dumpling over the
   fire</stage>
  <stage>glancing up</stage> Hi.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>look of sadness</stage></speaker> I should never have left home.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Eh, come on, you wanted to save your father's life. Who knew you'd end
  up shaming him, disgracing your ancestors, and losing all your friends. You know, you just gotta,
  you gotta learn to let these things go <stage>looking as if he's about to cry</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Maybe I didn't go for my father. Maybe what I really wanted was to
  prove I could do things right. So when I looked in the mirror <stage>picking up her helmet and
   looking at her reflection in her helmet</stage> I'd see someone worthwhile. But I was wrong. I
  see nothing. <stage>throws the helmet down and a tear runs down her cheek</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>picking up the helmet and spitting on it</stage></speaker> Well that's
  because this just needs a little spit, that's all. Let me shine this up for ya <stage>wiping the
   spit to clean the helmet and holding it up to Mulan</stage>. I can see you, look at you, you look
  so pretty. <stage>seeing Mulan is not cheered up by his actions, he shows sorrow on his
   face</stage> The truth is we're both frauds. Your ancestors never sent me, they don't even like
  me. I mean, you risked your life to help people you love. I risked your life to help myself. At
  least you had good intentions <stage>Mulan smiles</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee <stage>jumping on top of the helmet beginning to bawl</stage></speaker> Chirp,
  Chirp, Chirp. Bawl, Bawl.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> What!? What do you mean you're not lucky? You lied to me?
   <stage>Cri-Kee nods</stage>
  <stage>to Khan</stage> And what are you? A sheep?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>sadly</stage></speaker> I'll have to face my father sooner or later.
  Let's go home.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Yeah, this ain't gonna be pretty. But, don't you worry, 'kay?
  Things'll work out. We started this thing together and that's how we'll finish. <stage>Mushu hugs
   Mulan. Mulan smiles</stage> I promise.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Shan-Yu's falcon flying over the avalanche site. Shan-Yu's hand pops out of the snow.
  He gets up and glances around</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>screaming</stage></speaker> Rrrrrrraaaaaaaaahhh!</sp>

 <stage>Hun Archer, Long-Hair Hun Man, Hun Strong Guy, Hun Bald Man #1, and Hun Bald Man #2 each pop
  out of the snow and join Shan-Yu. They set off towards the Imperial City</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>seeing them from behind, gasps</stage></speaker> Huh. <stage>Mulan runs,
   grabs her sword, mounts Khan, and heads out following the Huns to the Imperial City</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Home is that way! <stage>points to the opposite direction Mulan is
   heading</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I have to do something.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Did you see those Huns!? They popped out of the snow, like
  daisies!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Are we in this together or not?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Cri-Kee <stage>emphatically</stage></speaker> Chirp, Chirp.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Well, let's go kick some Huny buns! <stage>Jumps onto Khan and utters
   fighting words as they ride off to the Imperial City</stage> Wu Hu Ha Ga, Wu Hu Ha Ga</sp>

 <stage>Cut to the victory parade in the Imperial City. Fireworks go off, kites are flying. The
  drummers march by, followed by the flutist, followed by the acrobats. The Parade Leader follows,
  then Shang and his men, followed by lion dancers</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Parade Leader</speaker> Make way for the heros of China.</sp>

 <stage>Shang leads the men on horseback, all have sorrowful looks on their faces. Mulan rides up
  through the crowd and stops. She looks around and sees Shang in the parade</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling out</stage></speaker> Shang! <stage>riding next to
  him</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>surprised</stage></speaker> Mulan?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> The Huns are alive, they're in the city.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> You don't belong here Mulan, go home.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>with a scowl rides khan to the other side of Shang</stage></speaker>
  Shang, I saw them in the mountains. You have to believe me.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Why should I?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>riding ahead to block Shang's horse</stage></speaker> Why else would I
  come back? You said you'd trust Ping. Why is Mulan any different?</sp>

 <stage>Shang turns his horse and rides around Mulan and goes forward</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>to Yao, Chien-Po and Ling</stage></speaker> Keep your eyes open. I know
  they're here. Hya.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan rides off and stops near the entrance to the palace, she dismounts Khan and runs into
  the palace yard</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Now where are you going?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling over her shoulder</stage></speaker> To find someone who will
  believe me. <stage>Mulan runs into the palace yard</stage>
 </sp>

 <stage>Cut to the parade procession stopping in front of the Emperor on the steps of the palace.
  Chi Fu stands next to Shang and gives him Shan-Yu's sword. The Lion dancers stop behind Shang. A
  palace man strikes a large gong and the people fall silent</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> My children, heaven smiles down upon the Middle Kingdom. China will
  sleep safely tonight thanks to our brave warriors.</sp>

 <stage>The crowd cheers</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan at the fringe of the crowd</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>approaching Man #1 laying her hand on his shoulder</stage></speaker> Sir,
  the Emperor's in danger! <stage>Man #1 rips his shoulder away from Mulan's touch and moves
   away</stage>
  <stage>agitated</stage> But the Huns are here! <stage>Mulan walks up to Man #2</stage> Please, you
  have to help me. <stage>Man #2 walks away from Mulan</stage>
  <stage>turning to Mushu who is standing near her in the yard</stage> No one will listen!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Huh? Oh, I'm sorry, did you say something?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>irritatedly</stage></speaker> Mushu!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Hey, you're a girl again, remember?</sp>

 <stage>Cut to Shang holding the sword before the Emperor</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>kneeling down giving the sword to the Emperor</stage></speaker> Your
  Majesty, I present to you the sword of Shan-Yu.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> I know what this means to you, Captain Li. Your father would have
  been very proud.</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu's falcon swoops down and takes the sword as Shang is giving it to the Emperor. The
  falcon rises above the roof and drops the sword to Shan-Yu who was sitting next to the gargoyles
  in the shadows blending in. He rises out of the shadows to catch the sword so that all the people
  can see his face. The masses of people gasp at the sight of Shan-Yu. Shang begins to draw his
  sword. All 5 of Shan-Yu's men jump out from behind the dragon knocking down Shang and grab the
  Emperor knocking off his hat. Hun Bald Man #1 and #2 carry the Emperor into the Palace.
  Long-Haired Hun Man and Hun Strong Guy close the palace doors as Hun archer knocks his arrow
  retreating into the Palace to threaten would be rescue attempts</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>getting up and running toward the closing doors</stage></speaker>
  No.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>beckoning to the other soldiers</stage></speaker> C'mon.</sp>

 <stage>Shang reaches the palace doors just as they close with all the Huns inside</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>laughs evily</stage></speaker> Ha, Ha, Ha, Ha, Ha, Ha.</sp>

 <stage>Shang and his soldiers pick up a big stone statue and use it as a battering ram. They are
  unsuccessful at opening the door. Mulan sees what's going on and arrives at the steps</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>to herself</stage></speaker> They'll never reach the Emperor in time.
   <stage>She looks at the columns and runs near to the Shang and his soldiers. She whistles loudly
   catching the soldiers' attention</stage> Hey guys, I've got an idea. <stage>Mulan runs around the
   palace to the right towards the columns</stage></sp>

 <stage>Song: I'll Make a Man Out of You (reprise) plays in the background during the next action
  sequence</stage>

 <sp>(Be a man) We must be swift as the coursing river (Be a man) With all the force of a great
  typhoon (Be a man) With all the strength of a raging fire Mysterious as the dark side of the
  moon</sp>

 <stage>Yao, Ping and Chien-Po look at one another then drop the statue and follow Mulan. Shang
  looks astonished. Around the corner Yao, Ling and Chien-Po begin to take off their armor and dress
  as women. Once the transformation is complete, they take out their sashes and prepare to shimmy up
  the columns. Shang arrives and taps Mulan on the shoulder. He takes off his cape and wraps it
  around the column to signify that he's coming along. They shimmy up the poles together</stage>

 <stage>End song</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Hun Bald Man #1 and #2 arriving with the Emperor and a high balcony within the
  palace. Shan-Yu drops down from the roof</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> Boo. <stage>Shan-Yu steps into the balcony next to the
   Emperor</stage>
  <stage>to Hun Bald Man #1 and #2</stage> Guard the door <stage>they walk off down the stairs that
   lead to the balcony</stage>. <stage>pacing around the Emperor</stage> Your walls and armies have
  fallen, and now it's your turn. Bow to me.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to the entrance to the stairwell that leads to the balcony. Hun Bald Man #1 and #2 come
  down the stairs and close the door, joining Hun Archer Man, Hun Strong Man and Hun Long-Hair Man.
  Mulan and company are around the corner</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>whispering</stage></speaker> Okay, any questions?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>whispering</stage></speaker> Does this dress make me look fat? <stage>Mulan
   slaps him</stage> Ow.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan, Yao, Ling and Chien-Po walk out smiling, giggling and trying to act lady-like
  including holding fans and waving fans</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Archer</speaker> Who's there?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Bald Man #2 <stage>putting down Hun Bald Man #1's sword</stage></speaker>
  Concubines.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Hun Bald Man #1</speaker> Ugly concubines.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Ling <stage>waving daintily, speaking to Yao</stage></speaker> Oh he's so cute.</sp>

 <stage>Hun Bald Man #2 smiles and waves back. Hun Bald Man #1 elbows Hun Bald Man #2. A bitten
  apple falls out from beneath Ling's dress. He pulls the dress out and turns so as not to expose
  the loss of figure</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>from around the corner putting his head down into his
   hand</stage></speaker> Aww.</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu's Falcon sees Shang and starts to squawk. Mushu from above singes off all his
  feathers with his fire breathing</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>to Cri-Kee sitting above him</stage></speaker> Now that's what I call
  Mongolian Barbeque. <stage>Cri-Kee rolls on his back in laughter. The stunned falcon doesn't do
   anything</stage></sp>

 <stage>Hun Bald Man #2 picks up the apple and offers it back to Ling. Ling, Yao, and Chien-Po pull
  out the fruit they were using to simulate a woman's chest. Chien-Po takes his watermelons and
  smashes them on the heads of Hun Bald Man #1 and #2. He then smashes their two heads together and
  they fall to the ground. Ling pushes the apple into Hun Long-Hair man's mouth and kicks him in the
  stomach causing Hun Long-Hair Man to stoop over on the ground. Ling uses his head to crack Hun
  Long-Hair Man's back. Hun Strong Guy lunges his fist at Yao and misses, he misses with the other.
  Yao grabs the outstretched arm and flips him over onto his head. Mulan kicks away Hun Archer Man's
  bow and knocked arrow, avoids his strike by turning her back to Hun Archer. She follows with a
  left elbow to the stomach followed by a left upper cut knocking Hun Archer to the ground. She sits
  on his back and uses the bow to pull his head back</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>calling out</stage></speaker> Shang, GO!</sp>

 <stage>Shang runs out from behind the corner, charges through the door and runs up the
  stairs</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Shan-Yu and the Emperor on the balcony</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> I tire of your arrogance old man. <stage>yelling and putting his
   sword at the emperor's throat</stage> Bow to me!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> No matter how the wind howls, the mountain cannot bow to it.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> Then you will kneel in pieces. <stage>Shan-Yu draws back his sword
   to strike the Emperor</stage></sp>

 <stage>Shang runs up in time to block the striking blow of Shan-Yu with his sword. Shang swipes
  with his sword. Shan-Yu grabs Shang's arm and throws him towards the edge. Shang grabs onto a
  column and he flies over the edge and uses the momentum to swing back and kick Shan-Yu. Shan-Yu
  falls to the ground, Shang on top of him. Shang punches Shan-Yu. Shan-Yu grabs Shang and rolls
  over forcing Shang to be on his back underneath him. Shang uses his knee to hit Shan-Yu from
  behind as he uses his hand to hit him in the head. Shang forces Shan-Yu onto his back and grabs
  his arm pulling it behind Shan-Yu's back. Mulan, Chien-Po, Yao and Ling enter the balcony from the
  stairs</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Chien-Po, get the Emperor.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chien-Po <stage>standing in front of the Emperor and bowing</stage></speaker> Sorry,
  your Majesty. </sp>

 <stage>Chien-Po lifts up the Emperor and runs over to Mulan who is by a rope attached to a column
  in the balcony. Chien-Po uses his sash as a pulley and rides down the rope to the ground. Shan Yu
  watches the Emperor leave</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> No! </sp>

 <sp>
  <stage>Shan-Yu uses his free arm to elbow Shang in the face. Shan-Yu gets up and head-butts Shang
   and throws him to the ground. Shang lies limp. Mulan watches Shang fall then she looks over the
   edge at Ling and Yao now on the ground. Chien-Po runs off the screen out of sight</stage>
 </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Yao <stage>motioning her to follow</stage></speaker> Come on!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan looks down at Shang with a worried look. Shan-Yu begins to approach Mulan and the
  rope. Mulan looks at the approaching Shan-Yu and then down to spy his sword. Thinking quickly,
  Mulan grabs Shan-Yu's sword and cuts the taught rope. Shan-Yu reaches the edge and grabs for the
  falling rope unsuccessfully as Mulan leaves the sword embedded in the column and runs to Shang's
  position. The crowd cheers</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> No! <stage>He looks down at the crowd and realizes he cannot find
   the Emperor among the throng of people</stage> Yrraaaaahhhh!</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu turns and looks back and sees Mulan looking concerned, holding up Shang. Shan-Yu
  pulls out his sword lodged in the column and heads toward them. As Shang sees Shan-Yu approaching,
  he puts his arm in front of Mulan to ask her to leave and takes out his knife. Mulan slides away.
  Shan-Yu comes up to Shang, knocks away his knife, slaps him in the face, and grabs Shang by the
  shirt collar</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>in Shang's face</stage></speaker> You, you took away my victory.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan's shoe hits Shan-Yu in the head and bounces back to her feet. Shan-Yu turns toward
  Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> No! I did! <stage>Mulan pulls her hair back to look like she did when
   she was a soldier</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu <stage>looking at Mulan</stage></speaker> The soldier from the mountains.</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu drops Shang and starts after Mulan as she puts on her shoe and runs down the stairs
  and through the doors to the balcony. She closes the door with the latch falling in place right
  behind her. She leans against the doors. Shan-Yu punches a hole in one door with his fist. Mulan
  runs away from the doors down the corridor. Mushu riding Shan-Yu's falcon like a horse catches up
  with Mulan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> So what's the plan?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Ummmm.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> You don't have a plan?!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Hey, I'm making this up as I...<stage>looks out a window and spies the
   firework tower</stage> go. Mushu--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> I'm way ahead of you sister. C'mon Cri-Kee. <stage>Mushu and Cri-Kee
   jump onto a kite and use the wings to soar over toward the fireworks tower</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to Shan-Yu. Shan-Yu breaks through the doors and catches up to Mulan swinging his sword
  wildly knocking down a support column with every swipe. Mulan runs and ducks his every blow. Mulan
  climbs up a column to get out of Shan-Yu's reach. Shan-Yu slices the base of the column causing it
  to fall and break through the outer wall. Mulan screams as the beam falls and comes to a stop.
  Mulan gets up on the beam and jumps up to catch onto the awning. She looks off to her right and
  spies Mushu arriving at the fireworks tower</stage>

 <sp>
  <stage>Zoom in on the fireworks tower. Mushu lands near Barry Cook and Tony Bancroft (the firework
   lighters) on the edge of the tower</stage>
 </sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Citizens, I need firepower.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Barry Cook</speaker> Who are you?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>Mushu (using the wings from the kite) and Cri-Kee with wings spread like
    batman</stage></speaker> You're worst nightmare.</sp>

 <stage>Barry Cook and Tony Bancroft jump off the tower and plunge toward the ground</stage>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan. She pulls herself onto the roof and climbs up to the crest</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Man in Crowd #1</speaker> On the roof.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Man in Crowd #2</speaker> Look!</sp>

 <stage>Mulan lines up where she is standing with the fireworks tower across the way. Shan-Yu breaks
  through the roof behind Mulan surprising her. Mulan backs away and searches for something on her
  person to help her against Shan-Yu. She finds a her fan, takes it out, and opens it</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shan-Yu</speaker> It looks like you're out of ideas.</sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu lunges with his sword. Mulan dodges to her right and lets the sword go right through
  the fan. She closes the fan back up on the sword and twists the fan with both hands so that
  Shan-Yu loses his grip. The sword flies toward Mulan and she catches it by the handle slipping off
  the fan with her sword movement</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Not quite. <stage>calling out</stage> Ready, Mushu?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>behind Shan-Yu tied to a large rocket firework</stage></speaker> I am
  ready, baby. <stage>He blows fire onto a stick and hands the stick to Cri-Kee who's standing on
   the firework</stage> Light me! <stage>Cri-Kee lights the fuse</stage></sp>

 <stage>Shan-Yu approaches Mulan. Using the sword as a lever, Mulan lunges at Shan-Yu kicking him in
  the face then sweep kicks him and he falls to the ground. Mulan picks the sword back up and stabs
  it into Shan-Yu's cape. The rocket on Mushu ignites and hurls him toward Shan-Yu. Mulan lies flat
  down on the left side of the roof. Shan-Yu sees the approaching rocket and tries to run, but the
  sword has him pinned to the spot. The rocket hits Shan-Yu square in the belly propelling him
  toward the firework tower. Mushu grabbed onto the sword as he went by letting the rocket do the
  work. Cri-Kee hangs on to Mushu's tail. Mulan jumps back up to the crest of the roof and runs away
  from the fireworks tower grabbing Mushu and Cri-Kee off the sword</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>while running</stage></speaker> Get off the roof, get off the roof, get
  off the roof.</sp>

 <stage>The rocket rides Shan-Yu into the fireworks tower causing masses of explosions and fireworks
  to fly everywhere. Mulan jumps near the edge of the roof. Propelled by the explosion, she grabs
  onto a lantern that is hanging on a taught rope and starts to slide down. She looks down and
  releases her grip so that she lands on the back of Shang causing the two of them to fall to the
  ground. Shan-Yu's sword follows and lands on the ground near by</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>landing and flying backwards on his butt a couple of times pointing at
    the fireworks</stage></speaker> Ah ha ha ha ha. <stage>Mushu's catches Cri-Kee with antenna on
   fire as Cri-Kee falls toward him</stage>
  <stage>to Cri-Kee</stage> You are a lucky bug. <stage>Mushu pinches out the fire on Cri-Kee's
   antenna</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>walking down the stairs in a tattered outfit and slightly
   burned</stage></speaker> That was a deliberate attempt on my life. Where is she? Now she's done
  it. What a mess. <stage>Shang and troops push Mulan behind them to protect her</stage>
  <stage>to Shang</stage> Stand aside, that creature's not worth protecting.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>in Chi Fu's face</stage></speaker> She's a hero.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> 'Tis a woman. She will never be worth anything.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>grabbing Chi Fu by the shirt collar</stage></speaker> Listen, you
  pompous--</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor <stage>walking down the steps</stage></speaker> That is enough!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Your Majesty, I can explain.</sp>

 <stage>The Emperor motions for Shang to stand aside. Shang and his men part giving the Emperor a
  clear path to Mulan. Mulan steps forward and bows before the Emperor. Chi Fu with a sinister look
  waits to write down the words of the Emperor</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> I've heard a great deal about you, Fa Mulan. You stole your father's
  armor, ran away from home, impersonated a soldier, deceived your commanding officer, dishonored
  the Chinese army, destroyed my palace, AND...you have saved us all. <stage>the Emperor bows to
   Mulan</stage></sp>

 <stage>Chi Fu looks at the Emperor actions astonishingly then immediately falls prostrate before
  Mulan. Shang, Yao, Ling, and Chien-Po follow suit. Mulan looks up then turns around hardly
  believing what she sees as the entire Chinese population within the palace grounds fall prostrate
  on the ground in a wave like pattern, bowing to her. Khan bows with Mushu and Cri-Kee on his
  back</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> My little baby's all grown up and savin' China. <stage>to
   Cri-Kee</stage> You have a tissue?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> Chi Fu,</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu</speaker> Your Excellency?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> See to it that this woman is made a member of my council.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>muttering to himself</stage></speaker> A member of your
   coun...<stage>realizing what the Emperor has said</stage> what? <stage>stutters</stage> But there
  are no council positions open, your Majesty.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor <stage>to Mulan</stage></speaker> Very well then, you can have his job
   <stage>pointing out Chi Fu</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Chi Fu <stage>wobbling to and fro</stage></speaker>
  What?...My...<stage>faints</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>smiles big then turns to the Emperor and bows</stage></speaker> With all
  due respect, your Excellency. I have been away from home long enough.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor <stage>taking off his pendant</stage></speaker> Then take this, so your family
  will know what you have done for me. And this <stage>handing her the sword of Shan-Yu</stage> so
  the world will know what you have done for China.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan takes the gifts and hugs the Emperor</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Yao</speaker> Is she allowed to do that? <stage>Shang, Ling, and Chien-Po
   shrug</stage></sp>

 <stage>Mulan walks away from the Emperor and is embraced by Yao and Ling. Chien-Po comes up and
  lifts all three of them off the ground in a big bear hug. Chien-Po lets them all back to the
  ground again. Mulan walks toward Shang and stops in front of him. As Shang begins to speak Mulan
  starts to smile anticipating something good</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker> Um...<stage>Mulan grins</stage> You... <stage>Mulan smiles</stage> You
  fight good.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan <stage>smile turning into disappointment</stage></speaker> Oh, thank you.
   <stage>Mulan walks toward Khan</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang</speaker>
  <stage>turning toward Mulan and grunts with disappointment in himself</stage>: Hmm.</sp>

 <stage>Mulan mounts Khan</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Khan, let's go home.</sp>

 <stage>Khan jumps down the steps and gallops on the flat parts of the stair case back down to
  ground level. The crowd cheers al the while. The Emperor approaches Shang and clears his
  throat</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor <stage>to Shang</stage></speaker> The flower that blooms in adversity is the
  most rare and beautiful of all.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>dumbfounded</stage></speaker> Sir?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Emperor</speaker> You don't meet a girl like that ev'ry dynasty. <stage>The emperor
   puts on his hat and walks back up the steps to his palace</stage></sp>

 <stage>Cut to Mulan's home, her father is sitting beneath the blossom tree. A blossom falls and
  lands on his leg. Mulan appears at the threshold and moves toward her father. Fa Zhou sees her
  approaching and starts to stand</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> Mulan. </sp>

 <stage>Mulan quickly moves in front of her father and kneels causing him to sit back down</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Father, I brought you the sword of Shan-Yu <stage>hands the sword to
   Fa Zhou</stage> and the crest of the Emperor <stage>hands the crest to Fa Zhou</stage>.
   <stage>with head bowed</stage> They're gifts to honor the Fa Family.</sp>

 <stage>Fa Zhou takes the gifts and throws them down to the ground beside him to the surprise of
  Mulan. He bends down and holds her arms outstretched</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Zhou</speaker> The greatest gift and honor, is having you for a daughter. <stage>Fa
   Zhou wipes away Mulan's tear then hugs Mulan</stage> I've missed you so.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> I've missed you too Baba.</sp>

 <stage>Fa li and Grandma Fa watch from the doorway</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Fa Li <stage>sighing</stage></speaker> Ahhhhh</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa</speaker> Great, she brings home a sword. If you ask me she should have
  brought home a ma--<stage>leaving her mouth open when she sees Shang</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>just arriving</stage></speaker> Excuse me, does Fa Mulan live here?</sp>

 <stage>Grandma Fa's mouth stays open as she and Fa Li point toward Mulan's position. Shang walks
  toward Mulan and Fa Zhou</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa</speaker> Woo, sign me up for the next war.</sp>

 <stage>Shang approaches seeing Fa Zhou</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>bows before Fa Zhou and speaks confidently</stage></speaker> Honorable Fa
  Zhou I--Mulan <stage>Mulan steps up. Shang sees her and speaks insecurely</stage> Uh...Uh...You
  forgot your helmet. Ah but well, actually it's your helmet, isn't it?...<stage>handing the helmet
   toward Fa Zhou</stage> I mean...</sp>

 <stage>Fa Zhou motions with his head for Mulan to take over. Mulan holds the helmet Shang
  offers</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Would you like to stay for dinner?</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Grandma Fa <stage>speaking from stage right</stage></speaker> Would you like to stay
  forever? <stage>Mulan shakes her head with a smile at Grandma Fa's statement</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Shang <stage>reassuredly to Mulan</stage></speaker> Dinner would be great.</sp>

 <stage>Cut to First Ancestor grinning happily looking at the scene through the temple window. He
  watches Mulan hand the helmet back to Fa Zhou. Mushu climbs up to the window sill by First
  Ancestor's his head</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>tugging on First Ancestor's ear</stage></speaker> C'mon, who did a good
  job? C'mon, tell me who did a good job.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>hesitantly</stage></speaker> Oh, all right. You can be a
  guardian again.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Yeeeeeahhhhhhh. <stage>Mushu runs to his post and Cri-Kee bangs the
   gong awakening all the ancestors</stage></sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu</speaker> Take it Cri-Kee.</sp>

 <stage>Song: True to Your Heart -- No characters sing in the song</stage>

 <stage>Ancestor 1 does a dance from Pulp Fiction while Ancestor 3 does the Hand Jive</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Ancestor 3 <stage>spoken to Ancestor 1</stage></speaker> She get's it from my side of
  the family.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Mushu <stage>spoken while swinging on a chain</stage></speaker> Call out for egg
  rolls!</sp>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>disgusted</stage></speaker> Guardians.</sp>

 <stage>Mushu lands on the steps outside the temple. Mulan walks up to him and rests besides him on
  the steps</stage>

 <sp><speaker>Mulan</speaker> Thanks, Mushu <stage>kisses Mushu on the forehead</stage>.</sp>

 <sp><speaker>Little Brother</speaker> Bark, bark, bark, bark, bark, bark, bark </sp>

 <stage>Little brother runs up the steps and into the temple with the bag of grain tied to him. The
  chickens follow him in</stage>

 <sp><speaker>First Ancestor <stage>annoyed</stage></speaker> Mushu!</sp>

 <stage>Roll Credits</stage>

 <stage>The End</stage>
</xml>
