<lyrics>
<section type="verse" n="1">
<l>You are somebody that I don't know</l>
<l>But you're takin' shots at me like it's Patrón</l>
<l>And I'm just like, damn, it's 7 AM</l>
<l>Say it in the street, that's a knock-out</l>
<l>But you say it in a Tweet, that's a cop-out</l>
<l>And I'm just like, "Hey, are you okay?"</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>And I ain't tryna mess with your self-expression</l>
<l>But I've learned a lesson that stressin' and obsessin' 'bout somebody else is no fun</l>
<l>And snakes and stones never broke my bones</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>So oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh</l>
<l>You need to calm down, you're being too loud</l>
<l>And I'm just like oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh (Oh)</l>
<l>You need to just stop, like can you just not step on my gown?</l>
<l>You need to calm down</l>
</section>
<section type="verse" n="2">
<l>You are somebody that we don't know</l>
<l>But you're comin' at my friends like a missile</l>
<l>Why are you mad when you could be GLAAD? (You could be GLAAD)</l>
<l>Sunshine on the street at the parade</l>
<l>But you would rather be in the dark ages</l>
<l>Makin' that sign must've taken all night</l>
</section>
<section type="pre-chorus">
<l>You just need to take several seats and then try to restore the peace</l>
<l>And control your urges to scream about all the people you hate</l>
<l>'Cause shade never made anybody less gay</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>So oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh</l>
<l>You need to calm down, you're being too loud</l>
<l>And I'm just like oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh (Oh)</l>
<l>You need to just stop, like can you just not step on his gown?</l>
<l>You need to calm down</l>
</section>
<section type="bridge">
<l>And we see you over there on the internet</l>
<l>Comparing all the girls who are killing it</l>
<l>But we figured you out</l>
<l>We all know now we all got crowns</l>
<l>You need to calm down</l>
</section>
<section type="chorus">
<l>Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh</l>
<l>You need to calm down (You need to calm down)</l>
<l>You're being too loud (You're being too loud)</l>
<l>And I'm just like oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh (Oh)</l>
<l>You need to just stop (Can you stop?)</l>
<l>Like can you just not step on our gowns?</l>
<l>You need to calm down</l>
</section>
</lyrics>
