<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>In the Name of the Grandfather</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>14</epNum></ep>
<date>03/25/09</date> <runtime>22:15</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>SCHOOL BELL RINGING</stage>

<stage><person>BARNEY</person> BURPS</stage>

<stage>HORN BELLOWING</stage>

<stage>PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>PANTS</stage>

<stage>GROWLS</stage>

<stage>BARKING</stage>

<stage>TV SHATTERS</stage>

A home and garden show?

<stage>ALL GROAN IN DISAPPOINTMENT</stage>

Mom, you said we were going to a videogame expo.

5000.

Please, can I get it, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>? Please, please?

I can have all my birthday parties in it.

I'll be less stressed. And I'm really freaking stressed!

If I'm more relaxed, I'll be a better mom. Can we? Can we?

Wait a minute. Who am I pleading with?

Beats me.

I don't know.

Please, please, please.

<stage>ALL MOANING HAPPILY</stage>

Now I know why lobsters let out that joyful squeal when they're dropped in the pot.

Uh-oh.

We're starting to attract swingers.

All right!

Yeah.

Yes!

Look at that.

<stage>ALL EXCLAIM IN DISGUST</stage>

I'm on it.

Go back to your day spas!

<stage><person>DISCO STU</person> HUMMING</stage>

<stage><person>DISCO STU</person> EXCLAIMS</stage>

Maybe we should get out now.

Interesting proposal.

Now with an opposing point of view, bubbles!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: Oh, yeah!

<stage>ALL MOANING HAPPILY</stage>

<stage>ALL MOANING HAPPILY</stage>

Hey, cool your jets! We're trying to get to sleep!

Hey, <person>Flanders</person>, why don't you join us?

Afraid you'll get your mustache wet?

Well, yes.

Come on, man! Baptize your buns!

Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.

<stage>ALL MOANING HAPPILY</stage>

<stage>MURMURING CONTENTEDLY</stage>

<stage><person>NED</person> CONTINUES MURMURING CONTENTEDLY</stage>

I feel like we're forgetting something.

Mmm. There was a note on the fridge marked "urgent." Funny word, urgent.

Urgent. Urgent.

One of us should go look at it.

Mmm. Probably a reminder to relax more.

Oh, yeah.

That's it.

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

I'm sorry, <fam>Abe</fam>. We just can't wait for your family any longer.

But they're coming. My son even put a note on his refrigerator.

Please wait.

I'm afraid it's too late.

On your mark, get set...

No!

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

<stage>CROWD CHEERING</stage>

They're blanks, <fam>Abe</fam>.

<stage>ALL MOANING HAPPILY</stage>

Hey, what happened to the bubbles?

You good-for-nothing jellyfish!

While you were lying here soaking like a bunch of dirty dishes, I was lonelier than Estes Kefauver at a meeting of m*rder lncorporated!

That actually makes sense! Look it up!

Sorry we missed your special day, <fam>Grampa</fam>.

We'll definitely go next year.

The thing is, I ain't got much life left to live, and a wasted day like today is one I know I'll never get back.

Oh, Dad, I never knew you had dreams or emotions.

We'll make it up to you.

We'll do something you've always wanted to do but never got the chance.

Well, there are a few things I was hoping to do before I become dust in a jar.

Whoa, whoa, whoa. Who said anything about a jar?

Anyway, I made a list.

Okay.

<stage><person>HOMER</person> READING</stage>

"Pitch in the n*gro Leagues."

I can think of at least two problems with that.

Can't read that one. My thumb's over it.

<stage><person>HOMER</person> READING</stage>

We'll do that one!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>: This place is in lreland?

<fam>Abe</fam>: That's right.

Now let's make our reservations!

Lousy old man, making me look up at an airplane.

<stage>IRISH FOLK MUSIC PLAYING</stage>

Pilot on P.A.: Welcome to lreland, also known as <location>the Emerald Isle</location>, Potatoville, <location>East</location> <location>Boston</location>, Freckle Bog, the Land of Poetry and the Land of Bad Poetry.

And on your left, you'll see Western lreland.

On your right, you'll see Kathy lreland.

Hi, everyone.

I'm finally back.

The days I spent at O'Flanagan's Pub were the happiest ones of my life.

All: <stage>SINGING</stage> We drink all day We're full of guilt.

We know we're not Scots 'cause we don't wear a kilt.

We toss our darts with a beer in our hand.

We boil our food till it tastes really bland.

This is the life in lreland.

Ireland!

<stage>LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING</stage>

<stage>BLEATING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> Oh, this is the life in lreland

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: Dunkilderry is so quaint.

It looks like the puzzle at the pediatrician's office.

Get ready to step back to a simpler age, filled with tweed caps, cheerful sheep and unending troubles.

What the...

Upscale boutiques?

Yup-rechauns!

<stage>SPEAKING GIBBERISH</stage>

Plasma screen TV.

<stage>SPEAKING GIBBERISH</stage>

Summer in Tuscany.

Well, Ireland is at the forefront of <location>Europe</location>'s tech boom.

In your face, Belgium!

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, if you hate Belgium so much, maybe I should take your Tintins away!

No! I'll be good.

But my favorite pub is still there.

This isn't the way I remember it! Where's the customers?

Where's the singing? Where's 20-year-old me?

Run! Run, you big sack of glue!

Tom O'Flanagan?

Quiet!

They're in the home stretch now! Come on. Come on. Move your fetlocks!

Damn it! Will you ever win this race?

This broadcast is from 1979.

Yes.

I'm just an old man yelling at me tapes.

I've got lots of time for that now no one comes into me bar anymore.

<stage>MISPRONOUNCING</stage> It's been years since I've sold so much as a pint.

Don't you mean "pint"?

It's been so long I've forgotten how to say it!

It's a joke to even call this place a pube.
What happened, Tom?

Everyone got jobs, that's what happened.

Sir, I brought my father thousands of miles just to drink at your bar.

Do you mean it? Look, don't toy with an old man's heart now.

Give me a beer and a sh*t of whiskey.

I'll have one drink, one cocktail and one booze, please.

Oh!

While your father and your grandfather have a drink, we're going to see sights.

Hey, I just spent 10 hours on a plane. I'm staying here.

They've got German <person>Krusty</person> on TV.

<stage>GREETING IN GERMAN</stage>

<stage>SPEAKING GERMAN</stage>

<stage>SPEAKING GERMAN</stage>

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

Such a beautiful language.

That's not how a family vacation works.

We do things together while your father has fun without us.

All right, Tom, pour me a drink.

We have this delicious Australian Shiraz.

<stage>SPUTTERS</stage>

An lrish drink.

Fine.

Here's some Bushmills whiskey served in a potato, floating in a Guinness stout!

<stage>SPUTTERS ANGRILY</stage>

I said an lrish drink!

That's better.

"The Giant's Causeway is the result of a volcanic eruption."

Well, kids, isn't that an informational fact? Kids?

Come back here!

<stage>Q*BERTTHEME MUSIC PLAYING</stage>

<stage>VOICE SPEAKING GIBBERISH</stage>[/i]

Guinness has been brewed since 1759. Who'd like to know our secret recipe?

<stage>ALL EXCLAIMING EX CITEDLY</stage>

I'm not going to tell you.

<stage>ALL EXCLAIMING</stage>

Sure if I did, it wouldn't be a secret.

Man: Oh, yeah.

That concludes our tour.

Woman: She is great.

<stage><person>MARGE</person> HUMMING</stage>

<stage>GROANS</stage>

Well, you may know the ingredients, but you don't know the ratio!

Fifty-fifty?

<stage>SPUTTERS ANGRILY</stage>

<stage>FOG HORN BLOWS</stage>

<stage>MAN COUGHING</stage>

50 years old! Better toss it!

Hey, boy-o! How about a tall cool one?

How about you, Green Sleeves? Irishmen love to get drunk!

I'm in AA.

Who are you? Stuttering Fonzie?

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>

What about you, Bicycle Pants?

I'm late for a teleconference with Hong Kong, you fat gob!

Why, you...

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

Uh-oh.

Our first sale!

Our first refund.

Find any customers?

Yeah! Look at them crowding the bar!

There's Sully and Mack, Jimmy D. And Jimmy B. What can I get you, boys?

The usual? We are so screwed!

It must be Bloomsday.

<stage>BOTH EXCLAIM</stage>

2000.

Oh, son, you know how I love a good analogy.

<stage>CHUCKLING</stage> It was apt.

Let me say, I've always admired the lrish, Knute Rockne, Larry Bird, and especially Mr. Potato Head.

Go on.

But I ask you, who does smoking actually hurt except the smokers, those around them and the unborn children of the pregnant women we let in free on Expectant-Mothers-Drink-Free Night?

<stage>GROANS</stage>

So I hope you'll forgive two well-meaning Americans for trying to take lreland back to the good old days of Angela 's Ashes.

Thank you.

<stage><fam>ABE</fam> CHUCKLES</stage>

That was absolutely terrible.

But fortunately for you, the punishment for your offense is deportation and a small fine.

Thank you, Your Honor.

And may I say, I'm glad I could see lreland again, even if it isn't what I remembered.

It got a lot nicer since we sent all our incompetent half-wits to <location>America</location> where you, for some reason, made them police officers.

Top of the morning to you.

Chief Clancy <person>Wiggum</person> here to pick up the Simpsons and take them back to the...

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

Jeez, that smarts! Better put a little ouchie spray on it.

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

Oh, boy! I better call for some backup.

This is Unit One...

<stage>GROANING</stage>

Oh, God.
</txt></xml>