<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Father Knows Worst</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>18</epNum></ep>
<date>04/30/09</date> <runtime>08:24</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

It's dark.

<stage>SCHOOL BELL RINGING</stage>

<stage>BURPS</stage>

<stage>HORN BELLOWING</stage>

<stage>PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>sh*t FIRES</stage>

Hot dogs! Not so hot dogs!

Cold and droopy!

Fried dough! <location>America</location>'s worst legal food! Never leaves your body!

Wow. The Truth in Boardwalking Law has really done a number on this place.

sh**t an oversized basketball into an undersized hoop!

It's impossible! The prizes have been here for 50 years!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>: Ooh. Oh.

<stage><person>HOMER</person> WHIMPERS</stage>

Maybe we should just check out the street performers.

<stage>VIOLIN PLAYING</stage>

Big deal! I could juggle six pins if they let me use a unicycle.

Well, if you think it's too easy, why don't you throw me something else?

Are you insane?

You can't throw a little boy into my cascade.

Stop tossing kids!

<stage><person>BART</person> LAUGHING</stage>

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

<stage>ALL LAUGHING</stage>

Oh, man. I love Saturdays.

Man, I love Saturdays.

Finally I can have fun with something I bought for myself, a new water heater.

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

Almost there...

Five more water heaters and we get a free water heater.

<stage>HUMMING</stage>

Huh?

A mysterious door?

It's like a sauna in here.

It is a sauna in here!

3.85.

Yeah.

Can I work it off? Don't worry. I won't embarrass you!

I'll start you on Jell-O.

<stage>SINGING</stage> I'm big and yellow and I'm serving Jell-O

If you're a fellow and you want some Jell-O

You better bellow.

Hey, big guy! Give me some Jell-O

No Jell-O for you, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>. It'll keep you up at night, like last week when you crawled into bed with me and Mommy.

<stage>ALL LAUGHING</stage>

Sure is hot back here.

And there we go.

Don't worry. I won't embarrass you.

I used to date your daughter.

Buddy, I'm here to eat, not make interesting conversation.

Dad, do you have to hang out at my school?

It's bad enough I have to be here three days a week.

Well! I know when I'm not wanted!

Am I wanted?

No.

Hi. <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson. Mind if I sit near your son? Mine sucks.

Well, we certainly are proud of Noah. He's a straight-A student.

Noah! State capitals, alphabetical order, on my clap.

<location>Albany</location>, Annapolis, <location>Atlanta</location>, Augusta, Austin, Baton Rouge, Bismarck, Boise, <location>Boston</location>, Capital City, Carson City.

Wow. He's terrified of you.

That's why I'm here. To make sure he gets good grades.

Whoa, whoa, whoa!

You come to school to help him get good grades?

Isn't that why we pay public school teachers those enormous salaries?

Well, call me over-involved, but someday, your son will be my son's chauffeur.

1000 savings bond for their college education.

$1000? That's what my house is worth.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam> Simpson, what will you be making?

I don't know.

Time to take control of my son's life. Let's see. What can he build?

Too obvious.

Gotta be something from <location>earth</location>.

You're no help!

Perfect.

"<location>The Washington Monument</location>?"

<location>Washington</location> Monument.

I like <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s idea.

You're not in this class.

Willie swept me in here.

My mistake.

I did it. I helped my son. Helicopter <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, away!

Black Hawk down! Black Hawk down!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, I found this book in the "What's wrong with my daughter" section of the bookstore.

It tells you how you can get popular.

Dad, if I join a clique, I'll be the kind of person I hate.

262, a '67 SS GTO, an Alfred E. Neuman, with interchangeable arms.

We'd like some balsa wood, please.

Enough to build a <location>Washington</location> Monument.

What scale are you using?

What cologne are you wearing? None of your business!

Now we'd like our <location>Washington</location> Monument to be one-five hundredth the size of the real one.

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>

<location>Washington</location> Monument? Aren't you gonna even try?

What do you mean? And who are you?

I'm your son's principal.

And <location>the Washington Monument</location> is the most uninspired model choice there is.

It's like saying, "I don't care. My kid's a loser."

But... You...

What's the hardest model there is?

That would be, Westminster Abbey.

Attention, parents, children and childless weirdoes, my son and I are going to build Westminster Abbey!

<stage>ALL GASPING</stage>

You've gotta be crazy!

Prepare to be frustrated.

You won't get past the north transept!

Hey, how hard can it be? All we have to do is follow the directions.

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, the boy and I will be making Westminster Abbey.

Blabby's gonna build an abbey. Groovy.

But first, as part of Operation Popularity, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> and I are hosting a "Decorate Your Own Cell Phone" <location>party</location> in the backyard.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

Britney and Caitlin are here! Where's my spray-on tan?

<stage><person>HOMER</person> READING</stage>

Why do I always read the labels after?

Ladies, we've got it all. Rhinestones, stickers, tassels, everything to make those $100 phones look like $5 toys!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, this <location>party</location> is twisted!

You're fierce!

<stage>LAUGHS NERVOUSLY</stage>

I've never been called fierce before.

Strident. Hectoring has been tossed around.

Let me take a picture of you for my cell phone.

I'll put you on my desktop.

I'm gonna make you my friend on Facebook.

Please confirm.

Confirmed!

<stage>YELLS</stage>

<stage>ALL LAUGHING</stage>

I am such a great parent to both my kids.

Hello, little girl. Who do you belong to?

Hey, boy. Why don't I do that for you?

Isn't this supposed to be my project?

All the other parents are doing it for their kids.

Now stand back and I'll take it from here.

A little further back.

Do you want me to watch and learn?

No. That kind of creeps me out.

Must finish Poets' Corner or <fam><person>Bart</person></fam> will work for Noah with his hot mom.

<stage>SNORING</stage>

<stage>BELL TOLLING</stage>

That's not Henry VII! That's Henry VI! Stupid, stupid, stupid!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, don't give up till you finish my dear abbey!

Geoffrey Chaucer? What are you doing here?

Well, I'm buried here, and I want to tell you you're right to do all <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>'s work for him.

It's the best thing for the boy.

That's terrible advice.

Anne of Cleves?

What you do for your son, he'll never learn to do for himself.

And where is this delightful boy?

Oscar Wilde?

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, there are only two tragedies in life.

One is not getting what one wants, and the other is getting it.

But that makes no sense!

Experience is simply the name we give to our mistakes.

Shut up!

These days, man knows the price of everything and the value of nothing.

Whatever happened to "boo"?

<stage>BELL TOLLING</stage>

<stage>MOANING</stage>

Now we could smash the real Westminster Abbey so it looks like this.

<stage>GROANS</stage> There are no flights to London till 5:00.

Welcome to <location>Springfield Elementary</location>'s Next Top Model Building Contest.

Kenny, he said your show.

I watched it once!

Now, judges, start your nodding.

Mmm-hmm.

Mmm.

Mmm. Mmm-hmm.

Flawless. Stunning. Awe-inspiring.

Meticulous.

Mmm?

Hmm.

<stage>WHIMPERS</stage>

<person>Skinner</person>!

These models are clearly the work of meddling parents.

8 this"?

I'm sorry, Dad. These girls are nice on the surface.

But it's hard work staying this shallow. I hope you understand.

Yeah. It's clear to me now.

The best thing I can do as a parent is simply check out.

No, there's a middle ground.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, a light bulb is either on or it's off.

Not if you use a dimmer switch.

That's what the dimmer switch companies want you to think.

What's wrong, <fam>Homie</fam>?

I tried to fix the kids' lives.

But instead, I led them to rich and rewarding personal decisions of their own.

Well, I know a place in this house where you can really relax.

The mattress the dog sleeps on in the cellar?

No. I gave that to the homeless shelter.

That was stuffed with cash!

Well, I'll make you forget all about it.

<stage>BOTH SIGHING</stage>

Feeling better, Super Dad?

Oh, yeah.

<stage>BOTH MOANING</stage>

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

I feel like I've died and gone to hell.

The Simpsons

<stage>ALL VOCALIZING</stage>
</txt></xml>