<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Gone <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> Gone</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>13</epNum></ep>
<date>03/19/09</date> <runtime>01:07</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>ALL GRUNT</stage>

2027.

We have totality, people.

<person>BART</person>, <person>HOMER</person> AND <person>LISA</person>: Wow!

We'll be talking about this together for years.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>: For years!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: For years!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>: I finally feel like part of a family.

Oh! I can't miss out. Just one little peek.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

It's beautiful.

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

Now, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, your eyes must stay completely covered for two full weeks.

Don't worry, honey. I'll be your seeing-eye <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

We're in some kind of doctor room. Bunch of stuff on the walls.

It's kind of hard to describe. I'm gonna take my break now.

Now, Simpsons, I must warn you, any stress could increase the blood pressure in <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>'s eyeballs, leading to what we call.

Tex Avery Syndrome.

<stage>MUSIC PLA YING ON TV</stage>

Wolves are taking all our women.

<stage><person>BART</person> HUMMING</stage>

<stage>SNIFFS</stage>

You guys have treated me like a princess.

Every day's been like the first 10 minutes of Mother's Day.

You just rest those rods and coddle those cones.

Everything's taken care of.

Aw...

Dad, come in the kitchen, quick!

Is there any other way to enter a kitchen?

<stage>SQUEAKING</stage>

Aw... Rats in the kitchen, just like that delightful movie I taped in the theater.

<stage><person>HOMER</person> CHUCKLES</stage>

Ooh!

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>

He's controlling me with my hair, using me to cook a delicious sole meuniére with a celery root purée and carrots Vichy.

Mmm. This is good.

Good but not great. I'll go get some rat poison.

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

<stage>TOY SQUEAKING</stage>

There you go. This'll k*ll those dirty rats and the clean ones, too.

<stage>EXCLAIMING EX CITEDLY</stage>

That's not candy, sweetheart.

What is it with kids and candy-colored poison, huh?

<stage>CLERK CHUCKLES</stage>

<stage><fam><person>MAGGIE</person></fam> FUSSING</stage>

<stage><location>SANTA'S LITTLE HELPER</location> GROWLING</stage>

No, you stupid dog! That's <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>'s bunny!

Not in front of the poison man!

Whoever is biting me, stop it!

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage><person>HOMER</person> GRUNTING IN FRUSTRATION</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

23.

<stage>LAUGHING WICKEDLY</stage>

Hmm.

<stage>READING IN LATIN</stage>

That's Latin. '"Deum '"is God. And of course '"quaerite'"means seek.

"Seek God with heart and soul."

Heart and Soul!

<stage>PLAYING HEARTAND SOUL</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> I fell in love with you Heart and soul
<stage>TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYS</stage>

<stage>TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWS</stage>

<fam>Homie</fam>, I haven't held <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> all day. Can you hand her to me?

No problem, sweetie.

Ooh! Mommy's little baby is getting big and chubby.

Who's a chubby baby?

But that doesn't mean that you can't have a little dinner.

Hmm. You're not usually this greedy.

<stage>IN LOW VOICE</stage> Cool it. She's getting suspicious.

<stage>IN DIFFERENT VOICE</stage> You cool it! I'm hungry!

Cryptic message. Maybe this will <location>lead</location> me to the gem.

Hmm. What if I read every other word?

<stage>READING</stage>

That's not very nice. I will try again but not because the wall told me to.

<stage>READING</stage>

<stage>GASPS</stage>

Big ring.

Big ring.

So many rings.

But which one is the key to finding the gem?

Well, did you get it?

No. I'm not a smart nerd. I'm just a weak nerd.

The biggest ring in <location>Springfield</location> comes from the bell in the <location>Springfield</location> bell tower!

Oh.

Oh!

Good night, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

I'll be right in, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>!

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

Good night, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

Good night.

<stage>PLAYING POORLY</stage>

Ooh! Jazz.

Keep going and I'll scat.

<stage>SCATTING</stage>

<stage><person>LISA</person> EXCLAIMS</stage>

Principal <person>Skinner</person>? <person>Comic Book Guy</person>?

What are you doing here?

Following you. We seek the gem of St. Teresa.

Oh. Well, I seek it so I can find my sister. How do you know about the gem?

We are an ancient order of mystery buffs who hide in shadow and call ourselves The Brethren of the Quest.

Because we do our sleuthing in Mother's Nissan Quest minivan.

Tell me all you know about the gem.

Never!

Does your mother know you're using her minivan?

You see, legend has it that on her deathbed, St. Teresa of Avila had a vision of a jewel that would usher in an era of peace and harmony.

She dispatched a team of nuns to the New World to seek this fabulous gem.

They landed at what is now Philadelphia, <stage>PHILLIE PHANATIC HONKING NOSE</stage>

And used the timbers of their ship to construct a convent.

The order flourished, never forgetting its sacred mission.

But word about the gem got out, and a group of high-ranking Freemasons led by Benjamin Franklin, George <location>Washington</location>, and King George III staged a phony w*r of independence to cover their search for the gem.

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

<stage>BOTH LAUGHING</stage>

<stage>BOTH GROWLING ANGRILY</stage>

<stage>BOTH LAUGHING</stage>

Fleeing the v*olence, the nuns of St. Teresa 's left the colonies and settled here in <location>Springfield</location>.

Legend and Wikipedia have it that the gem will be revealed during the first full moon after a solar eclipse.

That's tonight!

<stage>EXCLAIMS MOCKINGLY</stage>

One question remains.

Why did you come here?

Because I cleverly deduced the answer to <location>Springfield</location>'s biggest ring.

<stage>EXCLAIMS IN FRENCH</stage>

Well, it gives me no pleasure to say your deduction was faulty!

This is a fake, papier-mâché bell.

The real bell was melted down in World w*r II to make Civil w*r chess sets, four of which I own.

Oh, my God!

I know what the biggest ring in <location>Springfield</location> is!

It's been right in front of us the whole time.

Ah. Ah, yes. I see it.

I see it, too. Let's head that way.

We'll walk or drive to the obvious solution.

Oh, the word "ring"!

<stage><person>LISA</person> AND JEFF SNICKER</stage>

<stage>DOGS PANTING</stage>

Well, well, if it isn't the Tardy Boys and Nancy Clueless.

Mr. <person>Burns</person>? What are you doing here?

I've known about the gem for years.

You see, my dear girl, I joined the Freemasons before it was trendy.

That's my eyeball on the dollar bill. That's also my pyramid.

Hence, I trailed you on your quest, accompanied by my faithful albino.

I keep telling you, I'm not an albino! I just use a lot of sun block.

Then why do I give you all the albino holidays off? Hmm? Hmm?

Look! There's writing on the "R."

Everything is writing to you young people.

From this angle they're words.

<stage><person>LISA</person> READING</stage>

Great crimes k*ll holy sage?

The puzzle is solved. We must warn the holy sage at once!

No! That's not it.

A secret message this awkwardly worded is always an anagram.

Fine. Then you unscramble those letters to spell out the location of the gem while you two dig your own graves.

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

Superman, I have believed in you for years.

If you can hear me now, please come help me dig this giant grave.

So the anagram spells...

<stage><person>LISA</person> READING</stage>

So the gem is inside you?

Sir, stop. She is the gem.

<stage>GASPS</stage> Of course. St. Teresa wouldn't be interested in a mere bauble.

Her greatest treasure would be a pure young girl.

You are pure, aren't you?

Does kissing <person>Milhouse</person> count?

No.

No.

No.

It all adds up. I am the gem that will bring world peace.

How brilliant of God to remove my skepticism by making me his chosen one!

According to legend, the gem must be brought to the convent by sunrise.

We could make it if we took Mr. <person>Burns</person>' helicopter.

Hmm. I don't really want you people inside. But you could dangle from the skids.

Deal.

It feels good to help someone, doesn't it, sir?

No. It feels weird.

<stage>JEFF GRUNTS</stage>

<stage>ALL SINGING O FORTUNA</stage>

Look who's here!

<stage>ALL CONTINUE SINGING</stage>

Fine, fine. Finish your song. I can be patient.

After all, I am the Gem Child.

Hush, you foolish girl!

The gem is over there.

<fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>? No, no, no. The solution was, "Regally, the rock gem is <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>."

Oh, please. How many sentences start with the word "regally"?

This one.

Oh, give me that!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: "It's really <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>, Sherlock."

You know, I have to point out that this only makes sense, if I get the wrong answer first.

I said hush!

Now begins a new era of peace and prosperity for <location>Springfield</location>.

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

Come on, man! That's the fifth call you've missed today!

That's it! You're out of...

Just set it to massage.

<stage>EXCLAIMS IN PLEASURE</stage>

Something tells me the Gem of St. Teresa has been returned to its throne.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

<fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>, it's true! You are the Gem Child!

Four centuries of patient sacrifice has finally paid off.

All is peace and harmony.

Give me my baby back!

Mom, how did you know <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> was here?

A mother knows!

<stage><person>MARGE</person> MURMURS WORRIEDLY</stage>

<fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>, you're coming home with me.

Mom, wait! <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> is the Gem Child! She's brought peace to our town and reports of less road rage in <location>Shelbyville</location>.

She has to stay here.

Well, it would be nice if the first thing I saw was a world at peace.

<stage>GURGLES</stage>

You're even more beautiful than I remembered.

I'm sorry.

But I know God would never ask a mother to sacrifice her child for the good of the world again.

<stage><person>MARGE</person> MURMURS WORRIEDLY</stage>

Maybe I'm just being selfish. I don't know.

No, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>. You're the most giving person I know.

Besides, I gave them another Gem Child to sit on their precious throne.

Step aside, ladies. I'm bringing the peace.

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

<stage>ALL SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>CHUCKLES</stage> I am so staying up past my bedtime.
</txt></xml>