<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle><fam><person>Homer</person></fam> and <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Exchange Cross Words</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>06</epNum></ep>
<date>11/20/08</date> <runtime>05:22</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

Lemonade! Sweet sunshine in your mouth!

Buy a cup or I punch my sister!

It's true! He's not bluffing!

Ow.

Maybe we should put a dollar in the jar, prime the pump.

What are we? A piano bar?

<stage>PEOPLE CLAMORING</stage>

I'll take 15 lemonades.

Make that 16.

Huh?

Lousy dog. If you had your way, I'd walk you every day.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

Lemonade!

<stage><person>HOMER</person> PANTING</stage>

Girl: Stop pushing.

Six cups, please. And put it on my tab.

Keep moving, deadbeat. Cash only.

Fine. Lemonade's for babies, anyways. I'm going to <person>Moe</person>'s for beer!

Have fun drinking your lemonade, babies!

<stage>CAR ENGINE SPUTTERING</stage>

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>? Can Daddy borrow your bike?

I guess.

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

<stage>MOANING LOUDLY</stage>

<stage>SIGHS IN RELIEF</stage>

Hey, <person>Moe</person>. Give me a...

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, shush.

We're watching Krabappel try to break up with <person>Skinner</person>.

Seymour, I have something difficult I want to say to you.

I understand.

It can be very difficult for a woman to propose marriage.

But I am willing to go halfsies on a ring.

Seymour... Excuse me.

Any of you lugs want to break up with my boyfriend for me?

I'll buy you a beer.

Seymour, Edna asked me to talk to you.

Splendid. Shall we discuss music or the weather?

No. This is about you. Edna wants to break up.

She wants to break up?

Yeah.

With me?

Yeah.

Look at it this way. You're a free man, unlike me.

You have all your hair, unlike me.

No kids tying you down or a crippling mortgage that you refinanced at 26% because a dancing lnternet cowboy told you to?

<stage>CRYING</stage> Oh, God, I hate my life.

<stage>SOBBING</stage>

Gee, compared to you, my life is one big half day.

Exactly. You're good-Iooking. You have a decent job.

What lonely widow wouldn't consider you an option?

Thanks, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

I don't think the school pep squad could've cheered me up more, and they were state runners-up in 1997.

<stage>WHISTLING</stage>

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, that was amazing.

He actually felt better coming out of the breakup than he did going in.

Say, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, you're real good at this.

Think you could dump my girlfriend Doreen for me?

Doreen, she's cheated on you with everyone.

Well, except for me.

And I've showered her with gifts, fancy soaps and massage oils and what have you.

Here she comes. Work your magic, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

Is <person>Lenny</person> here?

I'm afraid <person>Lenny</person>'s d*ad.

What? I just talked to him.

And you will again because he isn't really d*ad.

Now this next piece of news won't seem so bad.

Lemonade! We want lemonade!

Lemonade! We want lemonade!

Don't worry, folks. Our master chef is stirring up a fresh batch.

Stop that transaction!

I'm a part-time field agent with the <location>Springfield</location> Department of Commerce!

Great gig.

It is a great gig.

May I see your vendor's license?

I think it's... We don't have one.

35 cents? Where did that come from? Can't be mine. Must be yours!

I don't care if it's 45 cents, I don't want it.

Submit this form to the license bureau. Until then, this stand is closed!

Boys!

Geez, I'm thirsty. You got any lemonade?

Not anymore!

<stage><person>LISA</person> MUMBLING ANGRILY</stage>

<stage>PEOPLE GRUMBLING</stage>

Come on, come on! I was halfway through an operation when my license expired.

I'll get to you just as soon as I finish this crossword puzzle.

Come on.

Let's go, buddy!

I left bananas in my car!

Let's see, 10 across, Franklin Roosevelt's middle name.

Excitement! Wait, that don't fit.

<stage>ALL GRUMBLING IN FRUSTRATION</stage>

Maybe you could use some help.

FDR's middle name, Delano. Oxidized surface, well, that's rusty.

Bartenders serve them "dirty."

Ham sandwiches!

No, martinis.

Oh, right.

One more word. Singer of Yentl. 13 letters!

I got it! Isaac Bashevis.

Now give me my license! Give everyone their license!

<stage>CHEERING</stage>

What is a four letter word for hero?

Hero!

Yes. But I meant <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>! <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>! <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>! <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>! <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>!

<stage>TELEPHONE RINGS</stage>

Y'ello?

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>? It's your old roommate, Grady.

The gay guy?

That's not all I am! Well, it's a lot of what I am.

Anyhoo, I heard how good you are at breaking up couples.

I need your help to break up with Julio.

Because I met someone new, someone much more cool and refreshing.

Uh-huh.

Got it.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, I'm going to a hardcore gay club and I won't be home till 3:00 in the morning!

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>: Have fun!

<stage>CHUCKLES</stage>

Ay, <catchphrase>caramba</catchphrase>!

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, I've fallen in love with crosswords.

It finally happened. You've gone completely fruit loops.

Froot Loops! That's the answer to 38 down, Toucan's delight.

No. I mean you're loco in the coco!

Cocoa! Ice rink drink.

You're losing it!

Losin'It! Risqué '80s teen flick.

Fine! Go nuts! See if I care!

Eye care. Optician's concern.

Thanks for your help, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>! <person>BART</person>. San Francisco people mover!

Speaking of San Francisco people mover...

<stage>DANCE MUSIC PLA YING</stage>

Grady is breaking up with me?

You'll always have a special place in his heart.

In his what?

Oh!

Oh, baby, you are the breakup king.

You have made the seven minutes that I'm gonna go without love so much more bearable.

Anyone else want me to get rid of that special someone?

Okay, everyone. Rotate one to your right.

Guess what, Mom? I'm a cruciverbalist!

Another religion?

You know, you're just gonna drop the whole thing when you go to college and get a Jewish boyfriend.

Probably. But a cruciverbalist is a fan of crossword puzzles, which I am.

Me, too! I've been doing them since 1958.

Back then, we called them alphabet hotels 'cause every letter gets its own little room.

I still do the <location>Springfield</location> Shopper puzzle every day.

Let's see there...

30 minutes or your breakup is free!

<stage>BLUES MUSIC PLAYING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> I'm leaving you, baby.

With my clothes in my hand.

100 for every customer I'd broken up, I'd have exactly this amount 'cause that's what I charge!

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

<fam>Homie</fam>, I'm not sure about this new business of yours.

You're making it too easy for couples to break up just because they hit a rough patch.

I know this is hard on you.

But in time, you'll come to see it's for the best.

That's one of your breakup lines!

What would've happened if there was someone who could break us up every time I had my doubts about you?

<stage><person>MARGE</person> SNORING</stage>

<stage>BOTH SNORING</stage>

Who are you?

We are the spirits of the relationships you k*ll.

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

We're the babies those couples would have had.

And we're the antiques those couples would have bought together.

Get him, chairs and babies!

<stage>SHOUTING</stage>

<fam>Homie</fam>?

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, I'm getting out of the breakup business, and I don't know if I'll ever sleep soundly again.

Well, maybe...

Wow. So this is what this is.

Cruciverbalists from far and wide have gathered here for a no-holds-barred test of k*ll.

Surely some holds are barred?

No, none.

Well, it sounds really exciting and you're a delightful young lady.

Now if you'll excuse me.

Hey, what's going on?

It's kind of a secret, so shut the door most of the way.

We found a way to make this tournament interesting.

We bet on the matches.

Really? Well, I did bring this envelope full of money.

And these days, betting in a bar is safer than any stock, bond or real estate investment.

Agreed. So who are you gonna bet on?

I want you to put it all on my little girl. And parlay with the Asian kid.

He has a name, you know.

What is it?

I don't know. He's not my kid.

I win!

She won! And like any prudent gambler, I know when to walk away... Never!

<stage>SINGING</stage> Dah pretty ladies around the world.

Got a weird thing to show you So tell all the boys and girls.

Tell your brother, your sister And your mama, too 'Cause they're about to go down And you'll know just what to do.

Wave your hands in the air Like you don't care.

441 little boxes.

It might be a fun way to k*ll a couple hours.

A couple hours?

I can do the Sunday puzzle in less than one hour.

"Couple of hours."

Last clue, loses on purpose.

Huh...

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

Diet!

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>

Will Shortz, you clever rascal.

And a new record time! Wait a second.

"Dumb dad sorry for his bet."

Wow. It's almost as if Dad planted that message.

No. It must just be a weird coincidence.

But what if it's not? It must be. Or mustn't it not?

Dad, I know this is crazy, but did you plant a message to me in the <location>New York</location> Times crossword puzzle?

Well, I had a little help from this guy.

<stage><person>LISA</person> GASPS</stage>

<location>New York</location> Times crossword editor, Will Shortz!

And master puzzle constructor, Merl Reagle!

I actually wrote that crossword.

And I edited it.

Now get back to crosswording!

Yes, sir.

Well, I must admit, I'm kind of touched. "Dumb dad sorry for his bet." Nice.

You didn't get <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>'s whole message, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

I didn't?

Take a look at the first letters of all the clues.

Dear <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, you make me so happy.

Really, really, really happy.

Sorry. He told me I needed 144 letters. What was my point again?

Oh, right. Bouvier or Simpson, I cherish you.

Oh, Dad.

<stage>CHERISH PLAYING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> Cherish is the word I use to describe.

All the feeling that I have hiding here for you inside.

You don't know how many times I've wished that I had told you[/i]
</txt></xml>