<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>The <person>Burns</person> and the Bees</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>08</epNum></ep>
<date>12/11/08</date> <runtime>10:06</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>SCHOOL BELL RINGING</stage>

<stage>HORN BELLOWING</stage>

<stage>PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

Sir, we're two minutes from landing at the billionaire's retreat.

Ah! My favorite week of the year.

Sophisticated financial discussions with my fellow plutocrats.

Food fight!

<stage>ALL CHEERING</stage>

Take that, Ted Turner. In your face, founder of Facebook!

Skinny dip!

<stage>LAUGHS EX CITEDLY</stage>

Yee-haw!

<stage>ALL CHEERING</stage>

Man: Gangway!

<stage>ALL SHOUTING EX CITEDLY</stage>

<stage>CHUCKLES</stage>

<stage>HUMMING</stage>

"Men." The room for me.

<stage>WOMEN SCREAMING</stage>

Nice prank, Simpson.

I dare you to dump that bees' nest on those second-grade babies.

Why would I want to?

Because I said, "I dare you." <person>Kearney</person>, can you read it back?

"Nice prank, Simpson. I dare you to dump that bees' nest on those second-grade babies."

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>: Why would I want to?

<person>Jimbo</person>: Because I said, 'I dare you.'

"<person>Kearney</person>, can you read it back?

"<person>Kearney</person>, reading: Nice prank, Simpson. I dare you to..."

The point is, Simpson, a dare has been placed on your nards!

My nards accept!

Stingamajigs!

Save yourselves!

Huh?

Where are the bees?

No bees?

Dare annulled.

Can I appeal?

Yeah. Appeal to other guys, Captain Wuss!

Other than the birth of my kid, this is my happiest moment.

All the bees are d*ad!

Aye, lass. The bees are dying, and not just here. All over the world.

From Glasgow clear to Edinburgh. And no one knows why.

<stage>PLAYING AMAZING GRACE ON BAGPIPES</stage>

I've lost a lot of wee friends of late.

<stage>STIFLES SOB</stage>

Willie, I didn't know you were an apiarist.

From context, I can tell that means beekeeper.

'Tis a tragedy, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>. No man should outlive his bees.

They're stinging God now.

<stage>LAUGHING CRAZILY</stage>

And the call from the SEC was coming from inside their own brokerage house!

Jeff Bezos wet his pants!

I did not. That was apple juice from before!

I fold.

I raise a million dollars.

And to sweeten the pot, my assistant, <person>Smithers</person>.

If you lose me, sir, may I say what an honor it's been to...

Bets don't talk. They see and raise.

<stage><person>SMITHERS</person> GROANS</stage>

Well, if we're betting people, I got a whole herd of them.

My professional basketball team, the Austin Celtics.

Well, they're hardly worth a <person>Smithers</person>. But we don't have all night.

Can you b*at nine high?

Damn! Eight high!

So I own a basketball team, do I?

Take good care of them, Burnsie. Don't let the forwards mix with the guards.

And if they're acting sluggish, slip some steroids into their cocaine.

<stage>CONTENTEDLY</stage> Mmm-hmm.

Fortune Four Lotto numbers are nine...

<stage>SNORTS</stage> Knew it.

Seven...

Duh.

Three...

What?

And...

Boring.

Dad, we have to do something! All the bees are dying!

<stage>MOCKINGLY</stage> Oh, no! No bees? Ooh!

Now who will sting me and walk all over my sandwiches?

But, Dad, bees pollinate flowers.

<stage>SCOFFS DISMISSIVELY</stage> Flowers. The painted whores of the plant world.

No bees means no honey.

<stage>RAGGED BREATHING</stage>

Synthetic honey, just like you remember.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

Honey?

<stage>WHINING</stage> Thank you.

<stage>MOANING</stage>

<stage><person>HOMER</person> YELLING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

I never dreamed the future could be scary.

Let's go, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

We've got some worms to save.

Bees.

Worms, bees, ticks, fleas. Let's go, go, go!

I'm glad you called me.

I know I'm not the first scientist in the phone book.

That's Associate Professor Aaron Ableman.

How I hate him.

<stage>GASPS</stage> Thundering thorax! It's just exactly what I feared!

In there. Close. See these red dots?

10 whole seconds.
<stage>CHAINSAW WHIRRING</stage>

It's time for this peacock to show his feathers.

You know, the feathers with the big eye that trick them into thinking that's my front?

Said feathers are what I'll flaunt!

Mom, maybe you shouldn't have put so much syrup on the pancakes.

<stage>GULPING</stage>

The secret is not to swallow the stingers.

<stage>SPITTING</stage>

Dad, don't eat the bees!

They're just drones, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>.

They only live for like five minutes anyway.

And they only have haploid cells, not diploid, like me and <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!

Yeah!

Listen, <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, I was trying to think of a way to help your bees.

And I remembered this abandoned greenhouse outside of town.

Which used to be a beautiful thriving greenhouse till I was hired to run it.

Your bees will have plenty of room in this old greenhouse.

Plus, there are flowers.

And it's near a prison, so they'll have a place to sting people.

Oh, Mom, it's perfect! Go live your lives!

Get off my face!

I miss them.

Now you know how I'll feel when you go to college.

You'll always have <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, always.

But he'll be gone a lot, repairing refrigerators.

Always.

Announcer on <location>PA</location>: Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome your new fun-Ioving owner.

You've seen him on the cover of the December 1943 issue of Collier's Magazine, Montgomery <person>Burns</person>!

<stage>CROWD CHEERING</stage>

Silence! Now let's make some noise for everyone's favorite basketball team, whom I have renamed <location>the Springfield Excitement</location>!

I knew it!

Now I would like to sing our national anthem.

<stage>SINGING TO MELODY OF GOD SA VE THE QUEEN</stage>

My country 'tis of thee.

Austria, Hungary.

Obey your king

<stage>WHISPERING</stage> Sir, the Archduke is d*ad.

What? The Archduke is d*ad?

And the empire is destroyed.

Then what happened?

World w*r I.

Then what?

World w*r II.

Then what?

A postwar period.

Then what?

The Cold w*r.

Then what? Then what?

<stage><person>SMITHERS</person> WHISPERING UNINTELLIGIBLY</stage>

Then what?

The European Union.

A European union? Good heavens.

Mr. <person>Burns</person>: Ladies, hold on to your husbands.

It's time for the saucy antics of <location>Springfield</location>'s own.

Basket-Belles!

<stage>LIVEL YPIANO MUSIC PLA YING</stage>

<stage>CROWD BOOING</stage>

Enough of this vulgarity! Back to your brothel, harlots!

Now enjoy your game and the madcap antics of the freewheeling title holder of this asset, me!

<stage>HIP-HOPHOORA YPLAYING OVER <location>PA</location></stage>

Hip-Hop hooray! Ho! Hey! Ho!

Hey! Ho! Hey! Ho!

<stage>RAPPING</stage> You drew a picture of my morning.

But you couldn't make my day...

<stage>g*n</stage>

Sir, were those real b*ll*ts?

Yes. Was that a real gorilla?

No.

I see.

<stage>CROWD CHATTERING ANGRILY</stage>

Sir, your escapades, while well intentioned, seem to be driving away our fans.

We have to turn this business around.

Time to think outside the boxiola.

What would Mark Cuban do?

I'm out of my mind!

That's not much help.

Build a new arena, state-of-the-art!

New arena.

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>GASPING</stage>

That's it, men! Pave and tar the way God intended!

Mr. <person>Burns</person>, you can't do this!

I can, I shall, and in the future, I will have done!

I cannot be stopped.

k*ll his acorns and make him watch.

First, one announcement. I regret to inform you we are not offering childcare tonight.

I don't know who that guy was you were leaving your kids with.

Now without further ado, let's get ready to referendum!

There's only one place in town where the bees can survive, and Mr. <person>Burns</person> wants to tear it down.

<stage>MR. <person>BURNS</person> GULPS</stage>

Please, people. You didn't listen to me about the snail darter.

You didn't listen to me about the osprey.

And you didn't listen to me about the javelina!

The feisty pig of the desert?

Apparently not feisty enough.

804 million dollars.

Wait a minute! Someone crunch the numbers!

He's only worth $996,036,000!

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

He's not a billionaire at all!

Wait, wait, wait! It's only a matter of four million.

I'm sure I can find that somewhere. I have $50 here in my wallet.

Mark, can you get me off the hook for old times' sake?

Can't do it, Monty.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

Don't worry. You'll feel a lot more comfortable <stage>MOCKING</stage> in the millionaire's camp.

No! No! Just k*ll me now!

<stage>SOUTHERN ACCENT</stage> Howdy do! I own a minor league hockey team!

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>
</txt></xml>