<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Mypods and Boomsticks</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>07</epNum></ep>
<date>12/04/08</date> <runtime>03:39</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>SCHOOL BELL RINGING</stage>

<stage>HORN BELLOWING</stage>

<stage>PLAYING DIFFERENT TUNE</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

Santas: <stage>SADLY</stage> Ho-ho-ho.

All: <stage>SINGING</stage> O Christmas Tree, O Christmas Tree.

You're on the curb and d*ad now - You're on the curb and d*ad now.

Your Christmas lights are in the box - Your Christmas lights are in the box.

In two months we will change the clocks.

O Christmas Tree, O...

They sure give the Christmas spirit the bum's rush around here.

And they've already started exploiting the next holiday.

15 month calendars! That gives you three extra kittens!

That's the last time I get you guys a Christmas present at the last minute.

Man, those are ugly kittens.

Mom! Dad! Our mall got a Mapple Store!

It's so sterile.

MyPods. MyPhones.

A Brainiac Bar.

My question is the following statement.

Operating system 4.2 has sloppier architecture than a Tijuana anthill.

Did you get peanut butter in your Ethernet port again?

No. I got mayonnaise in the CD drive.

I see you're admiring our MyCube.

40.

I'll never get a Mapple anything.

<person>Krusty</person>: I hate this MyPod!

I can't watch movies on a screen this small!

And the music today, don't get me started!

I said don't get me started!

Come on! Isn't someone gonna get me started?

Let's go, Teeny.

Maybe somebody at Old Navy will get me started.

Here, kid. You take it.

Thank you, <person>Krusty</person>.

Don't thank me.

Thank the Jewish Clown Awards gift basket.

I'm a Mapple person!

We're all Mapple people.

Sorry.

Announcer: Attention, Mapple universe.

Prepare for a live announcement from Mapple Founder and Chief lmaginative Officer, Steve Mobs.

Steve Mobs!

He's a genius!

He's like a God who knows what we want!

Greetings. It is I. Your insanely great leader, Steve Mobs.

I'm speaking to you from Mapple headquarters deep below the sea with an announcement that will completely change the way you look at everything.

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

And that announcement is...

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>: <stage>ON MIC</stage> You're all losers!

Huh?

You think you're cool because you buy a $500 phone with a picture of a fruit on it?

Well, guess what? They cost 8 bucks to make and I pee on every one!

<stage>ALL EXCLAIM</stage>

I have made a fortune off you chumps, and I've invested it all in Microsoft.

Now my boyfriend Bill Gates and I kiss each other on a pile of your money!

<stage>ALL MUTTERING</stage>

Traitor! Your heart is blacker than your turtleneck!

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

Who dares question the boss we fired 10 years ago and then brought back?

It was my brother, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!

Flay him with your earbuds! Flay him, I say!

MyCube, take me away!

<stage>SINGING</stage> Loving you is easy 'cause you're beautiful

Get him! Get him good!

Stupid angry mob, chasing me because I shine a harsh light on modern society.

Now I know how Dane Cook feels!

<stage>SNIFFS</stage>

Mmm. What's that exotic aroma?

Smells like a hamburger cooked at a rug store.

Hello. Would you like some lamb?

Whoa! All these years I've been petting lambs when I should've been shoving them in my mouth!

I'm <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>.

I'm Bashir.

My family and I just moved here from Jordan.

Jordan. That's on some map somewhere, right?

Bashir, introduce me to your new friend.

Bashir, you didn't tell me you had a sister.

Such a charmer.

Would you like to stay for dinner?

Hey, I never refuse food from strangers.

Okay. You're new to our school, so here's the deal.

We call <person>Skinner</person>, Skin Rash.

Mr. Wiener is Mr. Whiner.

And <person>Groundskeeper Willie</person>, Grounds Creeper Stupid.

That's not clever.

And I have so many aspects you can mock.

I'm poor. I'm dirty. I can't read or write. I think movies are real.

<stage>BOTH LAUGHING</stage>

Okay, next.

Here's the food at the cafeteria that will make you sick.

Coleslaw, tuna, all chowders and gumbos.

The only thing that's safe is the pork chops.

My religion says I can never eat pork.

A different religion? Do not tell anyone that, because if the bullies around here find out that you're different...

<person>Jimbo</person>: Who's different?

What's your name, sweat stain?

Bashir.

Bash Here?

I love a kid that comes with directions!

Okay, Bash Here, tell us where you came from so we can punch you back there.

I'm gonna punch you extra hard because I secretly think you're cute!

Whoa! Whoa!

You can't just wail on him because he's...

What religion are you anyway?

Muslim.

Oh, boy.

You're the reason I can't carry toothpaste on an airplane!

Ow!

Look, guys. Everyone's different.

<person>Jimbo</person>, you're Christian. <person>Dolph</person>, you're Jewish.

And <person>Kearney</person>, your family's in that cult <person>Moe</person> started.

I had to join. My mom's doing the savior.

I mean, the one true <person>Moe</person>.

You're the one true <person>Moe</person>.

<stage>BOTH LAUGHING</stage>

Help me, oh, mighty <person>Moe</person>!

I can't.

I'm not really a God. I was just acting crazy to get out of jury duty.

38.

Thirty-eight waist I might believe.

Hey, <person>Carl</person>. Got any idea what direction Mecca's in?

Why don't you ask <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>?

1,200?

But I only downloaded 1212 songs.

I gotta prove the genie was right.

Off to work.

Sometimes I wish you would quit that awful business.

But I love blowing up buildings.

Oh, my God!

Safely and legally in order to make room for new buildings.

Darling.

I think you're working much too hard.

Yes. I am k*ll myself.

But it is all for the profit.

And after the expl*si*n, I will be in a better place.

That corner office with the downtown view.

Oh, it's you. What do you want?

I want to apologize for being such a jerk at dinner.

And I thought the best way to do that would be to come to your house and poke around.

Mr. Simpson, I accept your apology. Goodbye.

Wait, wait, wait, wait! I read somewhere your people are hospitable to guests.

Is that true?

<stage>SIGHS</stage> Yes.

Praise be Oliver.

That's Allah.

We'll look it up in the Corona.

So, now that we're alone, death to <location>America</location>, right?

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, why are you really here?

Look at that!

We're out of almond paste! Don't get up! I'll grind the almonds myself!

A computer.

I'm in.

<stage>READING</stage>

They're gonna blow it up!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, I don't hear almond grinding.

Just listen! I'm grinding them now.

<stage>MIMICS GRINDING</stage>

Ow!

My finger!

Here comes the ambulance!

<stage>MIMICS AMBULANCE SIREN</stage>

My, you're a handsome fellow.

Just get in the ambulance, Mr. Simpson. We'll see to your finger.

Why, thank you.

<stage>MIMICS AMBULANCE SIREN</stage>

My finger!

Everyone, get out!

Run for your lives!

Run for your...

Stay where you are.

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>!

Boy, don't blow up this mall.

It has the cookie store that gives free samples!

I can't believe your dad gets paid to blow stuff up.

Actually, <fam><person>Bart</person></fam>, my job is about math and engineering.

Every calculation is to make sure the expl*si*n is safe.

Did you factor in one bald idiot?

No, I...

USA! USA! USA!

Dad, it was an empty building. It was supposed to come down.

What about the bridge?

That was supposed to open tomorrow.

Do we really need a bridge there?

The Duff brewery is on that island.

I'll save you!

<stage><person>HOMER</person> CHUCKLING</stage>

That banner has really paid for itself over the years!

We accept your apology.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, add another name to our Christmas card list.

<stage>WHISPERING</stage> Next to our Jewish friends.

Where is <fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>?

She said something about the bottom of the ocean and "be back in a month."

Announcer: Welcome to Mapple headquarters.

The cost of this journey will be added to your bill.

Come on. Come on. Yes!

Sixteen million results!

Mr. Mobs, there's a surface dweller here to see you.

MyTunes user Jazzgal62.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam> Simpson. Send her in.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>! It's insanely great to see you.

Mr. Mobs, I sort of downloaded too many songs onto my MyPod, and I don't have the money to pay for them.

And do you think you could consider a reduced payment plan?

I'm sorry. I know our posters say, "Think differently," but our real slogan is, "No refunds."

<stage>SNIFFLING</stage>

Can't you open your Mapple menu and click on the "compassion bar"?

Oh, please?

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, how would you like to work for Mapple?

Would I ever!

Think differently.

Think differently.

Think differently.

<stage>SIGHS</stage>

Think differently.
</txt></xml>