<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Sex, Pies and Idiot Scrapes</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>01</epNum></ep>
<date>10/02/08</date> <runtime>19:13</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>BRAKES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>ALL SHRIEK</stage>

<fam><person>Bart</person></fam>: Woo-hoo!

St. Patrick's Day. I love how they made the river green.

Actually, my nuclear plant did that. And now that you know, your life is in danger.

<stage>HUMS HAPPY TUNE</stage>

Greetings, fellow lrishmen and lady lrishmen.

I, Joseph Fitzgerald O'Malley Fitzpatrick O'Donnell "The Edge" Quimby, welcome you to <location>Springfield</location>'s first booze-free St. Patrick's Day!

<stage>ALL BOOING</stage>

Come on, people.

Your drunken shenanigans destroy this town every year.

And lreland is so much more than the imbibing of spirits.

The lrish gave the world the paddy wagon, the shamrock shake, and folk dancing where you don't move your arms.

<stage>IRISH MUSIC PLAYING</stage>

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

Where's the IRA when you need 'em.

<stage>IN IRISH ACCENT</stage> We renounced the ways of the g*n and the b*mb.

<stage>ALL CHEERING</stage>

<stage>SIGHS</stage>

In the old days we would've been all over that.

<stage>BAND PLAYING IRISH MUSIC</stage>

<stage>PEOPLE CHATTERING</stage>

<stage>SILENCE</stage>

<stage>CHILDREN CLAMORING</stage>

<stage>BAND PLAYING HEROIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC</stage>

Oh, no. The Northern lrish are also having a parade.

Two kinds of lrish people? What are they fighting over?

Who gets to sleep in the bathtub?

Actually, those Prots and Cathies have hated each other for centuries.

<stage>SIGHS</stage> It always comes down to transubstantiation versus consubstantiation.

<stage>BOTH SPEAKING IRISH-ACCENTED GIBBERISH</stage>

Stop it, both of you! You have a common land, a literature, and the sweetest songs on <location>earth</location>!

<stage>SINGING</stage> Too-ra-Ioo-ra-Ioo-ral.

Too-ra-Ioo-ra-li.

Hush, my little baby.

Hush now, don't you cry All: Too-ra-Ioo-ra-Ioo-ral.

Too-ra-Ioo-ra-li.

Too-ra-Ioo-ra-Ioo-ral.

That's an lrish <location>lullaby</location>

<stage>ALL CRYING</stage>

Oh, no! Without the booze, these guys all remember how much they hate each other!

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

This was such a pleasant St. Patrick's Day until the lrish people showed up.

<stage>CHILDREN CHATTERING</stage>

Urchins!

They took my cupcakes!

<stage>IRISH ACCENT</stage> All right, you unwanted miracles, give back the lady's cupcakes.

You don't have the teeth for it.

<stage>IRISH ACCENT</stage> Aye, but we could gum the frosting.

Well, if it's good gumming you're after, wouldn't you rather have this lovely cabbage?

Children: Cabbage, cabbage!

Here you go, ma'am. Not a sprinkle nor jimmy askew.

Thank you so much, Mr...

Patrick Farrelly at your service.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam> Simpson. Well, Mr. Farrelly, the least I could do is offer you a cupcake.

Mmm.

Light, moist, and such a marvelous shape retention.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>, I own a small bakery. Will you bake for me?

Me? A professional baker's employee?

Imagine how different my life would be.

Here we are at school, kids.

Hey, what are those boxes in the back?

Cakes!

Both: See ya.

I'll do it!

Bless your heart.

You won't regret it.

I already don't.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>! I've got great news!

I'll use my one phone call to find out all about it!

Mulk request change of venue.

Green monster cannot get fair trial in downtown <location>Springfield</location>.

Granted.

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson? You're a repeat offender.

Three-peat.

Bail is set at $25,000.

<stage>SCOFFS</stage> I make that in a year.

I suggest you see a bail bondsman.

Okay, Simpson. All of your information checks out.

I called your boss to verify your employment, and he says you're fired for getting arrested.

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

You'd be amazed how often that happens.

Oh!

We'll put up your bail money.

Just pay us 10 percent and show up for your court date.

And if I don't show up?

Then you gotta deal with me. The name's Wolf, and I'm a bounty hunter.

If someone skips bail, I track 'em down and bring 'em back.

I also take a tooth, make a plastic cast, put it on this necklace, then replace the tooth at my expense.

Well, time to go back to my world of sleazy bars, tattoo parlors, and greasy spoons.

What a great job. And I could use a job right now.

Whoa!

Not just anyone can be a bounty hunter. You have to pass an online exam.

No, wait. They got rid of that. There is a ten-dollar filing fee.

But you can get around it.

Congratulations. You're now a bounty hunter.

Mmm.

Okay. I've set my trap.

Now to scatter my cheese cubes and the rats will come.

Condos! Affordable condos! Bail jumpers welcome!

"Bail jumpers welcome." That's refreshing, after the cold shoulder we got at <location>the Town Homes</location> at <location>Sterling Point</location>.

Let's not get too excited till we find out if it's in a good school district.

Well, so wait. Are we telling people now?

Stop! In the name of a private citizen with no connection to the law!

Now are you gonna come quietly, or do I have to...

<stage>SCREAMS</stage> Now let's think about this.

If you sh**t me, I won't be able to stop you and you'll be free to go. But someone may come after you.

Probably not, given your reputation for sh**ting people who come after you.

What I'm trying to say is, not sh**ting me now would be the biggest mistake of your life.

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>GROANS</stage>

Huh?

b*llet-proof glass.

<person>Flanders</person>?

Yep. I'm just replacing the front window of my store, which was broken in the riot.

Young man, what would your mother say if she knew you were sh**ting nice people in the brain?

She'd say that year off from Princeton was the worst decision I ever made.

Well, son, if you take responsibility for your actions, this could be the start of a better life for you.

Maybe you're right. Maybe I should just...

<stage><person>SNAKE</person> GASPING</stage>

This case is in the bag!

<fam><person>Homer</person></fam>, you could've k*ll him!

I sure could've. Thanks to you.

Now I can clearly see potential customers walk right past my store.

Enjoy your shopping elsewhere.

Hey, <person>Ned</person>. I brought you something.

<stage><person>HOMER</person> CHUCKLES</stage>

What the...

It's your share of the money for bringing in that bail jumper.

<person>Ned</person>, I never thought I'd say this, but we make a great team.

Us? A team? As the salad said to the soup, I'm all mixed up.

We should be bounty hunters together.

You're kind and smart. I'm cruel and strong.

Together, we're nothing.

But together, we're the perfect bounty hunter.

Well, I could use money. But you have to promise me something, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>.

Sure. What is it?

1. "The book of the genealogy of Jesus Christ, the son of David, "the son of Abraham.

"Abraham became the father of lsaac. Isaac became the father of Jacob.

"Jacob became the father of Judah and his brothers.

"Judah became the father of Perez and Zarah by Tamar."

Simpson, we're gonna put you away for a long, long time.

Make it life and you've got a deal.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>: Don't feel too bad, <fam>Homie</fam>. You'll be free tomorrow.

And I used all my new baking k*ll to make a special cake to remind you of me.

<stage>CHUCKLES EXCITEDLY</stage>

Baby!

Thanks, <fam><person>Marge</person></fam>.
</txt></xml>