<?xml-model href="../schema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<xml><txt>
<metadata><ep><epTitle>Four Great Women and a Manicure</epTitle><szn>20</szn>x<epNum>20</epNum></ep>
<date>05/14/09</date> <runtime>01:03</runtime></metadata>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ The Simpsons ♪ </music>

<stage>BIRD CAWS</stage>

<catchphrase>D'oh</catchphrase>!

<stage>TIRES SCREECHING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

Mmm...

<stage>LOUD CRASH</stage>

My daughter's here for her first mani-pedi.

Mom, I'm glad you brought me here, but isn't it more important for a woman to be smart and powerful than beautiful?

A woman can be smart, beautiful, and powerful, like Queen Elizabeth I.

She had it all. Except the most important thing.

Please don't say "a man."

No! A husband!

The year was 1588, 400 years before Kirk Gibson would hit his famous home run.

Queen Elizabeth ruled over all of <location>England</location>.

Every eligible bachelor in <location>Europe</location> wanted her hand in marriage.

Majesty, thy suitors await.

I don't understand why I need a king.

So you can pump out a son and then I don't gotta work for no broad no more.

My liege.

Announcing Prince <person>Ralph</person> of Austria!

Off with my head!

Pass.

King Julio of Spain.

Hello, Queenie baby.

Forget it. I've seen you making goo-goo eyes at my court jester.

Well, I like a man who can make me laugh!

But for you, I'll make an exception.

Hands off my harlequin! This is 1588, and his material is fresh and hip.

You have made a big mistake, lady!

His Excellency Sir Walter Raleigh.

Hmm...

Your Majesty, I have returned from the New World with a gift.

This healthful and slimming herb, tobacco.

Ooh!

<stage>EXCLAIMS</stage>

If I ever have sex, this'll be great afterwards.

I'll show those uppity English food boilers.

What is the status of my armada?

A hundred and twenty of the finest k*ll machines ever built.

Ooh! Not bad. Not bad at all. Now take me to the real ones.

Those are the real ones. "Watch out, <location>England</location>."

<stage>IN ENGLISH ACCENT</stage> "No! Have mercy, my lord!"

"Never."

Guards!

Take him away and put things inside of him.

Nice things?

No. Not nice things.

Allow me.

Ooh!

You have the strength of a plow horse but the charm of a cart horse.

<person>Selma</person>: Treason!

How dare you make out under my crenelations while I make out not? Don't you know that I love you?

I've always loved you!

Which one of us are you talking to?

I'm not sure. Both! Neither! What difference does it make?

Take them to the Tower!

Whoa. Someone call Beowulf! Grendel got in again!

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

It's you, Your Majesty.

<stage>CLEARS THROAT</stage>

The Spanish Armada sails for <location>England</location>.

Armada? What's "armada"?

Nothing. What's armada with you?

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

Seriously, though, we're in real trouble here.

Come, Tea Biscuit.

<stage>GRUNTING</stage>

<stage>NEIGHING</stage>

The time of battle grows nigh.

<person>Moe</person>: So here's us, and a whole lot of them.

It's probably a little too early to be standing under this.

Lord Jesus, although our country turned Protestant for the sole reason that our fat, mean king could dump his faithful wife, we know you're on our side.

So please destroy these horrible monsters who believe your mother should be revered.

Amen.

Abandon ship!

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

Normally, I love to see flaming dreamboats headed my way, but not like this, baby! Not like this!

For destroying the Spanish Armada, I dub thee "Sir" Sir Walter Raleigh.

And I grant you two my blessing.

Your Majesty, it's so kind of you to give up the one man you truly loved.

I don't need a man. For I have <location>England</location>!

Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.

<stage>TOY SQUEAKING</stage>

You keep soaking. We're going to Koo Koo Roo.

Which in our language means nothing.

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>, you are going to look so pretty.

Thank you.

But I know a story of a dangerous obsession with female beauty.

It's called Snow White and the Seven...

Excuse me. The story you're about to tell is the copyrighted property of the Walt Disney Corporation.

Can you sharpen these?

Excuse me, but Snow White is a fairytale from hundreds of years ago.

No one owns that.

Are there any dwarves in your story?

Yes. But they're my own original creation.

There's Crabby, Drunky, Hungry, Greedy, <person>Lenny</person>...

<person>Kearney</person>!

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: And Doc... tor Hibbert.

<stage>CHUCKLING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> <music>♪ Ho-hi ♪</music>

<stage>ALL SINGING</stage> <music>♪ Ho-hi, ho-hi. ♪</music>
<music>♪ It's off to work Ho-hi. ♪</music>

This song's not like any song you know.

9 who's...

<stage>EXCLAIMING</stage>

Bring me Snow White's heart in this box.

What'll I do with the rest of the body?

Put it in this box. Then you'll get your reward.

<stage>THUNDER RUMBLING</stage>

<stage>HUMMING</stage>

Now turtle, I'll need you to get in the soup.

<stage>EXCLAIMS HAPPILY</stage>

<stage>PANTING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

I... I cannot do it!

Run, lassie! Find wee little men and hide with them!

Now to fool the queen with a pig's heart.

I... I cannot do it!

<stage>SOBBING</stage>

Maybe I'll make her a heart out of construction paper!

I... I cannot do it!

Let's see. Gingerbread house.

Grandma's house.

<stage>CACKLING</stage>

Ah! Here we are.

<stage>YAWNING</stage>

All that walking made me sleepy.

This bed's too hard.

<stage>CREAKING</stage>

This bed's too soft.

And this bed is just like the first one! Also too hard!

I guess I'll sleep in the one that's too soft.

<stage>YAWNING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> Ho-hi, ho-hi it's time to now get high.

We'll take some shrooms and go to our rooms...

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

There's something in our house.

Let's put a pickax in its brain!

You're in marketing. Why do you even bring an ax?

If you were in marketing, you'd know.

<stage>ALL GASP</stage>

She's beautiful!

Maybe she's been placed under some kind of a curse.

And all that will wake her is the kiss of a handsome...

I'm awake! I'm awake, already!

<stage>SIGHS</stage>

Guess it's you and me again, doorknob.

Goodbye!

Now beware of the evil queen. She's a master of disguise.

She could be anyone.

I'll be careful.

<stage>LAUGHS</stage>
<stage>BIRDS CHIRPING</stage>

No, no, no! That's too much! Go back outside!

Who are you?

Care for an apple?

Okay. I'll take a green one.

No! Take the red one.

<stage>BOTH GRUNTING</stage>

Take a bite, deary.

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>CACKLES</stage>

Uh-oh!

You'll never take me alive!

Ooh!

Herbivores! I'm so scared!

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<fam><person>Lisa</person></fam>: So Snow White slept and waited for her prince to come.

But he never did.

Because a woman shouldn't have to depend on a man.

2?

Macbeth!

Macwho?

<stage>GROANS</stage>

<stage>GAS HISSING</stage>

<stage>LAUGHING</stage>

<stage>LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY</stage>

<stage>DR. HIBBERTLAUGHING</stage>

This number is for emergencies only.

<stage>GROANS</stage>

He who laughs last laughs d*ad.

"In last night's Macbeth, "the best performance was <person>Barney</person> Gumble as Duncan, "followed by Duffman as Macduff, <person>Lenny</person> Leonard as Lennox, "<person>Eddie</person> and <person>Lou</person> as the two soldiers without lines, "then last, and least, the <location>lead</location>, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam> Simpson."

Why do they write a new review of this play every single day?

All I heard was more names of actors you haven't k*ll!

Unless you're not man enough!

No, dear. I'm a man, dear.

<stage>FESTIVE MUSIC PLA YING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>SCREAMS</stage>

<stage>ALL GROANING</stage>

<stage>SINGING</stage> k*ll makes me hungry.

Eating makes me thirsty.

Drinking makes me sleepy

Why did he have to k*ll everyone in their costumes?

It was you who k*ll us! You!

No! It was <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>!

Your dark ambition guided his m*rder hand!

No, I just encouraged him.

Encouraged by withholding sex!

Sex!

<stage>ALL WAILING</stage>

<stage>SCREAMING</stage>

<stage>SOBBING</stage>

Well, at least you can't nag me anymore.

That's where you're wrong. Get out on that stage!

<stage>GRUNTS IN PAIN</stage>

Okay, <fam><person>Homer</person></fam>. It's our last performance.

You're the only actor that's still alive, and there's nobody in the audience.

This is your moment.

I'll be in my office going over the books on my Subway Sandwich franchise.

You call a sandwich maker an artist, it's like an invitation to steal.

That guy's going nani-nooni-bananas in there.

It's my moment!

To-morrow and to-morrow and to-morrow, creeps in this petty pace from day to day, to the last syllable of recorded time.

And all our yesterdays have lighted fools the way to dusty death.

Out, out, brief candle!

Life's but a walking shadow, a poor player that struts and frets his hour upon the stage, and then is heard no more.

<stage>APPLAUDING</stage>

<fam>Homie</fam>. You were brilliant. I knew you could do it. I knew it.

Now nothing will stop you from taking on all of Shakespeare's greatest roles.

King <location>Lear</location>, Hamlet, Othello, Richard III, Henry IV, Part One, Henry IV, Part Two, Henry V, Titus Andronicus...

<stage>g*n</stage>

Me having to read all those plays would be the real tragedy.

That's it. Three stories. That's all we always tell.

Looks like <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> wants a story, too.

Ooh!

<stage><person>MARGE</person> READING</stage>

Mom! Isn't that book the Bible of right-wing losers?

Yeah. But the guy on the book jacket is one sexy slice of beefcake.

<stage>GROWLS PLAYFULLY</stage>

So anyway, this is the story of <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> Roarke, an architect who refused to compromise.

Now children, while I do traffic school online, you'll be playing with blocks.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>: <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>'s genius and creativity far exceeded that of the others.

And I'm not just saying that because I'm her mother.

But her teacher, Mr. Elsworth Toohey, wanted every child to conform.

Banal. Very banal. Wonderfully pedestrian.

This isn't right. <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>, dancers shouldn't kick too high, and buildings mustn't reach the sky.

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

There!

Your rubble is still a little bit higher than the others, so let's just...

<stage>GRUNTS</stage>

There. Welcome to the real world, baby.

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>: He would not let <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>'s creativity flower.

Mediocrity rules!

All right, <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>. Today is parent/teacher day, so I want everyone to see how uncreative and beaten down you've become.

That's right. You're beaten down. Yes, you are.

I don't know how you put up with all these kids, Toohey.

If I were you, there'd be a lot of strangled babies.

Now let's see what your children have done, shall we?

Don't brace yourselves. You will believe your eyes.

<stage>GASPS</stage>

You will be tried as a toddler!

Babies and gentlemen of the jury.

<stage>CRYING</stage>

This child's crime was to remind the rest of us that we are merely ordinary.

When a blade of grass rises above the others, do we applaud it?

No! We cut it down!

I recommend nine time-outs served consecutively.

<stage>CLEARS THROAT</stage>

Throughout the ages, the finger painter, the Play-<catchphrase>Doh</catchphrase> sculptor, the Lincoln Logger, stood alone against the daycare teacher of her time.

She did not live to earn approval stickers.

She lived for herself, that she might achieve things that are the glory of all humanity.

These are my terms. I do not care to play by any others.

And now, if the court will allow me, it's naptime.

<stage>YAWNS</stage>

<fam><person>Marge</person></fam>: <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam> grew up to be a world-famous architect.

Her building became one of the wonders of the world.

And on the very top floor was a daycare center, where every child was free to follow their dream.

Because nothing is...

<stage>GASPS</stage> <fam><person>Maggie</person></fam>, get away from there!

Bad baby!

Ho-hi.

Ho-hi, ho-hi it's time to say goodbye.

If Disney sues we'll claim their use.

Ho-hi, ho-hi, ho-hi, ho-hi.

Ho-hi, ho-hi, there's nothing we won't try.

We'll get take-out and then make out.

We're bi, we're bi, we're bi, we're bi
</txt></xml>