<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><introduction></introduction>
    <line><character>Pat McHale</character><dialogue>In the dark recesses of the mind, a disease known as FEAR feasts upon the souls of those who cannot overcome its power...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn and Jake chase a Fire Newt to the ocean</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Come back, thief!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The Fire Newt spews fire at Finn and Jake</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Whoa!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fire Newt</character><dialogue>Stop farting on me! It's gross!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You can't just go around stealing boots.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yeah, and you know the penalty for stealing boots. It's poots... on newts.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Both</character><dialogue><stage>Laugh</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The Fire Newt wades into the ocean to avoid Finn and Jake</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>He's getting away in that lake!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Dude, that isn't a lake. That's an ocean.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake stretches and heads towards the ocean, a poot following behind, barking</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs and runs after Jake</stage> Bark! Bark! Bark! Bark! ...Huh?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The hue of the ocean and sky changes to red and ominous music plays as a wave crashes</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Finn backs away from the water as it washes onto land</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Uhh...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Laughing and farting on the Newt</stage> Poots on newts! Poots on newts!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fire Newt</character><dialogue>No!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Slow-motion</stage> Poots on newts!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>laughs and starts removing his shoes</stage> I'm coming, Jake. I'll poot on that newt as soon as I'm barefoot. Uh...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The ocean turns a red hue again and ominous music plays as a wave crashes</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Finn gasps and rapidly crawls away from the water</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Breaths heavily, his stomach rumbles</stage> Ow! Why is my stomach going nuts?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A black smoke rises out of Finn's navel</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Ow!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The smoke forms into a face and laughs</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Wh-wh-wh-Who are you?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>I am the manifestation of your fear... fear of the ocean!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What? I'm not afraid of lakes, wells, or rivers, streams, or deep wells or puddles. Why would I be afraid of- <stage>Screams and backs away from the water</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs</stage> 'Cause you're a wuss.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'm no wuss! I'm the hero around these parts!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>Ha! You're too scared of the ocean to ever be a true hero.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Not true! I'm not scared of nothin'!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn charges towards the ocean, screaming, but stops when he sees a wave crash</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Shakes his head and takes a deep breath</stage> I shall conquer my fear.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>Yeah, right.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No! I will. I'll conquer my fear.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>Of course you will, <stage>Receding back into Finn's navel</stage> and I live in a two bedroom apartment that doesn't smell like vomit <stage>Laughs</stage> ...Sarcasm.</dialogue></line>
    <line> <stage>Jake comes onscreen, panting, and shrinks back to normal when he reaches Finn</stage> </line>
    
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Dude. Dude, did you see me? I was all like womp, and then I was all like take this! Womp! Womp! And then... Hey, what’s wrong with you, dude?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake. I think I'm afraid... of the ocean.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Say what, now?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I need your help to overcome my fear. Will you do it?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Um... No... I don't really wanna do it.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake! Come on!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm just messing with you. I'll do it. Hmm... Where to start? Oh, ok. I think we should just take a few steps in the water. You can hold Jake's hand if you're scared.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake grabs Finn's hand and starts walking towards the water, but Finn doesn't walk and falls over</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Um... Oh it's ok, dude. I see the problem. It's just your feet.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake walks over to Finn's feet and takes his shoes off</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Manually moving Finn's feet forward one at a time</stage> Boop. Beep. Boop. Beep. Boop. Beep. Boop. Beep. Beep. Boop. Beep. Boop.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Don't be scared. I shall not be scared.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Still moving Finn's feet</stage> Boop. Boop.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The water touches Finn's feet</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'm afraid! Ah! <stage>Jumps on top of Jake and starts punching him</stage> Jake, get me out of the water! Now, Jake! Now! Now!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake inflates his head and walks Finn back to shore</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Hot jam! You're really scared of the ocean. In fact, you're so scared... it gives me an idea. Let's start a business of being scared of the ocean!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Ok. Ok. I have a plan to get rid of your fear. We'll start tomorrow morning.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>But I must conquer this now! <stage>Runs towards the ocean screaming</stage> I'm not afraid of you!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Multiple waves crash directly in front of Finn in rapid succession and a single droplet hits Finn's face</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>reels back in slow-motion and screams</stage> No!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Running backwards</stage> I'm afraid of you! I'm afraid of you! <stage>Screams</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Exhaustedly crawls to Jake's feet</stage> Ok, yeah. Let's try tomorrow.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The scene changes to Finn and Jake's bedroom where Jake is sitting on top of a sleeping Finn</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Fiiiinn. Finn. Hey, Finn. Wake up.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Opens his eyes</stage> Morning, Jake.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Ready for me to help you get over your ocean fear?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Yeah, man.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Cool... but I can only do this if you ask me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'm askin'!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Then get ready for my three-step plan. Watch your troubles melt away with step one!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake punches the bedroom wall and the entire structure breaks apart, leaving Finn and Jake floating on Finn's bed in the middle of the ocean</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Screams</stage> Jake, are you crazy? This is not an OK thing to do!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Hey. Hey. Come on. The ocean is your friend, and you got friends all around you right now. Miles and miles of friends.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You're nuts. <stage>Wriggles from side to side</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Don't try to struggle, man. <stage>Pulls the blankets back, revealing that Finn is tied to the bed</stage> I'll let you out in a second. You just need to calm down.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Really? Ok. I'm calming down.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>That's great. You're doing great. Ready for step two?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Breathing heavily</stage> Yeah, man. I can do it.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Alright, dude. Step... two! <stage>Unties the rope</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The bed collapses and falls into the ocean, leaving Finn floating inside his sleeping bag and Jake on top of him</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Screams</stage> Jake, this isn't a joke! It's touching me!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Let it hold you, man! Let it hold you like a child!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Heart pounding</stage> I'm trying to let it hold me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Control your breathing!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Breathes in and out</stage> This isn't working!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>That means we gotta move to step three. Just don't scream.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>W-what?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm gonna push you underwater with my jowls. Just don't scream. Don't scream.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake pushes Finn's head underwater</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Don't scream. Hold your breath, Finn. You got it, dude!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn screams and bursts out of his sleeping bag, sending Jake flying into the water</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Finn jumps onto Jake's head and starts pounding on him</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Get me away, Jake! Now, Jake! Now! Right now! Get-Get me away! <stage>Screams</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Finn! Stop it, Finn! Ow!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn grabs Jake's ears and stretches them until they catch wind and carry both Finn and Jake to an island of pre-war ruins</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs</stage> I'm safe! I'm safe! How'd I do?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I think we should give up.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What? I made it all the way to level three.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Look, Finn. It's not that I don't want to help you... I just don't wanna get beat up anymore. I mean this <stage>Pointing to his face</stage> is my bread and butter. I can't have you messing up my bread and butter, dude.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You have to help me. I can't do this without you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Ok. Fine... but only if you swear not to hit me anymore.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I swear I won't hit you anymore.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>And also swear to only speak in rhymes. Speak in rhymes all the times.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I swear... and pigs have hair.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yes. Perfect. And since you want more... it's time for step four.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What? I thought you said it was a three step plan... man.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm not that good at counting. <stage>Laughs and grabs a small, rusty submarine</stage> Come on. Let's go kick your fear of the ocean where the sun don't shine... in the sea cucumber.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The scene changes to underwater where Finn and Jake are heading to the ocean floor in the submarine</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Check it, dude. One hundred percent awesome-itude.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Eyes closed, breathes heavily and shivers</stage> Yeah. It's pretty math... you psychopath.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>You know, it looks way more math if you open up your eyes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Opens his eyes</stage> Whoa...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>See, man? The ocean is beautiful. There's no reason to be afraid of things that are beautiful.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Hey. This isn't that bad. I'm actually glad.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Points</stage> Hey, look! A black abyss! Let's go check it out... sauerkraut.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No, Jake! Turn around! Turn around!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn sees the Fear Feaster's face appear in front of the abyss</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Noooo!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Saying, "Turn around" twice doesn't count as a rhyme, dude.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn pushes Jake away from the submarine controls</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Hey, you swore!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn pummels Jake</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Ow! My bread and butter!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn grabs the controls and jerks them violently</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>No, dude! Don't!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The submarine moves wildly and launches torpedoes, one of which hits a building</stage></line>
    <line><stage>The building topples and hits the submarine, causing it to start filling up with water</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Don't worry, dude. Everything's cool. This is the perfect segue into level five. <stage>Handing Finn a dive suit</stage> Here, put this on.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn starts putting on the suit</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Just make sure you don't pull the emergency tab.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn pulls the emergency tab</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>No, dude! I said don't...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn's suit expands rapidly and knocks Jake back, hitting his head against a valve and knocking him out</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Finn floats to the surface and watches Jake descend into the abyss along with the broken submarine</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake? Jaaaaaake!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn reaches the surface and jumps onto a buoy</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs</stage> Pathetic! You can't even overcome your fear now that your friend is about to die! Your un-heroic body will never let you save Jake. <stage>Laughs</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Sadly</stage> You're right.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>What? Really? You think I'm right? Well, that's... that's great!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Holding a wrench</stage> If my body won't let me rescue my best friend, then there's only one thing left to do.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn removes his helmet, hits himself on the head with the wrench and falls into the ocean</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>No. Wait. No! Noooo!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn lands on the ocean floor and wakes up next to Jake</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Jake groans</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake! Jake! Wake up!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake opens his eyes</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You ok, dude?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yeah, man. Wait... Finn, you did it! You conquered your fear!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>You're at the bottom of the ocean!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn screams and tries to pull his emergency tab, but nothing happens</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Maybe we should celebrate on land.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake grabs Finn and pulls his own emergency tab, so they both float to the surface</stage></line>
    <line><stage>Finn and Jake run onto the beach and fall backwards</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm proud of you man. You did it!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Thanks, dude.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Fear Feaster comes out of Finn's navel</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>You've nothing to be proud of, boy! You will never get of your fear of the ocean!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Whoa, dude! What's with your bellybutton?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>To Fear Feaster</stage> What the flip, man? I just swam to the bottom!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>No you didn't, cheater! You just sank to the bottom. You will never be a great hero.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>He's right. I'll never be a hero.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn's stomach rumbles and a black-smoke limousine comes out of him and parks nearby</stage></line>
    <line><stage>The limousine’s windows roll down and Three Wise Men come out</stage></line>
    <line><character>Wise Man 1</character><dialogue>Finn, you are wrong. The mark of a great hero is his flaw.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>You know nothing, Wise Men!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Wise Man 1</character><dialogue>Silence, Fear Feaster! We know a lot!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Wait... Why did you wait so long to tell me?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Wise Man 1</character><dialogue>Because the limo driver's flaw is being late!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Limo Driver</character><dialogue>Sorry. <stage>rolls up window</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Wise Man 1</character><dialogue>Farewell, Finn. You truly are the greatest hero of Ooo.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The Wise Men go back inside the limo and then the limo drives back into Finn</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>It's time for you to go away, Fear Feaster!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue>What? Am I supposed to live in your tummy for the rest of my life?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Everybody has a flaw... and it looks like yours is smelling like my nasty guts.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Fear Feaster heads back into Finn's stomach</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fear Feaster</character><dialogue><stage>Sarcastically</stage> Wonderful...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Pat McHale</character><dialogue>And so fear is forced deep within the soul of a hero. Conquered... at least, for now... <stage>Maniacal laugh</stage></dialogue></line>
    <credits>The episode ends</credits></xml>