<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><introduction>The episode begins at the Tree Fort. The camera pans to the bridge linking the living room and attic.</introduction>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs</stage> Ahhh... YEAH!!! <stage>Busts through living room door and lands on bridge.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Entering</stage> Heh heh. <stage>Deep voice</stage> Aw, yeah. <stage>Chuckles</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake, get ready for a slap in the jowls. <stage>Slaps Jake's nose; Jake does a snorting laugh</stage> Seriously, though... get ready... for a day filled with adventure!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Whoa, really?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn: Yeah, man!! <stage>He slaps Jake's nose again, making him snort and laugh again</stage> I wrote on my arm this to-do list of cool junk. <stage>The clouds begin to get darker and bigger</stage> Number one: back flip off this bridge and do the splits. Number two</character><dialogue>track down and slay a goblin horde. Number three...<stage>Glances up at thundering clouds</stage> storm clouds?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Examining</stage> Hmmm... <stage>Knives fall from the clouds and Jake gasps.</stage> Finn... it's a knife storm!! <stage>Finn slaps Jake's nose yet again</stage> It's raining knives, man! Come on! <stage>Exits</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I've never seen a knife storm before... It's beautiful.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Knives begin falling near Finn; Jake pulls Finn inside before knives can fall on him.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Looks like we're stayin' in today, kid.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Well, what're we gonna do?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Who wants to play video games??</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn and Jake</character><dialogue>BMO!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>What's on the menu, BMO?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I've created a new game called Conversation Parade.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Hah! Alright!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Start it up, BMO!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>singing</stage> What do you think about the stars in the sky?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>'S okay, I guess.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yeah, they're cool.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>That is an interesting response! Battery low... Shut doooowwwwn...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Booooo.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>BMO, that was weak.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What now?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Ooh, ooh! Dude, I know somethin' totally rockin' we can do!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Whoa! What?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Let's use our imaginations, man!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Barf that! Imagination is for turbo nerds who can't handle how kick-butt reality is! I'm a kick-butt reality master!! I would rather die than be imaginative. I mean that.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Eh. Your loss. <stage>Beat</stage> AAAH!!! Lava!! Lava all around us!! <stage>Panicking and jumping around</stage> Lava on the floor!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Shut up, man...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Seriously, man! There must be an enchantment on the house or somethin'!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'm not playing you child-style games, guy. Watch and learn as I master... reality. <stage>Moves his foot nearer and nearer to the floor</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>NOOOOO!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Places foot on floor; it suddenly catches fire</stage> AAAAH!!! <stage>Putting fire out</stage> Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Jake! What the hey-hey?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I was just playin' around with my imagination... <stage>In Jake's view, everything is on fire and lava is on the floor</stage> ...and then everything got intense.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>It's like... whatever you imagine becomes real... That's bananas!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>To himself</stage> Don't imagine blowin' apart my own brain... Don't imagine my eyeballs coming alive and flying around with rocket packs...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Dude! Imagine that BMO invented a better video game, and that he has new batteries.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Everything in the room begins to melt.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn and Jake</character><dialogue>WHOA!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>But first stop imagining lava!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I can't! My imagination's too amazing!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Imagine turning your imagination off!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I can't, dude... but I think I can imagine an imagination turning-off machine... that is upstairs, surrounded by a crud-load of traps, ghosts, monsters, and poison fountains, and... and... girls. Cute girls, and hamsters.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Can't you make it easier to get to that machine?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>You can't hold this baby back! That's bad parenting, mamma!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Then it's up to me to take your imagination downtown! Let's go to the den and suit up!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Neat! <stage>Finn and he enter the den</stage> Grab that missile.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Okay.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>And... get that cosmic gauntlet.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Nah. There's a better one over by the desk. Ah! UNH! <stage>Finn leaps into an invisible wall.</stage> What did I just hit?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm imagining a wall. You can just go around it.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Really? That's it? There isn't any invisible, angry troll or anything?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Oh, there's one now. <stage>Troll roars</stage> Look out!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Aah! I can feel it on my foot! <stage>They stumble over, and Finn's shoe seemingly floats in midair.</stage> I'll kill you, troll! Yah! Yah! Yah, yah, yah, yah!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>You're kickin' too high! He's shorter than you!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Yah, yah! <stage>Finn's blows finally start to land.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Alright! You're gettin' him, man! <stage>Finn continues attacking</stage> Uh-oh. Now you're uppercutting his family. <stage>Finn kicks in the air and a scream is heard.</stage> Heh heh heh heh heh! You just kicked his wife in the face! <stage>Troll wife yells incomprehensibly.</stage> She's comin' back for revenge.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Cram this! We gotta book it to your imagination machine! Yah!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn leaps out the window into the knife storm.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>The knife storm, remember?!?! <stage>Finn frantically pulls himself and Jake up to the attic. They rest and pant heavily.</stage> Oh, boy... Ooh... Finn, I found some candy. <stage>Eats some</stage> It tastes like banana candy, man. <stage>Sips drink</stage> Here, man. Try some.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn eats some candy.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Standing up</stage> Okay. Try to imagine some kind of steel umbrella over the bridge so... we don't get knifed.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Okay! <stage>Does it</stage> It is done.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Walks out cautiously</stage> Haha! Ha! Hey, you did it, man!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Riddle Master</character><dialogue>No, voyagers. To pass this bridge, you must first pass the test of the riddle.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>To Jake</stage> An imaginary riddle master?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake laughs sillily.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Sighs</stage> Ask me your riddle, Riddle Master. I accept your test.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Riddle Master</character><dialogue>Then brace yourself, fool, for this riddle comes from a mysterious, far-away land.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Ready</stage> LAY IT ON ME!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Riddle Master</character><dialogue>Yes, um... The riddle, uh... It... cometh... uh...</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I can't imagine a riddle.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Dude, just make it super easy.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Riddle Master</character><dialogue>THE RIDDLE COMETH! Tell me, voyager. What is simple, and yet also... a riddle?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Man, that riddle sucks.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Riddle Master</character><dialogue>THAT IS THE WRONG ANSWER!! The penalty is... DEATH BY SNAKES!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>YEAH, RIGHT! I'VE GOT A MISSILE!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn launches it and it explodes on the other side of the bridge. Finn and Jake scream in pain.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>You exploded the snakes right at us!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I can feel them all over my face! Imaginary poison coursing through my veins!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm sorry, brother! I'm so sorry!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Let's just get to your imagination machine and we'll be okay!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>AAH! A big bowl of baby elephants, chainsaws, and doo-doo's flyin' towards us!! JUMP, DUDE!! <stage>Finn evades the obstacle.</stage> Here come's a soul-eater! Snap its neck! <stage>Finn jumps up and does so. A weapon is heard charging up. Jake gasps.</stage> The Bazooka Goblin has you in its sights!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Hey! Don't shoot us with that bazooka!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Bazooka Goblin laughs.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Don't you do it...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Bazooka Goblin continues laughing.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>DON'T DO IT, MAN!!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Bazooka Goblin</character><dialogue>Hee... heehee... hee... Okay.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>YEAH!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>AW, YEAH!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn and Jake laugh and do a celebratory fist bump.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Alright, use your powers or something. This poison is about to kill me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Alright. Goin' up. Check it. My imagination-off machine is left of the bed.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Is it clear?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yeah, I mean there's a bunch of cute girls... but they shouldn't bother you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn fidgets around and mumbles to himself ("Ah... where, ah... Where is this, I ca—Ah... man.") before finding the machine.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Oh! I found the shut-off lever!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Cool, man! <stage>Invisible girl giggles.</stage> Dang, girl. If you weren't a figment of my imagination, I'd want to have your baby. <stage>Another girl giggles.</stage> What're you laughin' at?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Alright. I'm gonna turn it off. <stage>Finn is suddenly hit by an invisible force.</stage> UNH!! You said it was clear of danger!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Dude... I can't see anything... I must've imagined... an invisible monster!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What?! Well, how do I kill it?! <stage>Finn gets beaten down.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'm comin', buddy! Alright, Invisibo. Eat a piece of this! <stage>Punches it</stage> Hurry, Finn! Get to the lever!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Okay! I'm doin' iiiit!! <stage>Finn pulls the lever; Jake falls down; Finn's wounds are healed.</stage> Aw, yeah! The imaginary poison is gone, Jake! Jake? <stage>Jake groans.</stage> Hey, come on. Wake up, man.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn pats Jake a few times.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Completely regular tone</stage> Hello, Finn. I am awake and healthy.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake... what happened to your bombastic personality?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I do not know what you mean. I am perfectly bombastic.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Nah, man, nah. Somethin's wrong. Tell me something amazing!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>But Finn, I cannot tell you something amazing as there is nothing amazing happening around us that I could describe for you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Ah, see, man, you suck now! Crap, it's your imagination. You need that thing. <stage>Sighs</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Jake reaches for his viola and plays a continuous G♮</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake... Stop it, man. You're just playing one continuous note.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>One note is all that is needed.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Scoffs</stage> I'm gonna turn your imagination back on. <stage>Fidgets around and mumbles to self</stage> Jake! Your imagination on-off switch has vanished!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>True. Doth thou not remember shutting down mine imagination?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I remembereth.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I am happy that my imagination is gone. It was purposeless.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No! It was the opposite of that stuff. I know this now... <stage>Saddened</stage> ...only too late. Okay, man. I'm gonna try to imagine an imagination back-on switch for you, and so you know, if there's anything dainty inside my imagination, I'm gonna be mad. Imagination... go... <stage>Finn appears in his imagination land.</stage> What the stuff? Well... this isn't so bad. <stage>Imagination back-on machine appears</stage> Nothing lame, at least. Hey! And there's Jake's imagination switch!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Suddenly, the Lyre Player enters dancing and singing the Imagination Song.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Disappointed</stage> Cram. Oh! Maybe I can try imagining something. <stage>He imagines a penguin, and a bowl of spaghetti. The Lyre Player trips over the former and lands in the latter; Finn laughs.</stage> Now for that switch.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Bellamy Bug</character><dialogue><stage>Entering</stage> Good morrow, sir! My name is Bellamy Bug! Would you care for a crotchet doily my daughter made? She imbued it with her tears. You see, she recently broke up with a gentle dandy.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No! How'd you get in my Imagination Land?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Bellamy Bug</character><dialogue><stage>Giggles</stage> I don't know, my young fellow! You tell me. Perhaps I represent your secret desire to be civilized!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>REPRESENT THIS! <stage>Smacks Bellamy</stage> And this. <stage>Imagines two arms protruding out of Bellamy (one cephalopodic and one robotic) which both punch him.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Bellamy</character><dialogue>Oh! I say! Oh! Ah! Ouch! Ah!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Penguins take Bellamy away.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Haha... Penguins... Hahahaha! Heh, alright. <stage>Runs over to the machine</stage> I hope this works, Jake! <stage>Pulls lever; Jake's imagination returns.</stage> Haha, yeah! <stage>A fairy comes near the machine giggling.</stage> Hey! Get away from that! Don't push that hyper drive button! <stage>The fairy pushes the button anyway with her butt</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Jake's head grows rapidly</stage> Aaaah!! I can imagine EVERYTHING!!!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Frustrated sigh</stage> Take a hike, fairy! Normal style! <stage>Pushes "NORMAL STYLE" button</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Head shrinks</stage> Aw, man... I imagined my mom naked! <stage>Finn appears next to him.</stage> Yugh!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You okay?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I think so. Lemme check. Mmmm... Yup. She's clothed now. And hey, man! It's clear out now! We can go on an adventure!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I don't know, dude. I think we got all the adventure we need right here... <stage>Thinking</stage> with... lava on the floor!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Huh?! <stage>Body starts melting</stage> AAH! AAH! MY LEGS ARE MELTING! Just kidding. <stage>Chuckles and reforms his body.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Hahahaha! Good dog. <stage>He pets Jake</stage></dialogue></line>
    <credits>and the episode ends.</credits></xml>