<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root> Buttermilk Waffles <authorinfo><name part="first">Rey</name>
    <name part="last">Lopez</name> for <publisher>The Washington Post</publisher></authorinfo>
    <date>JAN 19th, 2022</date> 
    Buttermilk waffles are a morning treat, and these can be whipped up
    at a moment’s notice on a special or ordinary day. As written, this easy recipe creates crisp,
    versatile waffles that are a blank canvas for your choice of toppings. It’s flexible as well.
    Try swapping in whole- grain flours, such as whole-wheat, spelt or buckwheat, for up to half of
    the all- purpose. Cornmeal is lovely, too. Use your favorite extract, and experiment with citrus
    zests. Or take the waffles in a savory direction with spices, diced chipotle peppers or sliced
    scallions. Buttermilk is worth keeping on hand for this recipe, and we don’t think substitutes
    cut it. It can be frozen, but it will also keep for months in the refrigerator. Your waffle
    yield may vary depending on your appliance. We tested the recipe in both round and square waffle
    irons. 
    <time>Total time: <quant>40</quant> mins </time>
    Storage Notes: The finished waffles can be refrigerated in an airtight container for up to 2 days or frozen for up to 1 month and reheated in a toaster or toaster oven. 
    <serving> SERVINGS: Tested size:<quant> 5</quant> servings; makes five 7-inch round waffles </serving>
    <ingreds> INGREDIENTS 
        <measure><quant>2 1/4</quant> <unit>cups </unit><quant>(280</quant> <unit>grams</unit>)</measure> all-purpose flour (see headnote)
        <measure> <quant>1 1/2</quant> <unit>teaspoons</unit></measure> baking soda
        <measure><quant>1/2</quant> teaspoon</measure> fine salt
        <quant>2</quant> large eggs 
        <measure> <quant>2</quant> cups (<quant>480</quant> milliliters)</measure> buttermilk (whole or low-fat)
        <measure><quant>4</quant> <unit>tablespoons</unit> (<quant>1/2</quant> <unit>stick</unit>/<quant>57</quant> <unit>grams</unit>)</measure> unsalted butter, melted and cooled (may substitute some or all neutral oil),
        plus more for optional topping 
        <ingred> <measure><quant>1 </quant><unit>teaspoon</unit></measure> vanilla extract (optional)</ingred>
        <ingred> Neutral oil, for brushing the waffle iron</ingred> 
        
        When you scale a recipe, keep in mind that cooking times and temperatures, pan sizes and seasonings may be affected, so adjust accordingly. Also, amounts listed in the
        directions will not reflect the changes made to ingredient amounts. 
        
        <ingred> Maple syrup, for serving(optional)</ingred> </ingreds>
    
    <steps>DIRECTIONS 
        <step num="1">Preheat the oven to <temp><quant>200</quant> degrees</temp>. </step>
        <step num="2">Have a large, rimmed baking sheet ready.</step>
        <step num="3">In a large bowl, whisk together the flour, baking soda and salt until combined.</step>   
        <step num="4">In a separate medium bowl, whisk the eggs until lightly beaten.</step> 
        <step num="5"> Whisk in the buttermilk, butter and vanilla, if using, until combined.</step> 
        <step num="6">Stir the egg mixture into the flour mixture until it forms a smooth, thick batter. </step>
        <step num="7">Brush a waffle iron with oil or spray with nonstick spray, and preheat it according to the manufacturer’s directions. </step>
        <step num="8">Ladle enough of the batter to cover three-fourths of the surface of the waffle iron — this will vary by model, but expect <unit><quant>1/2 to 3/4</quant> cup</unit> (<unit><quant>120 to 180</quant> milliliters</unit>) of batter per waffle</step>
        <step num="9">Close it, and cook for <time><quant>3 to 5</quant> minutes</time>, or until the iron alerts you the waffle is done. </step>
        <step num="10">If your iron does not have an alert, look for the waffle to be crisp and golden brown. </step>
        <step num="11">Repeat with the remaining batter, placing finished waffles on the baking sheet in the oven to keep warm, if desired.</step> 
        <step num="12">Serve with maple syrup, pats of butter or other toppings passed at the table.</step> 
        <largerserving>VARIATION: 
            <step num="13">To add extra lift and crispness to your waffles, separate the eggs and use only the yolks when you whisk in the buttermilk and butter.</step> 
            <step num="14"> In a separate bowl, beat the egg whites with an electric mixer on low, then medium- high speed to form soft peaks.</step> 
            <step num="15">After the flour and egg yolk mixtures have been combined, fold half of the beaten egg whites into the batter until barely blended, then fold in the remaining egg whites; use a gentle hand to keep the batter light. </step></largerserving></steps>
    
    RECIPE SOURCE Adapted from “The Williams-Sonoma
    Bride and Groom Cookbook,” by Gayle Pirie and John Clark (Free Press, 2006). Tested by Becky
    Krystal. </root>

