<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<xml>
    <meta source="https://www.depaulatrading.com/blogs/news/icarus"
        title="The Story of Icarus from Greek Mythology"/>

    <section title="Good Old Dad">
        <p n="1"><people name="KM">King Minos</people> was greatly <emotion conotation="positive"
                >impressed</emotion> with the work of <people name="Dae">Icarus' father</people>,
            which led him to the decision of <impPoint factor="imprisoned because of Kings greed"
                >imprisoning <people name="Ica">Icarus</people> and <people name="Dae"
                    >Daedalus</people> so the inventor could work solely for him.</impPoint> The
            king's <emotion conotation="negative">greed</emotion> led the young man and his father
            to be locked up in a cave above sea level. <impPoint factor="only two escape routes">The
                only way to escape the prison was through the Labyrinth where the <mythicCreature
                    type="Minotaur">Minotaur</mythicCreature> was locked, which was also surrounded
                by the king’s soldiers. The other way to escape the prison was through the entrance
                situated on the side of high cliff plunging down to the sea below.</impPoint></p>

        <p n="2"><impPoint factor="situation was alright">At first, <people name="Ica"
                    >Icarus</people> and his father <people name="Dae">Daedalus</people> were
                    <emotion conotation="positive">content</emotion> with <people name="KM">King
                    Minos</people>' decision to lock them up. Everything Icarus’ father asked from
                the king was instantly provided.</impPoint> They both received plenty of food and
            the inventor tools he could use when working on his new inventions. Icarus was young
            when they were imprisoned by the king, and didn't complain - he even <emotion
                conotation="positive">enjoyed</emotion> being able to help his father with his new
            inventions and especially playing with the toys his father made just for him.</p>
    </section>

    <section title="Despair">
        <p n="3"><impPoint factor="Icarus becomes impatient">As the young Icarus grew, he realized
                he would be imprisoned in the cave for a lifetime.</impPoint> Daedalus also thought
            about his son’s well-being; Icarus was <emotion conotation="negative">tired</emotion> of
            living in the cold, damp cave, and despaired of never having a life.</p>

        <p n="4">The 16-years old Icarus started to complain to his father and stated he wanted to
            go on adventures, meet a girl, make her his wife and have his own son. He even expressed
                <emotion conotation="negative">his hatred</emotion> for the king, the cave, and his
            father. However, after the outburst, Icarus immediately apologized. <impPoint
                factor="because of Icarus, Daedalus tries to get him out">Because of the <emotion
                    conotation="negative">rage</emotion> Icarus had shown, his father asked for King
                Minos to make his son one of the royal guards, which the king
            considered.</impPoint></p>
    </section>

    <section title="Wooden Wings">
        <p n="5">Ultimately, the king decided not to let Icarus go and instead stay with his father
            and keep him company, <impPoint factor="Kings greed trumps fathers request">because he
                might have acquired his father’s skills.</impPoint> For them to escape, Daedalus
            created wings from wooden frames. <impPoint
                factor="Father designs wings for them to escape">The wings were covered with big
                feathers and were tightly secured using wax.</impPoint></p>

        <p n="6">When they took to flight, Daedalus advised Icarus <impPoint
                factor="clear instructions on flying">to fly in between the sun and the
                ocean</impPoint> - far from the sun because it would melt the wax, and not too close
            to the sea for it would dampen the feathers. However, as they flew, <impPoint
                factor="Icarus dies">Icarus got carried away and despite his father's <emotion
                    conotation="nuetral">passionate pleas</emotion>, ventured too close to the sun,
                melting the wax and causing his plunge hundreds of feet below, resulting in his
                demise.</impPoint></p>
    </section>
</xml>
