<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book>x
    <meta><title>Autobiography of a Yogi</title> by <author><name part="first">Paramhansa</name>
            <name part="last">Yogananda</name></author> WITH A PREFACE BY <prefaAuthor><name
                part="initials">W. Y.</name>
            <name part="last">Evans-Wentz</name>, <name part="initials">M.A.</name>, <name
                part="initials">D.Litt.</name>, <name part="initials"
        >D.Sc.</name></prefaAuthor></meta>
    <preface>
        <header>PREFACE</header>
        <prefaMeta>By <prefaAuthor><name part="initials">W. Y.</name>
                <name part="last">EVANS-WENTZ</name>, <name part="initials">M.A.</name>, <name
                    part="initials">D.Litt.</name>, <name part="initials">D.Sc.</name></prefaAuthor>
            <authWorks>Jesus College, Oxford; Author of The Tibetan Book of the Dead, Tibet's Great
                Yogi Milarepa, Tibetan Yoga and Secret Doctrines, etc.</authWorks></prefaMeta>
        <prefaText>
            <para>The value of <bioOf>Yogananda</bioOf>'s Autobiography is greatly enhanced by the
                fact that it is one of the few books in English about the wise men of
                    <locat>India</locat> which has been written, not by a journalist or foreigner,
                but by one of their own race and training--in short, a book about
                    <group>yogis</group> by a <group>yogi</group>. As an eyewitness recountal of the
                extraordinary lives and powers of modern <group>Hindu</group> saints, the book has
                importance both timely and timeless. To its illustrious author, whom I have had the
                pleasure of knowing both in <locat>India</locat> and <locat>America</locat>, may
                every reader render due appreciation and gratitude. His unusual life-document is
                certainly one of the most revealing of the depths of the Hindu mind and heart, and
                of the spiritual wealth of <locat>India</locat>, ever to be published in the
                West.</para>
            <para>It has been my privilege to have met one of the sages whose life- history is
                herein narrated-<storyteller>Sri Yukteswar Giri</storyteller>. A likeness of the
                venerable saint appeared as part of the frontispiece of my <practice>Tibetan
                    Yoga</practice> and <practice>Secret Doctrines</practice>. 1-1 It was at
                    <locat>Puri</locat>, in <locat>Orissa</locat>, on the <locat>Bay of
                    Bengal</locat>, that I encountered <storyteller>Sri Yukteswar</storyteller>. He
                was then the head of a quiet ashrama near the seashore there, and was chiefly
                occupied in the spiritual training of a group of youthful disciples. He expressed
                keen interest in the welfare of the people of the <locat>United States</locat> and
                of all the <locat>Americas</locat>, and of <locat>England</locat>, too, and
                questioned me concerning the distant activities, particularly those in
                    <locat>California</locat>, of his chief disciple, <bioOf>Paramhansa
                    Yogananda</bioOf>, whom he dearly loved, and whom he had sent, in
                    <time>1920</time>, as his emissary to the West.</para>
            <para><locat>Sri Yukteswar</locat> was of gentle mien and voice, of pleasing presence,
                and worthy of the veneration which his followers spontaneously accorded to him.
                Every person who knew him, whether of his own community or not, held him in the
                highest esteem. I vividly recall his tall, straight, ascetic figure, garbed in the
                saffron- colored garb of one who has renounced worldly quests, as he stood at the
                entrance of the hermitage to give me welcome. His hair was long and somewhat curly,
                and his face bearded. His body was muscularly firm, but slender and well-formed, and
                his step energetic. He had chosen as his place of earthly abode the holy city of
                Puri, whither multitudes of pious <nationality>Hindus</nationality>, representative
                of every province of <location>India</location>, come daily on pilgrimage to the
                famed <locat>Temple of Jagannath</locat>, "Lord of the World." It was at
                    <locat>Puri</locat> that <storyteller>Sri Yukteswar</storyteller> closed his
                mortal eyes, in <time>1936</time>, to the scenes of this transitory state of being
                and passed on, knowing that his incarnation had been carried to a triumphant
                completion. I am glad, indeed, to be able to record this testimony to the high
                character and holiness of <storyteller>Sri Yukteswar</storyteller>. Content to
                remain afar from the multitude, he gave himself unreservedly and in tranquillity to
                that ideal life which <bioOf>Paramhansa Yogananda</bioOf>, his disciple, has now
                described for the ages. <prefaAuthor><name part="initials">W. Y.</name>
                    <name part="last">EVANS-WENTZ</name></prefaAuthor></para>
        </prefaText>
        <footer>1-1: <publisher>Oxford University Press</publisher>, <time>1935</time>.</footer>
    </preface>
</book>
