<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<root>
    <intro> Learning to knit can seem a bit daunting, so if you're keen to kick start your knitting
        journey but you're not sure where to begin, you’ve come to the right place! We've got loads
        of brilliant learn to knit videos that cover everything from beginner tutorials on how to
        hold the needles and knit your first row, through to more advanced knitting techniques such
        as how to work those tricky button holes. You'll be knitting up a storm in no time! </intro>

    <extraInfo> Getting started Before you begin your journey of learning how to knit, you’ll need a
        few essentials to get you started. We'll talk you through the essential first steps to
        getting started including picking a knitting project, choosing the best needles for the job
        and selecting your yarn, as well as showcasing some fabulous kits. Then enjoy browsing our
        gallery of step-by-step tutorials. </extraInfo>

    <mainSteps>
        <step main="first">1. Pick a pattern</step>
        <extraInfo> The first step on your knitting odyssey is to pick a pattern! We've got hundreds
            of knitting projects from a host of designers and much-loved brands for all abilities.
            Whether you're looking to craft a cosy hat for a buddy, a snuggly baby blanket, or
            dreamy scarf, we have a beautiful pool of projects to inspire you! </extraInfo>
        <step main="second">2. Choose the best needles to get started</step> First up, if you’re
        learning traditional knitting techniques, we would recommend starting with single point
        needles, which are used in our beginner videos. But there’s a whole menagerie of knitting
        needles to explore from DPNs to circular in different sizes and materials, from bamboo to
        plastic. <step main="third">3. Select your yarn</step> Yarn glorious yarn! One of the
        greatest joys a knitter has on her way to making divine projects is choosing which yummy
        yarn to work with. With so many yarns to choose from in every shade imaginable, it can
        easily get a knitting newbie in a tangle. From selecting a suitable fiber to exploring
        color, we’re here to help! <step main="fourth">4. Cast on</step> Before you start knitting
        the very first step to knitting is learning how to tie a slip knot and cast on the number of
        stitches you will be knitting in your row. See our step-by-step guide and video on how to
        tie a slip knot or follow these simple steps! </mainSteps>

    <slipKnot> How to tie a slip knot and cast on <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="first"> 1 Leaving a nice
            long tail (which you’ll sew in later), take the yarn and wind it around your fingers. </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="second"> 2 How to tie a slip knot step 2 Reach through the loop
            around your fingers and pull your working yarn (attached to the ball) through. </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="third"> 3 Pull tight your slip knot Remove your fingers, and pull
            the working yarn tight to produce a slip knot. You’re ready to start casting on! </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotTip slipKnot="tip"> PRO TIP A slip knot is a special knot on your yarn that means
            you can adjust the size of your loop. </slipKnotTip>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="fourth"> 4 Secure slip knot around needle Place your loop around
            your needle and adjust size to secure if you need to. Hold in your left hand. </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="fifth"> 5 <knitStep step="first"> How to knit step 1 Insert
                right-hand needle diagonally underneath and into the stitch. </knitStep>
        </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="sixth"> 6 <knitStep step="second"> How to knit step 2 Take the
                working yarn and wrap around the front of the right needle. </knitStep>
        </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="seventh"> 7 <knitStep step="third"> How to knit step 3 Bring the
                right needle back and place on top of the left needle, bringing the loop of yarn
                with it. You will have a loop on each needle. </knitStep>
        </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="eighth"> 8 <knitStep stitchStep="third"> How to knit stitch step 3
                Now, transfer the loop on your right needle onto your left needle, so you have 2
                loops on your left. You’ve cast on your first stitch! </knitStep>
        </slipKnotSteps>
        <slipKnotSteps slipKnot="ninth"> 9 Now repeat step 5 - 8 until you’ve cast on the amount of
            stitches you’d like to knit! </slipKnotSteps>
    </slipKnot>
    <mainSteps>
        <step main="fifth"> 5. Knit a row of stitches</step> Now you’ve cast on you’re ready to knit
        your first row of stitches. The knit stitch, which is also called garter stitch, is the
        first basic knitting stitch to master when you begin. We’ll show you how step-by-step. </mainSteps>

    <knitStitchSteps> How to knit stitch <stitchSteps step="first"> 1 Insert your right needle
            underneath the first stitch on your left needle. </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="second"> 2 How to knit step 2 Bring the working yarn around the right
            needle. </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="third"> 3 How to knit step 3 Slide the right needle back bringing the
            yarn with it, so the right needle sits on top of the left. </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="fourth"> 4 How to knit step 4 Slide the stitch off the left hand needle
            so you now have one knitted stitch on your right. You’ve completed your first knit
            stitch. Go you! </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="fifth"> 5 Knit your first row Repeat your knit stitch until you’ve
            completed the first row! </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="sixth"> 6 Turn your right needle around and transfer it to your left
            hand. Swap your empty left hand needle into your right hand to begin stitching your
            second row using steps 1-5. </stitchSteps>
        <stitchSteps step="seventh"> 7 Repeat the number of rows you’d like to build your fabric.
        </stitchSteps>
    </knitStitchSteps>

    <mainSteps>
        <step main="sixth">6. Bind off</step> Binding off is the final knitting technique you’ll
        need to complete your first knitting project. While there are lots of ways to bind off,
        we’re going to show you a simple bind off method to get you started. </mainSteps>

    <bindOffSteps> To ‘bind off’ just means fastening up your live stitches using your needles, so
        you have a nice neat and secure edge. Once you’ve got this finishing technique in the bag
        you're ready to start your first project! <header>How to make a simple bind off</header>
        <bindOff step="first"> 1 How to cast off step 1 Knit your first stitch, as if you were
            beginning a new row. </bindOff>
        <bindOff step="second"> 2 How to cast off step 2 Knit the second stitch so you have two
            stitches on your right needle. </bindOff>
        <bindOff step="third"> 3 How to cast off step 3 Use the tip of your left needle to insert
            underneath and into the first stitch on your right needle. </bindOff>
        <bindOff step="fourth"> 4 How to cast off step 4 Use the left needle to lift the first
            stitch and pull it over the second, and that’s it! You’ve completed your first bind off
            stitch. </bindOff>
        <bindOff step="fifth"> 5 How to cast off step 5 Repeat this bind off method all the way to
            the end of your row. Once you’ve reached the end use your scissors to snip the working
            yarn leaving a tail. Pull the tail through the final loop and tighten to secure a knot. </bindOff>
        <bindOff step="sixth"> 6 Now you’ve finished binding off, sew in your ends to complete!
        </bindOff>
    </bindOffSteps>

    <extraInfo> Knitting videos for beginners Get started with the knitting basics! If you've never
        picked up a pair of needles before, the thought of learning to knit can seem pretty
        overwhelming. Our beginners' knitting videos are packed full of helpful tutorials and tips
        on everything from knitting your first row to experimenting with super simple stitches - and
        once you've learned to knit, there's even a step-by-step project to practice your new skills
        at the end! </extraInfo>
</root>
